Morning
team. Morning team. How's it going?
How's it going everyone?
Still waking up there. I've been awake
like an hour and still feel not too
fresh. It's been a uh a long week this
week. At least for me it has been
fantastic week of trading. We've
absolutely hammered
the profits this week again. So far the
start of this year has been incredible.
Best start of the year I've ever had.
Normally I close the year strong. At the
moment it's great start of the year. All
right. So what we looking at? What we
looking at after that big sale? Well,
we're still looking at this daily,
right? We always start in the daily. We
are breaking out of the current week.
All right. So here is the Monday low,
Tuesday, Wednesday high. Those have done
the course. You know what we're talking
about. Tuesday, Wednesday high, big
sell. Thursday breaking Monday low. All
right. So maybe maybe a back test in
here. somewhere in here before a resell
down maybe. We don't know. But what we
do know is we've got now this lower
ballinger band and what do you know the
fiveday playing catchup? Some smart
person told you that will probably
happen and then it's all depends whether
we can set a trend under here. All
right. What we are looking at here is
are we going to go expansion again and
come and try and take out these lows
down here which we have not swept yet,
right? because we've held the 200 day or
are we going to wait a few days and
maybe do that next week? Very possible.
All right. So, we're going to watch
these levels inside here. Big week
already. So, don't go forcing today.
Please folks, don't be forcing yourself
on the market today.
All right. Hourly. Let's focus on here.
Hourly. You can see we are currently
trading right inside yesterday's range.
So if we look at yesterday's range,
previous day value area low right here
725.
Okay, we are bouncing between previous
day value area low and previous day
point of previous week we point of
control. Sorry. All right, so this is
currently the rotation. We have been in
a strong sell. We have some degree of
compression. Doesn't mean it can't go
lower, but shorting down here starts to
become very very risky, doesn't it?
Because any break, I would say
especially over previous day point
control, any break over here, you will
start to see potential upside lift for a
retest up here. Look how thin we are
yesterday. All right, so we're watching
920s and over. You want to be very,
very, very careful. All right, very
careful into that kind of level. Can we
get rid of you, mate? All right, so
we're watching a rotation here between
these levels here. Okay. And if we get
over once, certainly if we keep
rejecting this gray box, we're going to
keep coming back down into these sort of
725s.
Under 725s, acceptance under 725s, we
can look for overnight low and previous
week value area low. All right. Over
sort of 810ish, over 810ish. And
certainly over these pivots here, 850,
we can lift towards 900. So, I'd say in
here is going to be somewhat chop and
slop, right? And the range isn't bad.
It's about 100 points of chop and slop
in there if you want to play it. Uh I
will prefer this move here or this move
here or a failed look and down or like a
failed break and up. That's going to be
the easier play in my mind. Um if we
have a look up here on fiveminute chart,
you will notice I have put the GEX
levels on here for you today. All right.
So you can see there is a currently a
put wall before the open at least. This
will change after the open at at uh 7:25
which lines up perfectly with previous
day value. Currently we keep holding
this and currently we keep getting stuck
as we come into the call wall 850. So
like I said 725 850 lines up pretty well
with this up here 900. All right same
kind of levels. So if we fail 825 there
is a wash down to previous week value
area low which lines up pretty well with
the next call wall. Surprise surprise.
All right it's the same areas. right
over uh 825 and 900s there is a lift up
the previous day value area high which
lines pretty well with the cool wall.
All right, so they line up pretty well
this morning. We'll see if they move
during the day. They will move in the
next hour or 30 minutes. But really,
we're very very careful here because
this can definitely be compression. I'm
not saying to long it. It's not what I'm
saying. But it can get relief to here
and it can get relief up here. And if we
get up here, you know, then we maybe
look for the sell back down once we
clear out all these stops like we always
talk about. Doesn't have to do that. It
can absolutely just go [\h__\h] no. We don't
want to hold over the weekend. We're
expecting gap down Monday. Sell, sell,
sell, sell, sell. Get rid of all of our
inventory, which is what happened late
in the afternoon yesterday as we talked
about in Discord before it happened. All
right, moving up. Lower time frame.
Lower time frame. Right. So you can see
just this compression, right? We're in
stuck in here, right? Just for those of
you who can't see, we're stuck in here
right now and with some stops up here.
So this is the rotation. This is a stop
hunt area up here. Very thin above.
Right, let's have a look at ES. It's
going to look pretty much the same here.
Pretty much the same here. We can flip
this. It's very much.
Okay. And a little box here. So we're
holding uh 25. trading 25s to 60s right
now. Um, I have one of these on there.
Probably put this on there for you. See
if it lines up.
Yeah. So, same kind of levels, 20s.
Um, I mean, I don't see it doing that.
So, 20s, it's just where they hold these
dips. The highest one's right down here.
So, they're expecting a sell through
here on ES by the looks of it. We'll
see. But, same kind of story. Let's have
a look at the spiders and the ETFs.
Five minute here.
All right, into this we have an old gap
down here. It's worth noting into 73s.
Let's quick look out of interest.
Oh, surprise surprise for the gap fill
at 75s. All right, so bit of a
resistance here that we I imagine we've
chopped this morning before they make
their mind up on what it is that they
want to do here. Uh, but we definitely
have potential for an old gap fill here.
I just want to make sure that's legit.
It's the overnight gap. It's not the
best, but there is something. All right.
So, we'll see. We'll see.
Uh, no. What's just happened there?
My cues, please.
Q's, same story. 600. Massive, massive,
massive level. 600. We lose 600. All
right. we sell through. Okay, we can
start thinking about a wash further down
uh 595ish
down into here. Yeah, these old lows
here. Like I said to everyone in
Discord, watch this fifth and sixth the
uh fifth and sixth pivots. We lose that,
we're going to watch this low. We lose
that, we're going to start really
attacking. Remember, QQQs have got to
catch up to to go to get to the 200 day
like we talked about. ETFs have not hit
the 200 day the same way the futures
have. So if they want to sell, they
still have a back test of that 200 day
to go, right? Dixie trying, desperately
trying to find a bid, right, after
curling. Not a great attempt yet, but
it's better than nothing, I guess. Uh, a
little bit of a bounce back on gold, I
guess, after those huge sells that we
talked about. Again, still pinned in
here. Same thing on silver weakness like
we talked about. Still dropping lower.
All right, MAG. Actually, VIX first,
please. Right, Vicks elevated remains
elevated here this morning. If we keep
basing over 2050 or even down to here
over 20s, we can have a run up towards
what's this pivot here? 22 and 23. If we
start taking that out on VIX, right? Any
run up here, this market's going to get
so weak, I cannot explain. All right, if
we go on a rip on a Friday on VIX, the
market will start tanking. So, worth
setting some price alerts at these
pivots.
Apple big sell yesterday, over 5% down
yesterday. a huge riskoff moment into
consolidation. All right, huge sell into
consolidation. Maybe it needs a bit of a
back test to resell and then we see if
there's a failed breakdown or
continuation lower.
Amazon
under the 200s, isn't it? It is under
the 200. Same story. Big wash sideways
in here. You're watching either side of
this for breakout, breakout, fail,
breakout, fail, breakout. All right,
this is going to be the same story
across the board. Right now, Google
pretty much the same, right? Sell
sideways, little fail break in the
pre-market,
gapping down again. Meta, that's weak
right now. That's the one that's been
had more strength recently. We are
undercutting now. So, if they fail to
stay heavy under here and they start
reclaiming, it's a good sign for Meta,
but it looks weak at the moment. Same
story here on Softy. All right, big sell
came a couple days ago actually. And
here's the base. Right, big sell base.
They need to make their decision either
side of this. Right. I don't like
trading in these. I'll wait to see what
we do outside of those as we always talk
about. Nvidia
failed to break the highs. Again, look,
this is the high it needed to break. Big
sale yesterday. And we will be watching
this kind of level here. 88 into 90s, I
guess. But 88's really any rejection of
that. We're looking for continuation
down here for this gap, which is kind of
where we're starting to find some early
covering by the looks of it. Tesla, all
right, failed to break out. Classic
failed failed breakout here. All right,
failed to take out the high. Buyers get
trapped. We revisit failed to break out
the high. That's why it's a double top
underneath their stops and we're
selling. We're now potentially backside
of this move. So any fails into 22s,
even argue 20s, but 22s and 26s, any
fails into here, you'd look for downside
pressure on Tesla for a backside move.
All right, equally weighted. It's
probably going to look pretty ugly. Here
it is. There we go. So big slide on the
equally weighted. There was the old box,
right, for a few sessions and we've slid
under. So we'll wait. Can we back test
and rotate down for a bleed out in the
market? We can have a look at some of
the weaker names, broaden names. Oracle
still holding up. All right. All right.
I'm still holding this long on Oracle.
You can see where I'm long from. Still
holding this long. Looks okay for now.
And uh
not huge size in this, but we'll see if
we can get up into these 70s and some
relief above. How we doing for time?
Hood got absolutely slaughtered, but I'm
still in the money here off that low.
Waiting to see if it finds a bid or if
this pig is going to keep dropping. And
if it drops, I'll take the rest off.
It's fine. Netflix into some of the
levels that we talked about, folks, for
the swings, right? It might want to
drift down lower here, but we've now
filled that gap. Uh lower the better. We
can see we're backside of this trend.
We're coming into some pivots here. So,
those who are looking for some of the
swings with me, right? Anywhere in any
of this block even starting now looks
pretty good. This fade from the high,
remember this is like an a swing for
permanent hold. This is not like oh the
two or three month. We're down 43%. If
we can get anywhere in here, we can get
a maximum of 65% down, that would be
absolutely glorious and we'll start
scooping here longterm. All right, this
is for my swing account for my uh Roth
IRA. Again, I'm should tell should tell
you in case you do not know. I'm not a
financial adviser, guys. I'm telling you
what I will do with my accounts. Maybe I
get them wrong. All right? So, make sure
you do your own due diligence, but this
is certainly something I'll be looking
at into here. Here I've already got a
piece on as we know. Any drift lower I
will start scooping this aggressively.
Aggressively.
Um that is pretty much it. That is
pretty much it.
Manage your own book. All right, folks.
Manage your own book. Best way of me
saying it. All right. Zoom this in.
So many lines on the chart. It's ugly
right now, isn't it? It is ugly. Let's
uh see if we can move some of these
That's a big level there on the edge.
Give me a second, folks.
Don't think we need this node. Don't
think we need this node. Do think we
need this one.
Cleaning the chart up for a moment.
Sorry, folks.
There we go. All right.
Two, three minutes to the open.
Remember, it's Friday. Our job today is
to not lose money. Our job is to not
give all the money back. All those great
plays that we've had all week. you got
that 100 pointer twice with me yesterday
or maybe you got the 100 pointer and
then you held for the 400 pointer like
we talked about, right? Do not go giving
that back today on a Friday. The best
moves for the week have probably
happened.
They have probably happened already. All
right, do me a favor. Smash that like
button nice and early for me. Then I
don't have to uh nag you lot
this over on this screen.
I think we're clear for news. Yeah,
we're pretty much clear for news today.
We had CPI this morning.
We look good.
I'll be taking it nice and easy today
unless there's something very very
clean. We know the levels. We've gone
over the levels. We're currently holding
into here. This uh
put wall at the moment. If we start to
lose that, maybe we we can wash down to
previous week value area low. So, I'm
watching the rotation between here and
this gray box. All right. And if we lose
one side, maybe like we talked about the
rotation at the moment is between these,
right? If we lose this, there's an
argument for it to come down here. If we
get above this, there's an argument for
a squeeze up to here. But we need to be
very careful of fail breakouts in
inside. Right?
This stream up so I can see
How many of you in here? 1,500 of you in
here. Less than 400 likes. Come on,
folks. Come on, folks. Let's get that
thing moving early so we can do some
nice giveaways.
Do I know if I can use take profit in
Canada? Yeah, I'm pretty sure you can.
You've been a game changer for me,
teaching me so much, especially
patience, which is something I've been
struggling with. Appreciate you. Yeah,
you're welcome.
Good morning. Signed up for your free
indicator. Was looking forward to trying
it out. Make sure you've put everything
in correctly. A lot of people say that
they haven't got it and then they go
back and they haven't put their trading
view uh incorrectly. Thank you, John.
Always so kind. Always so kind. All
right, 20 seconds here, folks.
Number 25 that uh previous day value
area low currently holding. If we lose
that and stay heavy underneath, there is
potential for a wash down into here. We
don't know, but there's potential for a
wash down into previous week value area
low. So, they're holding dips so far
this morning into that um previous day.
Here's the sell. So, they're right down
into it. If they lose this, we can get
heavy, heavy, heavy.
We'll see if they keep pinning it here.
We might see that pop back up upside.
They're trying to pin it here. Here's
the relief off that 25s.
Back down to the 25s.
Can they make their mind up what they
want to do? Selling through the 25s.
People coming in at 25. Big sellers down
here at 17. Do they wash all the way
down? They are attempting to wash all
the way down. Not going to do anything
with this yet. We will just watch to see
what happens at 25. Reclaim of 25s.
Maybe back to the 25s. Back to the
previous day value low. Can they get
back up to the 800s?
Maybe the squeeze is on here, folks. If
they've reclaimed it, a wash and little
reclaim. It's possible. It's possible a
squeeze is on here. If they can hold
above 25s, it's possible a squeeze is on
here. There or thereabouts. No, back to
the 25s. But value area low. You can see
the importance of it. So, they've washed
reclaimed. Zooming this in for you.
And guess if they get back over this New
York open, they can think about the 800
move, which is what they're trying to
do. It's very messy on the tape here
this morning, folks. So, I am just going
to let this do whatever the bloody hell
it wants for a minute. We will see.
Certainly some absorption there into
25s. There we go. So maybe here's
previous day close. Maybe through this
pivot there is maybe a little mini
squeeze up to here. I won't be playing
it, but I'm just telling you what I'm
seeing.
Let them uh do whatever it is they want
to do this morning on a Friday morning.
Thank you, Alex. Please don't get mad if
some trolls come here. 14 one down 400
people to learn from you. Your calm way
of trading is amazing. Best trader I've
seen. Thank you. You're welcome.
Okay, stuck at this view up. Just look
at how tight we're getting in here while
they make their decision. Just let this
play out for a bit. You got big big
dealers trying to uh decide what they
want to do right now.
What is the mag doing? Let's have a
look. All of the mag red other than
Microsoft relative strength in Microsoft
everything else gapping down and selling
and give you a readout. Tesla zero or
approaching half% down now. Nvidia uh
72% down. Microsoft.15% up. Meta 1.32%
down. That's the week one today. Google
0.40% down. Amazon 0.5% down. Here's the
squeeze back up. They're trying to get
this move back up. So they've held 25s a
few times. They're going to look for the
800s here if they can. All right. and
then through 800. They've got a shot at
moving up towards 850. If they run these
stops uh 830, 850, 900. So, here's the
squeeze. They held 25s. They're trying
to get up to 800. We've pretty much
tagged it. So, if you took 25s, you
should be peeling some off here at 800.
And then you should be looking to run
the stops at 835 and 850.
I didn't want to take that today on a
Friday, but you could see it was there
and kept dipping and holding the 25s.
So, they hit the 800 previous week point
of control. Huge, huge level from the
previous week.
Can they get a lift here is what they're
asking. Can they lift it?
Spy looks a little bit stuck up here at
the top of GlobeEx. Let's try it a
couple times.
Not sure they know what they want to do
with it right now. Don't blame them
after yesterday was so big.
Okay, back down to the 50s and the 25s
again. So, failing to break out of the
800s rotation all the way back down.
This is what we talked about where the
rotation will take place. Why I'm
avoiding this right now, waiting to see
what we do each side of the rotation.
Quick 120 on a micro there. Thank you,
sir. You're welcome. Back to the 800s
again. They're going to try.
Can they make their mind up? Can we get
something today which is a little bit
cleaner? Doesn't look great on the tape
right now.
Big buyers and big sellers down here.
It's not very clean. Just going to let
them let them figure it out for a
minute.
Let them figure it out for a minute.
Yeah, we got to understand, guys, we did
a huge bleed yesterday, right? Huge,
huge sell yesterday.
We're right, we're opening up like if
you guys joined me for the pre-market,
we are opening up right on the lower
Ballinger band. Okay, right on the lower
Ballinger band. The only thing left to
go through would be an expansion. We
haven't really given it much time. If
we're going to expand under here now,
then there is a possibility of a move
down to the previous week value area
low. All right. So, if they stay heavy
under here, it would be TP1, TP2. If
they reclaim it, they will try and go to
here and here again. And we will keep
chopping in this building liquidity. Why
are we building liquidity? Because we've
done a huge move. Okay, just think about
what we've done already. We've done a
monstrous move. This was a straight
sell. This is some form of compression.
You cannot rule out this here and a run
of these stops here. What would be
better? That that would be better. Might
not be what we get. We haven't got that
all week. When I've been waiting for it
to get a swing on with the short, we
haven't had it all week.
You see, it's 25. It's very sticky
around here at the moment. 131 lot buyer
came in here trying to force it back up.
There is a seller caught at 700 right
now. He's not huge. He's a 40 or 50 lot.
He's caught down at 700.
But they keep buying. We've had one,
two, maybe 300 lots of orders in here at
the 20s. They keep trying to nibble at
these 20s.
They're looking for that upside move.
They might not get it.
Very very very messy right now, folks.
I'll show you what I mean. Very messy.
Look at all this size. All this size.
Big buyers, big sellers. No one winning.
All right. Rotation.
Let it do what it needs to do, folks.
600's on uh
on uh Q's as well. Important and I guess
680s and 685s on spy.
All right, back to these 20s again. Do
they get back over these 20s or is there
a big sell coming from here? They keep
trying to get back over the 20s and 25s.
They're not succeeding really. Here they
go. They're trying.
Still the tape's very messy.
Even bookmap struggling to keep up here.
And it's just given me a warning. CME
struggling to keep up.
My thought on a 15minute orb trade
today. Um
maybe just be aware of the range you're
in, right? You know, if you're going to
trade the breakout of an orb and you're
right at the bottom side of the range,
for example, you might struggle.
Put my mic closer. There you go. You
have to remember, guys, I'm not going to
shout. It's 6:30 in the morning for me.
Okay. So, trying to wash. Do they reject
25s or reclaim it? It's the same story.
Can they get down to the GlobeEx low?
42s. And then under this blue box, I
guess 21s. We can move this down a
little bit
here. It's where they're trying to get
to at the moment. If they wash that,
there's a shot of going to 550s at the
moment
down into here. It's all about this
level. Do we reject this level or are we
going to reclaim this level?
Very kind, Virgil. Thank you very much
for that trade you just made.
Oh, current session volume. Sorry. Yes,
I haven't put it on yet because we're
jumping around. But there you go. Oh, is
it forgotten again? Come on. Get out of
it.
Come on. Trading. You sort your life
out. Even this looks blocky.
Okay, back to these 25s again.
Spy found a little bid there at 680 we
just talked about. Just be aware of
that. Spy just found a bid at 680.
What is it that they want to do here?
Vic still basing out here. Not really
doing much.
Welcome Gordon. Good to have you with
us.
Small caps acting like a safe haven is
crazy. Yeah, they're not. It's not like
they're a safe haven. It's just a when
you've got to think, we've talked about
this numerous times, right? How much how
big has the tech run been for the last
two, three, four years? It's been
monstrous. Monstrous. All right. So,
you're seeing profit taking from tech
rotation out of that into names which
need to catch up like small caps. They
know that they can force some small caps
up, which is why the RTY is moving,
right? Why you've had like positive
divergence in the RTY. Once they're done
with it, you'll see a rotation back into
the mega caps again. It's always the
same, right? You buy something cheap,
you pump it up to it's expensive, you
sell it. You buy the other thing cheap,
you pump it up to it's expensive. Rinse,
repeat. Rinse, repeat, rinse, repeat.
Okay, they're rejecting these. Now,
here's GlobeEx, right? So, this is your
TP1 if you took it. Caught monologuing
there. And your next TP is down here
into 550s.
And we lost the 680s already. This is
very weak on the spiders now. Very, very
weak on the spiders.
Oh, Alex, you got talking in there. You
should have just absolutely hammered
that at 16s. All right, so TP1 here, if
you're short, TP2 is down here, 550s,
and then you can hold. All right, if you
get lucky, you'll get a move even deeper
here um to take out that previous week
low. But I would I would be paying
yourself some here and definitely some
into this. All right, some around here
for sure. That's the previous week value
area low. Oh, he's missed the trade
talking. [\h__\h] me.
Well, that is upsetting. It's what we
just talked about. If we leave this,
we're going to trade down to here and
then down to here.
Don't rehat, Alex. Don't rehat only 10
minutes into the day. Nice, Peter. You
took it. Yeah, this is all planned
pre-markets is what we talked about. Oh,
I'm upset myself there. Caught reading
questions in chat.
That is a 100 pointer straight out in
two minutes.
Yeah, you got you lot got it. Good. You
lot got it. Well, it was planned, wasn't
it? You can hold runner for down here.
And if we break this, all right, if you
break 550, you can look for 520s. And if
we break that, we are looking all the
way back down into this blue box down
here. It's very, very possible.
[\h__\h] me.
I might have to set a new rule where I
don't read questions the first 15
minutes in the day. Might have to be a
new rule.
Okay, selling aggressively here into
previous week value area low coming up.
Yeah, lots of you getting it. Nice,
nice, nice, nice, nice. I think you get
550 and 520. Then we see how much follow
through they've got. Yeah, some bids at
550. There's a big lot down at 500.
There's a huge buyer down at 500 281 lot
sat there at the moment. Let's see if I
can swipe this lower for you guys at the
moment. Big bleed out. VIX absolutely
tearing. This is exactly what we talked
about pre-market.
Oh my god, look at this nice like build
out here with the failing to re reclaim.
That was it. Okay, huge seller coming in
here on the tape at 95. Worth
remembering that number now. you should
still move lower, but there is a big
seller just came on the tape here at 95.
So above him, there is potential for a
little bit of a retracement up, but I
think we are due to move lower overall.
But here we go. We're above that that
seller now. Here's the retracement back
up into the next seller at 21. So
they're pricing between 95 21s. Here's
the squeeze back up. All right, here you
go. So that seller getting caught. This
was just going to be a short-term
squeeze up. I think they will resell
this, but it's just about this seller
who got caught into 93s. Again, I can
show you here. This guy right here got
caught and now we're lifting and we're
going to look for where these other
sellers came back in. Right, look at
that lift straight out of it. He did the
damage. He shorted at the lows. He
shorted at the lows. So, back up to
value area low here. You have to see if
you reject this now.
See if you reject this now.
Right the way back up. All the way back
up. Right the way back up to value. And
these 20s. Probably if they get back
over 25, you're going to see us squeeze
further.
Do they come back down here? They can
retest 20s and 25s if they want. Looking
for the short. If they do, we'll play
the long if we reclaim everything. Oh,
we've just held a bid there at those
sellers at 700. So, we've reclaimed
value.
We will see.
Where are we at?
680s. By reclaiming 680s, they might
start squeezing here. We get over we
might see a squeeze here. We will see.
Be very aggressive if they get over
these 25s. They might absolutely rip
some faces.
Come put that. There's the 25s. What
they going to do?
Very washy.
What do you want to do, Mark? You going
to reject this and come right back down
or you going to hold and squeeze up?
Right in the middle of this range.
Squeeze up. It is then. Here's the
squeeze.
[\h__\h] me. Can't do much with this.
Cannot do much with this right now.
This is just the options market more
than anything else here by the looks of
it to me. Straight down. Straight back
up because that player got caught
straight into these trap buyers here at
50s. Now
we might keep going here. Oh my god.
It's missed the play down. Misses a play
up. He's not with it today, that's for
sure. He's not on the money.
Right. All the way up to previous week.
Point of control is possible now. And
then through that, we can get going as
well. All the way up to 50s. So up here,
here, and here is possible. Looking to
see if they hold sort of 25s. Otherwise,
I can't do anything. They're just going
to rip it. Oh my god, man.
Soon as I saw that guy trapped, I should
have gone in. It's 200 point rip.
Right off that trap player.
Oh, they are on a mega squeeze.
Right. If they hold 25s now, we will we
will look for an entry. I tell you
what's not helping as well. The spy
is playing its own own game. Here's
the expansion then. Can they get up to
sort 50s?
They're bidding 750. Can you get up to
850 is what I'm asking.
And maybe up to 900 if you really want
to get going.
Like a dip rather than just a hold and
squeeze here, please.
See if they hold these 25. Sellers got
stuck here at 88 last time round in the
80s. They've reheld that dip. It's so
aggressive both sides here, folks. These
orders are big, big, big, big. Right up
to where the buyers got trapped this
morning. If they let these guys out,
we'll see that move towards 850. Clear
out the highs. Here
we go. 825s.
Get up to 850s.
825s. Let's get through this and go
850s. Let's get through this and go
850s. Let's go through this and go 850s.
Through the 25 [\h__\h] sake.
320 lot here. If we get through that, we
should see a little squeeze through.
Come on.
There we go. Yeah, there we go. There's
40s. Can we get 50s? Here we go, folks.
But me finally getting something. And
then we look look for 900s. We're going
to trim up here. Pay myself some into
this level here into the gray box and
then see if we can get 900s now. What a
[\h__\h] rip, man. Oh my god. If I just
entered where that player was trapped at
the bottom, we would be up huge,
wouldn't we? Here we go. 50s now. All
right. Small piece left and we'll see if
we get 900s.
Other
right into the 50s. That might be it. If
it can't get 900s, I'll cut the rest.
If we get 350s, I'm looking for 900s.
Then we can really get going.
We still haven't tested 25 since we
broke back over it. I'll say that much.
If we drop below 80 here, I'm out. It's
where the sellers got stuck at 80.
How do I maintain sanity when I miss the
moves? Well, I mean, there's not much I
can do. I mean, I would have had to be
so quick once we saw the seller down
here. It's a big buyers just got stuck
up top now, right? Once I saw this
seller down here, I would have just had
to enter long off no structure and we
should have really come down into here,
right? So, we didn't get we missed it.
So, it's very hard. Needed a 50 more. If
we done a break of of a previous week
value area low, if we'd come here and
then reclaimed, I would have been happy
to long at the bottom. But just a dip
and rip like that and now stuck into the
50s. Look at the 50s, right? Big big
buyer now. Stuck at 24. So, we're
probably going to come back down and
test these 20s again. It's messy. It's
very messy. I'm out now, folks, because
it's probably going to come back to the
25s again.
I have to see if they bid 25s now or
somewhere around there. And if they
don't, we might wash all the way back
down and finish the auction down here,
right? We might come all the way back
down here if they don't hold these sort
of 20s, 25s because we're very thin up,
aren't we? Very, very, very thin up. So,
they need to bid here and bid now.
Otherwise, we're probably going to go
low of day.
Watching this.
No, they're not bidding. Not yet.
It might go lower day here folks. This
is awful. You reclaim 25s.
What is this market? What are we doing?
What do you want to do market?
If they bid here, they might retest 80s.
It is terrible both ways though in back
inside the orb. It's not uh not an A+
setup, is it? they lose this, we're
going to probably go back to the low of
day, back towards where that seller was
stuck at 90. What was it? 592.
So, you got to make a decision. We're
right in the middle. We are right in the
middle right now.
It just feels like they don't know what
to do. They're like, "We should sell,
but you know, we're really extended. We
don't want to sell. We want to push up
before we sell." Okay, they're trying to
rebid 25s here now. How much of a
squeeze can they go? Can they go back to
80s if we're going to join this? I need
to get it over the New York Open and see
if we want to go back to 80s if I'm
going to play.
And we have to trim some at 80s. Oh, I
got stuck there at 50s. Can't play. Not
over that New York open.
Still waiting
back underneath now. I think this just
needs to be leave alone for a bit. I
don't think they know what they want to
do.
So, we got a big buyer stuck at uh 8.
What's his actual level? 825
and we've got a big seller stuck at 593.
How mad's that the volatility 593 825 in
one two 3 minutes we did that rip. So we
got buyer stuck up here, seller stuck
down here and we're just going between
the two and they do not know what they
want to do with it right now.
Okay. Well, don't drink, but I will have
to do it after stream. I can't do it
right now, my friend.
Back over 25. They're going to revisit
the 80s now. Do they sell 80s now is the
question. It's very hard to do anything
here.
So, back to the 80s. This is where all
the sellers came in, right? So, if
sellers want to defend this, they're
going to try and set a lower high. If
not, then we can see that move back over
850 to 900. Remember that buyer is stuck
up there currently. So, we go back to
these 80s like we talked about. 25 to
80s is the rotation.
And they sold 80s. Surprise, surprise.
And we go back down. Right? So, we just
talked about this, didn't we? 25 to 80s.
They literally just hit 80 and they come
back down to 25s. They don't know what
they want to do, folks. I can tell you
from looking at the book, they do not
want know what they want to do here.
You want me to go and get coffee? It is
time that I need to get a coffee.
Actually, I'm thinking about going to
get coffee.
No tea today. I've got tea here. It's
right here.
Thinking about my mushroom coffee right
now, though.
Okay. Big seller coming on the book
here. Defending 75s. 216 lot.
Mushroom copy. Yeah, I have a mushroom
copy.
We are literally right where we opened.
Nothing's changed. If you're wondering
why I'm still right now, we're right
where we open. Look at this huge node
developing.
We're not moving. We are pinned.
Coming back up to this 70 level. They're
trying to get this buyer out. There's a
new buyer coming in at 70. Got caught.
And now lifting to the 800s again. Are
they going to squeeze through this and
let this guy out at the high of day
82 here on SPY big level
where you have to be so patient.
800s.
It's by 82. Can't get through 82.
If we look above, that's failed so far
this morning. 800s again.
Remember, there is a buyer caught up
here at 824.
The other buyer was at 770s. So, if they
stay above 770s, he's got a shot. This
is what we're testing now. They're
testing that buyer at 770 saying, "Do
you want more or not?
Trying to see if he's going to come in
or not here. Doesn't look like it. If
not, we're going 25s again.
50s and 25s again. Oh, there's no market
to play here, guys. You can't play this.
Well, I can't play this. Or I'm not
willing to play this is a better way of
putting it, I guess. Back to the 25s
again. Are we going to sell all the way
down now? [\h__\h] me. How are you supposed
to do anything with this when they don't
know what they want to do?
Sell through then. If you're going to do
it, you might as well sell all the way
through. Are you going to just rip all
the way back up again now because you
guys don't know what to do? Yeah,
probably. [\h__\h] hell. This is a weird
Friday, that's for sure.
So, back to the 25s again. Are they
going to make a decision now if they're
going to go low of day or just rip it
back up again?
This is terrible.
Dude, who keeps asking what the current
CVD is? Why don't you just get it up? I
don't understand. On what time frame? On
what stock? on what time frame in the
minute. Like just get it up. It's right
at the bottom of the bookm right in
front of you. Like right here. There you
go. Minus 539 rolling like
Okay. Do they drop this now and come
back down low day?
Back to 25s again. [\h__\h] hell me.
There's quite literally nothing I can do
with this.
If they don't know what they want to do
with it, I certainly don't know what
they want to do with it.
We are pinned. We are pinned in a $2
range on the spy
and we're pinned currently between 25
and 800 on NQ. And if we fail 25 and we
fail uh aggressively from 25, we can go
back down to these 93s on ENQ. Uh as in
593s,
this thing's [\h__\h] awful.
What am I watching right now? This is
might be the worst market I've seen for
some time.
The size of these orders though. Jesus
Christ.
Part of me is like, fade it, fade it
back down. But I just
don't trust it in the slightest right
now. Not in the slightest.
developing this thick node here where
they will not lose the bottom of the
node and we can't hold a bit above the
top of the node. And they are just going
to do nothing with this.
Ready to go back to sleep. If it I tell
you what, if it's like this for another
half an hour, I will be getting off the
screens, guys. I'm not going to sit here
on a Friday and watch this.
to 25s.
What are these idiots doing? Bunch of
clowns. Back to 25s. Back to the 40s.
Back to New York Open. Failing New York
Open. If we get through this, I try and
get back up here again. There's no way
I'm touching this.
There is no way I'm touching this.
No edge here for me. 680 won't let go on
spy. 600 reclaim on QQQ.
All
right, back to this trap buyer at 770s.
They're going to test him. If they get
through him, they're going to go for
823s again or 800s.
The 770 is still stuck. He just sold on
that last push up.
We come back down to 25s again probably
this New York open.
Can I explain why not to trade? Well,
what's the Okay, here we go. Uh flow
zones flat bot flat. We are in this
after a huge sell. A huge sell with
compression where we're not moving. What
trade setup is there there right now?
Right? What setup is there? Ask
yourself, what setup there is there? And
then ask yourself, okay, if there's no
setup, why why am I trying to trade?
There's quite legitimately no setup. And
there's another huge buyer coming in
here trying to force it up and getting
absolutely nowhere.
Can I? Yeah. Okay. I'll tell you when to
buy and sell. Buy now. I'm joking.
Obviously. No. I keep telling you
there's no trade. There's no trade.
What are you guys after? There's nothing
here right now, folks. All there was was
a seller caught at the lows and a
straight rip and a big buyer caught up
here. There's There's really quite
legitimately nothing to do at the
moment, folks.
Two. Don't be Don't be impatient. Just
be patient. It will come. It will come.
Right. Over 2,000 of you watching.
Incredible. Let's get these likes up so
we can do some giveaways.
Oh, I send out my swing trades in
Discord. I do. Yeah, there's a swing
there's a swing uh swing channel in the
Discord.
Yeah, exactly. Yesterday we had to wait
and then we got the 400 pointer. They
still got this guy stuck at 770. Can
still see him stuck. He's still right
here stuck. Right. And sellers came in
above him. The big lot is stuck up here
at H24. We're just inside of balance.
We're inside of the opening range. We're
inside of the current value. We're not
doing anything other than rotate, folks.
All right. This is just building a huge
amount of liquidity.
Back to the 25s again.
by two point range 80 to 82 pinned
there. Absolutely pinned there. All
right, they saved 25s this time. Vpo
holding. Do they let this buyer out at
70s
Man, who just said bull flag for me? Um,
dude,
that ain't a bull flag. Don't know what
you're looking at. Even if it pops
higher, this is trapping both sides
right now.
You got to understand everything's stuck
up here. We're pinned. Like I
personally, you do what you want.
Personally, I'd wait to see if we find
acceptance right now cuz at the moment,
like I keep telling you, we have a buyer
stuck at 70. Cannot get through that
buyer. Every time we popped up to to
him, he's sold. And we keep rebidding
25. So, there's just a rotation there.
If they lose 25s, they're going to come
down to 87s. If they lose 87s, they're
going to cut gut at 60. If they lose
that, we have a trap setter at the low
of day at 594. That's all we can do.
Reals, thanks for joining.
Back to 25s again.
Sorry folks, this is I'm just like I
say, it's one of the worst markets I've
seen for a while for the open.
Yeah.
Is there anything you say in your
course? Anything? What?
Dude, why do you keep spamming the same
thing? You got one more chance. If you
say that one more time, you're gone. I
don't know what you're on about.
Back and held again. Reclaim 25s. Back
to New York open again. Can I come and
retest 770s?
Can I explain buyers and sellers?
Oh, trapping buyers and sellers. Yeah,
well, it's just when aggressive
participants come in at the extremes.
All right. So, if you think about this
morning when we sold off at the low of
day here, we had a huge seller come in
and we didn't move lower. So, when we
move above his point, he starts stopping
out causing the squeeze. When we came up
to the high of day, we had a 292 lot
buyer come in. We don't move higher. He
gets caught buying the high of day. So,
when we start washing, he starts
stopping out, which means we get sell
pressure. Now, we're just pinned. We're
absolutely pinned.
Look at that. Byron sending five gift
memberships. That's very kind of you.
Thank you, Byron. Well done all of those
who just got it.
I explain the nodes. It's just an area
of high volume. It's just where where
we're building out a lot of high volume.
So this is current value area high on
the day, value area low on the day,
point of control on the day. And this is
the rotation. You can see we are not
finding acceptance outside of this. We
are building liquidity. We will abuse
everyone in here later. Whether I'm here
for that or not is another thing, but
that's what we're doing. We're chopping
in that range.
What's the EMA with the buy cell? It's
the flow zone pro. It's right here. But
I ignore those when we're going
sideways. Look, the flow zones are flat
right now. So, back to 770 again where
this buyer keeps getting caught. If they
get acceptance through this, they can
try and lift to value area high. If they
get through value area high, they will
lift to 823s. At the moment, they can't
get through the guy at 770. They keep
trying, but they can't get through it.
If they get through it, then yeah, you
can watch maybe 90s.
So 770, we have a buyer stuck. Over that
we go 90s. So they're trying to get over
it now. Still can't get over it, right?
They just wick over instant sell.
Here's the 90s. All right, let's see.
Are you guys going to do something fun
here?
70 to 90. Watching this high now. Now,
do we start squeezing? Yes, we are.
Imbalances up here into 800s again. It's
a big level, the 800s.
So, they've got to now rebid 770. If
they rebid 770,
maybe I'm interested in a lift or in
front of 770 and then a break of 800 and
then we will have to take some partials
in front of 825.
So there's a 770 rebid. You just see it
come down and rebid 770. So let's see
now. Can they get above 800 or not? If
you took this, I'd put your stop break
even at 770 straight away.
800. Here we go, folks. Right, we need
to get up into 20s. Right, I will sell
some here in front of 20s
cuz we know that buyer is stuck at 825.
So, we get above 825, we've got to
squeeze up to 850s,
which will be 100 points if we get up
there.
Want it to hold 90s now if possible.
Nice. Keep holding 90s. Don't reflush
90s. We've got sellers call 90s now.
Want you to hold this. Don't really want
it to come back to 70s. Would be a fail
break.
The ' 90s test. Oh, it's going to come
back to 70s.
We break 70s. I'm fully out.
Out.
This tags me and goes.
You [\h__\h] know it's going to do it.
You [\h__\h] know it. It loves to stop
Alex every [\h__\h] time.
What was my entry? 70s.
70s. Right. On the guy's pain point,
right? Entry was 70s. We talked about
this guy is stuck. Once we get above
him, I said if we hold 70s, we're good.
We held 70s. I'd sold some into 800s. I
stopped out on the reflush. I wanted
them to hold this 90s now. Now, you're
looking to take some money out into 25s.
This is where this big player is, right?
So, pay yourself into 25s. And above
that, you're looking for 850 and 900. We
might get going here. So, you're lifting
up into this guy at 25. You must pay
yourself some here. And then through
this 850s, they're piling in buy side
now.
So you're looking for 850s now through
this. So you've paid yourself now. So
you're 770 to 820s and you're looking
for 850s and 900. Now do not be buying
up here. You will get caught, right?
[\h__\h] stop me out.
Absolute buckers.
How many days have I had that?
All right, let's see then. Let's see
then. Can you get 25s and 50s without
me? You've got 25s already. Can you get
50s and 900s? Really?
You really ideally you want to stay
above 825 where that buyer was caught
above that squeeze potential.
Just know there is resistance up here
into 50s. Okay.
Stopping Alex out has been the theme of
the week, hasn't it? Just stopping Alex
out on like all runners. I get like a
little partial and then that's it. I get
stopped every time.
No, I don't watch it on ES as well,
folks. Sorry. I my brain I can't watch
it across everything. If I was trading
ES, obviously I'd watch it on ES, but it
is uh it takes quite a lot out of you to
watch take the way I do and obviously
comment on it and try and give you guys
the levels.
All right, they're losing this bid here.
They need to hold this bid at 800s
otherwise you're going to go back to 70s
again. Good, good hold of 800s there.
You need to get back above 25s. You must
get back above 25s here. This is where
that buyer stuck.
Man,
that's deeply upsetting. Had a really
good entry there. Ignored all this
[\h__\h] Took the entry. Right. Let
them do all this nonsense. Took the
entry. Got the partial. And then it
wicks me out. And what we're looking for
now is here 850 and then 900. All right.
TP2,
TP3.
You're looking for this into here if it
will go. But you must be aggressive
taking profit today. This is not a day
to just hold on.
I don't do it based on points, folks.
Okay? I don't do my stop loss based on
points. I do it based on where I think
the trade is no longer valid. For me,
the trade was no longer valid if we got
under 70, which we did. It just stopped
me out by five points.
What are you going to do? It's volatile
market.
Vo shifted up here. Now, you really want
to see them hold the bid of 800 and
around there. Otherwise, you're going to
get a slide back down to 70 again, and
we're just going to be in a range
rotation market.
So maybe that down to 70 here. There you
go. Coming back down 70. Obviously I'm
already out of this. If they lose this,
you do not want to hold it. If they
start losing this, do not want to hold
it. If they start losing this, it would
be another fail breakout. There you go.
They've lost it. Back down to VWAP. Very
volatile.
Do I re recommend passing emails in in
one day? Uh, probably not because it
means you're oversized. Only if you're I
do it like that. I try and do it in one
or two days, but you have to be very
accurate.
Be very accurate. This is horrible.
Yeah, we're just ranging around, right?
So, we came, remember, we we were taking
profit. I said if you take this 770s,
we're taking profit 800 and 825. So, you
still got what's that? Uh 55 points,
right? We didn't hit the 850 and 900
which would have given us the 100
pointer. We're still holding here or
hereabouts, but it's looking not very
nice. Now,
look at spy. Still can't get a close and
hold above 82s, right? Big big level for
spy.
Would I be looking at another entry for
sure? Yeah, I'd like to trade some more.
I'm willing to play both ways.
One of the worst days of the year
probably
probably at the moment. But I mean look
look at the sales we've had uh the last
few days. That's why
and understand like where we are higher
time frame folks, right? What's this
gray box
here? Right.
We're stuck on the previous week level.
Right. We know we've got some
compression here. We know that they've
got stops to hunt. know we probably want
to move lower, but we probably need to
try and get up to move lower, but they
are just not letting it do it on a
Friday.
We are pinned. We are pinned in here. We
are not seeing relief
for that move there, which I'd love. And
we're not seeing this. We're just seeing
more of this, right? And we know when we
do this, we build out liquidity. We
don't really love trading in that. Try
and avoid that where possible.
Okay, so they've lost the top side. Back
to the 25s again.
Alex, if I buy the volume and order flow
course, do I get the flow zone indicator
that mentioned in the beginner to
advance course? You do not. You do not.
They're only in the beginner to advance.
Why is there no reaction from buyers?
Reaction from buyers where there's
reaction from both lots. What you
talking about? We're not in a trend.
There's reaction from both lots. We're
building.
Go back to the start of this video. Like
9:15 a.m. We talked about this building
liquidity. Zoom out, right? We are
starting to go sideways,
tapering,
horizontal, tapering,
right? We're building liquidity. You can
argue that's a failed break, but we
haven't seen continuation up here
because we're heavy up here right now.
Lots of people who are trying to buy are
just going to cut their losses here or
get out break even.
Back into patient mode here, folks. I
can't control the market. I'm really
sorry. probably lots of you, you know,
have seen like the previous videos and
well this day you got 100 points and
this day you got 400 points and this day
we can't we can only trade what's in
front of us.
That's awesome. Ben just read that
message. That's awesome. You and Daniel,
that's great work.
I don't think the support zone is down
to around 24620. And if it breaks that,
you should go short. 24620
4 oh 2 4 620 or basically the low of day
I mean you'd be shorting low of day if
you're going to short low of day you're
shorting low of day and you'd have to be
covering something into 550s
um 550s
and 520s you're not leaving yourself
that much room if you're going to short
low of day low of week are you on a
Friday it's asking a lot I would rather
a bull trap higher to short if I'm
honest.
Freaky Fridays. Yeah, freaky Fridays.
That's it. It is freaky Fridays.
It is Friday the 13th. You guys are
right.
I caught the 400 pointer with you
yesterday as a first-time watcher. Your
market analysis is spot on. Oh, that's
awesome, man. I'm glad you got it. Alex,
I've only got $120 left to pass my eval.
Well, don't be trying to pass it today,
right? Unless it sets up. This is not a
day to try and pass an eval if we're
going to keep doing this. So just wait.
You don't want to give back.
Hood. Doing well today. Yeah, it's
finding a bid. It's finding a bid versus
that low it put in uh last week,
which is great.
Why Friday is usually so [\h__\h] for
trading? Uh normally because we've done
the range of the week already and you
have options expireies as well.
Do I have a telegram where I share
trades? No.
Okay, back to the 800s.
This where all those buyers last got
caught. Value area high here.
Are they going to turn the bid on? Are
we going to move out of this range that
we've developed?
I mean, if you're a uh range trader,
surely you're enjoying this right now.
You can just keep bidding 25s and keep
selling 800 over and over and over and
over again until it's until it's done
with it, right?
Again, spy can't get through 82. Again,
it can't get through 82. It just had
another go at getting through 82. It
failed again. Spy
on the spiders
back down to 25s again probably
New York open.
They fail this. What What are they going
to do? Are they going to come all the
way back down again? Just wonder like
this has all been left open since
the 50s
770s again. That same player over 70s.
We're going to go back to eights over
70s. I don't know. I'm not going to take
it no matter what because they don't
know what they want to do.
How do you handle these type of markets?
You just got like the biggest problem I
think most people have is they come to
the this is different to going to like a
9 to5 and having to do like the same
thing every day, right? It's about
opportunity.
There's not there's no opportunity. I
would say the best opportunity today
happened with the trap guy down here,
right? It happened
here,
right? This guy here got caught. All
right, all this selling got caught. Look
at the shift from big sell delta to big
buy delta. Once this guy got caught,
that was the opportunity. I was late on
the trigger and I just wasn't willing to
buy a 100 points higher with that
happened in seconds. Literally in
seconds. That was the best opportunity
of the day. Um,
but you know what was wrong with that
opportunity?
We didn't come down to value, right?
They trapped him and rebid over 600. It
would have been much nicer if we'd come
down
into this and rebid. All right? So, I'm
not going to blame myself on stuff like
that. And it's knowing that I cannot get
a trade today or I can have that break
even one. And that's fine. I made all my
money this week, right? We've already
made it. So like you only need one
really good trade a week or a month or
in a career really with people who are
big swing traders to change your life.
You don't need to try and tack
everything all the time.
It's not there's not always stuff
available.
Okay. Over 70s. Going to go and test the
800s again.
Yes. Still can't get through. Sorry,
Spy. Still can't get through the 82s.
We are just trapped here. We're
absolutely pinned.
No acceptance outside of value. The blue
on your screen. We're not finding any
acceptance outside of this right now. I
can't even get up to the 800s this time.
It's getting weaker and weaker both
ways.
I just think there's a nasty candle
coming soon, like a massive candle. I
don't know which direction, but we can't
do this. Whatever. Someone will stop out
and get frustrated and it will cause a
big big candle.
Back towards the 800s.
Bpo, are we going to go through the 800s
now? Yes, we're going through the 800s.
Oh, it's tempting, man. It's tempting.
Is this the candle?
Still just tapping the top side. If they
base over here, they've got a chance to
go 2550 again, but we're not basing yet.
800s. Can they base?
Spying to uh 682, which it cannot get
over so far today. It's peaked through
it, but it can't get over it. This is a
cool war on Spy. If they get over this,
they get a chance. But uh so far today,
SPY cannot get over this level.
Sorry folks, I can't I can't control it.
I wish I could. You want an Alex
bathroom break? I do need a coffee. All
right. Big seller coming in here, folks.
Huge seller just came in here. 100 lot.
He might get caught soon.
He might get caught soon. They look
they're looking to lift up to 25s and
50s. That seller's just got caught. Here
we go. All right. I'm going to try a
little piece long here. See if we can
get up to 25s and 50s. Uh versus 95. Not
going to let it come under 95. That
seller's got to stay stuck once I saw
him come in there. We'll try and use his
pain here. If we're going to get above
800s. Here we go. Let's go 25s and 50s.
Let's go 25s and 50s. Give Alex at least
something today. Okay, here we go,
folks. Let's get 25s. Let's get through
25s.
Big buyer stuck up here. We need to get
through the 25s. If we get through 25s,
we can go 50s. Or are you going to make
me TP early? There's some at 25. Right,
let's see if we get 50s now. Once that
seller got stuck, it got a little bit
easier there for some follow through.
Must not come under what's his level?
96es.
Really would prefer a hold of 800s here.
So, stops moved into the money.
Okay, while this plays out, we're going
to look I'm going to look for TPS at 850
and then 900. Okay. Uh, make sure. Yeah,
850 and 900.
So, 850. This spike here, right? We're
going to take some in 25, some at 850,
some at 900. I'm going to put my limits
out. Move my stop up. Here we go, folks.
We might get one here. If we get 900s,
it will be 100 pointer. All right.
If you're like, why? Why? Why? Why? I
don't understand. It was just this
seller. I saw him get stuck at that key
level and I'm using his pain to go
higher. That's all it is. All right.
Here's the move towards 50s. Right. Let
me go and brew a coffee while this
happens.
Right. Coffee is brewing. Yeah. Almost
there, folks. All right. Only 900's
left. So 850's hit. Almost there, folks.
Almost there, folks.
We might get 100 pointer here. If we get
lucky, we're lifting to 955. So I don't
necessarily think we're going to do that
today.
Um, so we took this guy's pain and we're
trying to get up into here now if
possible.
Uh, you want this to protect 825 830.
All right, where the big buyers just
came in. All right, these big buyers who
just squeeze us up. We want these guys
to stay in the money. All right, 825
830. So we're almost at the level we
want. We want 900. We want to squeeze up
into here. All right, so we're using
this guy's pain. All right. Once this
guy piled in at this 800 after we' done
it a million times, I was like, "Yep,
I'm going to have you." Thank you very
much. And we're looking for 900. Now,
and that would be 100 pointer if we get
it.
Now, if we lift through 900, let's have
a think about what we can do. If we lift
through this,
if we lift through 900, there is an
argument for 956 and 25,5.
All right. So, if we lift through this,
there's an argument for this level here
or 944s.
Here we go, folks. Here we go, folks.
Yapping, yapping, yapping away today.
Well, some of you will learn. Just stay
with me. Once the trade comes, we get
it. Here we go.
Here we go. So, we're looking for this.
This is your next TP. And then we're
going to hold runners. And I tell you
what, if they turn the turbo on today,
it could be fun. So over this we're
looking for over 900 we're going to look
for the blue line above. All right. Over
900 we're going to look for this. And
over that we're going to look for this.
All right. So there might be 200 points
here if we get lucky. But this is a big
level. Sell some into this level. Please
look. We've missed it by a tick. Don't
be a dick for a tick like we always talk
about. I would move your stop up now.
All righters. We can come all the way
down to 25s. Don't not let it do that.
All right. You'd want to see an
imbalance hold here around 65s. Don't
let it come under that. I would say I'm
going to go and pour my coffee out and
come back.
Okay. What's the time? IB now set,
folks, as well. So, be careful of the
failed breakout. So, we pretty much hit
it. We missed it by a tick. You really
want this IB to hold. I don't really
want to offer it to redip all the way
down to 50s. All right. So, we really
want this to hold for the expansion.
Now, they're adding at 950 above, which
is good. We look good.
Holds of 850s look good. Everything
holding 850 looks good, but I don't
really want it to come down and retest
there. That'll be given 50 points back
from the from the peak, won't it?
So, maybe I'll cut an off and read there
if I really want to. Come on, market.
Let's get squeezing. Let's go. Let'sing
go, market. Let's just [\h__\h] turn it
on, please.
Where was the seller court? 800. Here we
go. Let's go. Here's the squeeze. What
are we saying here? Someone's going to
get [\h__\h] soon. We can't sit there
forever. All right. Here we go, folks.
So, almost at blue line. This is your
next TP. Uh, right here. Right. That
would be 150 points. And if we're lucky,
we're going to get all the way up into
this 25,027. We will respect 25,000
being a whole number. But let's look for
25,046es.
Did we just run those stops? Did we just
run those stops? Not quite. Okay, this
is the level right into here. 45s if we
can go. Seller coming in at higher day
here, which is what I want to see. Let's
try and print above 20s. That's where
the big sellers just come in. We'd love
to print above 20s now. Don't want him
to be comfortable. We've got an
imbalance down to 900. Maybe we can move
our stop just under 900 here. And let's
see if we can print out here. Higher the
better. Here we go, folks. Here we go,
folks.
So, you are now coming into here. This
would be 150 odd pointer. All right,
let's see if we can get all the way up
into here. Do not add up here. I'm
telling you now, do not be adding up
here. You will get absolutely slapped.
900's got to hold here for me or I'm
out.
It can afford to come much much deeper.
So, I'm just not willing to give too
many profits back here. So, 900 for me
has to hold here. We have a little
imbalance at 900. So, Where's that
previous day control? 890s holding so
far here. Sellers trying to pile in.
Would like to see some absorption here
into 900 or I will be out.
There's 900.
Come on. Step in, Mr. Absorber.
Otherwise, I'm gone.
Don't do what you've done all week and
stop me out and then rip another 300
points, you [\h__\h] Pardon my French
today.
Come on. Absorb it or I'm out. Absorb it
or I'm out here because we got big
sellers stuck here at 9005 and 9003. I
want to stay above those sellers. Get
above back above 909 would be really
good.
No. No. I'm out. I'm out. Now, I know I
know what's going to happen. I know I'm
going to stop out and I know they're
going to rip it all the way to my TPS
because it's just how it works for Alex
this week. But I know I'm watching. If
you're looking at the DOM here. All
right. I can see these sellers down
here. Look, they're going to do it. [\h__\h]
me. I was trying to use them as my
stock. Oh my god. They're going to do it
again. Every day this week, I've been
rinsed on that move.
Oh, NQ, you're so harsh this week, man.
You're not letting me use their pain for
stops. Oh god.
Oh, why don't I get back in? I'm not
buying up here. No way, man. No way.
It's 100 points higher than my entry.
Not buying up here in a rotation. No
chance.
All right. Building out some liquidity
up here now. All right. So, you just
missed this TP here by what? A couple
ticks. Hopefully, it does it for you.
It's trying to hold previous day point
control. They rinsed me by five points.
That's twice today. They've rinsed me by
five. All right. Hopefully, you get this
and then this. That would be the
ultimate target for you. But definitely
this blue line must be some.
I stopped IB high. Um probably did, but
uh my stop was not based on IBH high. I
stopped at 900. No, I I behigh down here
at 870.
I was trying to use uh their pain,
right? So, we had a a lot of sellers
piling in, right? And I was trying to
make sure we stayed above this seller
here. You see him here piling in, right?
I wanted to stay above this seller. I
didn't want it to drop under this
imbalance, right? We dropped under the
imbalance, of course, and then ripped
back up and got above this seller. So,
these are the sellers which are piling
in. So if you get above 920 now there's
chance for a resque squeeze out
inverse repeat of yesterday pretty much
isn't it pretty pretty similar of
yesterday pretty similar of of yesterday
Alex getting getting ripped
that trader three thank you man I
appreciate that I appreciate that very
Why not add five to 10 points for the
next couple of weeks? It's tempting,
isn't it? But I'm not going to trade I'm
not sorry trade I'm not going to change
my trading for a couple of sessions
where the volatility's been up because
you know I try m like arguably I could
have risked a little bit more but you
know what it's a 100 point plus trade
see and I don't want to get caught in
that that there because now the sellers
are in control well not totally in
control but of this here. So sellers
have piled in in this volume node up
here. See, this is what I did not want
to get caught in. This is when my stop
went to 9005. So, look at what happened
up here. Once these sellers got the
break under their level, we are washing
right back down. Here are the
imbalances. 53s. Where can they revisit
820s where we broke out from? Remember,
we got long on this buyer's pain at 800.
All right. Buyer came in, pushed us all
the way up. Sellers come in. I use I
tried to use them as my stop. They take
over. I'm out. We're going to come and
revisit these imbalances and where these
buyers came back in at 820, 820s, 825s.
If we lose that, we come right back down
to VPO where we got back in. Right. So,
not going to force my way in.
3K for the day. Passed an email. Thanks
very much, man. Mainly practicing
patience. Your knowledge is uncanny. F
the haters out. I appreciate that,
Blake. Thank you very much.
peak above and fail. Yeah, absolutely.
That's what we've done. Um into previous
days value area high would have been
more ideal though. Did we take out this
stop? We didn't actually peak above it
all. So, this is one of the things I was
looking at. This is where the blue line.
All right. The peak above technically to
run all the stops would been 944s.
Right. This blue line current week
developing value area low. It's exactly
what I would have looked for, which is
what you've just said, right? I would
have looked to take profit in here and
here and then I would have been thinking
about that short back down. All right.
Definitely. We didn't actually run all
the stops. I would have liked a little
bit more. But that has been the story of
NQ this week. Right. ENQ this week.
Remember, Alex was looking for a swing
short.
Uh if we could have move this out, which
is what we're looking for in Discord. If
we could have just run
these guys here. I was looking to get
swing short in here for this move back
down to the naked point of control right
here and then follow through underneath.
Unfortunately, we didn't run the stop.
Same thing here. We'd like to run these
stops to get back short. We didn't run
the stops. It's the same story. NQ this
week. So heavy it's not popping those
stops.
Okay. and all the way back down to where
we got long. Right, this is where we got
long. So, obvious obviously, in case
it's not obvious, I stopped out right
under or right at 900 or wherever it
was. All right, so we're well well out
of this now.
Can I see the original seller trapped on
TV footprint? Uh, you probably could.
Where was that? Right.
could probably could on the delta here.
Uh
what level did I have it at? 95. Let's
see if there's somewhere at 95. It's
going to be this guy. Yeah, these guys
here, right? So, we had it here and
here. Same seller. And once we got above
him, he had to stop out. Yeah, same guy.
Look at the delta in those. Same guy.
Definitely
uh the highs. You're going to see the
shift at the highs as well. Right.
Buyers at the top, sellers kept coming
in. 900's needed to hold. Sellers came
in. All these buyers got caught. And
there's the big sell and repric. And
right back down to where we rebid first
time, right? So, right back down to the
area where those buyers rebid where we
first got in pretty much. Right. So now
you'd be watching
are they going to squeeze or do you see
a failed follow through here? So I'd say
you can sort of watch 850s
somewhere in here
right if they do a failed follow
through. I'm not sure. I love the
auction at the high but maybe in here
there is some failed follow through. If
they fail to reclaim this
back down into here again and under here
we're back into the slop and the
rotation. All right. So this is the
edge. They're protecting the edge.
Buyers will try and take this up. If
they fail to follow through, we come
back down. If we lose that, we come back
down to the other side, right? If buyers
reclaim this, they can try and finish
the uh rotation.
So, very, very weak. Failing to follow
through. Didn't even offer a pop to
sell. Very, very, very weak is how I
would interpret it. Interpret what's
just happened there.
Thanks FC. That's nice of you. Hey
Stephen, thanks for joining
buyers now caught. So all those buyers
we talked about at 824 and 830s.
All right, they didn't sell the highs,
they're now caught.
I would have been willing to resell this
on a popup here.
messy now. Now we wait again. We have to
let it develop again. If it just keeps
sliding, there's not a lot I can do with
it if it just keeps sliding. Do I trade
on NQ MT5 funding pips? If I buy
account,
uh I don't trade on funding pips
and I if you're trading on funding pips,
you won't be able to trade ENQ. You'd
have to trade uh NAS 100, I would
assume, because it would be CFD.
Can I adopt you?
You don't want to be adopted by me.
If 880 is denied, can we sell? Yes,
definitely. Definitely. 850 to 880. If
it's denied, I think it's a sell
potentially. Yeah. At the moment, we're
not even popping up there.
It assumes you seem all the huge orders
are day trading.
um seems flawed to me, but as I
understand institutions, it it doesn't
matter if they're day trading or swing
trading. Um it's where their pain point
is. It's how the end of an auction
happens. Um maybe maybe all the buyers
happened here, right, are just
absolutely accumulating. It's it's
possible and we're forced higher. It's
possible, but I'm going to trade where I
think their pain point is. And most
people, you will find are getting late.
All right, back to P uh DC here. So, we
just clo back to the close of yesterday
again. No trade opportunity here. So,
let's straight up straight back down. I
would have loved a fade, right? Once
we've done this move, I would have loved
a short back here for a TP1 and maybe in
the middle and then here, but it's not
offering it now. So, there's no trade up
here, folks. There's nothing I can do
with this. It's not a great auction at
the high either.
Flat top high. It's not perfect, really.
Why was 900 a TP? Did you say uh because
it was previous day point of control,
right? So right here, this was fair
value from yesterday. All right, we came
we were in discount. Look, this is
previous day value area low. Let's think
what what's happened today. We drifted
way under value area low. We reclaimed
it. Okay, no acceptance lower. We chop,
we chop, we chop, we chop, we chop. And
we go, hey, let's just see if
yesterday's fair value is still a good
value. We come up and they go, no, this
is actually too expensive today. Okay,
we're coming back down to today's fair
value. P of the day, right? This is pre
previous week fair value as well. Right,
so this is why it's so choppy in here.
If we lose this, we're going to come and
breeze visit previous days value low. If
they deem that too expensive, then we're
going to revisit previous week's value
low. If they deem that too cheap, then
we're going to bid back up off it. This
is just how an auction works. So the
reason 900 was a TP, yes, 900 whole
number is important, but it was more
that this is here, right? That's why.
And this blue line was also important to
me. It's developing. It was a bit higher
at the time. It's the developing
profile. And what I really wanted to do
was run
these stops. All right, this is where I
would have liked to have got a TP. All
right, when I was saying like 940, 950,
I would have loved to have just popped
up and run those stops out up here. All
right, look at this. Very, very, very
weak now. There's not a lot I can do
with this. There's not offering me a pot
to sell into here, unfortunately.
I draw everything myself, Enzo. Yeah.
All those all those are things I draw on
myself.
Yes. Yes.
So, right down to the New York open and
previous day low and previous day value
are low again now. So, do we find
acceptance below this and come and fill
Why have we got gaps in here? Come on,
CME. Sort it out.
Trying to be patient here, folks.
Let's have a look. Some adjusted levels
15 25
Was
that a Tyson trade to VW up? Um, I mean,
how are you getting that though?
Tyson was probably looking for the same
as me once we failed under was probably
looking for this to sell back down,
right? It was the trade, but it didn't
give him the setup. The same thing we
were talking about pop up towards 50.
Anything up towards 50 and and somewhere
up here to resell down would have been
Tyson's trade. Look above IB fail, but
there's no there's no failed follow
through. Remember when we were here, I
said if we get a failed follow through
now, we will play short. If we get a
failed follow through, we play short. It
never gave us the opportunity. This is
the thing today. Market's moving very
quick. It's not giving us It's doing
moves, but it's not always giving us
entry models.
Oh, sorry. I'm just seeing what you guys
saying.
Do I have any materials explaining how
to use Trading View for futures trading?
Um,
there's probably a lot on my YouTube for
free. Yeah. Otherwise, I go through
absolutely everything in the course.
Alex, since being on stream, I switched
from extreme FOMO entries to patience
and big picture top top down. Nice,
nice, nice. Alex, as always, your
analysis really helps me understand
market better. The knowledge you share
for free on stream is a real godsend.
You're welcome.
How do I feel about ICT inverse for
value gap?
I don't feel anything.
If it works for you, trade it.
I I feel nothing.
What was the key level in the middle of
the long candle? You said if it retested
that you would have gotten short. Oh,
this this is initial balance.
This is the initial balance. All right.
And it's also a pivot like think about
structure, right? Think about messy
messy messy messy messy messy messy
messy messy.
Right? We would have loved this,
wouldn't we? That's perfect. Back down
to VWAP. TP1 would be here. TP2 would be
here. TP3 would be here. TP4 would be IB
low break and low. It' be an IB reversal
from IB high to IB low. If they reject
B1,
if we had positioning, we could have
done that.
But we don't
cuz they've made our life very, very
hard.
Okay, here's the pop back up.
Can they make their mind up?
All right, back to pre previous week's
point of control. What are we doing?
Can we decide what we're doing, please?
All right. So, where were those buyers
stuck? 25s, 29s over that gets a little
bit thin.
Back in this chop zone. Then we go 800s
again. So, they do they come to 25s and
29s. And do they lift right back to IB?
And it's very, very thin above the 25s
and 29s from before. So, let's see if
they push and fail here or if they lift.
The S looks pretty strong here.
It's where the buyers were caught.
Remember, we can think about a short up
here if we start rejecting. We have got
point of control here at 800s again
under the 800s. Oh, it's very tempting
here to take a short honestly. Looking
at these guys here, I'm hoping we lift
up into these and then see them get
stuck again is what I'm trying. But
market's so weak, it won't lift up into
it.
I think I've just found my mentor for
life. Been wasting money on courses and
other people trying to learn what I
later would have learned from YouTube.
Looking forward looking forward to
trading. I think you're saying, "Yeah,
welcome. Welcome.
How long did it take me to master
orderflow? Um, it's a good question. I I
don't know. I couldn't put time on it.
Not too long.
Not too long. I've been trading a long
time, though.
What do I think the market is opening
24/7? I don't think it'll make a
difference, honestly. I think since co
I talked to a friend in chat about this
yesterday. Since COVID, I think
everything has been skewed to make those
who understand markets make more money.
So, opening 24/7, what does that do? You
might think it like provides more
liquidity and all this stuff, which is
true. Same with zero DTE, which came in
in 2022, right? So, we did STEMI checks
21, zero DTE 2022. Surprised I'm not.
And now we're going to 24-hour markets.
What does that open? Oh, mister. I just
got [\h__\h] hammered in a bar. Had an
argument. going to go and uh start
placing, you know, positions when I'm
absolutely shitfaced. That's what that
opens up. What does that mean? More
opportunity for those who know what
they're doing. I honest that's not about
me saying for me. I think that's that's
the big game.
Uh I'll take a buzz cap DACA. Thanks.
All right. We're trying to come into
where these buyers were trapped. Want to
see how we act here to into 25s and 30s.
If they lift, they'll go up to the IB,
but I want to see if we do trap more
buyers here and then sell through back
under the 800s. But they can lift all
the way up here. So, we know sort of 25s
and 30 is a big level. If they lift
through that, they can squeeze all the
way back up to 70s.
We we'll just see. We'll just see what
how we go here.
into where these buyers were caught.
This is where the buyers were caught.
The question is now, do they fail here
or do we start squeezing
tapping that 30s? They squeeze, they can
run it to 70s, 870s up here
above this. Now, can they come all the
way up here or we going to get stuck
right into this level 30s? Here comes
the squeeze. They're trying to squeeze.
I'm not going to play the squeeze. I'm
going to wait to see if they trap buyers
for the short. So, I'm going to wait and
see if it happens.
50s is an interesting level. Somewhere
between 50s and 70s is an interesting
level in my mind.
can repric this whole thing if they
really want be gross but they could
right buyers now comfortable over 25s so
back under that they'd be uncomfortable
so is this Look above into this level.
I'm watching this now. If they start to
fail right into these 25s again, right?
Like I said, this is where the buyers
are comfortable in the 25s. If we start
failing this, we will see a wash.
I'm watching this now very, very, very
carefully for the short here. Here we go
in now. Looking for expansion. Can we
see expansion back down under value area
high?
Come on, baby.
Nice. Let's get under the 800s now.
Nice. Let's go. Let's go. Get out of my
[\h__\h] way, baby.
Let's go. Let's see expansion lower.
Now, this is the failed follow through
that I was looking up for. This is what
we just talked about. Right. Covering
some 800s. If we get acceptance under
800s, I'll look down into here. So,
there's like a quick 5040 pointer there.
We need to stay heavy here at 25 or I'm
out
again. [\h__\h] me. So, at least I got a
decent lot lot out here. So, like I
said, into here was interesting for me.
If we trap more buyers, we did. They got
stuck again. We just washed right back
down to previous week point of control.
There might still be follow through. Um,
again, I'm just watching the order flow.
I have to be quick here. You You guys
might be like, why why why? I can only
react to what I'm seeing on the tape.
Okay, these were the buyers that were
caught. We popped over them. We trapped
more buyers into 44. Sellers came in at
36. We sold through. We cover some into
this buyer here who was comfortable at
96s. Right under that, I think there's a
wash back down to 71s.
Okay. Where this buyer came in this
morning. All right. So, if we get follow
through again now downside, it'll be
71s. If they keep bidding up here, they
can go to ibeh high. I'm out of it
again. So, I need to wait now.
603 QQQ key level uh on Gex just so you
know
850 key level NQ
on Gex second Cool wall
850 is the call wall right now. Over
that they can maybe lift to uh 25,000.
I wouldn't bet on it.
I'm going to move this now folks because
we put this red line in up here. Right.
Clean these charts up a bit.
Right back to the same level that we
talked about before. 25s and 30s.
Getting
stuck here again and just rotating a
little bit here. It's a little bit messy
here. I'm not going to lie. Back to
point of control again, the 800. So,
we're in like a 25 30 point rotation
here for a little bit while they build
out some liquidity, make their mind up
what it is they want to do. Do they want
to reclaim and squeeze or they going to
reject everything over 20s to 50s and
fold it back down into this range? If we
get come back into this range, we do the
same move that we did here. But maybe
there's an argument to to lift a bit and
trap. We'll see.
There's the eights.
They left against 25s.
We go back to 25s.
Buyers getting caught again in that last
candle on the 25s.
They keep stepping in there above 20s.
They're not finding acceptance above 20s
yet. I'd be very, very careful though.
All they need to do is one big candle
and it will wreck a lot of people.
Maybe they come for the 50s and that
imbalance 70s. ES trying to get up to
its IB high right now. So ES just did IB
high to VWAP back to IB high potentially
coming here on ES. Still 603 call on uh
Q.
Let's see. Let's see if we can get one
more decent trade. We got an hour left.
It' be nice for one more decent trade,
wouldn't it? be nice if we could just
get one more decent trade for the week.
What does IVB stand for? Initial
balance. So the purple line on your
screen is the initial balance high and
this is the initial balance low. It's
the high and low of the first hour of
trading. Uh there is a free video on my
YouTube on it. Just go on my YouTube and
type in in how to trade initial balance
or something. It will come up.
Okay, still doing this rotation. 25s to
800s.
back to 30s. They lift here. They're
going to try and go 50s and 70s.
So, we're in a rotation here. They're
trying to force a little squeeze out to
50s and 70s here. We're pretty thin
above this, honestly. All the way up to
905s. We get kind of thin.
There's the attempt to get back to 50s
again.
ES just hit IB high there, folks. So, we
just attempted to get 50s. ES hit IB
high. We're now trying to base over
value area high now. So, they're going
to try and force this up by the looks of
it.
Do they trap into 50s? And do we get
another short opportunity? Back to value
area high again. Can we get a short
opportunity here
again? I really don't know what they
want to do with this. I want to see this
dump. Honestly, we just tagged 50s. It's
just like I'd like one more trap, but we
just caught more buyers up there again.
Here it comes. Are they going to go 800s
now?
808 is where that buyer is. So, we got
buyers caught now. 825, 8:30, 808. Oh,
they're going to [\h__\h] do it without
me. Don't you dare. Don't you dare roll
this over now when I've been waiting for
you. Don't you dare. You didn't even
sweep up there, you dirty dog. NQ. You
dirty dog. I want it somewhere up here,
guys. I really want to see bulls be
trapped up here. So, what I'm looking
for is a bull trap up here. I want to
see buy delta heavy heavy heavy 50 to
here. And if they get trapped and we
move CBD down, then I will look for that
rotation for TP1. I don't One thing we
need to be careful of is value is moving
up. So, it's going to be a support
mechanism more and more and more. We
need to be careful of that. Very careful
of that.
you shorted this level five times.
That's what I mean. If you're a range
trader, if you're willing to scalp like
25 points, right? If you're willing to
like short 30, cover 800, short 25,
cover 800, etc., etc., you're going to
keep getting paid today. Uh I'm not a
range trader. I'm looking for
followthrough. Okay, come on. Come and
sweep the stops. We just caught buyers
again here into 840. This needs to move
higher and trap these buyers a little
bit higher for me to feel very, very
good about it. And this guy just got
caught again. 123 lot into 840 there.
Got caught again.
Why do I think I'm not going to get my
entry and we're going to see like a 200
point dump without me in it?
That's what ENQ's done to me all week.
Yeah. So, what to explain to you guys
what we're looking for, what I'm looking
for. You don't have to look the same as
me. Trade your own trade your own setup,
right? See all these buyers here? I just
want a little sweep, right? And I want
the buyers to get stuck. We do have an
imbalance up here. So, 50 is a big gamma
level, but somewhere in here, we could
we could lift right the way up here if
they want. somewhere in here. Let me
draw it for the team, please. Right. I
want to run all the short stops, right?
So, we get buy orders coming here. I
want buyers to chase the market. I want
them to get stuck anywhere in here and
then I want to look for them failed
followrough and use their pain to go
lower. That's what I'm looking for at
the moment. That might change if I just
think we're going to get be aggressively
buying and that doesn't turn up. That's
what I'm looking for at the moment. We
The worst thing about this is this
D-shaped profile we're building out.
It's the worst thing about this right
now.
Alex, if I open an account for Apex for
the monthly contest and then I win here
on your giveaway, would that be a
problem? Like not being able to get the
free one because you have one. No, no,
no. You can have up to 20 accounts. It's
not a problem. Okay, here we go. Come
on. So, there's a 50 tag. Come on. Get
through this level and trap some
players. Right. ES is above IB. So, we
do need to be careful. Like I said, if
they want to repric this whole thing,
big seller coming in here at 55s. That's
not what you want to see. That is not
what you want to see. Aggressive seller
here at 55s. That is not what you want
to see. It's the opposite of what I'd
want to see.
It's the opposite of what I would want
to see here. They're going to squeeze
above him. All right. So, IB is coming
up here. So, I don't like what I've just
seen here with this big seller.
So, we have to remember his level. 55 is
that guy. All right. How big was he? He
was big 258 lot just came in. So they're
going to squeeze to 70 now.
Bulls have actually got a shot here now
because that seller's caught, right?
It's because that seller's caught. ES is
going for high day by the looks of it.
So are they going to reverse this whole
thing? It's possible. Another big seller
coming in here at IB. 100 lot coming in
here at IB. And if they get over him,
they're going to look for a squeeze all
the way back up to 900. So they might
reverse this whole thing because sellers
have got too aggressive too early. So my
short thesis at the moment not giving me
an opportunity to entry because of what
I'm seeing on the tape. All right, this
is why I'm not going to just short a
level. So I now know a seller is caught
at 854 and another one at 868. All
right. So, we need to get under those
levels for them to be comfortable.
Still protecting these guys at the
moment.
So, maybe they're going to come for the
900s and the imbalances above now.
That's where that seller just came in.
That exact level 54s. This is where that
big seller came in. They need to get
under this for him to be comfortable. If
they hold this, he is caught.
So far, they're holding it.
What platform do I use for Dom and
footprints? Ninja. Yeah, Ninja and
Bookmat. I have it on Trading View as
well, but I'd watch it on Ninja and
Bookmat.
Looking for the squeeze back up. So,
that seller is absolutely caught there
into 54s. Right. So, they re they he
came in here, they retapped him. He's
stuck. If he remains stuck, especially
because he added at 69, then there is a
squeeze out to previous day point
control 900s. If they break through the
900s, all right, then again, it's the
same trade we were looking for earlier.
It's possible to get up to 25,000. So 25
uh 24 950 or 24 946 then 25,000. This
same thing we were looking for earlier.
They might do it now off a similar area,
which would be annoying.
We were we were positioned for this
move. So, they will be looking for this
red line here. And if they get through
it all the way up here, right 25,000.
I'm not going to play this long at this
point. I'm going to have to wait for
failures.
CVD diverging. Not for me. Not on a
fivem minute. Looks okay. Uh, have we
made a new high yet? No, it's it's in
line for me. Or at least on a five
minute. I don't watch it on a one
minute.
market trying to find a bit of a bid
here by the looks of it. Right, coming
back under IB. Remember that player got
stuck at 68 and the other player is at
54s. So 68 currently sort of holding on
by dear life.
bit different to what we've had this
week, folks. I know I'm having to call
levels out quite a lot, but it's we're
in a rotational market where we've been
sideways now for about 24 hours.
Basically, we've been sideways since
10:00 a.m. yesterday. We're in the same
level.
Okay, back down to where this player was
at 54s. Remember, remember 54s and 68 is
where the seller got stuck. 54s and 68.
So, we're under 68. We're coming.
Testing 54s. Still not under his level.
He's still uncomfortable. Now, we're
under his level. Okay. Now, now, now
Alex wants a short and it's just going
to break away from me. Is it? So, I'm
going to need a retest of like 54s or 68
to see uh follow through here. And we're
dancing to where those bulls came in at
29. They're going to make this very,
very hard. I'm going to show you how
hard this is on the tape. Right. This
level here is the big seller. Okay. the
big seller right here and here. Right,
we got above him, we came under him, we
came right down to the big buyers where
they bid off and value very high.
They're going to make this very, very,
very tricky today. Very tricky. It's
going to be C money, take money, and
you're going to have to be aggressive
with your stops. Not aggressive with
your size, aggressive with your stops if
you take it. I want to see this pump
back up to 50s and get stuck. 50s to 70s
and get stuck now. Otherwise, it's no
trade. Cannot join down here.
Come on. Don't Don't just break away
from me. Don't Don't
Right. They're absorbing 30 is where
those buyers were, where I just showed
you value area high. If we lose value
area high, maybe Vo is possible back
down to the 800s.
Please pop it first.
Why do I feel like it's not going to let
me get it
value area high here? Why I feel like
it's going to fail this straight down to
BPO.
Okay. What I'm looking for folks that
you understand is a little pop back in
here which I see them fail in. They're
going to need to fail in it. Might come
here and then it's going to be TP1, TP2,
TP3.
All right, here into 50s. Here we go.
Looking good. So, watching 54s here.
Might have just missed my entry while I
drew that out for you. For [\h__\h] sake.
Oh, I drew it out and missed it. Oh,
it's going to kill me. That's going to
[\h__\h] kill me.
Oh my god.
Well, you lot better have got it.
Tilt.
Tilt. This is tilt. This is tilt. This
is what tilt looks like
on the money. Right, folks. What did I
say? 54s. We just came to high 5325 and
failed.
Oh, I want to like bite my hands off.
I'm so annoyed. I don't think I can
trade the rest of the day, folks. That
that's me done. I will stay here and and
call everything for you. But I can now
feel the anger is now in me. So, I have
to just completely remove myself from
clicking buttons. All right? because
that for me if this now fails and we let
go of previous week point control this
would be a 100 pointer if we do it. So,
what did I say? TP1, TP2, somewhere in
here. TP2, TP3. If this collapses the
whole thing, TP4, this would be a giant
trade if it does it. Um, I can
not now chase or do anything. I'm just
going to woo woo woosa
woosa.
I know I was trying to help you. I know.
I know. This is This is the thing,
right? This is the hardest thing about
educating on
when uh you use orderflow
compared to like
compared to like I don't know uh like
traditional SNR which I do use
traditional SNR you know I love SNR
Malaysian SNR even like ICT stuff I
guess if like you were trading I don't
know inverse fair value gap there and
here or what whatever all right but I'm
trying to give you very specific levels
which I have to read on order flow,
which means if I'm if I'm trying to show
you and it does it and I miss it, you
know, on a move like that, I would have
been short in the 50s. By the time I'd
got back to my screen, we're 50 points
lower because the volatility is so high
today. Sorry, I moved my mic away.
That's how annoyed I am. Throwing my mic
around.
No, I'm not taking a re-entry up there.
I'm not taking re-entry up there. Even
if it comes up, not taking re-entry.
It's It's not even about the trade now.
It's about my emotional state. This is
about my emotional state now. So, it's
got nothing to do with the entry being
valid. Uh
cannot do it.
Cannot do it. They are now starting to
bid above those buyers as well, right?
Above these buyers, these buyers here.
These buyers just got caught. If you
protect 54s, then maybe. But, you know,
you've just come down to this big lot
down here and you're starting to reclaim
this. You want these guys to be out the
money. You want to get back inside value
because what you would like to do is a
rotation of value. So, you want to lose
these 30s and these 25s and you want to
come down underneath 96s and get down to
VW up and ideally down to 700s again.
That would be a really nice trade.
Otherwise, we're just going to keep
doing the dance. Big sellers just come
on the book here again. What size is
this guy? That's not a joke. 279 lot
just attacked the market at 40s here. Be
very careful.
He's very aggressive.
You hope it goes long now. I won't feel
as bad. No, I I will feel worse cuz I
want you guys to make money. I'm I'm not
selfish that way. I would love this
market. All right. At least you got your
TPS there. Uh I want it to fail under
here for you and under here for you. And
if it does that, you'll get this. But if
it doesn't do that, they're going to try
and repric up here again.
Like I said, see money, take money,
right? 50s fail. See money, take money.
There's 50 points. All right.
Do not like be forcing your way in. So,
back to this trap seller again at 54s.
Did they just tag him this time? They
just tagged him on the dot. On the dot
at 54. Look at that.
On the [\h__\h] dot. He's still stuck up
there.
Can you ex please explain why every time
you mention there is a big seller you
expect price to go higher from there
instead of in the same direction as the
big trade. Oh okay. Yeah it's not that I
expect price to go higher or lower. It
depends where price is. Okay. So for
example,
we have a big seller at 54s here, right?
And he came in here, right? So he needs
to stay comfortable, doesn't he? If he's
comfortable, price can go lower. But
what happens if we get above him? He's
uncomfortable, right? He's
uncomfortable. So he might start
stopping out some here. I would imagine
his stops here. So if he's uncomfortable
and we come up here and we have
thousands of lots being sold here, guess
what happens above here? [\h__\h] you candle
happens. That's what happens. So this is
why we don't risk above that. So there
you go. We just cleared that him out
probably. Uh the next level where we
have sellers is 68, which is where we
just tagged into, which is the IB,
right? So their stops are probably here
and here right now. They must defend it.
The buyers have started stepping in at
25 and 29. So, we haven't got much room,
right? So, it's like, think about this.
If there's a big buyer here, which there
is, right? If we come under that level,
what happens? Stops out. Sells. If we
retest it and he didn't stop out here,
what happens? Gets out, break even,
sells. Right? So, while we look for big
play, I'm not looking at this for small
players. I'm looking for the big
players. I'm looking to see what the
market makers, what the institutions are
doing, what the order flow is doing,
where are they trying to move this
market?
Do I use bookmap, heat map, tape only to
see the big sellers? Sometimes you show
something in bookmap when you're talking
about it. Yeah, I use bitmap which is
above me and I use uh like a footprint
chart with delta on Ninja Trader as
well. I use I use I use numerous tools
and I use the level two so I can see
them. Right? So even if you were just
using tape if your if the tape you have
has this volume profile delta you can
see right here look at this big seller
at 37s right 281 lot. So all the time
we're under him he's comfortable.
Where's the big buyer from before right?
Well there's a big buyer right here at
29. All right. And there's another big
buyer at 25. So if we go under that
those buyers start becoming
uncomfortable. Right? It's it's
psychology. Think about when you trade.
Think about when you trade.
If you and you guys are retail, so
you're not trading big size, right? Same
as me. But we're talking about like
hundreds and thousands of lots, right?
Hundreds and thousands of lots. We want
to get in the slipstream of that.
Why do I think he's a short seller?
Well, I know he's a seller.
It doesn't matter if he's a short
seller. or he's just selling his
position. It's the delta.
Okay, so we're now under those buyers
at uh 25 and 28. Like I said, this is
probably going to go for you now.
Especially if you get start to lose 95s,
right? If you start to lose 7 95s, so
you'd ideally you'd want 25s and 30s
protected here by sellers. You'd want
these buyers to become trapped and
become sellers. You don't really want a
lift lift of 38 and 50s again. So you
want sort of 30s to be protected here.
If they sell 30s, you want a close
underneath 96s. Underneath that, you're
looking for 72s. All right? So
underneath 96s, you're looking for 72s
as a cover. It's going to work out for
you. I'm telling you, it's just like I
can't. My psychology now I'm I'm spent.
Missing that move so quickly hurt. Even
though it offered me a re chance
mentally, I'm out of the pocket at the
moment. Here you go. So underneath this
level now this is Vpo and under here
you're looking for 770s same level as
earlier right and then under 770s you
can look for the edge of this. So it's
770s 730s 700 and then lower of day
honestly they do the full reversion.
So there you go folks. Hopefully this is
going to be a huge winner for you lot
now,
right? It's huge winner. 50's failed
and there's your IB trade. There's the
Tyson trade coming out into VWAP here.
Um but I think 770s is a massive level
and under that I would be watching for
here 730s and under that honestly you
can probably watch for this. All right
if you get start closing under 700s so
770s 730s 700 low of day.
Nice Tyson I knew I knew you'd be here
mate. Nice work mate. So we're coming
towards that 770s now. Remember that we
have a TP at 770s.
We have a TP at 770s. It's where they
have been bidding all day long. 770s.
I've been calling that level since the
open this morning.
Ale. Hey, Alex. Do you have any YouTube
videos for Ninja Footprint like how you
have for Trading View footprint? Uh, I
do not. I don't think. Uh, hang on.
Maybe I do actually. Yes, I have a small
one on it actually. But most of that is
in the um the course. But there is I
show you how to set it up, how to get it
for free. Let me find it for you.
Trading view.
Try and find a few mate. Give me a
second.
Sharable link.
This one might help.
All right, almost there, folks. So,
you're looking for uh 70s, remember?
770s or V1 anywhere around here.
Um, watch I would watch SPY 682. If it
loses 682, it probably goes back to 680.
So, they might pin it above 682 and you
can watch QQQ600s.
But again, for those who are wondering,
all right, you need to cover some into
770s. You need to cover cover some into
730s and then you can hold for this like
move all the way down here. Where was
that buyer stuck this morning? Let's try
and remind ourselves. Buyer stuck.
Sorry, seller stuck. He was stuck at
93s.
He can't have been stuck at 93. Hang on.
What's the low date? Where am I looking?
Where was that guy stuck this morning?
593.
93. Somewhere around there is where
we're trying to get. All right. So,
you're under 70s. So, that's your first
TP. So, your next one is the uh 30s and
and then 700s. 30s and 700s. So, I'll
just do little dots on the screen so you
can see them. So, you should TP some
here. 30s, 700s, and then here. This is
where we're trying to get to, right?
See money, take money. Don't be too
aggressive, right? Make sure you're
paying yourself.
Make sure you're paying yourself. You
guys getting this without me. It's
perfect. I don't mind.
Uh I use hotkeys. Yeah. But what what I
found um is I've had to take uh
affordable indicators off when I'm using
hotkeys. They get in the way of the
hotkeys.
So, if I'm not trading my accounts
linked, I'm happy to have affordable
indicators off. If I'm trading them
linked, I need it on. So,
no, I don't I don't really filter on on
bookmap. I like to see all the orders.
Um, but obviously I can see the the big
lots.
I know Bella, we're growing, Bella. It's
insane. It's insane. Everyone say hello
to Bella. Bella is the absolute queen
who gives you guys all the free Apex
accounts we do every day. Absolute
legend.
No. Quite right. Uh, one of you asked,
"Is there no way of knowing if it's a
short position or a long position being
squared off?" There's no way of knowing,
my friend.
No way of knowing. Okay, back into
previous week point of control. You
really I'm going to have to have a look
at this now. You really want this to
hold the 95s and 800s. You don't really
want them to reclaim this. All right?
You would like this to stay heavy.
Otherwise, there's a chance they revisit
24s and 25s and 30s again. You don't
really want that. So, if we can reject
800 here, for those of you who took the
short into 50s or 65s, you're good. If
you're willing to risk 25s, you can. I
don't like that risk at 25s. I think
it's very, very, very, very dangerous.
But
how are we doing on the likes here?
Thousand likes, 2,000 of you watching.
Shall we do some giveaways?
Great to see me respect my emotions. I
have to, man. I have to. I have to.
Like, there's no such thing as missing a
trade. Like, in my Obviously, there is,
right? Obviously, I missed it. I saw it.
I drew it out. By the time I got back to
screens, 50 point lower emotion spike.
Don't trade. It's just like, don't
trade. How have I learned that? Too many
years of doing it. Way too many years of
doing that. Getting absolutely cooked.
All right. So, they're coming back for
these 25s and 30s now. And you want to
be very careful. If they start getting
through these, they're going to revisit
50s and turn it on. And guess what? Spy
held the 82s. Remember I said watch for
Spy to hold 82s. If it holds 82s, there
is an argument for a squeeze today on
SPY back to 85 and 86es if it keeps
holding 82s.
All right, let's
do some giveaways.
Which one is Bella? Bella was in chat
earlier. She came in and said Bella Kim
4608. That's Bella.
A lot of people asking about whether a
seller is in pain or a takerit. Either
way, trades require buyers and sellers.
So, liquidity is liquidity. Correct.
Ransom. Exactly. Either way, we need
aggressive and passive participants at
the same time.
Otherwise, we don't do a deal. Giveaway.
Look at you guys. Giveaway. Giveaway.
Giveaway. Giveaway. Yeah, we're going to
do a giveaway. Don't worry. I'm going to
do a giveaway. Do I trade BT BTC? Uh
swing. Not trading it. All right. So,
look, squeeze is on now. So, reclaim.
So, all you got was uh the 770s.
Still not bad. What did you get out of
that? 80 plus points. Not bad. Not bad.
And we are now back in the range. So,
now they're going to have to try and
find a bid over 30s really or over those
25s again. If bulls find a bid, I will
not be taking this. But if bulls find a
bid here, they will try and clean out
all this liquidity here. We are 50s is a
massive massive wall on the options
chain. All right. So, if they can hold
over 50s, there is an argument for this
lift higher to clean this out. I won't,
like I said, I'm probably done for the
day. That really pissed me off that last
one. You've got it's not also one thing
I should say with trading. Maybe some of
you guys have experience in this. I call
it like tilt delta. All right. So,
yesterday Alex gets stopped out to the
tick. He gets like 150 points and he
misses the 400 point trade. And don't
think, oh, he wouldn't have got the 400
point. Oh, he would have. He would have
got the 400 point. He was ready for that
400 point trade all bloody week. Right?
I think the day before I got stopped out
to the tick or by three points. Today I
got stopped out by five points twice and
then I missed one. So the delta, right?
If we think about my journal will tell
you what is Alex's tilt, where does
Alex's tilt come from? His tilts come
from break even, break even, break even,
break even, break even, break even. Miss
a trade, miss a trade, break even, miss
a trade, and there it goes without me.
That has happened every bloody day this
week, right? So, I need to be very, very
careful with myself right now. Plus, off
the screens, I'm going through a lot,
right? So, I have to be kind to myself.
So, that's something for you guys to
note as well. You have what I call tilt
delta. It will build through a week or a
month, right? If you have, let's say you
have a flat day and a flat day and a
flat week and a flat week and man, you
are just very close to having a big blow
up if you keep doing that. And this
unless you got your emotions under
control because at some point you'll be
like, "This is [\h__\h] and you're going
to oversize or do something stupid." So,
it's what I call tilt delta.
Where do I place my stops? I place my
stops where the trade is no longer
valid. Normally, it's on a shelf, like
under a shelf. So, for example, if I was
going to buy here, all right, then I
would be trying to risk the other side
of this shelf where possible, right? But
like I said, they are trying to bid 25s
and 30s right now.
Why are they trying to bid 25s and 30s?
Because where they've been bidding all
day, right? 25s and 30s. They're trying
to bid 25s and 30s and take out these
sellers and lift it up here, right? And
we can see the bid at the low was
filling an old imbalance into VWAP. But
this was the level, right? 770s. We've
talked about it the whole time. 770s.
Reclaim Vo, reclaim the bid action at
25s, back to the 50s, right? So 50s to
25s can be a rotation while they build
and try and force a squeeze out higher
if they really want to. But 50s is a big
big big GEX level, right?
6K today. Nice work, mate. Nice work.
Call it a day. That's a great Friday.
Look, it failed 50. So, back to 25s. And
can they absorb this? If not, all the
way back down. It's just nasty, nasty,
nasty. Why don't I trade
I don't trade forex because I don't just
because I don't I don't feel I need to.
Does the course teach you how to use
Twin Peaks on Ninja? Uh, no. Not
specifically on that, but I mean we can
add that to it if you want. It's not a
problem. It just it teaches you how to
use It doesn't matter whether Okay, I'm
going to explain this. Twin Peaks is
just a third party app, right? I'm not
an affiliate with them or like I don't I
haven't made that thing or that app. All
it is is orderflow and delta. I show you
how to use it on numerous different
ways. It's up to you to decide what you
want. Twin pix is just one thing.
There's loads of platforms that do the
same thing, right? Bookmap does exactly
the same thing. So I teach you how to
use and see all that stuff, but it's up
to you how you want to which which third
party app you want to use or in-house
app. I know uh Ninja Trader are actually
working on stuff at the moment. Okay,
so Apex giveaway as we know FCT is
always the best code you can use for all
your prop firms other than take profit
trader. Use code flow zone and uh if you
type FCT in chat once now please do not
spam it. If you spam it, you will not be
entered. Okay? If you spam it, you will
not be entered. Type it once and we'll
give away a free Apex account.
Right? So they're trying to lift now and
force this squeeze because they just
held again. Look at how they ran. So if
even if I bid 25 and 30, they would have
run me out to this node. Look at this.
They're being dirty today. Here's the
node which someone just asked me about
to stop. If I bid here, I'd risk the
other side of the node. Well, they would
have just [\h__\h] taken me to go.
They're being horrible today. Horrible.
Horrible. Horrible.
We got what we came for though, right
folks? We got our money. So,
Oh, I'm tired, man.
Right. While you guys are entering,
I'm just going to
get some of you guys set up that were
saying you were waiting to get set up on
the free indicator. Get set up now for
you.
So, trying to force this squeeze back to
the IB again.
People
People can't even type in a basic bloody
code, like a basic form, and then
complain that they haven't got the
indicator. It's amazing to me.
Bombard me with emails and then I read
it read their form. I haven't even
filled it in.
Wild.
All right, give you guys 30 more
seconds.
Need an API to do all this. I have to do
everything manually.
Great name, whoever that is. Fish Taco.
Great name.
If you're watching, Evan Bean, great
name.
All right, that'll do for now. Pull the
winner for you guys.
your fish taco. Mango pickles. That's
awesome.
Oh, look at this. Regular winner.
A regular's just won. Uh, I can never
say your name properly. Som Nim. Somi.
Probably got that right.
Your accent is a Londoner, bro. Yeah,
I'm from London, mate.
[\h__\h] gazer from Londoner. Propagoner
who is not happy after yesterday's
result.
Are you here?
Hopefully I've said it right. I'm sorry
mate.
S O M N I O HM. You're here every day.
Are you here now when you've just won?
Proper lemon squeezer. Exactly, mate.
S
Samnomon.
Okay, sorry I got that so badly wrong.
All right, you have just won a free Apex
account. Congratulations. So, just email
me info@flowzonerader.com
and I'll sort you out with a free Apex
account, any size you want.
Gunners are not throwing it away. Calm,
calm down.
Calm down. It's a draw. Calm down
against a side placed seventh in the
league. Everyone calm down. We're not
throwing it away. Geez. Don't want any
of that. If I hear that in chat, we stop
the stream now and I won't do anymore
ever.
No negative talk about my team.
O Joey, cut it out.
Cut it out.
That's right, Mike. You [\h__\h] numpty.
I do not filter my bubbles. No, I do
not. Look at the cell off the 70s again.
IB. Jeez. Can these guys just make their
minds up?
Can they just make their minds up? All
right, back to the 50s again.
There is an argument if they hold 50s to
clear out above, but I like I said, I'm
done, man. I'm done. I've got to respect
my uh got to respect my my limits in my
head,
man. You guys are being mean about my
team here. It's not very nice, chat.
It's not very nice.
Nice. Paul, see that's that's the way.
Paul,
can you advise myself how to educate for
free as I have no budget to get the
course? There's loads on my website, on
my um YouTube.
Look, there's so much free stuff on my
YouTube, guys. Like I said, don't do the
course straight away. Like, make sure
you like how I teach. If you come to my
YouTube,
I've even put it in shelves for you guys
to make it nice and easy. All right,
there are shelves here, right? Move this
up. You come down, start here. Trading
strategy and education for beginners.
There is a ton in here that you can
learn. Then you can do volume and market
profile. There is a ton in here that you
can learn. These are not like small
lessons. Some of these are like 30 40
minutes. Some of these are hours long.
And then prop firm reviews. If you're
looking to use prop firms on like which
ones I advise. All right, that's it.
There's there's tons there and I will
keep producing more.
Do my best.
Love being at V Villa Park for the last
minute winner. Oh, that's amazing. What
a game that was. They've been decent as
well, Villa this year. I'm surprised.
I say nothing, Dean. Say nothing. All
right. They're trying to force this
squeeze up. They just held 50 like held
25s and 30s, right? So again, the big
buyers have been here, right? Failed
70s, held 25s and 30s. Can they hold
50s? I don't know. Can they get this rip
up here? I don't know. They don't know.
None of us know right now. These guys
can't make their mind up what they're
doing and trying to find acceptance to
increase value higher at the moment.
They're struggling. But they hel the
main thing held 82. It probably wants to
come up towards 86.
And uh yeah, we held the 50s.
There is an argument for it to do this
move here, folks, that we were looking
for this morning. We positioned for that
move this morning and we positioned for
the fade here. Did this without me
positioned for Were you guys positioned
for the fade here? Did I catch a bit
here? I can't even remember now. Can't
even remember. I don't think so.
Um,
sorting some of these out quickly.
What uh video would help you guys if I
made another free video over the weekend
or over next week? Is there a free video
like a video educational video that
would help you guys right now? You let
me know.
there's something that you're looking to
learn
that won't be too long. I haven't I
can't I can't do it like a huge course
or something, but
all those who just applied for the
indicator. It's coming. It's coming.
It's coming. Give me a chance.
If you've applied and you didn't put
your Trading View username in, I can't
do anything. Those of you who have done
that, I I literally can't do anything.
If you're not going to put your username
in, you're going to put something stupid
in there because you don't want to give
me your username or email, then not a
lot I can do with it, folks.
Right, there we go. Done.
trade recap vids. I kind of do those in
shorts. I that would take so long for me
to do because I have to go through the
stream each day. It would take me so
long. I have paid someone to to do clips
at the moment, but he's probably not
going to keep him if I'm honest. Sorry
if you're watching, mate, but uh you're
not doing what I want. Sounds harsh,
doesn't it?
Reservoir thug.
Why would you look for shorts on an
index that goes up more than down? The
odds are against you from the start,
just by dips. Hold until you're green.
Is this a swing channel? Are you talking
about swings?
So, how did that work for you um this
week, my friend?
I'm just curious
if all you did was buy
right the last few weeks. I'm interested
how that worked for you. Did you buy
here at the top of volume or here or
here when we left volume or here or here
or here or here or here? How did that
work for you?
Right? We're day traders here, right?
This is not swing. If I'm swing trading,
do I want to be biased for upside moves
in an index? Absolutely. I want to buy
discount for upside moves. But if I'm
day trading, why the hell would I do
that if the order flow is heavy?
No.
That's why we play what's in front of
us.
Will I try the new Fiverr's futures
program? Don't even know what that is.
What is it?
Order book and bookmap. Yeah, a few of
you have asked for that. That is
something I do want to do.
Gamer OP, thank you very much. I will be
thankful thankful to you for explaining
the indicators you are using right now.
Right now, here we go. Flowzone Pro,
right? All of this is my custom
indicator. It's on my website. A version
of it comes for free with the beginner
to advance course. So if you do the
beginner to advanced course, 20our
course, you get a version of this and
you get uh the Discord access for life.
It's $699 onetime fee. All right. So
that's what I'm using. On the right hand
side, all you're seeing here is anchored
volume profile. It is a tool, not an
indicator before anyone else because
it's right here. Projection anchored
volume profile. If you want the
settings, even though they're in chat, I
will tell you. I have it to tick per
row. I have it set to two, and I have it
pinned to the right with a width of 20.
I anchor it to the 930 open.
Um, other than that, all these
horizontal lines, these previous day
value areas, they're just measured out
from the previous day using this using
this here.
That is everything you need. Above me is
bookmap if you're interested.
Uh, let me Have you filled in the form,
Evan? If not, let me just add you now.
Uh, Ev,
there you go. I've just added you.
Okay, so EMA trend friend pro and just
added you there.
bought QQQ calls yesterday and closed up
already. Yeah. Nice. Very nice.
How do I join the course? It's pinned to
the top of the chat. flowzoneer.com.
Everything's there.
If you bought the dip yesterday without
stop, you would have lost all your
profit. Yeah, exactly. Let me
Why look for shorts on a green day
trading against the trend?
Do you think this is trending market?
Do you think this is a trending market?
Honestly,
honestly, you think this is a bullish
trending market?
We're pinned. We're in a range. There's
your range right here. This is the
current developing profile week. This is
our range. This is our range on the day.
That's why you play the edges, you play
the dips up, you play the edges down.
You play the dips up, you play the edges
down. If we break out and hold, you can
look for a move into here, which we've
been talking about the whole time. If
you break out and fail, you will sell
the edge back down because we're in a
rotation. We're not in a trending
market.
That's why it's dictated by this and
this. We are pinned in. So, we play
edges down. What have you seen at the
highs of day so far today? Every time
we've moved up here,
we've aggressively sold down. Why?
Because it's an edge. This right here is
value on the low uh value area low on
the week. We cannot find acceptance in
it. We trade down. What have you seen
the other side as we come into previous
week value area low? We've traded up.
All right. This is where you're pinned
in right now. If they're lucky, remember
we were looking for this move earlier
from a good trap. If they're lucky, they
get up into here. But I would say
anywhere in here will be a failure.
And that's why
you're just failing the same level
again. Right? This is fair value from
yesterday. You're failing the same level
again.
[\h__\h] me. I feel like I bang my head on a
brick wall sometimes explaining, but I
do my best.
This market is as trendy as my outfit.
That is a wicked comment. I love that.
According
to statistics by Edgeville, the initial
balance candle closes 7 green 76% of the
time the session sees continuation and
closes green data collected from the
past. What do you mean the initial
balance candle closes green?
You mean that that when we when we
complete an IB so the first hour you're
saying 76 time 76
can't talk. Are you saying that 76% of
the time in the stock market over the
last six months the first hour is green?
That's all I can see from that stat
you're giving.
Or are you saying if the IB is green
706% of the time we see continuation? Is
that what you're saying for the rest of
the day? So you does that mean you
what's that based on? Does that mean we
close green outside the IB?
I don't think we have a bullish session
of New York though. Like I mean if you
judge bullish by like okay we're above
this but like
I don't know man.
I like I guess you can argue look we're
we're pinning high but like what happens
if you do that and we close down here
can't see orderflow with all these lines
going on. Uh there's no orderflow on
here.
It's a lot going on. Yeah, unfortunately
there's an awful lot going on at the
moment, but it's because we've been
pinned in. So, everything's stacked. It
doesn't normally look like this, but you
got to remember
previous day low, previous day value
area low, New York open, ALOS, both
VWAPs, previous day close, previous day
point of control, current day point of
control, Asia IB, previous day point of
control. Let's just like everything's so
stacked, right? Everything's so stacked.
It's not my fault. Like, normally it
doesn't look like this, but right now it
does look like this.
70% of the market candles in the past 10
years is green, but what they don't tell
you is it only takes three red candles
to take out the 50 green. Well, that
spot on red candles. Thank you, mate.
Thank you, mate. Nice to see you here.
All right. Spot on. Right. We We walk up
as much as you want. Look at all these.
All of this walk up taken out in one
day. All right. All of this walk up
taken out very, very quickly. All right.
We talked about this. We've got three
months worth of trap liquidity here.
Where was the gap fill? It was up here.
Anyone who's traded me, where was the
failed breakout? It was up here. All
right. Where was the edge? It was here.
All right. This is the volume which is
currently trapped. We wash away from it.
We retest it this week. We stay heavy.
We wash back down. If we find
continuation, we will undercut this. If
we undercut this and lose the 200 day,
well, you can't even see it on this
contract, but we will trade under this
contract into new levels. All right,
24,000 very, very, very, very, very
possible because we have trapped volume
up here. If we reclaim this, we go back
into range. All right, for months and
months and months. If we get above that
range, we will see expansion. Right now
we have 3 months worth of volume trapped
right here. Which is why this move here
1, two, three, was so aggressive. It's
why this move yesterday was so
aggressive because we are retesting the
same level at which every participant
since October has been trapped. All
right, think about if you bought any
time after October 23rd, other than this
guy here, but most of this volume is
here. We talk about this at the
beginning of each day, folks. Red
candle's got an absolute valid point
here. We go to the daily.
All right. Where is all the volume
trapped? All right. The majority of the
volume since the high is here, right?
The profile for the last 12 months is
here. We are starting to lose the bid at
the profile for the last 12 months. If
we sell underneath this in the 200 day,
the next real notable node is really
here. 24,000 right this is possible if
we do this move I would imagine the QQQ
will play catch up to its 200 day right
the cash market there we go we will
probably hit that 200 day on the QQQ
let's get it on not on the futures let's
see what it normally looks like which
will be 580s right 580s QQQ is probably
what this wants to do 5day undercut see
if it finds a bid stay heavy Watch out
below.
Our job as day traders is just to trade
what's in front of us. And again, where
have we pinned off this morning?
Ballinger band cannot find acceptance
under it. We need to build liquidity out
now
for next week.
I don't use four candles. No.
Yeah. Stairs up, elevator down.
What ticker is this? NQ.
According to you, how much money should
I risk on a 50k eval? Uh how much money?
What per trade?
If what what's your um
what's your draw down on it?
Maybe risk 10% of your draw. Maybe 5% of
your draw. $250. If you got 2,500 draw
down, maybe if it's an email 10%, maybe
5% $125.
All right, we're going to give away a
course before we leave here.
Candle, I love that, Nick. Candlestick
patterns are astrology but for men.
Uh why is NQ delayed on Trading View?
Probably because you don't have any CME
data. You need data.
If you have data, it won't be uh it
won't be delayed. All right. Wait, wait,
wait, guys. I haven't set it up yet.
Please wait. Please wait. Please wait.
Please wait because you guys won't be
entered. Please wait.
per trade. Yeah, per trade. And limit
yourself to like three trades a day.
When do I wake up? I'm normally up about
5:00 a.m.
What's my opinion on EMA cloud stats? I
think they're actually really good, but
they work better in trending markets.
ignore like
I think I did a lesson on like
understanding market conditions before
you come to the market. If you're a
ranging market, you probably want to
ignore your EMAs. If you're in a
trending expanding market, pay close
attention to the EMAs. Okay. Um Oh, I
forgot my coffee. I'll have it when I'm
done with streaming. All right. Here we
go. Type course once in chat. It is a
beginner entry course. It's only two
hours long. It's only worth a hundred
bucks. But if you've never traded
before, you know nothing, it's a good
place to start.
So, here we go. We're going to lift now.
They're finally They've taken all day to
faf around. They're finally bidding over
the 850s. You're going to see these 950s
like we talked about. Big level here at
950. I'd be watching SPY into 686 here.
And if we lift aggressively here, you
are looking for 25,025.
Yeah, exactly. If you spam chat, you're
automatically disqualified. You just get
pulled out. So, please don't spam chat.
Okay.
Spy trying to get to that 686.
VIX coming down into that key pivot as
well. The high from Monday the 9th of
Feb. VIX coming right down into it. I
think once we clear some of this out,
there's probably a bit of a squeeze and
then a failure. We're very, very, very
thin as we get above 25,50. There's
probably a failure up here somewhere.
Okay, pulling this winner. Five, four,
three, two, and one.
Opin Christian, I think that is Opin
Christian.
Opin Christian. Hopefully I said it
right. Are you here?
Let me know you're here in chat.
Yes. Nice. Okay. Same thing for you.
Please email me info@flowzonetrader.com.
Send me a screenshot of you logged into
your YouTube so I know it's you and I'll
sort you out with a free course.
Do we think we go to 25,000 today? Uh
it's possible. Um yes, it's very very
possible. We can set a trap anywhere in
here, folks. Right. So this will be a
clear out of highs anywhere in here. If
you look at an hourly, if you look at
the volume,
I'd be very conscious about a trap being
set anywhere in here. Right? If we think
about the volume we just talked about,
if we thought think about how thin we
are, if we think about taking these
stops out, anywhere in here can be a
trap. If they set a giant squeeze, I
mean, we can't rule this out. I find it
somewhat unlikely. I think somewhere up
here, you will see buyers get caught.
That's what I would say.
Oh my gosh. It would be really nice if
they just came and clear out the levels.
Maybe we get a trade this afternoon.
Wouldn't that be lovely if they can come
and clear out some of these?
Any questions, folks, before I get off?
Of course, make sure you've uh signed up
for the newsletter. All the links are
down below. Newsletter is completely
free. Will be in your inbox tomorrow
morning.
What do I think BTC is going to do next
week? Let's have a look.
I think it's done 50% of the potential
move so far.
this right at the 50% where it's finding
a bid, right? So, let's just have a look
at some volume here.
Might be too far.
All right,
look at that. It came right into this
node.
Right into this node.
This is key.
Right. You lose that, you're going to
come down to equilibrium of the whole of
the bull run from last year.
Well, last year from yeah, 2024, two
years ago, right? So, right here,
if you lose this low that you put in,
right? Then there is a very, very good
chance that you come down into here. Now
anywhere from here possibly all the way
down to 30,000 like we've talked about
is where I think the best buying
opportunity is. Can they hold it here?
They can. But you know this is only two
legs. There is an undercut. They would
have to reclaim this undercut for any
bullish momentum to come back in this
stock. Has selling slowed down?
Absolutely. But they will probably be
waiting for a retest of somewhere up
here 75s. And if they sell 75s and they
get a crack under 60,000 I'd be looking
for this move here.
Right. And just remember we can do 70 to
80% pullbacks. We can if we do this move
here it'll be almost 70%. So ideally
accumulation ideally would happen around
here at 40,000 and maybe even down into
30,000. It's possible that they hold the
level we're at now. But historic
historically based on historically what
we do when we leave bull cycles, we have
the chance to come down into these
levels. It will be very upsetting for
you guys who are very bullish on it. But
uh I'm not it's not that I want it to do
these things. It's that's that is what
it does. But if we look also look
historically 50% retracement out of the
bull cycle.
Almost 50% retracement out the bull
cycle. So maybe we have done a 50%
retracement out of this bull cycle.
There's your thousand plus day bull
cycle. Maybe. But this bare cycle will
not be over. Not by a long shot.
It's got a long way to go and we've got
a lot of volatility uh in all markets
for the remainder of this year midterm
year.
Um can I send you the invites to
indicator when I get off stream I can do
stuff. I'm only a oneman band folks.
Session volume and anchor. Well session
you can choose where your session
starts. anchors. You pin it to the
anchor session volume on uh Trading
View. I can't get to pin to the right.
Anchor volume. I can pin to the right of
the screen. That's why I've been doing
it.
No, I cannot stay on for another hour.
I'm sorry. Do you think the 15, 20, 30
SMA is more profitable than using an EMA
cloud strategy like Okamoku or more
random cloud strategies? Um, I don't
know what time frame you're looking at
um to do that.
If you are using SMAs, I would start
with like a like have a low SMA, a mid,
and a high rather than a big cluster
together. Um, so you could have like a
13 or a 21 and you could have a 50 and a
200, for example. I'd do something like
that.
2026, the year of the bear, maybe. I'll
tell you who won't be very happy with
that, Donald. Cuz that will all [\h__\h]
destroy him, won't it? Can you imagine
if the market tanked while he was in
that the ego would have nowhere to go?
I want it to tank so I can buy cheap.
Where do you sign up for the newsletter?
It's pinned to the top of the chat.
Everything's pinned or or you can have a
look in the description. How do you get
EMA Trend Friend Pro? You just apply for
it for free. Watch the video on it.
Apply for it.
Can I post link tree for these people?
It's pinned to the top of chat, folks.
It's literally pinned. That message at
the top of chat is pinned.
Do you get access to Ninja Trader when
you start trading Apex? Yes, you do.
Even if you don't have Ninja Trader,
yes, you do. It's completely free. Same
with the order flow on Ninja Trader.
Was your form correct? Uh, I don't know.
What was your name on the form?
What? What's your name, my friend? I've
only got your username here. Don't drink
and root. I don't know. Fred Jaloop.
Outer heaven. Is that you? I think I
replied to you already.
I think I just replied to you recently.
Let me check if you're added.
Yeah, you're already added. I emailed
you back already. Am
I here Monday? Uh, I will make a
decision on Monday. I'll watch the open
on Sunday and we'll make a decision.
Probably not, but we'll see.
Yeah, black label right at the top here.
Let me post it again for you guys. It's
also in the description down below.
Everything is here, guys. Everything you
need is right here. Okay. Everything you
need is right here.
Yeah, I emailed him during the live
stream. Yeah, you just saw me add a load
of people to it. I did it like 5 10
minutes ago.
I think we're we're gr gearing up for
grinding up most of the day. We're not
below. That's about right. Do you mean
grinding up? Is that what you're talking
about?
I I just think
grinding up. I don't know, mate. This is
absolutely key here,
right? They can trap in here.
Depends how they want to close the week.
Do they cut Do they cover their puts,
right? and do we squeeze out inside to
close the week or are they just hoping
bulls get in and are they going to close
this week very very very heavy?
Both are possible right now but this is
a big big level. Look at compression
multiple drives down fail break back to
the upside but we know this is not a
level you want to be long.
Very very dangerous especially on a
Friday.
This is a nice buy now. I don't think
so, mate. I really don't think so.
Yeah, exactly. Uh 65% chance of a bare
market this year. Market average loss of
20%. Exactly.
No worries, guys.
All right, folks. I will be back maybe
Monday, if not um Tuesday for sure, and
we'll go again. All right, we'll go
again. Hopefully, you had a good week.
We had a monstrous week here yet again.
Another week where we absolutely crushed
it. Don't forget, hit that like and
subscribe button, send the video, send
this channel to your friends. Let's keep
growing this community and we'll start
doing more and more giveaways hopefully.
Um, peace and love everyone. Use hard
stops. Be patient. It's Friday. Don't go
forcing yourself into the market, giving
back your gains on a Friday. See you
guys Monday maybe, but definitely
Tuesday. Peace and love.