Morning
team.
Morning everyone. Sorry, running
slightly behind here. Let's get all of
this up. All right, hopefully some of
you have caught some nice moves
overnight. If you were prepared for
GlobeEx, it actually offered some nice
liquidity grabs as you can see on the
daily. Everything we talked about last
week, right, we're trading from one side
of the bowl to the other side of the
bowl. No acceptance above, no acceptance
below. No surprise there either. Okay,
these are our two standard deviations.
All right, top Ballinger band on the
daily, two standard deviations. We came
up here, what was this? Wednesday,
Thursday last week, couldn't close
outside. Failed back to the mean. Failed
the mean overnight and all the way back
down to the lower bottom and Ballinger
bottom ballinger band. Right. Everything
we talk about all the time. How many
times do we go over this? Many, many
times. basically every time I open the
chart. All right, so the rotation has
completed. We have found a bid of this
and we have an undercut. All right, the
key is here, this level here because
this created this sort of swing into
this. If we start getting stuck under
here this week, right? If we start
building liquidity down here around the
sort of 300s down to the 25,000s, 300
point range here. If we build liquidity
down here, all right, later in the week
and snap, then I would assume we are
then going to drive lower. We're not
seeing that yet. It might well build
out, folks. Right, it's a Monday morning
and we're not open yet. So, let's just
see how we go. We've got to be somewhat
careful of these key levels. You can see
we're going straight back into here
again with no change. And why is it lost
my volume? There we go. So big shelf
here uh off the last 12 months comes
into 671 and then over that into 865. So
6 670 is pretty big level. 670 is a
pretty big level. All right, moving down
into the hourlys.
Make sure you guys can see this. I'm
just going to make this one a little bit
bigger so you can see it. All right. So,
previous week
profile right here. What do we just say?
670s is a pretty big level that will
kind of line up with this old point of
control. So, we know that this level in
here 670s into 700 is huge. If we're
going to reclaim previous week's value,
we're driving up into it already. All
right. There's previous week's value,
previous day above here. We can get rid
of that in a moment once we go over it.
So, the big test now is do we find
acceptance? All right. Do we find
acceptance back above these 600s? Right.
Is this a look below into this gray box
that finds a bid and do we find
acceptance back above here? If we find
acceptance back above the 600s, all
right, then we are going to see a
rotation. This would be a failed
breakdown underneath previous week's
value, a hold of the week before and
then we would expect a rotation up to
700s. And if it gets through that, like
we said, that's a massive shelf, then
maybe up to 800s. The other option is of
course they reject this that they say,
"Hey, no, we're not going back inside
last week's value. That was actually too
expensive. We don't think there's any
fair value up there and we're going to
drive down." Obviously, these are naked
points of control. All right, previous
day, previous week. We haven't tested
that yet. We do expect that to get
tested within the first two days. So
maybe we see something like this and
then this and then it has to make its
mind up which way it's going. Very
possible. So this is what I'm looking
for this morning. I want to see how we
react here into the edge of previous day
and previous week. If we reclaim it,
then I'm waiting to see how we act here
into 700s and 800s. They've made it
quite easy. They've made it pretty easy.
700 and 800 850. They've made it the
whole numbers. So, o over six, maybe
seven over 7 850. Uh if we reject seven,
back to six. And if we reject six, then
back into these lows. All right. So,
they're making it somewhat easy for us.
If we move up to what we did in GlobeEx,
going to zoom in in here, make sure you
can see it. Oh, there we go. Right,
here's previous days or Friday. We can
call this Friday. Friday's value. You
can see that we rotated all through
Friday. All right, rejecting the 20-day
and we started to get a gap overnight.
So, this was the Sunday gap. They drove
up, they filled the gap, and as soon as
they filled it, became efficient, we
rejected it. Big sell off in GlobeEx,
new low, bid back up. This is the swing
point. All right. So, we're watching
this swing point right here into what is
this? 620s or whatever it is. 640s
somewhere around that. Lines up pretty
well with these value areas. That's what
I'm watching this morning.
All right, move it up into the lower
time frame just quickly so you can see
the previous day. We can Why is this
red? Let's get rid of you. You should
not be red. We're going to flip you. All
right. This is an area here that we're
watching. This kind of area here to see
if and how we act. This can be red.
There we go.
Right. So, we're watching how we react
here. Point of control and then this
block right the way up here, which was
volume. Right. So, balance between this
over this, maybe a drive up, fail
breakout back down into this, and maybe
a snap back down into this area here.
Let's have a look at some of the broader
markets. Quick look at ES for you.
Should look fairly similar.
Yes, very, very similar. snapped the
previous day low, expanded into what is
this? The old weekly. All right. Found a
bid underneath, failed breakout,
reclaimed that level, that old weekly
and then has driven straight the way
back up into developing point of control
um from the last month or so. All right,
so from the last month or so. So very
very similar gap fill would be up here
if it's going to fill that gap. We can
talk about that as well by the way in
the cues. If we are going to fill that
gap, we got to come right the way back
up to 673 so that you're all aware. Uh
QQQ
uh same kind of story. All right,
remember we didn't get all the overnight
action. So we got a big old gap down
pre-market failed to break lower and
we're driving back up. Previous day low
here on the QQQ. We can watch that if we
get inside it. Gap fill if we reject
previous day low back down here. ETFs
are going to make it a bit easier today,
I would say. So we can watch this level,
but we can set price alerts in for gap
fill. Add alert here. We call that gap
fill. No, we won't. We call that PDL tap
and then gap fill up here on QQQ.
My bad. Almost got that wrong on a
Monday morning.
Gap fill QQQ. And you can do the same
thing for the uh spiders. Wondering why
we do that. It's just so that we
understand the cash gaps on the ETFs. So
spiders already through previous day
low. The only thing left for them is a
gap fill which is uh up here. Right. So
it's almost there on the spy. Dixie has
found a bid. All right, Dixie's found a
bid. So, we'll have to see how how this
sort of uh yen Dixie and uh bonds
situation plays out. But you can see
that old inverse head and shoulder. All
right. And it's probably going to come
want to come up here. Pretty good for
the market if we do that. It's pretty
good. VIX still pretty much in this old
channel, right? Still pretty much in
this old channel. No change. Still has
increased volatility if it wants to go.
Let's have a quick look at the mag.
We've got to get move on. Right, Apple
in its range. That is absolutely
disgusting. But it is is holding that
key level of the 50s. Now just in a
range with a failed breakout here that
was on the earnings. All right. Uh
Amazon, right, has caught a bid down
here. This is blue box we talked about
coming back into. It's caught a bid so
far. Does it close his gap? Does it find
acceptance? Remember, it's a Monday
morning. Take it nice and easy. We're
going to go over the news in a minute.
Google gapping down very, very slightly.
It's got a gap fill above. It all
depends if they sell that gap fill. This
is seems to be the story of the tape
right now. Meta, same thing. Great
earnings shove up, right? Is this
bullish to come back up into here.
Remember, I'm long meta right now. This
is where I'm looking to get my next
partial out into 760 if it will let me.
If the market wants to play that and
Microsoft, all right, that looks
dreadful. Big sell off, right? It won't
get going until it gets a break over 39
and you might as well call it 440 break
on Microsoft probably opens the door for
a bit of a reclaim up into these. Until
that point, it looks pretty bleak. And
Nvidia, that's a gap down on Nvidia back
into the range. Same thing. All right,
failed breakouts. Bottom side of the
range down here, rotation in here. Same
story. And Tesla,
that has got to be the ugliest looking
chart out of everything for a while. All
right, unless you're a range trader,
you're probably having a lot of fun. If
you're swinging range trader, that looks
a lot of fun. But for everyone else,
that that looks like a bit of a
nightmare. Uh let's have a look at some
broader sectors.
Doesn't look too good on Netflix. All
right, possible continuation unless they
fail to break lower and then we'll get
that rip up. I have still got a small
starter on there. Let's have a look at
the chips. AMD trying to find a bid here
this morning and close its gap. And
what else we got?
AVGO. The chips look slightly weak.
Okay,
let's get ourselves all set up here.
Let's get a developing profile on.
You can get out of there, mates.
So, I'm going to set my developing
weekly profile now
down here.
and we can see what we get. All right,
so that's from the Sunday Open.
Morning everyone. Do me a favor, smash
that like button nice and early and uh
we can go from there and do some
giveaways. I'm going to have to get some
more giveaways set up. Uh we will
announce I will announce those guys who
did the competition on YouTube. I will
announce the uh funded next winner today
as well. And uh and what else was there?
And those in Discord, that free giveaway
of the volume profile and orderflow
course, we'll announce that after stream
as well. So, we'll get everything done
after stream.
And let's have a look at the news today.
Make sure I'm up to date with this.
Where we at? 4 minutes left. What have
we got today? 9:45 p.m. 10:00 ISM. All
right. So, some news coming there. the
big ones that we're looking at job
openings tomorrow, but probably really
Thursday, Friday this week. All right,
initial jobless claims and uh employment
report and then also we have uh Max 7
earnings again this week. All right, so
me just remind myself what days those
are. Right, we'll be looking at well I
will pay attention Palanteer tonight,
AMD tomorrow, but the big ones Google uh
on Wednesday and Amazon on Friday. Those
are the big ones. Thursday, Friday,
those are the big ones. But worth paying
attention to AMD if that has blowout
earnings. It might help chips find a bit
of a bid early in the week. All right,
no worries. Thanks everyone. Alex, do
you trade a bounce? Do you get on on a
shoulder? Do you How do you trade a
bounce? A bounce like a continuation or
you're just looking for a fib pullback
and into a key level, right? So, if you
were playing this bounce here this
morning, there's your break. There's the
hold of structure. Pull back. This is
pulling back. Same level. This is
pulling back. Failed to break lower.
Same level. Now, you wouldn't want to
play a bounce. You're probably going to
look to sell into here.
All right, let's have a quick look at
liquidity on the book as well.
Got any big players in this morning?
Anywhere dancing around? Yes. Okay.
600 625 which will be into our sort of
key levels. Okay, nice. Let's see if we
can get a morning drive and see if they
fail that drive and we can sell into it
if they're going to do that. We want to
be very careful if we complete the gap
fill and start to base above. So,
patience this morning.
Curious if I have a bias going into the
day. Um I don't want to be too biased,
but I you know there's potential that
they sell this early in the morning into
600s maybe the point of control.
Um but if we just look at the hourlys,
right, we think about where we are. It's
completed most of the move, hasn't it?
It's come and done this move here.
Here's last week. All right, we want to
see are they going to sell this or
they're going to sell this for this move
down. Then we have to take a partial
into this because we don't know if it
cracks. It might just build out
liquidity down here like we talked about
at the beginning. So, I would want to
see if we sell this or sell this early
on in the day. That's what I'm going to
be looking for. Do they sell this down?
Do they sell this down? If the answer is
no, right? If we're building out
liquidity here, then I'm going to expect
this drive up here. So, I want to see
how we build out early in the morning.
Okay. But this drive that we've done uh
since well, what time is this? Since
this low we've put in since 2:00 a.m.,
it's pretty good, right? It's uh well
approaching 350 plus points drive out.
So, waiting to see if there's a short
opportunity. Um, probably at the open.
That's probably the best way I can put
it. Hope that makes sense.
Right. Bell coming here in just over 30
seconds, folks.
Right. So, I'll be looking to see if the
market very clearly if we're going to
fail here or here. Gap fill is here. So,
are we going to do one of these moves?
If the answer is no and we do this,
we're going to build liquidity to go
higher. If we build liquidity lower,
then I'm thinking about that trade
underneath as well.
That's what I'm looking at. Right. That
is what I'm looking at.
Can do that. I want this one gone.
Right. Here we go, folks. 10 seconds.
Good luck, everyone.
Don't do anything stupid. Monday
morning. Don't force your way into
anything. This wants to lift up to 700
first. It will. Right. Here's the
morning drive.
Up we come into the value areas into
these 600s. Remember it can lift all the
way up to 680 even sevens if it wants to
go and then we'll see what we do once we
get here. But big big squeeze out this
morning.
And if they don't find acceptance
through here then I will be interested
in the short. Right. So if they don't
find acceptance through here watching
this there's some sellers up here into
605s. Wouldn't mind it a bit higher at
the moment. See how far they can squeeze
it. And that 700's going to be a big
level. Go. They're going for Gapville at
the moment, folks. They're going for
Gapville. Big buyer up here. Probably
going to get himself caught. 91 lot.
Okay. So, we see if we come back under
600 or if they hold the bid.
So, GlobeEx sitting at 45 is where we
are now. There or thereabouts. 35 sorry.
And then gap up here into 70s. Let's see
if they hold 600 or if they fail this on
the push. right in this now. Taking
partial straight away in case they find
a bid. Locking some in. Nice move to
start the date into that current point
of control. So, as soon as they failed
six, just took it straight back down
into this area. The reason I'm being
very quick there on the opening drive is
cuz they can now rebid this red zone.
All right. So, if we're going to get
continuation, it's going to be under
here. All right. And if they're going to
hold this, it's going to flip this whole
block for this move here. So short for
the 600 break straight down into this
taking a partial. Wait and see now if we
get acceptance lower. The answer is no.
So out and cover. And now we just wait
for the next trade setup. Probably the
very very similar setup
in the morning. Very very quick.
Let's see. Let's see. Let's see. Let's
see.
Watch your ATR here. Well over 50
points. They look like they're going for
gap fill here.
There's the GlobeEx. Let's see if they
get up into gap fill. And then remember
these are naked. Previous day point of
control, previous week point of control.
Those are both naked. 700 is going to be
a massive level. Here they go for gap
fill then. So the continuation long was
the play there off this red block which
is now blue. So, we now know that this
is a support structure. All right. So,
they're going to try and get up into gap
fill. This is gap fill. Now, let's make
sure the Q's are closing as well. Yeah,
Q's closing the gap. Spider's got a
little bit longer to go. I want to see
now if they react here or not. And if
no, then they're going to base out and
they look for a bigger squeeze.
So, gap almost filled that. Pretty much
filled. Missed it by what? A tick. A
bloody tick. It mixed it by a bloody
tick.
Let's see if they've got a bit more
juice for one more shove up. I'll give
you a little read out of the market.
Tesla 3.29% down. Nvidia 1.96% down.
Microsoft 0.62% down. Meta 0.32% down.
Google over 4% down. Amazon half% up.
And Apple 1 and a half% up. They look
like they just want to fill this gap and
then maybe flush it back down. But we'll
see. If they get through the gap fill,
then they can look for the 700s.
700s for me is going to be a big level
up into this. This is going to be a big
big big level up here
on Ninja. By the way, I have my previous
day value area low up there as well. So,
I should probably do this because
there's a divergence between these. I do
this and I call it NT
Ninja Trader previous day value low.
Right. So, let's watch again. If we get
weak under all of this, there's a new
short opportunity.
Watching this very very carefully to see
if they flush under here where this big
buyer came in last time. No, still
bidding here right now.
They're still bidding here. We're
extended. Would be much better if they
filled that gap and did 700 and then
failed to be quite honest at this point
because they can rebid this. I don't
want to be short versus this squeeze.
want to see them come up here, fill this
gap. Ideally, ES fills the gap as well,
and then we can sell it. Otherwise,
we're going to have to sell down here,
which is fine, but it's not ideal. I'd
like to get a premium price as close to
in here as possible.
Let's put some volume on for the session
as well before we forget. No, that's not
what I want. I want this one right here,
please.
There we go.
There we go. Right. Let's see. Ideally,
they squeeze this out a little bit
higher.
A little bit higher. Going to watch VIX
into that 1750 for it gap fill as well.
Building liquidity here. We're just
stuck in this value area on the session
right now. Ideally, we squeeze up into
this and then fail.
The sloped line moving average. This one
is what I call my higher time frame
algo. All right. So, when we're building
between higher time frame, lower time
frame algo is down here. Higher time
frame algo is up here. It's how I
dictate if the market's in a higher time
frame liquidity build from lower time
frame to higher time frame, which
currently it is. That's why we've got
this box up here. we start bidding above
this and the lower time frame catches
up, we can go on a big old squeeze. But
right now, I think there's probably a
rotation between these two for a bit,
which is why I'm looking to see if they
fade the market up here. If they don't
and they catch a giant squeeze, then the
next stop is 850s, 800 850s. If they get
through this 700s, they're going to go
850s. So, remember, we expected the
market to drive up this morning at the
opening bell. We're waiting to see if it
runs out of gas on a retest up here. So,
we're getting close now into this area
up here. Sevens would be interested. If
we base over sevens, we have to wait for
it for the EMAs to catch up and then
we'll look for a long to 850. Otherwise,
I'm looking to sell this if I see buyers
get stuck. Right? If I see buyers get
stuck, not if I don't.
Here it goes. So, towards the sevens now
getting very squeezy. Uh ES now filled
its gap. Spy now filled its gap as well.
So, those have completed the move. So,
this is the area where if they're going
to sell it, they should sell it around
here. If not, then they're going to come
all the way up here, and we're going to
have to look for a long. But, if they're
going to sell it up here, I'm interested
if they trap enough buyers. How we
doing? We got to remember, we've got
news coming in in uh what, just over 10
minutes. Just make sure that's right. 10
minutes, right?
Yes. PMI. Okay. 9:45 and then more news
at 10. 9:45 and then 10. All right.
Right into this block.
Pretty thick here actually. Aren't they
doing? What are you lot doing up here
playing some games on the tape
into the 20-day on ES bouncing off the
20-day on uh SPY. So, divergence between
the spy. There's between the ETFs and
the futures right now. QQQ into its
20-day as well. So, we're at mean. We've
recovered already. If we think about
what we've done overnight, we've gone
from lower Ballinger band to mean
already.
All right, so we talk about these kind
of trades all the time, don't we? Espec
It happens more frequently when the
Ballinger bands are getting tighter. You
can see we're starting to struggle to
move higher here. Yet they are starting
to struggle to move price higher through
here. We know it's a big level as
previous day point control. Fair value
from Friday. They are starting to
struggle to move higher. Can we trap
enough buyers here or have they got a
resqueeze up to 850s?
gap filled now QQQ. So just got the
alerts on that. Yeah, as well filled.
That is a slow alert trading view.
All right, VPO now moving up here. We
see we're starting to build out a shelf
up here now. Watching this for your as
your as an over and under for sentiment.
Can we change that, please?
There we go. All right, back down into
this previous day value area low on
Ninja Trader. So, did they find
acceptance through that or not is the
question.
If they keep bidding here, then there's
a resqueeze. If they fail this, we can
come back down. The big buyer came in at
97. So, we're I'm going to watch sort of
700 break here. Here's the break towards
97. So, we know there's a big buyer who
stepped in last time at 97. So, we're
going to need it under 97 under this
shelf here. Under that shelf here,
there's a big big flush possible. If we
come under this sort of shelf right
here, right? If we start losing the bid
here, then there's a big flush down
possible. like we're potentially going
to start doing. Need to see them get
aggressive and stay heavy.
Not before that.
So 97 still protected. Here comes the
flush. I want to watch 97 on a retest.
See if they stay heavy. They are staying
heavy versus 97. So interested if they
stay heavy.
They're faffing around a little bit
here.
I want to see this offer move down which
I'm not seeing. So still not in this
short yet.
Not seen the offer move down yet.
And now protecting 710s.
It feels close, but it's a bit iffy. I'm
going to be honest. The tape it's a
little bit iffy.
We're not under 700s. Interested in this
if they snap here. Back to 97s again.
All right, let's give it a go then.
Small size. Tiny tiny size versus
sevens.
I want to see this offer come down from
710s or I'm going to snap or I'm going
to cut it. Need to see this offer move
down from 710. They keep protecting this
lower side. Here we go. Keep protecting
it. Moving break even now because I
don't like this faffing around here.
Want to see this slamness now otherwise
I'm out.
90s. They got to let go of 90s here.
They're building a shelf and quite a big
shelf here. You can see the low volume
node underneath. They let go of this,
they will go. But they are getting
whippy. Moving my stop into the money
now.
We need to pro protect those 97s.
Going to be stopped out here on the 700
test. There we go. Stopped. Gave it a
go. Small size.
No juice.
I was just watching the tape here. Um,
where are you guys? No, this one. All
right. I was watching this. We kept
holding this like imbalance here. wanted
to see this seller move down and walk it
lower. We didn't see it. So, a small
size versus sevens, right? I was looking
to see if we'd flush this and fill this
in. We didn't. So, we can now if we
rebid, there is a chance to come higher
into the eights like we talked about.
All right. So, it's messy in here. This
shelf is messy. All right. If they bid
over this shelf, they're going to come
for a big squeeze. If they lose the
shelf, we can think about the same trade
again. We've got news coming in three
minutes. It's a little bit risky.
They're going to do it now, aren't they?
You bastards. It's the story of my life
right now. VIX almost filled its gap.
Not quite there.
Almost filled its gap. Not quite there.
So, VIX trading now at 58. Gap fill on
the VIX would be 42s.
If they rebid this, they can come up
here.
That would be very aggressive,
especially with the mag looking the way
it is. That would be amazingly
aggressive. Apple starting to lose its
bid. All right, remember that one and a
half% up. It's now just 0.20% up.
We are holding bids though. There's no
doubt about it. We're right into this
thick area from Friday. So, it's a big
area from Friday, but if they squeeze
through this,
88 850s is possible. Here's the squeeze.
So, not in this long. Might kick myself
for this. 8 to 850 is possible. Failed
breakout will be a push into this. Oh,
what's that? I don't know what that is.
Failed breakout will be a push into this
and a loss of this. Right. A breakout
will be a hold of this now for 800 and
this level up here that we keep talking
about these naked levels which it might
well have the juice to go to. We will
see. And we got news coming here in a
couple of minutes folks. Buyers
definitely got trapped there above 23s.
All right. Buyers just got trapped above
23s there. So they don't let them out.
That would be a bit of a shake and bake.
More buyers getting caught here. If they
can't get back above the 20, what did I
say? 23s and they're going to get
themselves caught.
If they can't get above 23s, they're
going to get themselves caught. We're
watching the same shelf for the snap
down. If they're going to let it go,
feels very messy here this morning
on the tape.
Back to these 23s.
You resqueeze this then there is a
chance to come on that P like we talked
about.
Waiting for news.
So just over one minute until the news.
Let's see what we do after that.
VIX almost at gap. It was almost there
on the VIX. All the ETFs have been
efficient. All the futures market and
now efficient. We close the gap and
above the gap
right on that 20-day on the QQQ.
Same on the NQ. It's got a tiny bit more
to go, but we're there or thereabouts.
We're right at mean. Okay. Still
watching this level. If we fail, I'm
still interested short if we fail and
stay heavy. Not unless we don't. I've
already had one little go at it.
When I say tape, you mean footprint and
not time and sales, right? I mean time
and sales. I mean right in front of me
on bookmap. That is the tape.
Time and sales. Like however you want to
look at that. But for me, if I'm looking
at the tape, the story of the tape, I'm
actually watching bookmap. Bookmap gives
me more of a story of the tape than uh
footprint does. Footprint does. It's
very hard to see like in each second
what's happening. Whereas in bookmap, I
can see every single tick that's coming
through.
Okay, opening range now sets.
News hitting the tape here. Let's see if
they uh duck this under this gray and
then come back down all the way down
into here or not or if they're going to
keep holding bids up here. Would like to
see them just duck this down and come
back for a 640s revisit. Seller coming
in now at 7:15 lot. So, they're trying
to get aggressive. We might leave this
tape now. This is what I'm looking for.
Can we leave this shelf now and be
aggressive?
Still, they are bidding and holding down
here. So, no break underneath where that
big uh participant came in earlier in
the day. 97s, remember 97s is where they
came in. So, it's kind of ugly here.
We've got one shelf here and then we've
got like another little low here. So, we
really got to come under this. We can
move this down. We've really got to lose
this whole section here. Until we lose
that, we can't really think about the
short. We'd have to lose that whole
section.
How much more juice has it got it?
Right. Point control here now shifted up
on the day. We have a lot of
discrepancies here today between uh
Ninja Trader and Trading View at the
start of the week.
Yes, trying to break out for a new high.
So, no flash under this gray box yet.
Momentum is bullish. Everything's
bullish right now. They might well want
to come up here. I'm definitely not
going to play that long up there today.
It feels like suicides to me right now,
especially without a trap underneath.
Maybe they just do it. Maybe they just
turn the algo on and go.
Right, VIX now filled its gap. So VIX
has now filled its gap as well. So we
have a completely efficient market.
Let's see if VIX is going to fade under
this gap. Market will continue to
squeeze higher. So 8 850s is still
possible here. 8 to 850s is still
possible here. It's a mine in my mind,
it's a very dangerous move to trade from
here to there, especially without like a
flush. If they'd flushed back down and
reclaimed, if they'd done something like
this,
right, I'd be more willing to take it.
But I'm more interested in this move
down into here
and then then I can think about the
long. But the way we're building this
squeeze base, squeeze base, squeeze. Not
really interested, especially when you
consider where we've come from.
Yeah, it's a big move into this same
kind of shelf. It's a very big move.
We will see.
Still stalking that same move.
Seeing some weakness now. Do they stay
heavy under this key level?
Point of control. Now I'm watching point
of control. 707s
and 97s. Remember 97's where they kept
defending earlier.
Back to this point of control.
watching. They're stalking this now in
case they offer it.
Still, they're absorbing down here. They
are relentless down there.
That's a fail break higher. If they
don't break higher now, I'm feeling
better about it. If we come underneath
the uh 700s,
they're still bidding this gray shelf.
We still possibly come up here. It would
be a huge squeeze day if we come up
there. If the low of overnight is 150
and we squeeze all the way up to 850,
that is
without a significant pullback. That is
going some. That's really impressive.
Yeah, PMI 10 minutes. Yeah.
So, we just had some news drop
which was uh
No, we just had PMI. We've got ISM in 10
minutes. PMI just dropped. It came in at
52.4. Previous was 51.8. There was no
forecast on it.
Okay. 750 being added on the tape above
us now. So, we've got passive sellers.
750, 740, 755, 760. Are they offering
even more above?
Yes. 800 is on the tape. What the [\h__\h]
mate? This is mental.
They're really just going to do a giant
squeeze today to 800s. Maybe.
Maybe.
It's a relentless bid up here this
morning.
The more I look at it, the more I think
we're going for that previous week point
of control. But there's no way I'm
playing that move. That is, in my mind,
is a complete psychopath move for a
straight up squeeze from the GlobeEx
low. If we're going to move from 150 or
180, whatever it is, to 850 with no
significant pullback. I mean, look at
this New York open. We've already
traded,
right? We've already traded from five,
but we're already 200 points higher
without any significant pullback. Here
we go. They're just going to do a giant
squeeze here then by the looks of it.
Nutters. Absolute nutters. But that's
what they are.
mental.
Someone's stuck. Do they want previous
day high on spy?
Yep, it looks like they do. They want
that five day and previous day high.
They are ripping this thing now. Nothing
to do here. Maybe if you if you traded
that gray box, you're braver than me.
But uh this is where it's coming now.
This is the target then for them. This
is where they're going.
Look at this squeeze. They caught them
all offside. This is their target.
So 800's coming up
and no acceptance underneath the
previous week. No acceptance underneath
the previous day. And we're going to
come right up to this naked point of
control by the looks of it. This is a
huge huge uh move to do in one go is the
best way of me saying it. To do in one
go. It's not necessarily huge move to do
without a significant bull back is uh is
very very aggressive.
So I'm selling here and if they keep
absorbing versus 85 they've got a chance
to move higher.
So you can see a little bit of a new
shelf developing here.
They squeezed up. If they let go of 85,
they can come back down. But we just
have to see how they operate on that on
that move.
Big seller came in at 90 there. So 90 is
a big overunder now. Gray box. So if
they retap into 90 and and lose it,
there's a possible wash down lower. So
90s is your level, your overunder. If
they reclaim 90s, then we're going to
expect 850s.
For me, spy looks like it wants previous
day high. They all look like the one
previous day high right now. So, we're
losing 90s at the moment. Do they come
and fill some of this imbalance down to
these 50s and below now
in this short
and we fill an imbalance the next
imbalance? We've tapped the first one.
Next one's down at uh 60 now.
So, short versus 90. Stop in the money.
We either get paid or we don't here.
So, short from here versus 90. Looking
for this play down into here.
Really, I'm more interested down into
here, but I'm playing this pullback. If
they base down here, I don't mind
playing that long, and I don't mind
playing that short.
Here we go.
Next imbalance will be 60s. Here we go.
Almost got it. Next imbalance is 60s.
Almost got it. Looking for a TP into 60s
here.
Protecting it so far.
Yeah. 65s
and 60s. Yeah, they're still finding a
beard in front of that balance at the
moment.
Going to protect my stop here again
because I am counter trend here at 90.
Any reclaim of 90, I'm out. Any reclaim
of that, I'm out.
How long we got some news? Five minutes.
Here we go. Coming for these 60s now.
Give me that TP.
They front ran it. You can see even on
the on bookmat.
Oh, they front run it just here. All
right. Looking to get filled into 60s.
There's an imbalance down here. They
front ran it twice now. So, this guy's
now stepping up. Very, very bullish
under there. If they use his pain, we
can go lower. So, watching this very
carefully.
I will happily play long if they uh come
back down to the 700s and base out now.
Tell you that much. There's just no way
I'm bidding up here.
This guy's moving up. Look at this guy
chasing the market higher now.
All right, sellers coming in at 75. So
75 and 90 of the level
news coming here in 5 minutes. Need to
let this news come. Uh what you guys
saying? I watch a pullback video and
it's very helpful.
What would be my next entry? Um
if I'm going to play the counter trend
fade, I'm looking for a rejection of
here. I got to be careful because they
keep building it out really nasty. I
think they want to come up here. So if
I'm going to replay this, I'm looking
for that.
If we base down here, I'll consider
longs down here. Right? If we do
something like this, I'll consider
longs. Especially if we don't take this
out. If we already take this out and
reject, I'm far less interested in the
longs. So, I'm willing to play both
sides at the moment. Why? Because if we
zoom out and think about where we are.
We expected the squeeze this morning and
I said to you, it's either going to
stop. They will end the squeeze here or
here. All right? We're between the two
right now. Remember that this morning?
We're likely to see a squeeze up to
here, here, or here. I would rip
straight through the first one into this
node. This is the next point. All right.
So, I would expect a pullback to happen
somewhere in here at some point. All
right. So, 800, 850 down to five, just
call it 600. There's probably a 200
point pullback in here somewhere, right?
While they build out this and then they
have to make the decision, are they
going to do that or are they going to do
that, right? So we expect this squeeze
here's look at the structure right we
expect this
then we expect this then I don't know
because then it has to make its decision
once it's built liquidity is it doing
this or is it doing this
uh one of you asked where I get Discord
if you've done the course go to the end
of the course it would tell you how to
get the Discord if you've bought the
course go to the end of
Still holding bits here.
Here come the 60s.
Come on.
Still holding bids. flow zone starting
to catch up. Order flow is still bullish
right now.
So if you're done 50% just just go all
the way to the end. If you really want
the discord just go all the way to the
end. You can go back and complete the
course. Just go to the end. One of the
end modules will tell you. Here we go.
TP here. Right now waiting to see if we
come down to 30s to this sort of block
down here or 20s. Right. So we're
filling in some of this. We want to see
if we come down into this and then do
they rebid off this or do we use that as
a complete collapse and leave buyers
trapped. Here we go. So, no matter what
going to protect my stop now and we just
see if we're going to come lower now at
this point into this block. Here we go,
folks. Jesus Christ. They squeeze that
for a long time today.
So, they're bidding here at 40s or just
under 40s 75 lot here into this opening
range. And like we said, this can be
absorbed down here. Now we built out big
shelf. So this is a big cover point for
us. If we get under it, we can think
about lower. Right. They just filled
this buyer here.
They just filled this buyer.
Change some of this. Make sure this
looks a little bit better for the day on
my Ninja Trader. Go build this shelf
out. Let's see if we can get into the
20s here. Opening range here. You can
move your stop tighter here. See if we
can get down into this gray box next.
So, we're short versus the 90s, right?
Short versus the 90s. We're 50 points up
now already. Let's see if we can get
down into here. Looks good.
Nice. Here's the opening range. Let's
go. Come on.
So, there's an imbalance upside now into
60. If they want to come up to that
imbalance and then fade it, which it
looks like they're trying to do. So, we
have to see if they reject 60. they only
reclaim a 60 now and then I'm not really
that interested in holding it especially
with news coming in
uh 40 seconds
finding a bid right in front of New York
VW up 20day and PDC right now so they've
got things stacked there if they do want
to hold so we're coming into big
overunder VIX reclaiming all right so
washed under its gap fill under PDC re
already reclaiming it into 1750s
Here we go. News print now 14 seconds
away. Stops in the money. I would move
stop comfortably in the money if you're
trading this because we might get skippy
on a newsprint.
There's a buyer on the tape today.
There's been a buyer on the tape today.
Look, it just got filled a little bit.
Here's the squeeze. There we go. On the
news. So, I stopped out there. Right
back to this shelf. Same shelf.
Apple now found a bid. Amazon's found a
bid. It's messy out there, folks. Tesla
over 3% down. Nvidia 2.34% down.
Microsoft 0.10% down. Meta 1.69% down.
Google 0.82% up. Amazon 1.68% up. Apple
now 1 and a half% up again. What are we
doing here? Come on, market. Calm
yourself down. Let's do something
reasonable. Can't trade this.
can't trade this. This is our edge up
here. We're playing edgeto edge. This is
kind of gross, guys. Right, that's where
we trap buyers. Remember 90s was the
level. This is this morning where we've
trapped shorts. This can be a rotation
under here. We can get weak and come
back down for this block here. Over
this, we can finish the rotation to 850.
We are bullish overall in the New York
session so far today.
It doesn't really matter what the
newsprint is. You're you don't don't be
too reactive to a newsprint. Just
because you think the data is bearish
doesn't mean does not mean a thing. What
matters is how the market react reacts
to it, not what you think of it.
Unless you're a fundamentals trader. I
do not trade fundamentals. I trade the
reaction to it. Otherwise, you're going
to be susceptible to sell the news, buy
the rumor, etc., etc. You're just
opening yourself up. Right? If we've bid
up for days and days and days and days
and days and the news is positive, you
think they're going to bid up more? No,
they're not. They're going to use it to
sell into it liquidity. Okay, back down
to this opening range again.
Why CFD moves differently? Yeah, because
it's not a centralized exchange. It
doesn't have as much liquidity and
because the broker's job there is
completely [\h__\h] you over on slips. All
right. So that's why I would not trade
CFDs. If you can avoid trading CFDs,
especially on markets where you could,
you know, trade the what you would call
the pair, you could trade the futures
exchange for it. Why bother? Why not
trade the centralized exchange which is
regulated?
What do I think of silver? I think
silver probably do a bounce and then
we'll see if they fade it on on on the
bounce. All right, so they're still
finding bids on flow zones and straight
back to this level. I still think at the
moment they want to revisit up here and
it looks like very much to me like ES
wants previous day high right now. So ES
previous day high is at 94s. SPY
previous day high is at about the same
94s
with the 5day up there.
We can't get through this shelf at the
moment. I think we will. Oh, it says OBS
disconnected. you guys there?
No, you don't need to say sorry at all.
You don't need to say sorry. I'm just
trying to help you guys. There's there's
no sorry about uh the news being bearish
or anything. You don't need to say
sorry, but just it's like the that
easiest play in the game, right? That
they they will uh use a print and go the
other way, right? It's the most obvious
thing in the game that they can do. You
have to understand where we are
positionally in technicals. Where we are
into that print, right? You just said
news was bearish. What are we doing?
We're printing upside. How many
fundamental traders went, okay, we're
going to be bearish, right? Well, guess
what? If they've all piled in short,
right, on that news, then we are going
to use them to go higher. Don't get
don't get too caught up in the news.
Worry about the reaction of the chart.
If it's breaking news, which isn't
priced in, it's a little bit different,
right? If we get some huge headline that
comes out, big war news or something
really really big that is not priced in.
Remember, most news is already priced
in.
Let me come back to this same level.
There you go. React don't predict.
That's exactly it. Okay. So, it looks to
me like they want to squeeze up here at
the moment. So, they held in front of
this shelf. We didn't quite get down to
it. Like I said, I was willing to bid
long down here if we did something like
this. And I think now they'll try and
complete this and we'll watch ES into
previous day high. And then we'll look
to see if they do a fail breakout above
that or not. OBS keeps telling me it's
disconnecting. If we get stuttery today,
please just let me know.
Vick's getting caught at that 1750. So,
no full reclaim.
Market probably going to slow down a bit
here. Coming into that whole number 800.
I still think it wants higher at the
moment. I think it wants this naked
level up into here.
It's what it looks like to me. It gets
very thick. If we look at the hourly
when we went there last week, this is a
big big level. We talked about this in
the newsletter. This level here is big,
right? Bears have got to defend this. If
Bears fail to defend this and we do
this, then we can go rotation right to
where? Top end and probably top side of
Ballinger, which will be Ballingers is
here. That's how tight the Ballinger is
right now. 176. We could go from lower
bowl to upper bowl in a day right now as
we build out the the rotation, which
would be kind of gross, but it's very
very possible at the moment. All right,
here they go. So, they're lifting.
All right, orderflow bullish. Flow
zone's bullish. I played this little
short back down into this Waiting now to
see how we react up here. Might be
kicking myself that I didn't just buy
dips all morning today, but there we go.
I'm going to come up to here.
26 210 26. Yeah. All the way up here
will be top bolt. It's possible. It
would be pretty mad, but it's possible.
I think they want a little bit higher
here
this out.
Yeah, look at this 161. That would be
perfect into this kind of level. Even a
two measured move will be fine. They're
almost there. They're almost there. And
I imagine that would be a big target for
them once they get up into that. That
they might call it a day there. Unless
they really want to turn the jets on.
they will have to get over 900 then for
a move back up to 26,100.
So into this level and if they base over
at 26,100 but I would say that's fairly
unlikely. I would think it's more likely
that they shove up into here and then
sell their inventory. But we will see
folks. We will see. Could be like last
week where Monday, Tuesday,
even Wednesday bid up and then uh flush
back down. So almost there on uh the ES.
We talked about that previous day high.
It's very very very close on the ES
right now. Very very very close about to
actually five day. SPY is already
through it. It's just the ES. And then
you can think about that 7,000. SPY
already through it. My stomach is
rolling.
Need some food.
Right. Watching this level. See how we
react. previous day value area high,
previous week point of control. So,
we've completed a full rotation from
previous day value area low right back
up to previous day value area high. So,
no auction underneath it. No rejection
of it, no rejection of previous day
point of control, right up to previous
day value area high and previous week
point of control. I would imagine in
here there'll be a look above and a
fail. I would imagine unless they're
really going to go mental for the
26,100s.
ES almost there folks. We do have
divergence between the ES and the
spiders, right? Cash is already over
previous day high. ES is not.
What did I miss, Tyson? Starting with 5
PAS today. Most I've had at one time.
Nice work.
Yeah, I'm very hungry. Can you hear my
stomach rumbling? I'm very, very hungry.
It's what, 8 7 in the morning. So, we're
watching this shelf here. All right. So,
I'd like them to complete the squeeze.
If I'm going to play the short, I'm
going to need to see some buyers trapped
on up here and then short down into
here. And then if we find acceptance,
this move here,
not before that. We're not going to
short on the way up. All right, we're
going to need them trapped. A bit like
here. Once we saw that trap, we got this
down into here, cover, and then break.
Even on that news print right here,
there's still a buyer on the tape. 820s.
He keeps trying to walk up. He's been
here all day. I want to see this build
out a little bit more. A spike in a
buildout would be nice.
Here we go.
Alex, you're from the UK and live on the
west coast of the US. Yes, correct.
Correct. All right. Here we go. This
naked point control is probably where
they want to come. 850s. Remember we
said if we find acceptance over here,
700s, possible to go 8 and 850s. So over
700s, 8 and 850s. Did I trade it well?
No. Absolutely not. Did I call it? Yeah.
Terrible for me to be quite honest. I'm
going to look back at this and think,
what were you doing? You said it was
going to squeeze to sevens. You said
over sevens, eights. And you said over
eights, 850s, and yet you didn't trade
the move up. What a what a silly man.
What a silly man on a Monday morning.
Okay, almost there.
Almost there. Previous day high almost
hit on ES as well, folks. We're almost
there. It's getting close.
Value area high on the day now up here
as well. So, we're starting to build out
a bit more of a shelf. You can see the
shelf starting to be built out a little
bit more. We have imbalances here down
to 800 if they do want to do a quick
wash and catch before they go back up.
There's a buyer on the tape. He is
relentless. Amazon now 2% up. Apple
1.65% up. Google 1.28% up. rest of MAG
Red. So, they're bidding early. Google
and Amazon, obviously, they have
earnings this week. So, we're pricing it
in nice and early. They're going to bid
it up. They could bid up and sell the
news like they did with uh everything
else last week.
Meta 1.38% down. Microsoft quarter%
down. Nvidia 1.75% down. Tesla 2.77%
down. So, I'm going to build up a little
bit more shelf here. I still would like
them to complete this move higher first.
Come and take out the low hanging fruit
before they do the drop. would be nice
otherwise it makes it much harder to
play the move back down if we leave low
hanging fruit. ES also low hanging fruit
above is got the previous day high where
ES is trying to get into.
Where did you send emails?
Purchase flows an indicator for Trading
View but cannot open. What's your email,
please? And I'll have a look. Maybe you
went into uh my spam or something.
Nice
spam.
Tom, what's your email?
Or email me
info@flowzoneontenttrader.com
and I'll have a look at everything for
you. I haven't seen an email from you,
but if you've bought it, it should tell
you what to do because you need me to
approve it. So, if you've bought it, the
course for the indicator should tell you
what to do.
All right, almost there. It's almost at
that low hanging fruit
right into here. Sort of 850ish
somewhere around that. And uh remember
above 900s if we base out between 900
and 850. We can go all the way up to
26,100s.
Definitely 26,80s.
Do I have a Discord? Yes, it's for
members only. It's for people that have
done the 20our course.
I haven't seen you reply, Tom, so I
don't know if you're still here, but
here's previous day high now taken on ES
previous week point of control here.
Everything now being tagged into
so into all these key levels now
and we have big shelves up here. Now,
this is a big big block from Friday.
Now,
how do you do the course? All the links
are down below, guys. All the links are
down below. flowzoneer.com. Everything
is there. All the links are down below.
All right. So, all low hanging fruit has
been taken. If you were long, I would be
out 90% of your position. If you're very
lucky, you'll come all the way up here,
but I would be out 90% of your position.
Now, if you were long, uh, you've just
hit all the key moves. I would not be
holding, looking for anything beyond
this. You would be very, very lucky if
they continue to squeeze beyond this.
might very well be that you get very
lucky, but I wouldn't be holding beyond
it. Okay? Don't think there's a reason
to hold beyond this. They are being very
aggressive with the bid this morning,
but your job is to make money and lock
it in, isn't it? Your job is not to, you
know, gamble for the next move. Your job
is to lock in money where possible.
Now, starting to see if they can base
above this. I will not be playing longs
from previous week point of control
unless we build out a huge amount of
liquidity up into this level here next.
I would imagine there will be a fade
coming because they've done not really
built up much liquidity but at the
moment they had just been bid up bid up
bid up bid up all morning long and they
still bid up bid up bid up. It's very
very very aggressive here. This is
madness. Previous day point of control
on Ninja Trader is at 79. So I'd be
watching this is what I talking about
the divergence between NT
still it's going VIX might want previous
day low here. This is a huge squeeze out
for the day off GlobeEx low and we are
now what 800 points higher or something
ridiculous. 700 points higher.
Very hard to get in. Yeah, we should
have just bought that drive this
morning.
chat buys there for sure.
Might be a fade coming soon. Soon
enough. We know that this level here is
key. This gray box is key.
Here it comes. So, we've got imbalances
now down to 50s and 40s.
Big old squeeze. Don't love the excess
at the high yet. There is a decent
amount of 74s, but we haven't really
retested it yet. So, we'll see.
There's the 60s.
Still not retested these uh stuck guys
at 70s 74s. If they leave 74s and we
trade under 60s, they might get a bit
more aggressive under here. We leave
74s.
Watching previous day high on ES to see
if they rebid it or let it go.
We have got previous day high on the
cues to go for if they re they really
want to turn the jets on which would be
all the way back up to previous week
value area high. It would be a huge
move. It would be a move as big as last
week in one session from the lows to the
highs.
Remember our low overnight is 182.
Our New York open
is 543 and we're now trading almost 900s
with only really this little pullback
here. This was bullish. This is not very
uh good to buy, but this was the only
little pullback here. One little
pullback. That's it. It's all the market
has offered. All right, that's the first
reattack of 75. So, they haven't got
through the 75s that we just talked
about.
Are they going to come a little bit
higher? Looks like the answer is yes. is
previous day point of control based on
Ninja now taken. So there's literally no
hang low hanging fruit left unless
they're going to go for previous day
value area high based on Ninja Trader
which would be 917.
All right, based on NT 917 which is up
here. Is there anything left? This is so
squeezy. It's crazy
crazy.
7,000 now tagged on ES as well.
And we have got stops to aim for at 944.
If we start basing up here like oh my
god, talk about a turnaround.
We talk about a turnaround. If we base
up here, this is going to be quite a big
turnaround for the market after last
week.
We'll see. This is only the first test,
though.
So I have an old point of control from
uh Friday up here on Ninja Trader which
we've just tagged into which was 81s and
I actually have previous day value air
height just based on Ninja Trader at
917s. So we could this on Ninja Trader
is 917s. Remember at the beginning of
the day I said the divergence between NT
and Trading View is massive today.
Maybe VIX wants to prove your state low.
How did you lose all your profit? You
must you must be fighting it. Don't
fight the tape. There's nothing to fight
here. We don't leave areas. We're only
going one direction. Look, multi-time
frame bullish right now. We're going to
squeeze all day long. Don't fight the
tape. What do I always say? Don't get
front side. The only way you've lost
this is if you're betting against it on
on the way up. Just don't do that. If
you want to play the fade, it's going to
have to like wash out and leave
liquidity. We've had like one go at it,
which was like here. That was it.
You entered at 880. You entered what? At
880. If you longed at 880, you're nuts.
And if you've shorted at 880, there's no
reason to short. There's literally you
haven't left anything yet.
So if you've if you've longed at 880 and
you've lost all your money, you how have
you lost all your money? You must be so
oversized.
All right, so looks like previous day
value area high based on NT is the next
area. Then 920s here. Oh my gosh, here
we go. 920 is coming up.
920 is coming up. I would say big buyer
came in at 900. So all the time they're
above 900. 920s is what they're looking
for, which is previous day value high
based on just on Ninja Trader. If we get
through 920s and we base above, you
cannot rule out 26,070s.
Can't rule out up here if they get a
base above it. Back to the 900s we go.
Right.
So buyers now caught at 900s and above.
I don't want to get long now.
I don't want to get long now. We've uh
completed this whole move on NT. If we
think about this,
all right, based on Ninja Trader, this
was previous days, but this is so
different to uh
to what we were seeing on um Trading
View, but this like reclaim and a
straight squeeze without a pullback.
We've we've literally reclaimed the
whole of the previous week and previous
day, the whole way back up without a
pullback. I definitely don't want to be
long up here. I want it's going to have
to do a significant pullback and build
out a lot of liquidity for me to
consider any form of long. And I just uh
it's way way way too risky. The only
long opportunity I guess was here and we
were looking for a long down here into
700 off it. Didn't offer it. Do not do
not get overly bullish at the highs.
Nice, Tyson. Great work. Right. Big buy
came in at 900. We haven't quite got to
those 20s yet. We're not far away.
Indy on the footprint. So this is sell
side mount. It's 2645.
What time frame are we looking at? Like
15 minute or something.
Yeah, up here. There is. You're right.
There is
definitely.
Okay. Buy still caught at 900.
Tape still bullish.
No shelf to leave yet. I'm going to get
rid of this. This was a thick area from
last week. I'm going to get rid of that
for a moment. We've traded through it.
We know 830s is the level. It's the same
level here. So, we can build liquidity
in here for a bit if it wants.
Bro, you wouldn't even go short from
here. I will go short from here once it
tells me it's ready.
What's your trigger? Just that it's up
high. That's not a trigger. If we start
leaving volume trapped, that's a
trigger. Just because a stock's up high
and you go, "Ah, it's gone up too high."
That's not a trigger to go short, is it?
I'm watching these 900s and I know
previous day value area high based on NT
like we talked about we have like the
divergence on the tape. NT value area
high is up here. So I'm wondering if
we're going to go all the way up there
right now. That's what I'm wondering.
Starting to build out volume here. So
I'm watching this now.
fix from almost previous day low. Just
got a little bit more to go
to the edge of this volume shelf. We if
we leave this, it' be interesting. We do
have excess at the high. Here's the
imbalance down to 85. If we start
leaving this, I'm interested.
Not if we don't. If we keep finding just
duck under and holding imbalances and
come back in there, no way playing short
side here.
It look a little bit better here on a
tape. Let's see.
and then balance here down to 84s. It's
looking a little bit better here. Might
get flush through this.
Still holding that imbalance down to 84
at the moment.
Buyers are stuck at 900 and above.
Still holding the shelf. Low volume node
just absorbed again.
They're not done with it. Not yet. We
just rejected that 900 player though.
Still think 8 820s. 920. Can't believe
it's 9. Still think 920s is possible on
a reclaim. There you go. They might go
for it now. I think 920s is possible on
a reclaim.
We're not leaving this shelf. We've
ducked under, held the node, come back
inside, back inside this shelf. We have
some some excess here. It's not the best
excess. 900 is a big level. And we're
now building out. If we if we can build
out here for long enough or put in more
excess, I'll be more interested.
But 20s is possible. Let me check the
tape above. Is anyone up at 20s? Yes,
there are a couple players up at 20s.
Come on, just make your mind up. Tape.
Apple now 2% up. Amazon 2 and a half%
up. Google 1 and a half% up. Meta just
under 1% down. Microsoft 30% down.
Nvidia 1.18% down. Tesla 2 and a half%
down.
squeeze day so far. They will do a nasty
pullback at some point. It is just a
question of when. There's no They will
not just go straight up 7 800 points all
day long without doing a nasty pullback.
They will do it. It would just have to
be when they need their exit and they've
got enough people trapped back down to
this imbalance again.
Watching this very very carefully.
Watching previous day high on ES and the
fiveday as well. They're all at the same
level.
I need a coffee. Am I going to need a
coffee at the worst point?
Do I go for a coffee now and then you
guys will all get the trade? Is that Is
that the plan? I'd be watching 920
rejection and then a lose of the shelf.
Right. Be right back.
Oh, there's a loser shelf. All right,
let's see. Let's see. Let's see. Didn't
even get to 820s. 920s even.
Let's see. Let's see. Let's see.
Still absorbing here. There's a move
down into here. Possible 820. So that
there is a full move if we reject this.
There is this move is available. Uh the
other option is that go it goes 920 then
does this move. Those are both available
right now. Seeing if I can get involved
in this somehow. Here we go.
So this is current value area high on
the day. Here comes all the way back
down towards this shelf. Let's see
folks.
Seller at 880. Let's see if we can get
down into the 60s.
We've got a shelf here developed into
60s under here. Here it gets fun. Really
fun.
Here we go.
Covering a little piece here. Had to
chase that a little bit cuz I was away
from the desk. And really, I want these
30s if we get lucky. But I'm covering
some in 60s because we can very well
hold up here.
Coffee indicator. Every [\h__\h] time,
isn't it? Every time I need a coffee or
a pee, the market moves.
It's true. It's absolutely true.
I just got a little piece left. I had to
chase a bit there, but uh covered most
out here into these 60s in front of
these 60s. Let's see if we can get under
this now and get into this next shelf
down here. All right. And then we would
expect buyers might want to step back up
and go for the 20s.
Been quite the squeeze this morning.
It has been quite the squeeze this
morning.
That's what I'm saying. Who was I forget
who was looking short on you got to let
it build out volume. See how we build
out volume and then we leave it. Right
now it needs to reject this volume. If
it doesn't reject this volume, you're
going to have an inverse head and
shoulder. Right? If it doesn't reject
this, right? Then you're going to do
this and 920s is possible. Right? You
have to understand you cannot be short
on squeezes up just hoping. You have to
see it leave an area. All right? And
then you're counter trend and you better
be covering into each node. All right?
And protecting yourself because you
don't know if we're a protrend. If this
is the pivot, right, this is the pivot,
right? It might very well catch bids
around here and go back higher. You
can't be expecting the whole thing to
roll over. It might happen, but you
cannot have that that as an expectation.
Here we go. Come on. Come on.
Little bit lower. Can we get into here?
30s would be very, very, very nice. Can
we go to 30s? The moment we keep
protecting that level.
We get down into 30s. Here we go, folks.
Here we go. Lovely.
Want to see us just drop under this and
snap down into here. And then I'll be
taking most my position out here.
Big level here in previous week. Here we
go, folks. 50s. We've got imbalances
here into 50s and then another one down
at 37. All right. So, imbalances here.
We're going to get most out into this.
We want to be very, very careful.
Remember, we're counter trend in this
short. We want to be careful here.
Covering some into this 50 because I can
see a player trying to step up here. And
then through this, we should get a
flush. Just covered some into that.
Be patient for it. It cannot be front
side. Here we go. Right. Let's see if we
can get gray box. I'll be 90% out into
gray box. Here we go. 50. So, imbalance
filled here. Next imbalance is down to
38.
Hopefully some of you guys are in this
short with me. Do not be overly
aggressive. All right. Please not be
overly aggressive. Just manage your
position. and we're counter trend short
after a big squeeze out which has done a
full rotation. So, we're just playing
the short back down after that rotation
and we will go from there. See what sets
up afterwards.
Uh over a thousand of you have not smash
that like button for me. Please do me a
favor, hit that like button and I don't
have to say it anymore. Makes my life
easier.
And we will want this protected. If they
do not protect this, then we will expect
new highs, right? If this is if we're
going to measure out, we just talked
about this. If we're going to measure
out this leg, right, we want to try and
get down into here. It might be that
they don't do it. So, if we've built
liquidity and they do this, then we can
expect 820. And if they want to be
really nasty, they're going to come all
the way up there, which will be previous
week value area high. I cannot tell you
how insane a move that is when you
understand how we've got there. All
right? If you understand how we've got
there,
here's previous week value area low.
Right here, there's the gap fill. No
acceptance reclaim. Remember, reclaim a
weekly level.
That will be insane. This is a whole
week we might well do in a New York
session. And if you don't think this is
insane, that is this is this is normal.
This is insane. That is a straight up
squeeze, guys.
Very impressive.
Market not wanting to let go right now.
The rotation continues. All right. Still
rejecting gray box. That's a good sign.
That is a good sign.
What was the initial balance would be
the higher day? Remember higher day.
It's a low day. Or do you mean what is
the size of the IB? Um
it is
370 points.
Huge. That is a huge initial balance.
Absolutely massive.
How did we do on Friday? It was quite
messy. I'm trying to remember.
Um I think we got something good at the
end of day, didn't we? Or did I miss
this whole thing? I can't remember,
folks. I might have I think I can't
remember. I genuinely can't remember. I
ended up teaching I think we caught one
really good trade on Friday towards the
end of stream and then I think it went
might have gone without me. I can't
really remember but uh in the private
lesson in Discord uh everything we
talked about set up which was great. All
right. Flowzone still holding previous
week point of control still holding here
as a bid. If they want to complete a bid
from here, all right, then they would
look for this move up here to 600 26,73.
It's insane, but it's you cannot rule it
out. All I'm saying is you cannot rule
that move out. ES holding its 5day and
its previous day high, finding a bid
there. VIX still yet to close its gap.
I caught 30 points and then it went
without me. There you go. So MG
saying what happened. I seem to remember
having like two or three goes at it and
then end up doing it. You got funded
because of Friday. Awesome. Fantastic.
IB to VWAP would be quite a move. Yeah,
it would. It would.
Right. Still watching this gray level
here and we have a new shelf here. So,
this is a rotation between the two. If
we if if it's a big if we keep rejecting
this and we come under this, this move
here is possible. Big if. If they
reclaim this, you do not want to be
short. If they start reclaiming this,
you do not want to be short. You are
better to let it pop and fade back under
and then think about the short. Do not
guess the high of day, folks. It's a
sure way to get absolutely wrecked.
Hopefully that makes sense.
Called it well. Yeah, it was all right.
I wasn't too bothered about Friday
because I remember I think the day
before we had a net of 600 points or
something. It was a last week was a very
big uh week for me. Very very big week
for me. So not I wasn't too fussed about
Friday.
I'm going to buy the course someday with
the profit with your methods. There you
go. I mean there's no pressure to do
that but if if you think it will help
you definitely do it.
Okay. Point of control shifted up here
now.
So previous day point of control current
day point of control both at the same
area. This is fair value 880.
If we leave point of control, then we
can look for this move down here. We are
developing out some kind of volume shelf
here, though it's messy how they're
developing this. So, I'll say that much.
Let me email him.
get some new codes for you guys so we
can do some giveaways. Sure. I've got
some
set up.
Okay, still watching that gray box.
Uh, I chased the short. I had to chase.
Someone asked was I short. I had to
chase down here for that flush. I had to
chase it. All right, watching this gray
box. Now, this is key. If they get
through this gray box, I expect 820s and
new highs. If we reject this gray box,
it would be failure to follow through as
downside price action. Buyers are
currently stuck above 900.
Um so above that you will get a
resqueeze out. We have previous day
value area high around 920 and previous
week all the way up at 26,074
and previous day high 26,020.
So the next opportunities are basically
this is what I've been thinking about.
Either we reject this and we roll. We
take it, we go 920, we reject and we
roll. We take it, we base and we start
to come up into here. Right? These are
all available. And then that we are very
very very very very bullish on the day.
The order flow has been very very
bullish. They're just bid bid bid bid
bid right now. But we are you know deep
in premium. You got to think we are in
pre above premium of previous day or
coming into if you're following Ninja
coming into pre like the most premium
area of Friday. So it is not an ideal
area to be buying off right now. Okay.
Do I have any codes to reset pro
accounts for take profit trader? I wish,
buddy. I'm sorry. No, they no codes or
anything like that for take profit
trader. I am working on uh getting
stuff, but no, I don't think they would
do resets for pros. Resets are very
expensive for pro accounts. I think it
would cost you about 600 bucks.
Honestly, you're better off, in my
opinion, my humble opinion, better off
not resetting, paying 100 or whatever it
is, and just passing a new uh email.
What was the bias at New York open? Why
rally towards previous week, previous
day value? Because of the bullish
structure from London section and would
you have been ready for a long the bias
was uh to at least back test, right? So
I I was telling you guys that it's
probably a long um up for the back test
of sort of 600 over 600. We talked about
a back test of seven over seven 850
and over 859
26,100.
Why? Just structure, right? So this is
what we talked about this morning.
We think about this, right? Think about
previous week
and previous days in here. So gap down,
no acceptance. We expect a back test of
this. If we sell this, we said we'd sell
that back down to here. If they don't
stop here, they're going to come in for
700 test. All right, this node here,
this level here. If they don't stop
there, they're going to come up for this
level here that we're now at. All right,
if they don't sell this, then they're
going to come up for the next level
above, right? So, we don't This is what
I always tell you guys why the counter
trend's hard. We don't know where it's
going to stop. So, we have to wait for
volume to be built out. If they don't
build volume out, think about why is
this squeezing? I tell you why it's
squeezing. because shorts tried here and
tried here and tried here and they're
adding and they are fueling this fire
up. Yeah, there's a bid also, don't get
me wrong, but I don't really want to bid
here for this. This is so risky to bid
here for this.
All right, failure to break out here
gray box. So, we would imagine now the
rotation will happen between here. Here
are the important areas now for this
current current part. That was a failure
to take a high. ES did take the high.
So, we had slight divergence here. We go
gray box to gray box until they're done
with it and we can see what's what.
Yeah, 900s and above. They keep getting
stuck. The buyers, you can see it on the
tape. That's where they keep getting
stuck. You can see we can see maybe
here,
right? 900s and above. It's all buy
side. If we look at all this, it's all
buy side. It's all buyers. keep getting
caught up there. So, at the moment,
we're not seeing a passive buyer step in
and support a bid above that. We're just
seeing aggressive buyers get caught.
Gray box to gray box is the current
rotation.
Yes, rejecting IB high as well.
Okay, that down to this other gray box,
point of control. If we leave this, it
would get nasty. If they keep bidding
this, they've still got a chance to move
higher. We've got now got lots of stops
based up here. I have an anchored VWAP
or anchor volume profile to 930. I have
two ticks per row, but it doesn't look
like yours. Have I got it wrong? No,
that's right. What if you It should look
like this. You might need to reset it.
That's exactly what to do. Should look
the same. Maybe you got to change the
width to 20%. Maybe that will help you.
Okay. Seeing some sellers step in here.
back down to these same key levels.
Nothing's really changed here. Gray box
to gray box. If we start leaving one, we
can think about lower prices, but not
before then.
Certainly not before then.
They are trying to leave this area.
Watching ES into previous day high as
well. Right, ES into previous day high.
It keeps bidding there this morning.
I think they're going to try and clean
up some of these guys a bit lower into
60s again and then see what happens
the right level. Yeah, let's see if we
leave here then now and how we act.
We're building out a huge amount of
volume. It's a shame that they've left
this little low volume node. It's going
to be pretty dangerous how they're
setting this up.
still protecting this sort of edge here.
I let this develop a little bit there.
There's
there's a couple opportunities here,
right? If we go sideways long enough and
they leave it, there's a there's a big
uh fail down into here somewhere. Very,
very possible. If they go long enough
and they start bidding above, then I'm
gonna get more aggressively thinking
that we're going to go up here. I'm not
going to play the long up. I'm just not
I'm gonna ban myself. If I was going to
be long, I should have like said what I
was going to do, which was just like buy
the drive up and buy the whole that dip
had been a bit better. I would have
thought about it. If this structure had
been better, I would have thought about
it, but
got caught um
caught waiting a little bit today.
Monday morning, it happens. I'm not
perfect. I'm only human. won't grab
anything. Everything even.
Come on, guys. You know, one 1.3,000 of
you watching this. Only 586 likes. Smash
that like button, please. We got to get
it way way higher if we're going to do
some giveaways on stream.
Still holding the shelf.
Yes, failing to break out over IB high,
but not breaking down underneath its
5day and previous day high. There might
be some failure or like a deeper
pullback in this market. It's just a
question of when they're ready for it.
When are they going to be ready for it?
Right back into previous week point of
control again here.
Are they going to start leaving?
still absorbing this kind of level that
low volume mode
55s.
There are bids lower. Someone's trying
to chase this down here and he keeps
getting stuck. I'm just waiting for a
pop to see a pop up get really sold into
heavily again. Then I'll be more
interested
and balances down to 50. We have got
bids down at 50 and under. I want to see
a pop up get sold into more aggressively
and then I'm going to be more
interested. I'm very concerned if they
keep holding here long enough without
breaking down that we're going to go the
uh 920 kind of shove. So I want to be
careful. ES still holding previous day
high. That's going to be a good trigger
as well. So, we can watch ES as well. If
ES starts collapsing under PDH, then we
know there's probably a bigger trade
back down to that New York VWAP kind of
area on the ES, which maybe we can get
down into these two areas on Q. So, I'm
watching. Need pops to fail though for
me to be interested.
We'll see folks.
When I say they, um, it's just a way of
observing the market, right? So, it's,
yes, you you could say market makers and
and funds. Really, what I just mean is
the market. All right? If I say they,
the people in control of the market, if
we we view the market as one entity, all
right, if you just view it as one big
trader, it's an easier way to look at
it.
Yeah. Effectively, it's it's all the
funds and smart money. Not ICT smart
money. Real smart money. Real big guys
positioning.
Here we go. Watching this. Watching
these 50s to see if they actually have
continuation. Come on. But man, what are
you doing?
There's a balance here at 50s and then
35. So, watching down here to see if we
break under this and start like really
getting heavy down into this sort of
area here
and keep protecting this area. This is
where sellers keep coming in and not
getting follow through. That's what I'm
saying. I want to see a pop be sold.
Still protecting previous day high here
on the ES, by the way, folks. Still
protecting previous day high there on
the ES. Still finding a bid there at the
moment.
Alex, if you need to react fast via bid
ask or always stop limit orders. Uh
yeah, I like I chased a little bit here.
Normally I would have a stop or a limit
order and my uh covers would always be
limit orders, but I've got hotkeys as
well, right? So like if I feel like I'm
not getting filled, I can either move a
limit order with my mouse or I can mark
it out or I can close all with a hotkey
or I can move break even with a hotkey.
We leave this shelf. We can get more
aggressive here down into this area of
30. So we're just waiting to see this
sort of previous week point of control.
We're going to start being aggressive.
They're trying. So that's that first
imbalance filled into 50s we just talked
about. Instantly bid off 50 there. So
there was an imbalance at 50. The next
imbalance is down at 38 to 35. So it was
a flush to 50 instantly caught. You can
see on bookmap we had like a 70 lot at
the low of that sell side who just got
paired against. So they filled that
imbalance and held. ES held 5day and
previous day high still holding for now.
Can we get acceptance lower? I'm buying
this for a short but really I don't want
to chase down here. I want pots to start
failing. I just wonder if they're going
to leave this area at the moment. back
into his old imbalance. 35s is the next
level or 38s to 35s if we flush through.
Not convinced right now. No pops that
are failing, but just wonder if they're
going to roll this all the way down.
Here they come. Dirty [\h__\h] the way
they've built this. Pardon my French.
All right, imbalance coming up here. 38
to 35.
Sellside is 54s. Big sellers came in
versus 65. Here's that imbalance that we
just talked about. Here's 38 to35
tagged. If they trade through this,
we've got a shelf here at 3128s.
I want pops to fail though. ES now
underneath previous day high. VIX came
underneath previous day low. Found a
bid. Possibly forms a little inverted
head and shoulder here in front of 17s.
A break of 17s and we can get going on
the VIX which will increase downside
pressure.
Explain the imbalance. It's it's where
participants didn't get filled on the
way up,
right? It's here. It's where
participants didn't get filled on the
way up, right? Where we've had a big
squeeze out and there's an imbalance in
the market where people are likely to be
waiting to be filled. Right? So, we have
sell side imbalances up here, buy side
imbalances down here.
Okay. Retesting previous week point
control.
Current day point control. This gray
shelf now important. If buyers reclaim
this squeezes on, if they reject this,
then maybe we get some downside
pressure. I really don't like it how
they built this. This is uh you'll be
very careful here. You need to be very
careful here,
right? You need to see this here for
sellers. If we do this for long enough,
they're going to open this up.
Our
bids down at 50 still.
Tricky market, tricky conditions today,
I would say how they've built this out.
You still feel they want to take
previous day high first? It's quite a
big ask. It's possible.
Um, I have that as previous day value
area high on Ninja Trader as well, but
it's asking so much without a
significant pullback,
but it's very it it's possible. The way
they're building out N is nasty. No, I'm
still not sure, guys. I'm still not
sure. I'm watching this at the moment,
though, because that last pop up into
that 65 area was interesting. Watching
this now to see if we get follow
through. 65 was
uh current point of control and previous
week point of control there or
thereabouts. So if they sell that
aggressively, I will join the tape
back to these 50s again
and keep trying to bid down here at 50s.
That old imbalance. Like I said, there's
an imbalance down to 37s. I'll try and
show you what I'm looking at. Right, I'm
watching. We had one imbalance here.
We've tapped into this one here at 37s.
There's a flush point down here. if we
let go of the shelf, not not before it.
So, we've got to let go of this and get
through this to trade down. It's kind of
messy the way they've built out all
these nodes. We're going to have to be
very very careful if we're going to
trade counter trend today.
Uh reclaiming again.
So, this can be a two-leg and they can
rip this if they really want. So, I want
to be very very careful here if I'm
going to think about it
into this gray box again.
patience.
Should have, would have, could have.
Bought the open. Should have, would
have, could have.
I tell you what, I know I said, you
know, I gave you the areas where we
might come up to. I didn't actually
think we'd get up into the 900s in the
first hour of trading. I'll be honest.
If you if you thought we were going to
get up to the 900s in the first hour of
trading, if you thought we were going to
go from five, we're going to do like a
400 point ripper in the first hour of
trading. You should be very rich person.
I didn't think we'd do it in the first
hour. I thought we could potentially do
it today, but not in the first hour.
Footprint, man. If you're looking for
imbalances, footprint, you're going to
need to watch a footprint chart.
You can't do it otherwise.
Still rejecting up here. Move this down
a little bit. It's like that. It's
messy. It's so messy, guys. So messy.
Still rejecting that PC at the moment.
It's tempting. It's tempting. I just
don't see the heaviness on the tape at
the moment. It's very tempting to get
short here and look for this wash, but
I'm not convinced yet. I might have to
join late, which is not ideal, but I
want to be convinced that bears are
turning up. Like ES isn't even under
previous day high yet. VIX is still
coming downside.
If VIX fails to break lower, then I'll
feel a little have a bit more conviction
about this. Seeing some sellers step in
here. Let's go then. Let's see. There we
go. Back into this same shelf into the
50s.
Still got that imbalance down at 35s.
See if they pop up and sell 65s here.
Go from gray to gray for a bit probably.
They're trying to step on the gas here.
They're bidding 32s at the moment.
Someone's coming in it. They're trying
to force this under those 30s. There's
that imbalance. Just tagged. What do we
say? 38s to 35s. Do they trade through
this? Through this. Now we go gray
shelf. And then we can really get going.
If they've got any juice, they're going
to have to get through this though. Here
we go. You've got to snap this. Here
they go. Starting to snap it. They're
trying to reclaim already.
Here we go. 32s. Can we get going now?
Can we get going now into this gray box?
Taking a little piece here just in case
they're horrible with this and bid the
gray box. And if we get under gray box,
we're going to look for the 800s.
Here we go. Let's go. Right. Covering a
little bit more now cuz they're stacking
here. They are stacking here. Come on.
Let's see some follow through. Come on.
I want to let go of this gray box and
trade straight down to 800. Now, be very
careful your counter trend. Do not get
oversized here. Move your stop into the
money, please. It's the hardest trade in
the book that I always talk about. Come
on. Lots of imbalances down here into
8006 down to 800. I'll be taking 90% of
my position off.
Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go.
Let's go. One big flush, please. We'll
do it. Here we go. Here we go.
Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go.
I'm trying to fill some of these down
into here, please. This is what I'm
trying to get down into. gray box. I
want to go gray box to gray box. I want
to get down into here. I'm not going to
sit through a bid. They bought eight. Uh
they bought 34s. I'm not going to let
this come back above sort of 35s. All
right. They bought 34s. I don't want to
back 35s. I want to use those buyers
pain.
Going to retest this level, aren't you?
You're going to retest 34s.
Come on. Step on it. Step on it. Step on
it. Come on.
Getting tight here. I don't do not want
to get squeezed here above 34 35s.
Not going to get squeezed all the way
back out to 60s here. So, stop right
back down.
Protecting my profits here. Come on.
Let's sell through. Come on. Come on.
Come on.
Come on. Break this low. Got to get
under 17s here. Come on. Break this low.
You got to get under 17s. Hit me 800s.
Come on.
Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go.
Let's go. We got to break these lows to
get down to 800s. Come on. Buy stepping
in at 815s. Come on. Come on. Come on.
Come on. Snap him, please. Someone step
on the tape.
Step on the tape here, sellers.
They're bidding 15s at the moment. I
want to sell through 15s. We should get
We should get that fill then down into
the low 800s. Moving my stop a little
bit more into the money.
Don't like that. Don't like that. We
can't let this go above 33 34s. Can't
let it go above 34s in my mind.
above 34s they can rip it to 60. So stop
down there right now protecting this.
We'll be in the money no matter what.
There we go. Out. Not going to get
caught in a squeeze up. Can always add
back in on a move back to 60s if they
stay heavy.
Yeah, decent trade. Not bad. I don't
want to get caught in this squeeze now.
Right. So they're reclaiming the 34s.
There's a big buyer came in at 34s. All
right. So if they reclaim this, they can
come and visit up here. All right. So
the next rotation will be here to here
or here to here. All right. So I don't
want to get caught in the rotation.
Remember short. There's the rejection.
All right. And rotate. We can build out
liquidity here. Need to respect each
level right now because buyers have been
in control. We've been in a buyers
market this morning. Remember this can
be like this and go higher. So we have
to be proactive. We don't know. Maybe it
collapses. Maybe we get lucky. But we
have to be of the mindset that they can
very well trap and come back up. So we
have to be proactive with the covers
this morning.
Nice guys. Yeah, lots of you got that
with me.
They do it now. You [\h__\h]
They're going to do it now. You
You absolute asses.
Here they go.
How many days in a row? How many days in
a row they're going to knock a runner
out for me and then do it?
All right. Imbalances are 806 to 800s.
All right. 806 to 800s. Basically, this
here, right?
you want to be covering into this,
right? Because we expect this probably.
We haven't had like a higher time frame
shift.
Uh, Alex, do you trade props or your own
live personal? I have both.
Do I have different rule sets for each?
Probably a bit more uh aggressive with
props once I get through um buffers. Uh
my most my personal I use for swing
position.
So we can have a look what one of my
swings at the moment.
So I still swing long Apple since like
August last year. Up 50% on AMD. Still
smaller size than that. I did trim 80%
of my position before Christmas. Uh,
Amazon, uh, up 9.56%.
Meta I'm up 14.86% on. Open, I'm still
up 153%. I've got one share left on
open, folks. As we all know, I sold all
of it when I was 500% up on that. Uh,
that's my only position. So, I'm waiting
for this market to give a big old tank
and pull back for me to take some bigger
swing long positions.
Uh, I moved off Replicanto. I would
advise you use affordable indicators.
Uh, now you links are probably down
below, but if not, I will post it in. I
would say that it's a onetime fee. It's
a little bit more stable. Replicanto's
moved to uh a different um format.
Yeah, let me post it in chat for you
guys. Uh, you probably I think you'll
get a little bit of money off this. I
don't know. I'm not up to date with it.
I'm sorry. I'm really bad at uh keeping
up to date with everything like that.
Let me There's the chat.
So this is affordable indicators there,
right? That's who I would use if I was
you. Okay, they're still holding this
gray box. So gray to gray can be a
rotation. It can be a rotation.
I'm waiting to see if VIX can start
doing that sort of inverse head and
shoulders, which will help. So if we're
thinking about, you know, what I'd want
to see for confluence, right? If VIX can
start breaking above this, right? If we
have wicked out previous day low into
the IB, if we're going to do this move
on VIX up into here, this will help our
short thesis on the market. So, I'm
waiting to see if they're willing to do
that on VIX at the moment.
Yes, that's for copy trading. I mean,
you can use it for there got all sorts
on there, but they have a very good uh
trade copier on there. You can uh trade
all prop firms. You can set um targets
for like your eval. So if you're
aggressive with some S some others. You
can chart on uh NQ but trade on MNQ
without having to change your charts.
Here you go. Still looking for that
imbalance at I'm out of this. By the
way, folks, this is still looking for
that imbalance at 806 and 800s. So your
cover points are still into this next
gray box, right? And if you get lucky,
you'll get VW up here. That would be a
hell of a trade. All right, for you guys
that get this this short position. And
where's my short? Right. Something like
this here. Other side of the node. If
you get really lucky, you'll get this
move down into here. That would be an 82
pointer. But I'd be covering lots into
here. Right in into this pocket here.
You should have already covered some. I
got knocked out on the runners. And if
you get lucky, you get into here. Maybe
even this. If you get very, very lucky.
Move this here so you can see. But I
would definitely be covering some 806s
down to 800s. Right. 806s. and then see
if you can get all the way down. Here
you come. You're almost there. So,
congrats if you're in this. You're now
into this low volume node. So, you
should be trying to take some partials
into this deep pullback flow zones. All
right. So, they might very well bid
around here. So, you want to be more
aggressive in terms of your stop.
VIX trying to do that inverse head and
shoulder breakout. I'm waiting to see if
we can break 1690 17s here on VIX. Here
you go. Imbalances now. 806s. You're
starting to trade into the imbalances we
just talked about.
Right. Right here. Okay. Into these.
You're trading into these. These are
cover points for you. If you get lucky,
you'll come all the way down. But these
are cover points for you.
Alex, you mentioned about a big trade
indicator. A Ninja Trader. Big trade.
I'm not sure what I'm not sure what you
mean. Do you mean big orders? Maybe you
mean this. Um, you can get it for free
using the order flow. If you go on my
YouTube, there is a uh video on how to
get free order flow for Trader V and
Ninja Trader and uh I I show you how to
do it on there. There's a video on my
YouTube. Right, back to gray box. So, if
you you need a rejection of this to
trade down into this shelf. If you do
not reject this gray box, this is the
same story as we had here. Gray box to
gray box. gray box towards gray box. You
need to reject this and do this and then
this. Otherwise, we're going to go level
to level, right? Level to level. We
trade level to level, level to level,
level to level, level to level.
But your TP was in here. I think I said
sixes, sixes to 800s and then run us
down to here. So, you got sixes, you got
under sixes, and gray box is starting to
be reclaimed. If they reclaim this, I
would expect to squeeze back up to 60s.
Protrend is long today. Remember,
Protrend is is long.
You would want ES to reject previous day
high here. VIX failed to break out that
inverse head and shoulders we just
talked about. So, just wait to see if it
can still do it. We've got uh about 50
minutes left to trade here together.
Oh, feel like a bit of a mugggin today.
I'm going to be honest. Why couldn't
they have built this out a little bit
better for us? Maybe I should have been
more aggressive on dips here. I didn't
like the look of this. I look at that
now and just think,
should have, would have, could have.
This was almost there for me. And then
what a drive that would have been. Hey,
it happens. Uh, any of you who just buy
flow zones, well, you just had a great
day. If you just buy the flow zones, you
had a great day. If you sell the flow
zones, you had a great day. They are
giving you absolute golden opportunities
today.
Previous week point of control which
time included what's the whole week? I
mean, I think I draw it on the hourly,
but
it's the whole week.
No worries. Well done, guys.
Yeah, I mean, we're not actually a
trending market. um on on this session
you can say yeah we're we're bullish
trending market but actually we're not a
trending market we're we're completely
the opposite to a trending market if you
zoom out um actually let's just go on to
a daily
right we are not a trending market right
now right we're clearly the opposite of
a trending market we are boxed
same box we've been in since November
5th All right. Failed to look
underneath. Fail to get above. Failed to
come underneath. Fail to come
underneath. Fail to get above. Fail to
come underneath. Trapped between the
Ballingers. We are anything but trending
market, which is why I wanted to be very
careful today. Um, if we reclaim this
level,
then means we haven't undercut. They can
still sell this and come down. If we
reclaim this level, we can still
consider longs if they start expanding.
But they're going to make this very,
very tricky. um they don't know what
they want to do with it right now. But I
tell you what, we can't do this from
November 5th forever. Uh one way or
another, this is going to get nasty. And
the longer we stay here, the 200 day,
you can see now it's time to really
catch up. There might be an event where
we can just scoop this and they do
something horrible. But we are not going
to do this forever, guys. At some point,
someone is going to lose. I don't know
which side yet. And anyone who tells you
it's going to be this side or the No, we
don't know which side yet. We don't.
Bears had control coming into this
session. All they had to do was reject
this and come for this undercut and look
for these stops. That's all bears had to
do. Did they do it? No, they failed. All
right, so now we're back at this old
point of control. It's not only an old
point of control. If we look at the
volume for the last year, all right,
this is a year's worth of volume. We are
in a huge huge node here. If we find
acceptance over this node and the bowls
start going, we can do big drives out.
All right, we can do this for the rest
of the year. It's asking for us to find
acceptance. We can get up into 28,000
this year. All right, but it's got to
get outside of this.
So, I don't have uh a bias right now.
I'm I'm willing to play both sides of
the tape until we move outside.
Volatile. Volatile. Yeah, volatile's
definitely true, right? Definitely true.
All right. So, starting to reclaim. So,
gray box to gray box. So, that pullback
held. So, if we think about this from a
fib, remember we talked about this
earlier. Where did we h right into the
618? They're starting to hold this. So,
they're going to go gray box to gray
box. And if they find acceptance over
this, then this will be considered a
huge bullish momentum to try and get up
into here. If they fail this, fail back
under, we go between here, fail that
here, but I almost find it unlikely that
we come down to this at this point
today.
Don't see why they would profit take on
a Monday off the positioning this way,
but we will see. We will see. It looks
pretty bullish overall.
TP1 hit here hit here hit here hit here
hit here hit here hit here hit here hit
here hit here hit. That's your first
trade. Decent trade today that hit. Now
we just see it is possible rotation
between these gray boxes. We definitely
got a lot of stops at those highs if it
really wants to go for them.
Do I use previous days high volume nodes
or use developing nodes as SNR? Both.
Both. And ideally, they match up well
together. Same with previous weeks. They
all matter.
But if you look at where we're trading
into like the previous week right now,
guys,
right, the This even from the open. This
is from the Sunday open. Look at the
amount of liquidity we're building up
here already. Right? This is huge. If we
leave this, this move here is highly
probable at some point this week. Right?
This was where we clearly broke out just
before New York open. Right? We've never
come back to retest any of this. This
will happen. I would imagine this will
happen at some point this week, even if
we're going to be bullish from there.
And we can use these nodes here. So,
we're here, here, here, and then thick
here. So if we leave this, that rotation
is possible.
I'm looking at multiple time frames all
all the time trying to see where the
edge is. Right now it feels bullish.
61 pullback of this bullish, but you
know, we've got a trap volume above head
now for the first time today.
For the first time today
and we're inside initial balance. We're
in a rotational market on the day. We
are starting to find a bid above
previous day value area high. It's
possible that 920 is a level that we
want to visit today. Um on on NT I have
that as a previous day value area high.
I don't know what some of you have but
that's what I've got. If I look at bring
this over right I have this as a big
level from previous day value high from
Friday. I don't have the same on Trading
View. So there's a divergence or
discrepancy between Trading View and
Ninja Trader. You can see at the moment
we're just trading in the previous day
value. No acceptance underneath, no
acceptance over under previous week.
Trading inside previous day. If we find
acceptance above 920, then uh 26,50s
is possible. And previous day high,
previous day opens up here as well. So
we just have to see folks. It's been a
big drive this morning though. I'll say
that much. Been a huge drive.
call it a box. Are you ever inclined to
trade this or do you solely interested
in continuation? Yeah, absolutely. I
will tra I do trade it. Uh it's just not
my favorite setup, but I do trade it.
Absolutely.
I don't trade it on swing positions
though. I will not trade the box on
swing positions. I would rather look for
a break and a retest on a swing
position.
Alex, what's your win rate? You are
break even, usually at worst. Can you
talk about that? You don't be humble.
You earn all you get. Um, I normally
shoot between like a 67 and 73% win
rate. But like I've talked, I do say
this a lot of time. I think that is
probably skewed. Why? Because I am day
trading happy to move my stop break even
or break even plus one. So even those
trades which have let's call it positive
delta in terms of win rate
they're really flat trades aren't they
right? So I could do I could have a a
one tick positive one tick positive 100
times and it would have 100% win rate
but the reality is it's a break even
trade. So sometimes I think those are a
little bit skewed. I'll be honest.
You'll see me on stream take a lot of
break evens um before I get the move.
Sometimes I don't get the move.
Sometimes it goes without me like
Friday. All right, back to gray box. So
gray box to gray box if they reclaim
this. So this is 61 fib hold. They
reclaimed. We go back to gray box
through this. If they get acceptance
over 75s, they're going to come up here
for the 900s.
So this can be a big bullish play. This
can be a two-leg pullback. All right,
this is what we're looking like at the
moment. I would say sort of something
like this. All right, and then they have
to decide, are you going to reject this
down or they going to do this move here
for the continuation?
Yeah, I hope that makes sense on the win
rate. So, I'm just being honest with you
because I don't want you to think, oh,
like 67% of the time I get a 100 or 200
point trade. That's just not the case.
Uh what it means to me is I don't lose
67% of the time. I kind of see it the
other way. I don't trade gold. I take
swim positions. I'm waiting to see if we
see failed followthrough at the moment.
I can show you what I'd like to see on
gold and silver if you're interested on
swing positions. Right? One I want to
see
is a pullback. Right? If I'm going to
really think about the short, I want to
see a pullback somewhere into here. And
I want to see buyers get stuck and then
I'm going to take an ETF short position.
If they get stuck, if we leave these
buyers stuck, I'm going to take a
position down to here. I'm going to trim
a big piece of it. Then I'm just going
to see if the market wants to drift
lower. Macro-wise, it can very well bid
up, right? Macro environment, weak might
very well do this. By the moment, the
dollar is getting stronger, which means
we might rotate back out of this. A lot
of this depends on what the Asian
markets do. Understand the macro
environment.
I'm not going to day trade gold and
silver, but I will look for some swing
positions if it makes sense to me.
What does the Ninja Footprint indicate
cost? I can't remember. I think it's
like three or 400 bucks,
something like that.
Um
I think I've got like a five or a 10%
discount code. It's tiny.
Uh it's from Twin Peak. So, let me Where
are you guys again?
That's it there. I just posted if you
want that one.
Do I find affordable indicateators is
responsive? Yes, very.
Well, the thing is if you're using trade
syncer or stuff like that, you're asking
for lag because it has to go via a
web-based platform. I think that's
that's the problem.
Uh currency flipper. Yeah. So, the pro
is what I'm using here. The Pro is like
the upgrade. So, with the Pro, you get
like uh GlobeEx, opening range,
um I'm trying to think what else is the
difference. There's basically just a few
more levels in the Pro Indicator. Oh,
and the candle repaint as well. Candle
repaint, which you don't get in the one
that comes with the course, but you
don't have to upgrade. You can always
upgrade upgrade later. But the one in
the course is still sufficient. It still
works very, very well.
I prefer Me personally, Miles, I prefer
Delta for Footprint. I don't I don't
watch bid ask. Me personally, I prefer
Delta. All I really ever care about if
I'm looking for a trap player is delta.
All right. So, if this pullback now
holds this, we talk about this next
rotation. So, if the pullbacks now now
hold this, they're going to try and get
up to here, aren't they? If they fail
this, this is a look above to take the
stops and this becomes possible. This is
why the shelves matter. But overall,
we're bullish. We talked about this,
right? Held this starting to reclaim.
This can be a rotation. And if they get
through this, then we'll leave all these
sellers trapped. If they fail this, then
this can rotate back down to here.
Is my preference lower in rate?
higher RR. Yeah, that's my for me for me
basically yes is the answer to that
Dave. Even though I show a high win rate
um like I talk about
a lot of those are break evens but if
you joined me on stream last week you
would have seen we had multiple 100 250
point trades together. So but we will
only get that when the market conditions
are there for it. We won't get it all
the time. somewhat surprised we've
ripped as hard as we have today.
Exactly Dean. If this then that. If if
this happens then we do this. If this
happens then we do this. That's how the
market moves. Not we do this. No such
thing.
Right. So holding gray. So if they keep
holding this they are going to try and
rotate in towards these 890s. I will
tell you uh the buyer still got stuck at
900s. 95s is key, but 900s is where we
have like some outlying delta. Let me
have a look up here on level two.
Where's 900? Yeah. So, you can see if
you come up to let me pull this over.
Can I pull this over to you guys? If we
pull this up to 900s, you can see this
here a 380 lot and a 2998 lot. All
right, those are buyers, market buyers
who got stuck up there. That's the big
level. Sellers will not want it above
that. They will want to use their pain
to move lower. So 900s is a big big
level.
Does trading view value high value low
point control move slightly different if
you switch from 30 to 5? Yes, it does.
It does. You want to be on the lowest
time frame chart possible. Uh which is
why I do my daily levels based on a one
minute chart. This is so after today I
mark them out based on this. Right. But
if you're looking at uh like the
weeklies, yes, I do it on the hourly or
30 minutes. Sometimes it's probably a
little bit off, but it's there or
thereabouts.
The same as you, I take multiple break
even trades, but then I get three or
four R and have no issue taking profits
one to one slightly more. There you go.
Exactly. I think that's the best way to
do it. For me personally, that's how I
like to manage my trades. I don't want
to look for
no these traders who look for 20 ticks
or like three or five points. Like I
just I It's too stressful, man. It's too
stressful.
How apt are you to trade back into a
fair value gap when it presents
immediately? I mean, I don't trade fair
value gaps, so
So that's not what I do.
Did I take the trade today? Yeah, the
main trade I took, where did I get
knocked out? Somewhere here to here or
was it here to here? I got Can't
remember where it was now. I have to
look on my screen. One of these shorts.
Had a couple attempts at shorts.
Waiting to see if there's another setup.
Right, while this sets up, let me use
the bathroom. Come right back. Let's try
and get another 250 likes, 260 likes. I
want to give away um
course uh introduction course.
So start holding this gray box. We just
talked about this. So those of you
wanted to be long this gray box after
this buy signal, you're looking for this
move into here. Like I talked about 900
is a big big big level where the buyers
got stuck over 900. We can see a
squeeze. 920s will be your target over
900. Here's the 900 lot. Right. So,
we're coming into 900. Now, this is
where the buyer got stuck. We talked
about him being stuck. We talked about
this player up here being stuck right
here. This blue line. You see this blue
line? This is the player that's stuck.
If you get above him, we can think about
920 all the way up here. But 920 is a
big level that shorts will not want this
market to trade through. All right, I
will be right back. Let me use the bar.
All right. So, you can see that player
at 900 still holding the market up. So,
he got break even on that push up back
down to gray box. So, gray box to gray
box rotation again.
Overall conditions are pretty bullish
here if we think about how we build out.
But we have to see this this this was
the tag. We talked about the 900, didn't
we? We talked about the guy at 900.
So, do they hold between here and allow
this to 920s or do you now fail this
shelf after letting this guy out and do
you come back to here? Those are the
opportunities.
Those are the current opportunities.
Right. How are we doing for likes? Can
we do some giveaways?
Okay, back down to uh pointer control.
This gray box again,
I'll announce it live. Big um penoodle,
don't worry.
Blake, thank you. Thank you for joining.
How to deal with a fair value gap and
how to find it. I mean, okay, you're
adamant on using it. It's just this gap,
right? It's between two candles.
It's not how I trade, but there is
actually an imbalance in this one. All
right. So, it's a three candle
structure. That's all an it's all a fair
value gap is. When do they work best?
When you've seen a squeeze. You see this
candle here? One candle, large candle,
engulfing candle, second candle. It's
the imbalance left between the two.
There was a genuine imbalance in this
one. So, we're What does it mean is the
other way of putting it. If we've
ripped, there's lots of limit orders sat
in this price waiting to support the
bid, which is also in a shelf, right?
So, they're hoping that it comes down so
they can get filled to come up.
That's how you would use it. It's more
accurate if you're using orderflow. All
right, they're coming back again. So,
they held gray box, gray box to gray
box, gray box to gray box. Think about
what we are starting to shape up here.
Think about this liquidity. Think about
how they came down. Think about how we
build out this liquidity. Think about
what it opens if we run the stops. Think
about where you're trying to get to.
920. All right. And then if you get
lucky up here to the 26,000s, right?
We've drawn this out numerous times.
You're starting to see when we were down
here saying how we might shape up.
They're trying to do it.
Massive level is the 900. Okay? I cannot
tell you enough. It's a huge level. 95
is also a big level, but 900's massive.
You get over 900, you've really got a
shot. You have really got a shot.
Dave, love the way you trade, brother.
Order flow has been a huge help to me
these last few months. I'm closing up my
personal and props on a positive note.
Best of luck. Nice work, Dave.
Congratulations. Glad I'm glad it's
helped.
Thanks for today 50 points. Awesome. All
right, watching these 900s.
Watching ES into IB high VIX new low of
day.
You're in short. Do I think you should
hold this trade? Probably not. Well, I
don't know where you're short from for a
start.
We're starting to build quite a big
P-shape here. I think about the profile.
Building a huge P-shape is very bullish.
Where do I think it wants to go? 920 and
then up into these if it can. If we
can't get above the 900s, it would be a
fail break, but I wouldn't be shorting
up into this. I'd be waiting to see if
it fails and then leaves players
trapped. At the moment, it's not leaving
players trapped, is it? The counter
trend leg we tal about. There's the
counter trend leg. Held the pivot.
Remember that was a 61 fib from here to
here, right? And they're buying this and
they're trying to do that inverted head
and shoulders. Look for that squeeze
out. If they're going to do a squeeze
out, we can measure this
to see where they could possibly go to
and if it lines up with 920 or one of
the other levels.
Trying to get at the moment 980, but
measured move will get you to previous
day's high.
Possible.
It's possible.
Oh, Aaron, that's absolutely incredible.
Aaron is still holding longs from New
York. Congratulations, Aaron. That is
absolutely massive.
Trader Rick, thanks for joining.
Appreciate you.
Use my code for Apex. Oh, thanks very
much. Yeah, like all the codes are down
beneath, guys. You'll see it running
underneath. Helps me do this stream for
free. So, code FCT for all your favorite
prop firms. uh other than uh for
take profit, you need to use code flow
zone there, but all everything's
underneath chat, right? So, if you want
to support the stream, you can buy a
membership for $5 a month like some guys
have kindly done here, or you can just
use uh one of my codes that just allows
me to do this stream for free.
Let's
still try and build out this liquidity.
Gray to gray. Gray to gray.
Hopefully it makes sense for you guys,
especially those who are new.
What volume profile am I using? This is
anchored volume profile. Anchored volume
profile. Anchored to the New York Open.
Got 200 points today. 520 * 5 PA. Adding
footprint has really helped me a ton. It
feels impossibly easy now. Nice work,
man. Nice work.
Can we expect more downside? Um,
it is possible, but uh let me just
measure this on a daily.
We're right into the 618 on a daily.
There's one thing I want to be aware of.
All right, so we're not in uh let me let
me take you over here. One thing I'm
aware of just right now, obviously we're
coming into this shelf, is this from
last week's high week to the current low
of day, right? We're trading right into
the 618. Is downside possible? It is. Is
upside possible? It is. Why do I not
have a bias? Because we're boxed in. All
right, we're not seeing acceptance under
here. We're not seeing acceptance above
here. All right, I'm willing to play
longs above here. I'm willing to play
big shorts above here as in bigger
positions. Uh in here is just a range,
right? We're still inside that range
until we prove otherwise.
At the moment on the day, we're very
bullish, very very bullish, but we're
into a big level. I wouldn't want to be
a buyer up here. Um but it's got to get
through 900.
What do I think the condition? What do
you think are the conditions required
for lower prices? You will need trapped
buyers.
All right. You're going to need some
like serious trapped buyers, aren't you?
Even if we're thinking about here on
like a five minute,
right? You're going to need to see
something like a drive up where you have
uh market buyers, whether they be
breakout buyers or stops popped. And
then you're going to need to see this
liquidity here left for that trade
downside. Until that point, you're not
going to see it at the moment. There's
no buyers stuck. Remember, buyers been
entering all the way up. Everything's
fine, right? They're trying to get up
into here.
But if you see a failed breakout and
then we leave a shelf, we leave the
shelf, then maybe you get this move,
this reversion. Doesn't have to happen
today. It might be tomorrow, might be
Wednesday, might never happen at all. We
don't know, folks. Okay? I can only
trade what sets up in front of me. Same
as you guys, you can only trade what's
in front of you. Doesn't matter what you
think, matters what happens. All right,
we just tapped into that trap bar at 900
again. All right, so that big delta that
we've talked about, you can even see it
on bookmap. We drove right into his
level
uh right here into the 900 and we've
just trapped a little bit more there
again. So if we come up here on the left
hand side you can see 379 lot and a 377
lot with huge amount of transactions but
delta is stuck at 900. Buyers are still
stuck at 900 and above right now. Simple
as that.
How can I get your indicators on Trading
View? Um,
which indicators? The Flowzones. Uh,
just head over to my website
flzzontrader.com.
Right. 800 likes. Let's give away a
course. I haven't set it up yet. So,
don't do anything yet, guys.
Give away a very, very introductory
course. If you're brand new to trading,
if you've never traded before, this is
good for you. It's only 2 hours long.
It's very, very, very, very basic, okay?
If you know what you're doing already,
you're going to find this is way too
easy. You can always give it to a
friend, but does give you a little
discount on the main course, right? So,
just type course once in chat. Please
only type it once. Please don't spam.
You will be pulled out if you spam. Just
type it once. Just try type course and
we will pick a winner at random.
Jerome, I've just seen your email. I'm
just replying to you now. Get you in the
team. Sorry, my friend. Just seen it.
Looks like they're going to try and lift
900. They're having another go here to
come through 900 and squeeze this
through 920s and above right now.
Give you guys like another 30 seconds
here and we'll pull the winner.
What is the code for 90% discount Apex?
FZT is the code. Links are down below.
FCT.
Okay.
Going to pull this winner. Five, four,
three,
two, and one.
Mr. Slim.
Mr. Slim, are you here? Mr. Slim
ZV6S.
Mr. Slim, let me know you're here in
chat.
Nice. Congratulations, Mr. Slim. Okay.
All I need you to do is send me an
email, please. I'm making a note of your
name. info@flonenttrader.com.
And I just want you to send me a
screenshot of you logged into your
YouTube, please. All right. Just a
screenshot of you logged in
and then I know it's you.
Yeah, guys. There's no there's no Apex
giveaway right now. It's answering
someone's question. What is the volume
profile indicator? Anchored volume
profile. Anchored volume profile.
Anchored volume profile. You guys are
jumping the gun. You're going to have to
wait.
We need more likes.
Okay, there's the flush. I can't get
through 900. back down to this gray box
again. They just go back and forth and
back and forth until they make their
mind up. Back to point of control on the
session again. 20 minutes left.
Hello from Afghanistan. Hello my friend.
Boxto box again. Yeah, if they lose this
box, we probably come all the way back
down here. So they failed 900. 900 is
the big level. That's what we keep
talking about. Buyers are stuck at 900
right now.
So you'd be watching if they lose this
and rotate here. If they lose this whole
thing, right, then there's a bigger
flush in this market.
They'd have to lose the whole thing
back to PC.
So, this pullback, do they absorb this
pullback now
into this 50% kind of mark and try and
get back upside again? It's possible.
It's very possible.
Vick's trying to find a little bit of a
bid.
Messy up here, I would say.
right into that VPO again.
Watching this take to see if they sell
through these 60s because this is where
the guy keeps trying to absorb it here
or hereabouts on that pullback.
Still absorbing in these gray boxes.
Delta's diverging them. Have a look.
Uh, we're just sideways really.
No, it's okay. Like, you're not seeing
delta break that old low. We're not
breaking this old low.
It looks the same to me. There's a lower
high. We haven't broken out. It's It's
there or thereabouts. There's no huge
divergence yet in my mind on Delta.
Thanks for joining. Thanks for joining
all the new members. Fantastic.
And we drive back up towards uh this
next gray box again. And again, they're
going to try and get through the 900s.
That's where they need to get through.
If they can't get through the 900s, they
will continue to be stuck up there. The
uh buyers
is underneath previous day low. Kind of
messy at the moment. Do I trade every
day? Yeah, I do. Monday to Friday, 9:15
Eastern. all the way into lunch.
Am I a male or female?
[\h__\h] incredible.
I don't think you should be trading if
you can't work that out.
the indicator on the right side. Now,
it's it's a tool. It's not even if you
come up to here, right in here, go into
projections, anchored volume profile.
It's a it's for free. It's a tool. It's
not custom.
So, anchored volume profile. It's a
tool. It's not even an indicator. It's
just it's a drawing tool.
Yeah.
Oh, they were asking someone else,
right? Yeah, it's still pretty weird to
put in a chat.
Did you go over the awards show last
night? I haven't I haven't watched any
of it, actually.
back down again. This is the same level
I keep talking about the 60s. If they
don't absorb this, there's a flush down
here into 40s and 30s again. So, it
really depends what they're trying to do
with this at the moment.
And this is like the p it can still be
the pullback. The fact that we're not
breaking 900s is good for sellers, but
the structural is better for buyers
right now. The fact that we're not
breaking the 900s is good for sellers.
We're leaving buyers trapped up here,
but it's uh when I look through here
right now,
right, there is a shove down into here,
but we'd have to let go of absolutely
everything.
That's your first lower high and failed
breakout, but they can still scoop this
and go. So, like overall structure
remains bullish on the day. Remember the
high of day was the 61 fib based on the
daily that we went over. Here we go. So,
they're back into this previous week
point of control again. Do they flush
this now down to 40s is the question or
do they rescoop?
They're still trying to protect this
area. It's the same area
down into the 40s possible here if they
uh want to fill these imbalances.
Possible.
We could go gray to gray. Awkward inter
lunch. 15 minutes left.
Remember, I'm always looking at the
higher time frames. If you go from uh
high of week last week to the low of the
GlobeEx low, you will see that we are
already in uh quite an interesting area.
Right? If we do this
right right into the 61, this is the
golden pocket that they will want to
sell. So, it just depends. They start
here or do they let it through into the
26100s.
Big big question. But I don't know if
they do this today, but I'd imagine in
the next few days something like this is
coming and then the question is, do they
bid back up or is that just a huge stop
hunt and a collapse?
Why don't I trade ES? Why should I trade
ES? Everyone wants to say like, why
don't you do this? Why don't you do
this? You give me a reason why I should
if the volatility is here really good.
And if I'm reading it really well, why
should I look at another screen? That's
that's what I want to know. Why? I like
the personality of the asset I'm
trading. Here you go. Into the 40s like
we just talked about. So into these
imbalances
all the way down to 33s. And then this
gray box again can be present. We can
move this up about a little bit into
here. Gray box to gray box again. And if
we get acceptance under all of this,
there's a bigger fade. All right. If we
if they leave, if this is a fail
breakout, remember that's a 61 fib on
the daily. That's a fail breakout. If
they're stuck over 900s, if they let go
of this, this is open, but they need to
trade underneath all of this. Otherwise,
they can range here all day long. Right?
We can see it's a big Pshape, right?
They can range here all day long
and the volatility and range is too big
on ENQ for you maybe not for me. That's
a personal choice, isn't it? And surely
if the volatility is big and the range
is good, surely that equals opportunity.
So surely what you're saying is you need
to have good risk management.
Now, if you've got good risk management
and a good understanding of levels, ENQ
is a great asset to day trade. Great
asset to day trade. I would say the
spider is a better asset to swing trade.
You're going to get knocked out less.
You just got to understand the
personality.
But you do what's right for you.
Okay,
we bid this back up towards these 60s
again then. Here we go. There's the bid
back up to 60. We got 10 minutes left.
Uh, yes. Right here. There you go.
So, ticks per row. Two ticks per row. If
you want it on number of rows, I would
set this to 1,000. And then I change
this to width to 20% and placement on
the right. All right, that's it. Simple,
simple, simple. All right, here's the
bid back to 60s and this same area
again. And if they don't resell this
area, then we're going to go back to
80s. And through 80s, we're going to try
and revisit 900s and 920s.
They're rolling fibs. Uh what's your
name? Danib.
Rolling fibs. They're EMA rolling fibs.
I call them my flow zones, but they're
rolling fibs.
No worries, man.
All right. Box to box. Box to box.
building liquidity about 100 points
liquidity being built out up here. If
you're a range trader, this might be
your bread and butter. Uh this is not an
area I want to trade in right now. All
right. Certainly not an area I want to
long in, is it? Do I want to long here?
Right. No, this is not an area I want to
long in. We're probably due a pullback.
It doesn't happen have to happen today.
If we get above and base, then I'll
consider that long uh afternoon or
tomorrow. More preferable down here.
this short down into here. And if they
base, I'll consider that long as well.
If we lose this, then I'll consider that
short. I want to be very careful trading
in this range here. Anyone that read the
newsletter, this is the same thing as
last week. We want to be very careful
trading in here. We can trade away from
it. We can trade away from it. This is a
liquidity building part of the market,
right? And it's not just from this day.
We can go back here. Look at all these
previous weeks. Oh my god, look at all
the liquidity being built at this area.
Okay, I don't want to be the liquidity.
I want to use the liquidity. That
requires patience.
Been stuck here for a long time now
since uh November really.
I just bought take profit trader. Do I
have to make a trade for five day and
pass the email before I go pro if I pass
it? I don't understand what you're
saying, buddy. All you've got to do is
you got it's a 50% consistency rule,
right? So, you can pass it in two days,
but you need to just rotate like a micro
3, four, five, day three, four, and
five. But you uh you can't pass it
quicker than 5 days. You can take as
long as you want to pass it.
What are the most important key levels
for me? uh untest untested areas of
volume probably. So daily and weekly
levels the higher the time frame the
more important it is. So highs and lows
and gap fill closures and uh and then
big volume levels.
Do I know how the 30% thing on Apex
works? I always get confused. I get a
message rule my broker. Do you mean the
uh 30% consistency rule? Yeah, your one
winning day, one winning day cannot be
worth more than 30%
of your uh overall profit. That's how it
works.
That's very kind of you. That's very
kind of you. Um Joano, thank you for
saying that.
Do I think big orders on bookmaps are
better to think about as magnets for
price as potential areas for bounces?
It's a good question. Uh we can use them
as liquidity drives. Like they're just
resting liquidity. They don't always
work that way. Uh I use them to see like
are they serious? Like this person is
not serious. They're like they're
jostling up and down, right? Look at the
flashing on the book map above me.
They're just jostling up and down in
price. I don't see these guys as like
serious participants. But there was a
serious bid on the market today who has
stepped in numerous times chasing price
up. All right. So there have been some
serious bids on the market today. But
you can use them as magnets, but you
can't guarantee we're going to get
there. What you can use it is as
definite liquidity. It's absolute
liquidity. All right? So we can use
highs and lows as areas of estimate
where liquidity might be. But on using
bookmap, you actually know where that
liquidity is.
Mr. Just info@flowzontrader.com
please mate. info@flowzonerader.com
30% draw down. Oh, it's the same thing.
You just don't you can't lose more than
30%. It's it's the same thing in one
given day.
All right, Jake. Yeah, I I'll try and do
it today. M m Jake, you got to
understand I'm going through a lot of
stuff right now. I'm having to, you
know, look after members of the course
and trade and make my own money and
family stuff and you want me to listen
to music.
I'll do what I can, bud, but uh I am
limited on time. Okay, so inverse head
and shoulders are going to come back for
this 900 again for another attempt to
get through the 900s. They get through
900, you will get 920. Vick's new low of
day here.
Where in bookmap do I see the big
orders? Resting orders are the
horizontal lines and uh big orders which
are filled on the on the book. Market
orders are the bubbles.
Nice, mate. Good work. How do you get
volume profile to stick to the right
hand side?
We just went over it. You have to use
anchored and you need to do placement to
the right.
Right, here's the squeeze. So, back up
towards the sort of 900 level is where
they are attempting to get to. All
right, we're in the range being built
out here. You can see this sort of area
here. They're trying to get to 900s and
then 920s for that break if they can do
it. But you are in a big old box here.
100 point box right right here. This is
where you are. This is your rotation.
You've gone box to box to box to box
maybe to box. If they find acceptance,
it will have to be over 900 920. But on
a daily, you're right into a 61 fib.
They're trying to lift it into these
900s at the moment. So, some of you
saying you're long from down here. You
look pretty good. So, I'd just be very
careful as you come into here. If you
get through 900 and you get through high
of day, I would definitely be taking a
partial and then you're looking for 920.
I would say that there is a chance to
get up here. We did the measured move.
Remember, there is a chance. Doesn't
have to do it. Doesn't have to do it
today, but if they're going to complete
the measured move, it lines up perfectly
with that previous day high into 26,020.
It's possible. It's possible. Not
probable. It's possible. They've built
out a huge amount of liquidity here. If
they get a break and a hold, it's
possible. But you're getting very close
to lunchtime now. 3 minutes to go.
So here they go. They're trying to get
through this sellside imbalance here.
Break of 90 should get you up to 900s.
Here you go. So coming up to the 900s.
Through the 900s, you're looking at
920s. I would take a partial for the
break of high of day. You need to get
through the 900s. And if you get through
that, then this is where you're going to
try and go, right? So if those of you
who bought dips here, the only other
option now you would need a base above
this to do this. All right. So those of
you who bought dips here, I would take a
partial here and hopefully you get this
move. Just be very careful of a clear
out and a fail, which is why you're
going to lock some in
what the blue and turquoise waves and
the green one. This is my deep flow zone
pullback. These are rolling fibs. So the
deep flow zone pullback. These are
people that play deep pullbacks. They
will offer they will bid on this like
deeper pullback zone and people are
playing momentum are playing the lower
cloud. Okay. So you're watching these
900s.
Nothing's changed. Remember the buyer
has been caught at 900. We can see him
on the tape there. 377 and 379. That's
the size of the lots. So you've got
almost 800 lots who have been caught at
900. If he gets left out, lifted out I
should say, then you might get a break
of high of day. And then you want to
watch into sort of the 18 and 20 level.
VIX new lower day. You look good. Those
of you who are long, just manage your
position carefully. You're coming up
into lunch in 2 minutes. Here we go.
They're going to try and get you up into
these 900s now.
Here you go. There's the spike into 900.
So, they've cleared him out. Make sure
you're locking some in. ES new high of
day here, right? Make sure you are
locking some in here. The only thing
left now is 920 and then up here. Uh I
don't think we get above this 26,020. So
920 and then there's 100 points uh if
they can base, but this might be the
edge. Remember this is the 61% fib on
the big daily. So you have only got this
left. Otherwise, you should be out a
decent size of your position through the
900s. See that spike through 900 and
instantly back under it. You need it to
get back above 900 if you're holding.
Closed at 900. Yeah, nice. I would say
you can you can hold like a little
runner in case you get going, but you
want to move your stop positively up.
Like so if any of you bought the dips,
you know, gray box to gray box again,
isn't it? So you you'd want this to hold
74 75s now, right? But you're into
lunch. So the rotation can be here again
or they can hold this low volume node
and ideally they do this for you. 20 is
the level and then through that here
you can see we cannot get a close
through 900. We would have now we've
just added
even more b um bullish players trapped.
See this big blue line? This is where
they're trapped. All right. And if we
have a look here
we'll probably see there you go. An
imbalance left out there. So they they
keep buying up here and getting stuck.
They need to find acceptance through
this. Through this, you're going to go
920, right? Through this high day,
you're looking for 920. So if you're
holding runners, you're looking for 920
and then 26,020.
920 and then 26,020.
I'll stay with you a couple more minutes
just so we can manage this trade for
those of you who are in it.
Thanks, R. Cooper. Appreciate that,
mate.
All right, here you go. So, can he bid
over gray box and get to 920 and then
26,020?
920 and 26,020. You're almost there. New
low day, Vick. Still going lower.
This looks like a very good ABCD type of
breakout pattern on a fivem minute on
the QQQ here. It's got a shot at going.
Just mean need to be very careful of a
fail break, a swipe of 920 and a duck.
Here you go. So here comes the 920
coming up. So make sure it's right here.
So it's actually 18 is the actual exact
level. So you want to be taking a
partial into this. So 920 was almost
there. Two ticks short. We hit 1950. And
the only thing left is for you to hold a
runner all the way up to 26,020. All
right. They've done the damage. They've
done the damage. There's a 100 point
rotation in here. Failed to break lower.
They held. They never even did a
pullback here for you to buy. But there
we go. TP1 well TP1 900 920 TP2 and up
here TP3 now you can hold for a 100
point lift here right based on the
measured move based on the previous day
high it is possible it's also possible
they do a failed break so for the
afternoon if you're going to hold you're
looking for a measured move into this
previous day high basically 26,020
if they do a failed break where would I
not hold be beyond if they pop up here
and fail under here do not rebid it All
right, be done with it because they can
just take all their profits off, right?
If they pop and fail, they can take all
their profits off into end of day.
Remember, we're very thin, right? We're
very thin down here. This is a straight
leg up and then sideways. So, if they
fail to continue and they lose this
consolidation, they will drop it. So,
you do not want to be short on this
until we leave volume. And we're not
doing that. We've just created a ton of
volume. We're using it at the moment.
Y 2020. Uh previous day value area high
based on Ninja Trader. All right. So
previous day value area high right here.
So that's what we've just swiped into.
And then up here is previous day high.
This right here, previous day high. So
920 is previous day value area high.
Previous day high is 26,020.
those. That's why
I know I have previous day value high
down here, but it's different on Ninja
Trader for whatever reason. So, I
respect both at both key levels. They've
both been respected.
The one Dave 855 entry, 955 exit for me
locked in partial profits. 855 entry.
So, you were long probably on this side
of it, which would be a good long. So,
dip reclaim hold 855 and you're looking
for 955. You're looking for 100 point
move, but you've locked in partials.
Really good. Nice work. I' I'd move your
stop up in the money now. No matter
what, you don't want it to come under
this now where you entered long. You
don't want it under this shelf. Any back
test, ideally it holds here or holds
here. So, you can make sure that you're
going to lock in money on that runner no
matter what.
Possible short. The only possible short
will be a fail break if they trap
buyers. You're not seeing that right
now. Remember, buyers are now in control
from that 900. Remember the delta we
talked about a million times was 900 we
talked about here. All right, buyers
have been stuck above there or at there
all morning and it kept getting stuck,
kept getting stuck. Now you've gone
above them. So if we find acceptance
above it, what does that mean? Well, no
buyer is stuck. So why would you want to
be short if there's no buyer stuck,
right? Okay, if they're all in control,
then you don't want to be short, do you?
Right. This whole premise that newer
traders have or it's up too high.
It doesn't matter. Or it's into a key
level, it doesn't matter. Like it's what
happens after that, right? We mark out
the level. What happens next? What's the
reaction at that level?
Really nice, folks. Okay, how many of
you are here? Can we get a few more
likes, please, guys? And then we're
going to give away an Apex account. It
is lunchtime. I really want to give a
Apex away Apex account away to you guys.
Okay. So, what we're going to do,
code FCT, that's the code to use for
most the prop firms. You want to use
code FCT. Always get you the best sale.
Other than take profit trader, use code
flow zone. If you type FCT in chat right
now, we will pick one of you at random.
You only need to type it in once. Please
don't spam. Just type it in once and one
of you will be picked at random.
still absorbing up here. It's doing
okay, but uh you want to be very very
very careful up here
that's left on the bits trade into and
just zoom out on there. Yeah, VIX coming
right back down under that channel.
The next level on VIX I'll be looking at
is those 16s
these out the rest of the week while you
guys are entering that competition. All
right.
All right, picking this winner now.
Five, four, three, two, and one.
Evan
Vit Vitinho. Is that right? Vitinho.
Evan Vitterinho,
the winner of the Apex account. So, Mr.
Slim won the course. Evan won the Apex
account. Are you here, Evan?
Hey, nice. That's me. All right. Same
thing, Evan. All I want you to do,
please email me
info@flowzoneontrader.com
and just send me a screenshot of you
logged in just so I know it's you. It's
not someone else. And then I will sort
you out with a free Apex account. All
right. Happy days. Congratulations.
Congratulations.
All right, guys. That's that's pretty
much it. So, uh, very very bullish
action today. What I would be looking
for for the next day, well, like we
talked about, if you're going to
complete the measured move, those of you
who are long, if you're going to
complete the measured move, you're going
to need to try and get it all the way up
to 26,000. I would have locked in most
of my profit already for that squeeze
into 20 like we talked about. Where, if
and where would I be short? Well, this
is your range rotation.
All right? And if we develop a huge
amount of volume here and we leave this
volume, doesn't have to be today, this
might offer a short down into 700s and
beyond, that'll be something I'll be
looking for for the next few days if we
leave volume. Otherwise, we're going to
keep lifting up into these key levels.
All right, we're just going to keep
lifting and lifting and lifting and
lifting. At the moment, all we've done
is build out this. This is like your
typical ABCD kind of pattern. All right,
this can continue. This can continue.
They are very strong on the bid here
this morning. The moment they reclaimed
that was extremely aggressive. Kind of
hard to get involved in that. I would
have loved that kind of move there. This
kind of move here that we've done, I
would have loved down here. That's like
my favorite kind of move to get long on
these kind of plays. But there we go. It
is what it is. We'll be back tomorrow.
Uh those in Discord, I will pop in in
this afternoon and we can see what we
get. But again, I would just say manage
your positions. You can see how we just
held 900. Like we talked about, buyers
are in control of the market. There is
zero reason to be short on this right
now, guys. I cannot say it enough. There
is zero reason to be short on this right
now. Um, this is going to keep lifting
until they are done with it. Um, did I
place a trade? Yeah, I had uh not bad
today. So, so not bad. There we go. So,
so
and we'll just see see if we can get up
here. Some of that was overnight, by the
way. Should say some of that was made
overnight
um on the on the big account.
And I'll see you guys uh tomorrow night.
9:15 uh all the way into lunch as
always. Please make sure you join me
early. Make sure you mark out the key
levels off the newsletter. They will
come in useful for you this week by the
looks of it. All right, peace and love
everyone. Thanks for joining as always.
And uh be kind to each other. Use hard
stop. See you tomorrow. Peace out.