Morning
everyone.
Happy Friday.
>> Woo. Let's get that off. Happy Friday.
Happy end of week. Happy end of month.
We have had a massive week on stream.
All right. Absolutely huge week on
stream. Lots of new people turning up.
We've had a lot of big big winners. We
are not going to give back our week and
our month on a Friday. All right. Rule
number one. Worst time to lose Friday.
Why? Because then you have to sulk and
go into the weekend Saturday and Sunday
kicking and screaming at yourself
because of the errors you made. All
right? So, we're not going to do that.
Our job today, capital preservation. If
there's an opportunity, we are going to
take it. If there's no opportunity,
we're going to hang out and have some
fun. All right, so as always, we're
going to start off on the daily chart.
We can think about the weekly high and
lows. All right, you can see we're still
getting the Ballinger bads contracting.
Why? Because we had the ability to come
up here in base, right? We talked about
this move here. Did they do it? No. We
came up, we failed, we came downside, we
came up, and we're back into what? Into
this area here. All right. So, this is
very much a failed breakout. We're
actually waiting to see if we're going
to get continuation lower outside of
this or continuation higher. We've had a
failed breakout to the top side. So,
we're probably going to test this bottom
side. And if we start getting weak,
well, we can see this 200 day maybe
being looked at. And all these stops
here. But for now, we're going to
respect this range, right? Because this
has been here since November, right?
Beginning of November. Remember, we
filled the gap. That was our obligation
on the cues. We filled that gap. And
here is our box, right? And you can see
outside of this box, we have had no
success. All right, there's been no
success outside of this box. So, what
are we expecting? We are indeed
expecting rotation, right? Back inside
the box, we're going to expect rotation.
Even if we think about the weekly
pivots, right? This is your Sunday low
or Monday low, you can call it up to the
high. Guess what? We are opening right
at 50%. So even if you are going to be a
position trader and be like well I'm
going to risk the low to get to the high
or risk the high to get to the low at
best you are a one to one r there is not
very much edge right now in this market
until we see some follow through. The
other thing we need to be aware of is we
are stacked. If you look at the high
that we currently put in or the open we
can call it 5day. We drifted down to the
50-day. We found a bid on the 20day.
We're now stacked between these. You can
see these have got very very tight. This
is not what you want to see. All right,
healthy trending market will not have
that. It will have them stacked as waves
just like this. All right, 5day, right?
Top ballinger into 5day, 20-day is the
mean, lower ballinger and 50-day acting
as a big support system. All right, on
that lower Ballinger, we don't have that
right now. We are in a liquidity
building phase. It very much might be
that we collapse this market, but it
probably won't be today. Right. So,
we're expecting what probably as we're
opening up in an inside bar, as we're
opening up inside the week, as we're
opening up inside the range, we're
probably expecting some rotation in
here. All right. So, we want to be
careful with that. Moving down into the
hourly charts.
Make sure you guys can see all this. All
right. I've got this lined up right.
Yeah, that looks pretty good. All right.
Moving down into the hourly,
we can look at previous week's
developing profiles and current week's
developing profile. So, right now, this
is our current week developing profile.
You can see this level here is
absolutely pivotal. Okay, this block
here, what can we call it? We can call
this block basically, let's just call it
900 down to 850. All right, in that
block we have the current week or
developing week value area low. We have
the previous day value area high. So we
have the previous day point of control.
We can we have the previous week value
area high, right? Previous week value
area high. And we have the week before
that point of control. We can see this
area here. Look how many times we want
to test this area here. Look at this.
All these value area highs. This node
here, this point of control, this node
here. All right. This is a big area for
the market dating back to mid December.
Okay. Dating back to mid December. All
right. We're going back a long time now.
6 weeks. So we got to be understanding
of that. If we can hold all right, if we
are able to hold bids over 900, this is
the same trigger as those in Discord
took uh yesterday in the afternoon. If
we are able to hold bids over 900, you
can see we're thin here. It's possible
at that point they want to come and
retest up here into 26,000, possibly
even this point of control up here. All
right, developing weak point of control.
This was the relief. Anyone that got
long yesterday, remember I said the
final target if we got long down here.
All right, the final target would be
into what? This shelf here because up
here we have trapped buyers. All right,
we from Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday we
have trapped buyers. We flushed away
from them. All right, we expect that now
to hold as resistance. All right, so
this is the pain point. If we come up
here, all right, there might be a lift
from 900 up to there. you would expect
shorts to come back in play for the
rotation back down. If they don't come
back in play, and this is today or next
week, if we come up here and we start to
base, you best believe we're probably
going to go alltime highs because then
we will use this liquidity to move
higher. All right, so the first thing
I'll be watching today is can we find
acceptance over 900? If we can find
acceptance over 900, I'm looking for
that whole number 26,000, right? Right.
And if we get over there up into 2694,
26100 we just call it. I'm not expecting
the market to be able to move above
that. I'm expecting shorts to either
hammer us back down here or hammer us
back down here to the bottom side. Okay.
If we're going to lose the 850s,
right? So, if we're going to come down
here and reject this shelf, then we're
what? We're looking for the rotation
back lower. So, where's the next point?
Probably previous week point of control.
This node here. So if we lose 850s on a
retest, there's probably a move back
down to 700. If we lose 700, we have a
runner back down to 600. So we are going
to need to be available to play both
sides of the tape. This is available.
This is available. This is not an area I
want to trade in. All right, I do not
want to trade in 850 to 900. No interest
in trading in there. I will let everyone
else piss about in there become the
liquidity and if we leave that area we
can use it. The other thing I should say
and preface with this this a little poke
above 900 without basing is not a buy.
All right, that can easily be a trap and
a flush. Same as here. A little poke
under 800 that doesn't retest and stay
heavy is not a sell. That can be a
little poke under and a trap. All right,
we can trap each side of this like just
like here. So, we're going to be aware
of those. Let's have a quick look at
GlobeEx, which is just above us right
now, and uh see what we've got in here.
In fact, you know what I'll do? I'll
just put on a profile from Globex. Give
me a second.
I mean, just in case there's some key
levels that match up. There we go.
Right, there's our GlobeEx profile.
Here's the Asia high. So, Asia, we got a
drift down. We found a bid on. Guess
what? The 20-day we came back up to that
thick area and point of control value
area high. There was a fade from that in
GlobeEx back down to the Yep. 20-day.
Retested the previous week point of
control. Found a bid. Reheld 20-day back
up. You can see the rotation, right?
Failing here. Drift down 20-day. Recheck
point of control. Drift down 20-day.
Lose 20-day. Previous week point of
control. Back to 20-day point of
control. 20-day reclaim back to previous
day point of control. And you can see
the rinse repeat. All right. So, more
liquidity being built out in the GlobeEx
session. No edge there for me right now.
Okay, let's come up to this screen here.
And we're gonna have to get a little bit
of a move on here, guys. I'm sorry. Uh,
quick look for ES and the spiders for
you. You're basically looking at the
same story. Okay, that drive up and ES,
this is the same thing we just talked
about. Trapped buyers from this week are
trapped above here. There's the flush.
There's the retest. It stayed heavy.
This is now your range on ES. If you get
acceptance of follow through under this
right then you can dig for lower prices
looking for probably yeah 78s and maybe
back even into this cluster right down
into there into 830s but not necessarily
today but it's something we can
consider. Uh we can have a quick look at
the spiders and it will be the same
story. Yeah, same story. So 85 was the
gamma level. You can see we cleaned out
this liquidity at 85 found a bid. Same
story. All right, there's your range
here to here. That's the range that
we're currently in. So, you want edges
on range until proves otherwise. Same
story on the cues. It's going to be
exactly the same. There you go. Never
really got up into this pain point. We
only came into here. So, there's the
flush. There's the rebound. The question
is, do they sell this now or do we just
get stuck in here on the Friday?
Dollar um is trying to find a bid at the
moment. Actually, it's trying to curl
off these lows, but again, just one big
range. Very similar to the indexes,
right? We're stuck up here. Buyers are
trapped up here. So, that's the
liquidity build. Is this a giant bare
flag? We will find out by next week, I
would imagine. And we can have a quick
look at the VIX,
which is probably still in this channel.
Uh, let's just zoom this out a little
bit. Clean this up.
Yeah, still finding in this channel.
Still kind of getting stuck top side,
but we have found a bit of a bid the
last few days. So, I'll be watching some
of these areas. I'll clean them up on my
other chart right quickly. We got 5
minutes to go through the mag, right?
Apple held this key level uh that we
talked about yesterday. We can know that
this is now support. Had good earnings
yesterday, but uh obviously they didn't
like the guidance. So, there's a big
blowout on there and then Tim Cook
probably opened his mouth. I haven't
didn't watch the guidance, but I'd
imagine open his mouth and we get it all
back and we're just dancing in that
range. Nothing's actually changed there
on Apple opening up flat. Uh Amazon is
on a gap down. All right, you can see
this key pivot here. This is its key
area to hold right now on Amazon. It's a
big drive out. It is possible if we
start snapping under this. All right,
we're building liquidity. It can get
weak, might drag the market down. Goo
gapping down as well. Same kind of
story. There's your liquidity build. If
we start losing these areas, right,
here's your right shoulder. Left right
shoulder will be built in here. Sorry.
If we lose that, that's where weakness
will come. Uh Meta continues to be
strong, I would imagine. Yeah. So, a
slight gap down, but again, we are just
in a range here at Meta. Remember, I'm
long meta up like 25% on this now. So,
just looking to see if we can fill up
into there and I'll probably lock in
most of the rest of my profit.
Microsoft. All right, that is nasty.
That is a nasty one. All right, here's
failure to reclaim of the highs and
there's the giant sell. So, Microsoft
really stuck in this pivot. You'd be
watching 39s, so 40s to 50s really for a
resell on Microsoft. I would imagine
even if you you sell that and you cover
some into the lows and then wait to see
if you get underneath it. If it starts
reclaiming 50s, I wouldn't be risk off.
I'd say it's possible for a squeeze.
Nvidia gap down as well, but that is
very messy in its range, but holding up
pretty well right now.
Tesla trying to find a bid. Zoom out of
this a little bit. This has been messy
for the last week or two. Yeah, it
continues to be a bit of a mess. So,
back to the bottom side of its range.
There you go. That's the range since the
whole of this month on Tesla. All right,
it's just in a range until it finds
acceptance outside of the range. There
will be no continuation. So, you'd be
playing edges unless we break out and
retest. And the mag as a whole
doesn't look too good, does it? It just
looks a little bit messy since that
Wednesday pivot. Okay, let's have a look
just at some broader names quickly.
Oracle trying to find a bid, but again
underneath that range. Any back test of
70 to 72, I'd expect them to try and
sell Oracle. Uh Infl
coming back down to its pivot. So let's
see if they rebid that or if we just get
a collapse. Looks like very possible for
a collapse here
and then we might get the 70s on Netflix
that we talked about. AMD, yeah, pulling
back after that huge drive out the last
few weeks. So it's going to come back
and back test this kind of area here,
right? That's the expectation. Remember
breakout pullback. Question is then do
they rebid not if the market's weak they
won't.
Okay. So bias for today neutral bias in
a range
until we see otherwise. And uh remember
seven. What did I say? I'm going to have
to have a look at this again. Get this
off.
We will be watching trigger points of
900s and sort of 850s. 900s and 850s. So
there's the 800s right now. Is it 850s?
Just check this. 830s.
Yeah, there or thereabouts. What is this
level? No, don't need you.
Okay team market opening up in what?
Just over a minute.
Morning everyone. Morning. Morning.
Morning. Morning. Just seeing a couple
of uh you guys in stream. All right. Do
me a favor. Smash that like button nice
and early. Make sure you've gone through
your morning prep. We talk about this
all the time. Do not skip your morning
prep, right? You better be fit and able
to uh be present in this stream to be
able to take trades, mentally fit,
physically fit. Have you slept enough?
Have you drunk your water? Have you done
your meditation or your visualization?
Or if you're able to, have you been to
the gym or gone for a walk? All that
good stuff. It matters. I promise you it
matters, right? it really matters
and we will see how we go here.
Get my charts ready on Ninja. Making
sure they're all lined up. Okay,
it's probably no trade to start the day
for me today. probably just going to let
this uh play out and do what it is it
needs to do
and we will go from there.
Okay, here's the morning drive. Let's
see how we come up into these areas.
These 900s, remember key
these 900s key
into this sort of old supply block where
we got a bit stuck and we get thin
through there. I can we can think about
GlobeEx, but I'm going to wait to see if
we get acceptance above all of this.
Letting this do what it wants.
Spy coming up trying to fill its gap
right now. Q's trying to do the same big
drive. Gap fills all the way up here.
Remember this yellow line would be gap
fill. This is GlobeEx. So bunch of
liquidity up here. Remember this is the
edge where we talked about we kept
getting stuck in. So if we get
acceptance over all of this, if we pull
back and find acceptance over all of
this, then we can expect 26,000.
Otherwise, this can be a failed look
above. Again, this is why I don't want
to trade in this range that we're in at
the moment. I want to let this market
make its decision.
Let market make the decision. So failed
look above previous day high there.
getting trapped all the way back down to
point of control straight away. You can
see the choppiness to start the day
already. Very, very present.
Another 250 point day. We We'll see. We
got a few of those yesterday, didn't we?
Two. So, if you're joining me new on
stream today, we had two 250 point
trades together yesterday on stream.
Um, but we're end of week when lowering
the expectations. We did just wash like
quite a few stops here above the uh 904
90s.
So, we'll see. I'll give you a readout
on the MAC. Tesla 2.66% up. That's then
followed by Microsoft half a percent up.
After that, the weakness starts. Nvidia
0.15% down. Meta 1.63% down. Google
1.60% down. Amazon 1.21% down. Apple
1.80% down. So, failed. Look above the
900s. No base. Back down to the 825s.
Remember, this is the area of the other
side of the range. So, we've already
traded the range we talked about
pre-market. Sort of 825s up to the 900s.
Remember, this is our no trade zone. We
don't want to get stuck in here. I don't
want to trade these edges. I don't like
trading edges. If that's a bit of you,
for sure, go for it. You're talking
about 100 point rippers there out the
gate. Watch your ATR. Okay. Watch your
ATR.
I'm going to wait for us to move outside
of here. In fact, I'm going to remove
that and just watch this. Right. So, the
range we talked about pre-market already
come into effect. Right. We keep holding
around these sort of 800s, 825s and we
come up to the 900s and we're not
finding follow through over 900. So this
is our avoiding zone right now. This is
why we're leaving this zone alone.
VIX finding a bit of a bid in an old
pivot here. It's got gap fill potential
below as well. If it loses this pivot,
gap fill on VIX would be 1687. And that
will obviously be very bullish for the
market if the VIX does want to do that
gap though.
Okay, back up to current value area
high, previous day point of control. If
they resell this, there's probably a
retest down towards the 800s again,
which is coming now.
So, let's see if they give follow
through now underneath this. Looking for
this to see if they want to give follow
through underneath the 800s, underneath
820s to come back down into previous
week close. That's what we're waiting to
see if we're going to see that follow
through. Now,
don't want to trade in this range. So,
I'm going to wait either side. I'm
willing to play above this long and I'm
willing to to play below all of this
short if they base and retest the areas.
I'm not willing to play in between this.
Right. Not for me. That's not a trade
for me. Maybe it's a trade for you that
you guys like.
Back to the 900s then. They're still
chopping around.
Pop, drop, drop, pop. Yeah, both both
sides right now, Josh. Both sides.
They're just testing each side of this
range. Very, very tricky area. Like we
went over premarket. It's a huge area
dating back six weeks. Six weeks. You
got to understand that. Six weeks of uh
liquidity been built up around this
area. It's very, very thick.
Uh,
Victor, yeah, if you just purchased it,
once you go into there, it should tell
you what to email. Um, you you'll need
to email me from the email that you
purchased the indicator from and send me
your Trading View uh username and I can
get that done for you. If you've done
that already and I haven't seen it, I do
apologize
All right, back to these 900s. Remember,
we keep failing over these 900s for now.
So, it's still inside the dance. 100
point dance here.
100 point dance here.
So, what I was saying, folks, lower your
expectations today. We had a fantastic
day yesterday. We had a fantastic week.
100 point shop is crazy. It is indeed,
isn't it? Remember it is end of the week
and end of the month. All right? So,
we'll have to see how they position.
It's very possible uh that they if they
can get over the 900s and base they can
lift it like I said 26,000 and even
26,100 and then I expect sellers
probably come in up there. If we can
come underneath sort of the 825s and
base under that start to reject that
then that rotation down to 700 and even
5 575 is possible. So don't want to play
in here. Want them to make their
decision and we can join afterwards.
Understanding the conditions is so
important. Which days I want to attack
the open, which days I don't. Yesterday
once we washed, we got in very quickly.
I think it was 3, four, five minutes in
yesterday and we were ready to go.
Not today. That's not the type of market
condition we have today.
Vic starting to really get sold off
under that pivot now.
The range is nasty for a long time.
Yeah, I I agree, Mark Hammond. I agree.
I agree. We're right in the We're
dancing right in the middle of the daily
Ballingers as well. Like if you just
zoom out on a daily chart, go back to
the beginning of November. In fact, you
can go back beyond that. Go back all the
way to uh the the first week of October.
Go back to sort of October, what's this?
The 10th, right? We're still dancing
around that same kind of level. It's a
long time that we've been around here.
I still can't get through the 900s.
Let's put some volume on here. Now we
can see what we're playing with on this
opening print.
Right. So 900's still being sold.
And back down to the other side we come.
And if they don't bid this, then we're
looking for the fail underneath the 825s
or 830s. If they rebid this, then we're
going to go all the way back up again.
It's the rotation. Fun, fun, fun,
fun, fun. This is the market we're in.
We have to be patient. You do not want
to front run this.
Back up we go.
So, if you're a range trader, you should
be uh really enjoying yourself this
morning. You've probably made 100
points, 100 points, 100 points, 50
points, maybe 100 points back up. Crazy,
crazy, crazy.
far beyond my appetite.
Okay, back up towards the sort of 900
area again.
I'll say uh buyers keep getting stuck up
here into into around here. No
acceptance above it yet.
See if they lift. They're going to base
above here. Maybe there's a gap fill on
the spy. They can get above previous day
value area very high. Maybe maybe we get
this move here. We got to we're going to
have to see it do something like this.
And I would be taking partials on the
way. If you if we're going to see this
in a base above, you want to be very
very very careful.
And it's not something you want to
oversize in. It was not something you
want to add to a loser in. It is nothing
like that. Still no base above.
If I walk away go 900s. Yeah.
Or maybe I'll walk away and I'll come
back and it'll be 600 straight away. Who
knows? Who bloody knows, right? Who
knows?
After how they treated me yesterday, the
dirty dirty buggers yesterday letting me
uh go to the toilet and have back and
come back and you guys get a 250 point
move. It was actually more like a 400
point move if you held it to the end of
the day. Okay, here's the break above.
Here's the 920s. Let's see if they pull
back and hold now.
And if we can lift to 26,000.
Yes, going for that gap fill. Spy going
for that gap fill. Just just be aware of
this. We might not make 26,000 if the
obligation is for spy to fill its gap
and then fail. So you're looking for 94s
on the spiders if you're playing the
ETFs.
So 9350s now on the ETFs. you're looking
for 94s, I'd take absolutely take a
partial if you are long into that. This
dip's going to have to hold these 900s
or 890s. I would not hold beyond that.
If it's not willing to hold that, you
want to be out. You do not want to be
caught in a flush right back down the
820s. All right, so long from here. See
if we can get up into here. Watching the
ES very closely. Gloex, this will be a
TP1, by the way, into 34s, 34s, 35s.
There's your TP1 pretty much hit. Don't
be a dick for a tick like we always talk
about. And let's see if we can lift up
to 26,000. So TP1 TP2.
Move your stop up now. Do not get caught
in this.
Right. You do not want it under here.
TP1 here. TP2 is up here. That'll be 100
pointer if we get it.
It goes spy. Very getting very very
close. Another 304 cents on spy will do
it.
I would move your stop now up. You don't
actually have to. You can protect it
versus this, but it depends how much
size you've got. At least trim some on
that last push because you do not want
to get collapsed. If spy fills the gap,
if we do this and we fill the gap and do
that, you do not want to get collapsed
on. All right? You do not want to be
collapsed on.
Big sellers coming in here. Huge seller
just came in at 24. More sellers coming
in at 33s. Right. Just be aware of that.
That's some big big boy size.
So, we have an imbalance down to 900. I
will not let this come underneath.
Certainly don't want it underneath that
previous day value area high. We have
buyers join in on the tape at 95 and
900s and someone's trying to join in at
17s. Really don't want this to flush
much further down. Don't want to sit
through any pain here this morning,
especially this early in a volatile
tape. So, either way, going to lock some
in.
Yeah, 9:45 news. You're right. Um, PMI
9:45 Chicago PMI.
How long we got for that? Couple
minutes.
Couple minutes for that. Almost there.
You might want to move your stop even
tighter for for that. Don't want to get
flushed out.
Getting to
I'm getting ready to stop out on this.
Can always reload later.
Watching this value area high.
All right, out of this now. Don't want
to get washed 100 points down.
Just being protective cuz that can still
be a fail break above the 900s, right?
Can still be a fail break.
we start losing VWAP.
We can see this right here. So, this is
why I've stopped out. I can always get
back in. I'm going to probably wait for
the news now before I do that, though.
So, what do we get out of that? Not that
much.
How many points do we get out of you?
Not bad. Almost 40.
Almost 40. I'm out of this now. I'm not
risking this. I moved my stop up. Break
even.
Don't want to get washed in. Here we go.
Be very careful here, folks. If they
fail to see follow through upside,
there's very, very strong chance that we
get a giant wash down.
Remember, we're back into that range now
where I said I don't want to trade in.
ES failed to close its gap. So did the
spy. Spy came into uh like a supply
level. Would have liked to have seen one
of them close their gap just for
efficiency purposes.
news coming here soon. 40 seconds.
There's the wash back down. This is what
we talked about. This is why I cut that
trade.
Developing a shelf here. Now, you can
see the rotation here. 900 to 875 is now
key. They lose 875s, you probably get a
wash.
Remember, we're coming into news now. 20
seconds. After we get this news event,
we can think about what's next.
You lost big somehow. How do you lose
big?
It was just a trade from from here
straight up. That was it. And then I
said move stopped. Sorry to hear that.
Hopefully there was no bug in your
system or something. Okay, opening range
now set. We're right at the midpoint of
the opening range. Here comes the news.
We're starting to lose the bids here.
We're coming back down to that previous
day point of control again. We're in
that rotational zone where I want to
avoid trading.
If we're going to lose 825s,
800s, then we can trade back down to
700s as well. So, I'm willing to play
both sides of the tape outside of the
range.
Outside of the range.
Not in here. I really don't want to play
in here.
previous day point of control 850 being
tagged now
trading between the two VWOPS as well.
Very very ugly. All right, everything
going red other than Tesla. Let's see if
we get acceptance underneath all of this
for a wash. Now, if we've had that fail
break, if we come under here, find
acceptance under here. I'm willing to
play lower
as in I'm willing to short to play
lower. Previous day point of control
here
starting to find a bid here as well.
Back into old resistance level. Let's
see if they want to wash this. Let's see
if we can get going underneath value
area alone VWAP here. Here we go. It's
value area alone VWAP. Let's see if we
find acceptance lower or not. Still
they're bidding down there. So, still
into the edge of today's rotation. So,
right now 40s to 900s is the rotation.
60 point rotation in the day. Still no
acceptance underneath that. We'll wait
to find if we can find acceptance
underneath that.
Yeah, ABGO I mean 1.84% up. Nothing too
major. Most of if you look in the
broader market, a lot of it being sold
this morning. All those like I beta
names RTI, MBTS, and NQ
obviously IBIT, Cavana, PayPal, like a
lot a lot a lot of stuff being sold off
this morning.
Can have a look at the breadth. Let's
have a quick look on Bimbiz. How's
Finance is doing.
Yeah, the market's red, guys. Other than
healthcare, healthcare is the only one
holding up right now, which is why it's
holding up ES pretty well. ES just held
a bid into its New York open there, as
did we. We didn't quite get down that
low. All right, so they're rebidding the
rotation. Back to 900. Still no trade.
Just that first attempt where we cleaned
out GlobeEx.
Back towards the 900 now.
Do I look at gold or silver? Sometimes.
And see, silver's in that like 12% down
right now. Not touching it right now. I
will touch those trades, right? I will
happily trade gold and silver when
they're less crowded, when everyone's
forgotten about it. I'm going to treat
it like a small cap. When you guys when
retail have stopped talking about it,
I'll start a position for a long-term
short and
when it's done with for a fade right
back down.
Bounce on Dixie last night. Yep, it was.
It was indeed half% up. Trying to find a
bid on it, aren't they? was probably
from the comments of uh Trump and the
yen.
Come on, get out this range. Give us
something to do today. Give us something
to play with.
Yeah, I agree. Yeah, the orb is is doing
exactly what we expect. There's your
opening range high, opening range low.
These were the areas, right? So 900s,
800s, that's your rotation. Can we get
acceptance underneath?
Remember under sort of 835 we and we can
look for 800s. Under I would say under
790s that's where the bigger wash really
starts to accelerate. Under 790s we can
probably get a move down into the 700s.
Right now it just doesn't know what it
wants to do. That's why I said lower
expectations today.
Green dotted line, that's your 24hour
view up. All right, that's 24hour and
this is the New York view up. So that's
anchored to the 930 print. This one's
the 24hour one.
900 retest.
Someone's trying to bid this at 85s now.
Let's see if he actually walks up.
Yes, holding its New York open pretty
well. Google just gone red to green.
Microsoft gone red to green. Some of the
mag trying to find a bid. Nvidia not too
far away. Amazon not far away. Some of
that mag closing its gap trying to find
a bid.
Patience day today, folks. Just be very,
very, very patient. And it was similar
the last few days. We had to be patient
on stream, but if you stuck with me, we
then probably caught a net 6 or 700
points yesterday. All right, back above
the 900s. Do they find acceptance now?
Same question. We're asking the same
question. Is there acceptance for this
drive up into 26,000? We're back up to
that same level up here.
So, does this next pullback hold in and
around the 900s or they just going to
keep selling pushes over 900?
Yeah, I agree Raph. We made our money
for the week. I totally agree. Yes.
profile starts New York open. Correct.
Totally agree, Raph. That's why I'm
lowering expectations today. We had a
massive week. It was a big big week.
It's going to be one of my best months
for a long time. And remember, I didn't
even trade for the first 10 days or so
of this month. I was away with some
personal matters. Um, so we don't need
to force. Not every day is an A+ trade
day. Right now, this is not an A+ trade
day. It's probably going to be a B a B
scope trade day at best. At best. And
that's if we hold bids or hold offers
lower each side of this range. Right.
They're trying to build here versus 900.
VIX new lower day. VIX is going for gap
fill as well. So ES and SPY look like
they want the gap fill. Our gap fill is
this yellow line. If we can get going.
So there is a long here. If we can get
going above here. If we can get going. I
want to see it firm up and do this. All
right. If we can't firm up, if we can't
just keep holding this, then I'm not
interested in it because I do not want
to get dunked back on again just like
here. So, same kind of player we looked
at earlier. I want to see it firm up.
I want to see sellers get trapped.
Not seeing that yet. Is back down into
that previous day value high test. They
will need to bid here and firm up and
trap sellers. If they do, I'm
interested. But at the moment, I'm not
seeing that.
Some sellers starting to get caught
there now. How big were you? 115. Not
massive. Not massive.
Not convinced.
They're coming back into that 115 lot
around the 900 895. Let's see if they
absorb this tape or not.
No, they're bidding lower now. Don't
like it. Even if it goes without me, I
don't like this. I don't like it. Think
they sell through it. This is the level
where he got stuck. So, it's right here
at 95s.
Selling through. That's what I said.
Don't like it. Don't like what I'm
seeing on the tape.
Still selling down back into the range
again. Nothing's changed here, folks. It
might be boring for you guys. I'm so
sorry. I can't control the market. I can
only trade what's in front of me. Like I
said, wasn't going to Was considering a
dip by there, but the tape said don't do
it. So, I didn't do it.
Can I show where the gap is? Yeah. Right
up into here. 26,000 to 99999
25999 is the gap fill on NQ if it wants
to do it
guys you guys saying it's really bullish
because we reversed the move. Okay, like
you are incorrect. You are about as
incorrect as you can get. And this is
why. What did you reverse? Who is stuck?
What have you done? Nope.
Where's the pain point? Where are buyers
stuck? They are stuck here. All right.
We bid off this. This is not bullish,
guys. All right. This is not bullish.
This is the pain point. They want to
lift you here. If you get through that
and base, you're bullish until that
point. This can be sold off here. It can
be sold off here. It can be sold off
here. This can be a two-leg to build
liquidity to drive lower. Can absolutely
be that. It can also come up here and
hold and then be bullish. This right
here, this phase we're in here is a
liquidity building phase. To say that
this is bullish because we reversed the
move. What have you reversed? This was
your opening point yesterday. This is a
pullback. This is how the market moves.
It doesn't go straight down. we cover
here like we did yesterday which causes
this move to say this is bullish is a
awful statement that will get you very
very hurt. Very hurt based on what?
Based on absolutely nothing. You have to
respect the structure in front of you.
Do not convince yourself it's bullish
because we bounced off a key level. Like
markets move in waves.
All right? Don't convince yourself that.
I'm not trying to dig you you out who
whoever said that. I just don't want you
convincing yourself this is mega mega
bullish because it bounced. No. Right.
Just no. That's not how the market
moves. Right. We are in a neutral phase
of the market right now at best.
Neutral.
Still building. Still above the New York
open. Still can't fill the gap. Still
building in the same area. Go back to
beginning stream. We're still in the no
trade zone.
What are settings for volume profile?
It's an anchored volume profile. You
click on the 930 candle. Your opening
print. My settings. I have this set to
two ticks. All right. So, I like using
ticks. If you don't like using ticks,
you can use a th00and rows. 1,000 rows.
Mega chop and stop. Yeah, it is right
now. It is. Remember, it's end of month,
guys. end of month, end of week, we've
had big big moves already, right? Still
the same thing possible. If they can
base above here, if they can base above
here, we can try and go for that gap
fill. If they can't do that, there's
nothing to do. So far, every look above
here has been sold into, right? We're
not basing above here. Every look above
here, so far has been sold into. We're
not seeing this move here. Here, we did
not see that. We saw sellers come
through with follow through, which is
why I did not touch it. Right? And this
can snap soon. If they can't get going
soon, they're going to trap lots of
balls here. And under here, there can be
a rotation, right? There can also be a
failure like this. So, we want to be
very, very careful. This is the same
level we went over pre-market. So, I'm
trying to be as patient as humanly
possible right now.
How do I find define basing above
pulling back in? So, breaking out. So,
if we break out and we pull back in and
we base, we hold here and I see passive
buyers absorbing the tape. Right? Where
are we? If we see passive buyers
absorbing the tape above here,
right? If we break above and we see
passive buyers absorbing the tape and
sellers getting stuck, we're not seeing
that. Look, we're seeing aggressive
buyers get caught right now.
They keep getting caught. They keep
trying to step in and they keep getting
caught up there. every push up there.
This is looking very weak now. Back down
to the 860s point of control down here.
Sellers coming in there underneath 70s
so far getting caught. No acceptance
under 60s. 60s was a huge level where
big sellers came in earlier. This candle
at 947.
So no acceptance under that. The
rotation continues, guys.
Rotation continues.
Back to these 60s where the big seller
came. Can we get acceptance under this?
Do we start to lose the bid now? Are we
going to be more aggressive now is the
question. Tape looks pretty thin. I'm
going to tell you. Looks pretty thin.
All right, here we go. Here's the 50s.
Are we going to expand value now? We're
expanding value. Here's the VWAP now.
Does the next pull up, do they defend
50s and 60s and do we start selling
aggressively now? This coming back down
to the edge of the range now. I'm
starting to get interested in the short
for follow through. If we can do the
same thing if we expand and break out
and hold the pullback.
Here we go. So, watching these 25s down
to
even 790s and to see what we do. The
pullback now you would need sellers to
defend 60s, right? Sellers, you would
want sellers to defend 60s. Now, looking
for this continuation. Here comes the
low of day. I would expect here. Here we
go in this now. See how much we can
expand underneath. Trimming some into
this.
And let's see if we can get follow
through now. Down to previous week close
would be nice.
Can we get follow through
the moment? No follow through. Come on.
But Matt, why have you stopped? We've
got a bid at 800. We want to watch 800.
So going to trim some into 800. Buyer
stepping in here. I think we should
break him.
790 is big level. So already trimming a
lot of the position here. Remember big
level they need to defend now is 50s.
So now we will need to see rejection
here or I'm out.
Rejection here or I'm out because we
will resqueeze back up.
Good defense of 50 so far. That was the
level where the sellers came in. We need
to see follow through now for a new
lower day.
Watch your ATR. I'd be watching your
sizing today. These moves are very very
aggressive. So we need 50s to stay
heavy. We want a break of 800 for
continuation. I will cut above 50s and
if we can break uh 800 I'll be looking
is that 20 days. 752s would be nice.
Previous week close 738. Want to be very
careful here. Anything above 50s I will
cut. There was a seller and some
imbalance all the way up to 67 but I'd
rather cut and then read. So far we're
still defending it well. I will be
willing to be much heavier outside of
790.
We keep absorbing here. I'm not
interested. I want to see a break now.
We got to break lower now. We've tested
50s. We need to break lower. If we're
not going to do that, I'm going to get
out of the trade. Come on.
There's 25s. We know that this is a big
level. We talked about it pre-market.
Come on. Have you got any juice? I'm
just going to recheck this level here.
806s. We want a 800 break. 800 break
might open up the gate to 750s and then
700s and maybe even lower.
Sellers getting caught in that last
candle. Be very careful. Sellers getting
caught at 821s here. I will cut this at
850. Any break above 850, I'll cut. We
can always read if we reflush
out now. Taking that off. I I will read
if we reflush it. So locked in money
there no matter what.
Don't want to get caught back into the
same range. Same as the top side, right?
If fail breakout, if this is a fail
breakout, we go back into the chop. I
don't want to get caught in a squeeze
like this. This is exactly it. All
right. So play was from here down to
here. Partials, wait to see if they
stayed heavy. failing to stay heavy. We
come back inside this chop and we can
always read. So, we're having failure
above, failure below right now.
Retesting up here. We can read if we're
going to stay heavy. Now, I just didn't
want to get caught and give another
what, 50 or 30, 40 points back. Trying
to be disciplined here to see if we can
break down.
What percentage do I use? I use 70. Why
are you saying I don't use 70? It's
exactly what I use. Never change it on a
profile. Right back down to where these
sellers just last got stuck. Can we get
acceptance under 20 under 20 for a
re-entry now? 800's big level.
Here we go. Are they going to flush this
now? 20s, 20s, 20s, 20s. Do we move down
to 800 and snap it? Here we come. So,
looking to see if we can expand now.
Want to see 20 stay heavy at this point.
No expansion. Retesting value area low
here at 30s. 50 is still the big level.
No expansion under 20s yet.
800's still the level I want to see.
Snap. We've got a bid on the tape there.
100 lot.
Where's ES? ES right on it. New York or
open 24-hour VWAP on the spiders.
Where's the VIX? VIX can't get through
its pivot either. This is messy. And be
careful here. They might fail break and
rip this again. If they catch enough
shorts, they will have enough juice to
rip right back to the upside.
Oh, amazing.
No, I'm good. Thank you.
>> I'm looking for shorts. I'm looking for
shorts at the moment. If we expand,
that's what I'm looking for. If we
expand, I want to see continuation.
We're trying to do it at the moment.
Here we go. Watching these 820s is the
big levels, these 820s. So, I keep
calling it out. If we get under 820s,
800, 790s we get going. Is the opening
range low. It's being protected so far.
This white line on your screen keeps
being protected. You can see it trying
to absorb here. So, the question is, can
they rotate this or are we going to do
that? I'm not going to sit through
anything like that. Looking for the
rotation or the expansion lower. Looking
for the expansion lower back down into
here ideally. Here we go. Here's the
move to the teens. Come on then. Can you
come and take this 800 guy out?
Here we go. Trying to be patient.
They're front running this guy at 800.
100 lot 800. They're adding now at 780.
I'd like to see this come lower.
ES right on its VWAP 20-day and New York
open. Here we go. Come on. Hello
sellers. Any followthrough today? Are
you around? Do you want to give some
follow through? Back to previous week
value area high. That's going to be the
key level. I would not play this if we
start breaking above this. There we go.
So, no interest yet. Still waiting to
see if we can break that low of day and
get follow through. So, we had one
attempt. Patiently waiting to see if we
had follow through. Nothing. Still
back inside. and they can lift they can
afford to lift this right up to here.
Now, if they've caught enough shorts,
this is what I'm saying. This can be a
fail break. We go right back to the
upside again as they build more
liquidity out. I will play shorts,
right? If we come under here and we keep
rejecting this and we trap buyers in
here, I will play that. I will play
long. If we come under here and we trap
sellers in here, I will play that. I
will not play in this area here. I am
unwilling to do anything in this box
here.
And that's not just based on today.
That's based on previous day, previous
week, and everything we went over
pre-market. So, all we've had today,
unfortunately, is two little scalps. One
scalp there, one scalp there. That's it.
Haven't been able to get anything else.
They're looking to get filled with my
shorts.
Well, not really.
Not really, cuz we we got filled from
here down and then we didn't get the
break to re-enter. So, not really sure
what you're on about.
Okay. Screaming back up to the upside.
Sellers got caught under 25s. That's why
we kept talking about the 20s and 25s.
The low of day auction is terrible
though. I'll tell you now, they are
there are bids at the low of day. That
is not a good auction at the current low
of day. ES holding like we talked about
that 20-day New York opener VWAP all
stacked together. So I'm willing to play
this if we now base above for this drive
for the gap fill.
There's a giant squeeze up and every
time we've come up here this morning
we've got stuck again. Sellers up here
were at 24s and 33s. If we get over
those levels there's probably
continuation.
What's my TPN SP? What's that? What's an
SP? Stop loss. Do you mean TP and stop
loss? My TP is always into a key
liquidity target. Stop loss. Once we get
a fade and we're not getting
continuation, you'll hear me say it. I
move it. So like here, you'll hear me
say like I'm long partial here. Once we
get up there, I'm moving my stop break
even because if we can't accelerate, I'm
not interested.
Don't go to the toilet. Yeah. Well, it's
going to do a rip one way or another. ES
looks very strong now. off that 20-day
New York open and VWAP right up to high
day. Now it's got gap fill. I would not
be surprised if ES fills the gap and NQ
doesn't. Mag starting to rotate. Tesla
on a bit of a boomer here 3.43% up.
Nvidia down just under a quart%.
Microsoft found a bid 0.83% up. Meta
down 1.66%. Google now green on the day
0.18%. Amazon a third of percent. Apple
just a third of a percent down. They're
in a rotation guys. No one knows what
they want to do with this.
What am I showing on screen? Just a one
minute. Just a one minute chart.
Okay, it's messier today, guys. I cannot
do anything about the market, right? I
can only tell you when I'm going to get
a trade. And I've made it very clear all
day. I do not want to trade in this
choppy action. I want to trade outside
of the choppy action. Why do I want to
do that? Because everyone else is going
to become the liquidity, right? Everyone
else. Where's my arrow? Is going to
become the higher time frame liquidity.
I don't want to become someone else's
liquidity. I want to see a continuation
outside of this. I don't give a monkeys
which way. We can come up for a back
test of here and then fail that or maybe
even up here and fail that or we can
come for a back test of this and come
down to here. I'm happy to play either
side because both are viable today
because we are neutral. We are in a
neutral bias right now.
When did you hit 1k viewers this week?
Man, I don't know what's going on with
YouTube. It's been insane. I'm now out
to 1,400 of you watching today. That
means over 1,100 of you have not hit
that like button. I tell you what, I'm
going to be asking these prop firms for
a lot more giveaways for you guys. Now,
I cannot wait to give you guys some more
free stuff. I'm going to start getting
in touch with people. See if we can give
away some fun stuff as well. like maybe
each month get one of you guys a monitor
or something useful for you to trade
with. So yeah, smash that like button
for me everyone.
Smash that like button for me.
How many contracts do I trade? It all
depends on the account size I'm trading
right now. And it also depends on the
ATR. Right now you do not need any size.
Look, these are 100 point rips back and
forth. 100 100. You don't lead size.
Look, here's your 900. Failing above
900. Here's your 800. This is a 100
point range which is done once, twice,
three times, four times, five times, six
times, seven times, eight times, nine
times. There's been 900 points near
enough up for grabs here. If you're a
range trader, right? Look at the flow
zones, they're flat. Look at VWOPS,
they're flat. Look at previous day value
area high. Are we finding acceptance
above previous days value area high
right now? No, we can't find acceptance
above. Are we finding acceptance below
previous week value area high? No. What
does that mean? We're not rotating the
previous week. If we're going to rotate
the previous week, then we can expect
this and this, can't we? We're not
seeing that. This is the current week
developing as well. So, we can expect
this today if we let go. We're not
finding acceptance either side. What we
are doing is building out lots of
people. So when we have these sideways
actions, if you imagine bulls are all
positioned in this and bears, all right,
and bulls have their stops here and
bears have their stops here. If we pop
this, you will get a ripper. If we pop
this, you will get a ripper, right? So
don't join in on this. Unless you like
trading range and you're buying that,
selling that, selling that, buying it
back, buying it back, selling it, buying
it back, selling it back. All right?
Unless you, if that's your bread and
butter, you should be very rich today.
It's not my bread and butter. I try and
avoid those. The reason uh yesterday was
so good and this week's been so good is
because we've been in breakout or in
failed breakout of higher time frame.
And those are the moves that I like that
that's when we've been nailing those 250
point trades.
Just make sure my best advice is like
keep being zoomed out. Look at this
chart here. Understand where we are. All
right. We've broken away from trap
participants.
Broken away from trap participants.
We've washed. We're now in the liquidity
building phase in this huge node. And if
you zoom back, you can see the
importance of this level, right? It's a
huge level. Massive, massive level. All
right, let's see if they have another go
here.
Let's see. Do they hold bids now? ES is
about to fill its gap. Be very careful
here. If ES fills its gap, right, SPY
has now filled its gap. If you see a
failure here, it's because SPY's filled
its gap and that's all they wanted to do
on the cash market. So, SPY's just
filled its gap. ES has got a bit longer
to go. SPY pulling pulling back off that
gap fill. This is why I watch the ETFs
at the same time. SPY with the yellow
line. There you go. Has filled its gap.
ES is not too far away, right? It's
almost at the cash gap. Q's are nowhere
near. They've got a decent amount of way
to go. All right. So, we have relative
weakness in the cues.
Obligation filled in the spiders for
sure. Cash market has filled the gap in
the spiders.
Can I talk more about the ATR? Yeah.
What what what is it that you want to
know? I use the ATR on a very lower time
low time frame. So your opening print
this morning, the ATR was
95. So you had 95 point candle in the
first minute and then you gave the whole
thing back. Right now we're trading on
an average I'd say of about 30 points.
So per one minute candle, you're looking
at 30 points. So if you're someone that
uses a 20 point stop loss,
you're probably going to get stopped at
a lot today. So what's the best thing to
do? Shrink your contract size, increase
the stop- loss a little bit.
Yeah, shrink the contract size, increase
the stop loss a little bit.
All right, SPY really got hammered off
that gap though, guys.
So, we're just trading on the if you
look at the spiders and the cues. If you
look at the 5day and the 20-day, guess
where we're stuck between? You know it.
You best believe it.
It's the 5day 20-day chop.
What do I mean by spy cash gap? There is
a free video on my YouTube on that. But
what I mean is when I look at gaps, all
right, I don't just look at daily
candles. I look at the 4:00 close. All I
care about is the 9:30 open and the four
o'clock close because where is cash
traded? Look at the volume here. Look at
what's traded before that. Right? Look
at the volume here. Look at what's
traded after 4:00. Very thin. So I care
about what I call cash. Where is most
the money traded is in the cash market.
Where are the options traded? They're
are trading in the cash market. So they
care about the 4:00 close. They don't
care so much about a five:00 close,
right? 4:00 close matters. 9:30 open
matters.
How long will I continue these lives? I
mean, I've been doing them for, I don't
know, 15 months now. So, as long as I'm
enjoying them and I feel like I'm
helping you guys, I'll continue to do it
because trading is a very lonely job.
Um,
Moody, do I set my uh volume profile
only to the cash sessions? I do indeed.
Other than the developing week, I set
from the Sunday open, right? So,
developing week or weekly profile,
Sunday open, but each day's profile cash
for me. That's how I like to trade it,
but you know, each to their own. Some
people might not do that, but that's
what I like. I like trading for cash.
Am I waiting for a better signal? Yeah,
basically we are starting to hold here.
It's starting to look a bit better,
but the problem is for me now, we've
taken the low hanging fruit on spy.
It's looking a little better, but we've
taken a low hanging fruit on spy. So,
you know,
for us to do this, if Spyy's completed
it here, that's it's risky. I'm I'm
watching.
They did just defend 900 pretty well.
I'll give you that.
It's just not like a prime environment
that's making me screaming to try and
get a trade. ES is looking for that gap
fill. So you got ES and the 5day right
around 92. So if you're long ES from
GlobeEx from 78, you want to be uh
taking most of your money off at 92s.
Mag all now green other than Meta the
one I'm swing longing.
I am longing in Apple and Amazon as
well. So it's all right. Okay.
Are we going to hold?
They're still selling these 920s, 930s.
There is liquidity above. Let's see if
they hold these dips again into uh these
900s.
They're trying. There's a buyer down
here. I'm unconvinced. I'm very
unconvinced of what I'm seeing on the
tape.
In a sideways market, do I put weight on
VWAP? Uh, no, not really. I just I just
think it's a box because it is look, the
24hour is holding this morning. You can
see it is holding, right? They're using
it. But if we think about I just think
about everything like this, right? Those
are New York view up, 24-hour view up,
flow zones, and value. We're just boxed,
right? We're just boxed. Can they do
this? It's possible. They're trying.
They are really trying. They keep
reselling these 20s, though. If SPY had
not already filled its gap, I'd be more
willing to get long right now.
How has it felt to have financial
freedom due to trading? Is that part of
the reason you're extremely helpful with
the live streams, giving back to the
community? Yeah, it's funny. I talked to
um a peer about this last night. Um I
believe in giving back. I do not I also
guys I was you and got ripped off by
people
even by
I got ripped off to learn like pay
thousands and thousands thousands to
learn how not to trade. thousands and
thousands of thousands to learn the
worst possible habits ever, which took
me so long to kick. It's disgusting when
I look back. And then even with the good
guys that were like decent, you're still
looking at even on the sale $45,000 a
year to be in their uh trading rooms.
Um,
and you know, I was fortunate enough
that I had a good career before all of
this. But I I had some finances and my
wife was very supportive of me to do it.
But I don't think it's fair. Like there
don't need to be these locked away
secrets so much. Like I agree that you
you know should should pay for some
information but I also agree that it's
important to give back. You know I
believe in karma I guess is the best way
of saying it.
What were the bad habits? bad habits
adding to losers and at the time it was
uh I was trading small caps right so it
was more like shorting parabolic moves
but not stopping out right not doing
what I did today right you would have
seen today where would where did we go
long today I think it was here all right
and I took partial and then old me back
in the day would have added and added
and added and added and then maybe if I
was smart got outbreak even added added
add why we got a gap here what's going
on so but it it was a small cap era for
me is when I was trading small caps and
we'd have like parabolic moves. All
right, this this this this and add ad
add and Alex blows up and loses all his
money, right? Those were some of the bad
habits taught. Taught not just like like
I made them up. Taught actually taught
to do that. [\h__\h] Absolute [\h__\h]
So that's why I teach you the complete
opposite. There will be guys in chat
that will have had some of those bad
habits or traded with some of the
people, but I'm not here to badmouth
other people. So, I will not be telling
you their names.
Sellers definitely just got caught under
89 there. Definitely got caught at 80
there. Under 89 and 80. 20s is still the
level that they can't get through. But
sellers definitely just got caught on
this last dip to VW up. If we have a
look in here, you will see it. Look at
these sellers. They just got caught in
here. Right, this guy here, he's caught
offside. So, if they can't get back
under here, there is a chance. So,
they're going to come back down and
retest this. If they rebid this, this
will look okay. If they flush this, this
is a big sell. So, they're trying to
rebid now. See? See how this seller got
caught? You can see him right here. This
guy here into 90 down to sort of 77.
That is his pain point. If they flush
through, you'll get a wash. If they hold
this, they rebid it. This is why I'm
just being very patient. It's a
two-sided tape right now. And we're
right at value. This is value for the
session, right? This is point of control
on the session. It's VW for the session.
I don't really want to bid here on
value. All right. I don't have edge
bidding on value.
Like I said, spy already filled its
obligation of filling the gap.
They need to be badmouththed. Yeah. I
just I just there's part of me that
really agrees with you, Scott. Really
agrees with with you because they're
charging a lot of money um and teaching
really bad stuff. And then there's part
of me that's just like
Whether you want to call it God or
spirituality or whatever where I'm just
like I need to be a nicer person. I just
should not be [\h__\h] on someone's
mouth.
Just do the opposite of Ross Cameron. I
mean, if you've listened to my
interview, you will know that that's
what I used to do. I I quite genuinely
had a small cap room um or was in a
small cap room with some guys and we had
a subscription to Ross Cameron and
pre-market we would let Ross pump and
pump and pump and we would take the
opposite side of his position once we
thought he was getting out and dumping
on all his followers. It was a legit
thing that we did.
I do not com combine orderflow and ICT.
just
it's just order flow and structure
really.
Each to your own. Look, I don't disagree
with all of ICT's teachings, but they're
not his. Simple as that.
And they're not all as accurate as you
think. Order block is supply and demand.
Don't care what he [\h__\h] tells you.
It's what it is. Liquidity is a stop
hunt where wicks are. That's what it is.
I don't seismme I can have a look into
it. I've ne no one's ever requested it.
I can have a look if it's uh possible.
I'm not a web developer. Um I have asked
my web developer to do a few things.
Here's the wash, guys. All right, so
back into the range, failing the 920s
again, absorbing off that 24-hour view
up and previous day point of control.
This is still an avoidance kind of
session so far. I'm really sorry. Lots
of you guys might be new here thinking,
why are we not taking a trade? I promise
you. Yesterday we had a 250 point short,
then we had a 50 point short, another 50
point short, and then a 250 point long.
Um I I will trade when it sets up for a
trade. I promise you
once I learned enough and built enough
edge, I plan on doing the same as you
and work to lift others up without
robbing them. Yep, that's that's it. And
it doesn't matter what your career is. I
used to do even in my music career,
guys, I used to do the same. the amount
of artists I bought through. Um, so I
did a deal with I had my own record
label. I couldn't get a deal. 2011 to
2014, no one wanted to touch me. I could
not get a record deal anywhere. So, we
opened our own label and started putting
records out. The first record we put out
on vinyl was us, a guy called James
Denny, if any of you into DJs, Hannah
WZ, and Chris Lorenzo, right? That was
our first ever record on our label and
it flew and then after that we started
getting some traction and then in 2014
we were pitching a song around that no
one wanted to touch. We gave it to Annie
Mack on Radio One. She gave it a spin
and guess what? My phone did not stop
ringing on the Monday and we had every
single label chasing us for a deal. We
did a huge deal which lasted a long
time. Two years later, we sold our
record label to Sony and I still managed
to anard that label and I spent most
that time bringing young artists
through. All right. I didn't really care
about the big established artists. I
think it's important to give young or
doesn't even need to be young. People
who haven't had their break. Give them
the opportunity. All right? There are so
many talented people out in this world
who just are never given the
opportunity. So, it's really important.
So, it's the same in this. So, I want
want to help as much as I can.
All right. Still stuck. Jeez Louise.
Nothing's changed. What you might get
here is at some point today if they've
built enough liquidity, you might get a
very quick snap. It might be in the
afternoon if they don't do it soon. All
right, Google coming back down. All the
mag coming back down other than Tesla.
Tesla's on a pumper. 4% up. Let's have a
quick look if that's peaked out.
Let me zoom out here on a 30. See if
we're coming into a pivot. We are at
that same zone. So Tesla's coming back
up. This is like a two-leg one, two,
back into these pivots. If it can't
reclaim, we might see some weakness come
in the market. All right. Watching this
now for downside. All right. Same as we
were watching for upside, I'm now
watching for downside. If we want to
accelerate,
if we're going to let go
back into value area high from previous
week, can we find acceptance underneath
this and start getting aggressive? If we
can, we will trade it down and we will
try and get down into these gray lines.
We're looking good here now.
Watching this very carefully. Can we
trap some buyers down here and start
washing? Yes, we can. Come on, market.
Let's do something fun here. Let's start
snapping.
So, we've got an imbalance all the way
up to 50s again. That same level as area
as earlier is going to be key. Let's see
if we can get outside of all of this.
Let's see if they push back up and trap
some buyers and then start washing.
Here's the push back. The previous week
area high imbalances up to 50. Remember,
we've still got this buyer on the tape
down at 800 100 lot and below. So
watching to see if we come up and reject
and then if we see follow through or
not. ES still holding New York open VWAP
and 20 days. Say this is exactly the
same as last time we were here. We're in
a complete alignment is exactly the same
as last time we were here which was at
10:00. I think we might get expansion
here.
So revisit
sellers definitely caught up above 50s
right now on Yeah, 50s and 55. 60 is the
big level of the seller. So want to see
how they act. Here's the drive and 50.
Want to see how they act now? 50s and
60s. Do they resell this or not? This is
what's key. Do they resell this or not?
If not, we're going to go back inside
the dance back to the upside again. But
if so, and they catch enough, I think we
will get a wash. Good rejection there.
Here we go, folks.
Can we get a breakdown now underneath
these lows for follow through? Do we
have any follow through today?
Yes. Trying to find a bid on that New
York open. I think we're going to get
follow through here. We're watching this
short now for continuation and a snap.
Come on. We got to get under the 25s.
We've talked about it all morning. Here
we go.
Here we go, folks. Come on. Stay heavy.
Stay heavy. Stay heavy. Stay heavy. Stay
heavy. Stay heavy. Let's go. Let's go.
Let's go. Let's go. Beautiful. I want to
see one more push down and come and wick
out all of this. And if we run all these
stops, I think we can get down into
here. Let me just make sure I'm checking
these profiles. I'm going to just get a
gray box on where we thickened up on the
current week, just so we know. This
right here is key. This right here is
key. Under that we have room. Under this
we have a lot of room down into here.
Here we go folks.
Come on. I like I said low of day
auction is terrible right now. I think
we will make a new low of day because
there's a buyer down there. I don't
think that holds. I don't think it's a
good low date auction.
But this is a big area. So, if you're in
this, make sure you're paying yourself
into this. Outside of this, we're going
to get very weak.
Code code flow zone on TPT. Sorry. Code
flow. Here we go.
Let's go, baby. Let's go, baby. All
right. Here's 800s into the gray box.
Partial here. Let's see if we get
acceptance now down into here. So, TP1
now hit. We rejected 50s. Remember I
said 50s is the key level. I gave it to
you exact key level. We rejected 50s.
We're seeing follow through under 25s.
The wash now is to 90. If we break out
of 90, we're looking for 38s. We can
call it 40s and 700s. All right, let's
go, baby.
Let's go, baby. Nice rejection of 50.
So, here we go. Let me get this on.
Sorry, I forgot to put this on for you.
I got a little bit excited here. You are
looking for continuation now down into
here. And then if we get lucky down into
here, you should have locked in no
matter what, you should have locked some
in. So, nice rejection of 50. We could
actually risk up there and see if we can
get here. All right. See if we can get
this and then this. Really nice, guys.
Really good work. Patience, patience,
patience. Right. Patience, patience,
patience. Ideally, we reject the gray
box. I would not want this back above
the gray box. Certainly not above the 20
level, right? Where we built this shelf.
Let's see if we can get some follow
through.
Really don't want this back into 20s.
So, taken partial, stops now at 20s
because that was the break of 25s,
right? It was at 20 stops around here. I
don't want to risk back up to 50s.
Really nice. This rejection here was
key. Do you remember here? I said we're
doing the same thing as earlier. The 50
lift, the 50 lift, the 50 lift. Once we
broke 25s, that was it. right down into
here and see if we can get this, this,
and this now on the runners. It might
not give us the runners today. Might
very well do something like this. So,
we're not going to play for that. We
want this now down into here. If we
reclaim, I'll be out on it. Not going to
sit in case we do a failed break. We do
a failed break. I'm not going to let
this reclaim this level here. So, 2025s
is the squeeze back up. So, they're
going to test this level. If they do not
reject this level, then I will cut. Nice
rejection in front of that so far.
Really good.
really good. This is what we want to
see. We want to see big rejections now
and follow through. I would love to see
Amazon go red here as well.
I trade like by by 2% knowledge. What do
you mean I trade by 2% knowledge?
Not sure what you mean. If you think
I've got 2% knowledge, then when I get
the rest 98, I'm going to be a dangerous
man, aren't I?
Here's the 800 test.
That trade passed your funded account.
Nice. Good work. We had a big seller at
800 now.
Right. Bring you over here. Big seller
at 800. We have an imbalance up here
into twelves. All right. So, we're
watching for a rejection. 800 to 12.
Ideally, I don't really want it lift up
here. Want to see delta stay heavy and
follow through. So, I'm expecting a
pullback. I want to see that pullback
sold into. If we don't sell into it,
it's going to be problematic. And I will
cut the rest break even.
Where did I enter on the break after we
broke 25s? Right here where where we are
basically where this line is. Remember I
said I want to see 50s reject and a
break of 25s. 50s reject and a break of
25s. Same thing we were looking for
here. We want 50's reject and a break
25s. There's the break of 25s.
All right. So here to here and then
waiting to see if we reject this now
anywhere here for continuation. If we
reclaim this, I will not touch it. We
can always trade again afterwards. All
right. But if we start reclaiming these
levels, I will not touch it in case we
do that. Fail breakouts are very
possible each side of a range. So I'm
being extra careful today.
What is a break of 25? Right here. 825.
825. The level 825.
No, 825. If I'm giving you a number,
guys, it's here. I'm not going to say
25,825.
I can't say that all the time. So, we
just call it 25s, right?
Let's see if we can get continuation
now.
Initial balance now set. Is that right?
Yeah. IB now set. So, we want to be
careful of a failed IB. So, IB high to
IB low here. Let's just see what that
expansion might look like. Can we line
it up with something? Yes, that would
look pretty good. This would look pretty
good. So previous week point of control
is possible if we stay heavy here based
on the IB expansion to the 1618. So we
have alignment here if we can stay
heavy.
So here's 800 test like we talked about.
We have an imbalance here into sort of
812. That was your opening range as well
by the way. And then 825 there is an
imbalance up there which is where my
stop break even is right now.
If we get ES staying heavy versus New
York open here will really help. So it
keeps trading into that New York open
and 24-hour VW up. We would like to see
it stay heavy. I'm very aware that the
indexes right now are stuck between the
5day and 20-day. So here's the lift up
out of this now
because I don't want to get caught in a
squeeze back up. So out on the runner,
we can always get back in. Remember can
always get back in. I don't care giving
out on the run. I can always get back in
or I'm not going to risk as a fail
breakout getting caught with no stop and
it ripping from like 25 all the way up
to 900 again. Right. So fail break here.
Here we go. This is why we stop out on
the runner and right the way back up it
comes. This is why we don't stay in.
This is why I talk about the difference
between me now and me years ago is I
wouldn't have understood that if that
reclaimed it's likely to do this. There
we go. Squeeze back up. So fail break,
trade down. fail break. Trade up. The
rotation continues.
At least we got TP1. And there's your
IB. IB back to VWAP just happened. I
don't know if you traded that, Tyson.
There's your IP to VWAP.
And previous day value high now tagged
rotation the other side. And this is
back into the no man zone. No trade
zone. Not trading in here. Don't care
what it does. I'm not trading in here.
trading outside of it or outside of it.
I'm not trading in here.
It's my leave leave alone zone.
What is that move? It's just a squeeze.
It's a squeeze, right? So, lots of
people probably chased down here. This
was the target. Remember that's TP1 25
break into this node. TP1. The gray box
held. We couldn't reject the gray box.
We couldn't reject 25 for continuation.
So, we reclaimed. when we reclaim
everyone stopped out and they cause
this.
All right? So, if you've got short
sellers stopping out here, they cause
this. All right? Because if too many
shorts get in here, their stop is there.
They allow this squeeze right the way
back up. This is why I saying I don't
want to sit through a failed break and a
squeeze up, which is what we've had.
It's a messy It's a messy chart today.
So, you've got to be very disciplined.
No, I'm not getting in on and and
there's no anticip I'm never
anticipating the market. No. When we are
here, what did I say? I want to see a
reject of 50 and a breakdown of 25.
Right? When we were here, I want to see
a reject of 50. What's that? That's a
reject of 50 and a break of 25. What's
that? A break of 25. That is not an
anticipation. That is me telling you
what I want to see. There's the break.
There's the cover. All right. Stop then
goes to break even because I don't want
to get caught on a squeeze back up
because everyone else who's smart enough
to take that trade will cut here and
that happens. I'm never anticipating the
market. I'll tell you what I'm looking
for, but I'm not trading in front of
that happening. That's where you will
get caught.
I don't know what I'm do doing.
Yeah. Okay, mate. Okay.
Okay, bud. Even though I gave you the
exact levels and we had like 700 points
and we probably had two plus thousand
points this week together.
What are you? Are you ICT's [\h__\h] kid?
[\h__\h] dick.
Man, there are some cretins out there.
All right, so rehold a previous week
value. We will trade back up for a back
test of this. Now, this is the liquidity
build out. You can see it here. You can
see it between these values. Again, if
they base above here, the squeeze is on
to try and fill this gap. Like we talked
about, SPY has already filled that gap
though. Q's have not filled that gap. ES
has not quite filled that gap.
No, NT8 Ninja's fine for me.
It's been the same calls all morning,
guys. Nothing's changed. This is the
same thing outside of here. And outside
of here, we're willing to trade inside
of here. I'm not willing to trade.
What indicator that moves from red to
green? Flow zone pro. Flow zone pro.
It's hilarious, man. It is funny.
That's right, Matt. Matt has absolutely
nailed that. That is the statement. That
is exactly right. The market is the
perfect tool to move money from the
impatient to the to the patient. That is
the most accurate statement. Very, very
accurate. Think about yesterday,
right? What we traded yesterday. We were
short yesterday
for this breakdown under here into here.
And I got this to this and I missed
this. But then we were long on this trap
here all the way back up, weren't we?
Right? Because we were patient. We knew
it would be a long down here if we
trapped enough and it played out, right?
So, it's being patient and we don't
trade this mess. We don't trade that
mess. We wait for everyone else to trade
that mess. We trade outside of that
mess.
Very, very accurate statement that
and the 100 point chop continues. Just
think like Um really here no acceptance
over this. Not too much acceptance below
this like 112 point chop.
Market isn't respecting levels. It is
absolutely respecting levels. It's
exactly what it is doing. It is
absolutely respecting levels.
There's a reason that we've just held
this, right? There's a reason we held
this gray box.
There's a reason we just held this.
There's a reason we keep getting stuck
up here. It is absolutely respecting
levels. It's just whether you understand
the levels that it's respecting. We will
move to a higher time frame. Right? This
gray box here
and this five minute this node here
is being respected, right? It is being
respected. Being respected. Being
respected. Being respected. We drift
under it on a stopwatch. Oh, look. We
grabbed the 20-day. Never never guessed
that. It must be ICT that says uh 20
days and SMAs and emails don't work. He
must be [\h__\h] clever. Respect the gray
box. Respect the gray box. Respecting
this node.
Respecting this shelf.
It is absolutely respecting levels. It's
just whether you're zoomed out enough to
understand what the levels are.
All right, starting to find bids now on
the top side
into the edge of current day's value
9005. So, let's see if they hold bids
now. ES getting very close for that IB
high. If we're going to go IB high
rotation day, it would not surprise me
to see ES break IB high, fill its gap
towards 90. What is that? 93s and then
fade back inside the IB high. So I want
to be careful when we think about the
type of day we're in. We're in an inside
bar. We're inside the daily. We're
inside the weekly and we are inside
initial balance. Highly probable
rotational market which is what we've
seen this morning.
Alex, in your course do you teach about
the indicators you use and how to use
them? Yeah, absolutely. Absolutely. Of
course I do. Of course I do. So the c
the the main course you want to do if if
if you're looking to learn is the 20our
course that will teach you all the
indicators what I use how I use it
and with that you get the discord right
so if you're want to understand
everything on the screen that's what I
use if you already understand all that
stuff and you want to use like volume
profile delta delta divergence
imbalances
uh footprint bookmap then just do the
volume uh volume and order flow
VIX new low. Yeah, VIX just filled its
gap. VIX just filled its cash gap. So
that cash gap on the VIX was to what?
1686. It's into a pivot now. Good eyes,
mate. Good eyes. So a breakdown now
under 1670s. All right. Can allow a
flush on the VIX down to 1653s and then
we've got some like old gaps that we can
fill down to 1634s and lower days down
to 16. So we'll just see how the VIX
act. It's in a pretty key level right
now.
We are starting to find bids here. We
are starting to absorb and find some
bids here.
We're stuck at the value area high of
the day which is starting to lift and
move higher. ES wants that breakout for
that gap fill. I would not be surprised
if we break out, fill the gap on ES and
then come straight back inside the IB.
Can't reach my page really. I've seen
someone else say that. I'm wondering if
I've got someone uh
let me try it on mine. Wonder if
someone's being a bit of a pain. It's
working on mine. Let me uh post it in
here. Try that link there.
Still rejecting these same levels up
here for now. They are trying to find a
bid here though.
If you purchase multiple Apex accounts,
is there a membership fee for multiple
accounts or one membership for all the
accounts? Probably stupid question. Not
sure what you mean by membership fee.
You pay for those accounts. All right.
For your monthly fee. All right. Once
you pass those accounts, you have to pay
for each account um to be activated. If
you don't pass the accounts in the first
month, you you'll pay whatever the fee
is for the next month for the rollover.
So, I think right now it's 50 it's 90%
off right now. But if you don't, let's
say you buy one today on the 30th of
Jan, if you haven't passed it by the
30th of February, they will roll over to
the next month and you'll only get a 50%
discount.
Hope that makes sense. And I think I
don't know what activation is right now.
Or is it 70 $70 or something? Right.
Yes. Looks like wants to get going for
that gap fill.
We are starting to build liquidity here.
900 all the way down to 8.90 big level.
It looks like they want to lift this at
this point. They are trying to lift it
and run all these stops. And if they do
bust out of this
this shelf here, I'd say this top side
of this shelf here. If they can start
busting out of this here, right, this
shelf here, if they can build liquidity
and bust out and run these stops, we've
got the potential for this gap fill up
here into 26,000. Same thing we've been
looking at all day. each side of this.
Here we go. They're starting to run it.
Let's see then. Watching ES. I be high
now on the ES now. Tagged.
Let's see. Let's see.
Here we go. This is where the sellers
came in this morning. Looks good. Buyers
getting a little caught here, but I
think we're going to expand through this
high day.
We want to watch that higher time frame
algo as well. ES through that initial
balance. So watch very very carefully
for ES to trade into 9275s 93s. That
will be the target for ES. Gap filled
again on the SPY. So we're just waiting
for ES to play the catchup. Then the
question is do we do it? If you are long
in this pullback here, I would be
starting to trim some on the next break
above here. All right. Hopefully above
40s you get a squeeze, but I'll be
trimming some into that in case they uh
use that little squeeze to sell into
because remember market uh order buy
stops will be here. You'll probably get
a stop run here and it they could very
easily do a fail break of the IB and
turn back inside because we are in a
balanced day.
But you know, I don't know what I'm
talking about. Better listen to the guy
on stream who's 15 and follows a
delusional old man that wears a stupid
cap and has failed every single attempt
at every single trading account. Okay,
how am I seeing the buyers getting
caught? I'm using orderflow. So bookmap,
which you can see above me, and also
footprint, right? So this right here,
right? So buyers caught here, right? So
we're waiting to see sellers are caught
under here. This is the rotation. Can
these buyers find acceleration at the
moment?
It should come and pop those stops. ES
has already done it though. It has not
quite filled its gap. It did run the
high. Yes, it did run the high, but we
have not quite filled that gap on ES. We
have done it on the spy like I've talked
about. We have done it on spy already.
No worries, Chuck. All right. Failed
break of the IB high on ES. still hasn't
filled its gap. Like I said, SPY has
filled its gap. The one thing I'm aware
of here is SPY, like I said, has filled
its gap already. This yellow line's been
tagged again. So, it's a fail break
above it. And ES has not quite done it.
Very, very close. You can see that.
Whereas QQQ has a long way to go. We
need to run these stops and use these
stops to get up there. If they're going
to do it, they might not do it today.
You might see divergence between the Q's
and the uh ES today on that gap. So, it
would not surprise me at all to see
divergence there and then initial
balance rotation. But I would like them
to at least come and run these stops. At
the moment, they're unable to do it.
We're getting stuck at GlobeEx, the
orange line. Back down we come down to
this same level. So, can they now trap
sellers down here and do one last
squeeze up? They won't do it if they're
unwilling to do it on ES. All right. If
we're just going to trade the range,
remember, if you're a range trader, this
is like your bread and butter. I would
say buyers stepped in earlier today at
98.95. They will want to rebid that. If
they cannot rebid that, we will go wash
right back down to the other side of the
range again. If they cannot rebid here,
we will wash right back down to the
other side of the range again. Sellers
getting caught on that last little shove
down underneath 905s. So maybe they've
got a chance here. We just filled that
imbalance.
I'd say 900 to
89 is key. 900 to 89 is key for buyers
to uh absorb the tape. 900 to 89 is key
down here.
Since I started trading with you, I've
been more profitable. That's great.
Okay, down into that same level we just
talked about it. 900 down to 89. We just
chapped 8925.
This was the level.
They will need to lift this now. If they
don't lift this, if they get a breakdown
under here, we will wash all the way
back down. Buyers must hold this area
now to complete the rotation. Buyers
must hold this in here to complete this
rotation. Failing to hold this in here
will collapse this whole thing back down
again. This is your node. I mean, at
least down to here, right? This is the
node. So, at the moment, we're not
seeing what they need to do happen. And
they're coming into the key level and
waiting to see if sellers get trapped.
We're not seeing it. The liquidity looks
pretty terrible on the book right now.
Just stacking both sides. Here they go.
They're trying now to lift. Here's the
910s. Can they lift through this and get
going now? So 900 to 890 held well. No
lift through the 10. They tried. That 15
seller just came on. Big block just been
put in there.
Back and forth. Back and forth. Back and
forth. They don't know what they want to
do with it.
back down to the 90s.
I'm going to come try and get back to
the 900s. Big seller stepping in at
900s. He just slammed it. He just
slammed it. 100 lot. He's chasing it
down now. He is chasing it down with
size now. He's had enough. He's been
like, "Piss off. I'm done with you guys.
You're You're annoying me." He came in
with some serious size there for the
chase. So that 900s and 890 is big big
level now. All right. He came in, he
chased it down, followed through down
all the way down into 82s. Low of that
auction was pretty good. So we'll see
his pain point now will be the 900s.
It's where he started chasing in for
some big follow through. He had big big
size.
900 will be his pain point. It's where
he came in. If we live through 900, we
test 915s. He's still got a passive
order up there.
Oh, the chop and the slop. There's
nothing to do
still. He's selling. He's selling hard,
hard, hard, hard, hard, hard. Came in
very aggressive again. So, back into no
man's land, the other side of this node.
If we lose this node, like I said, is
likely that we come down into here. So,
no follow through at the top. We didn't
even take this high divergence to ES.
didn't fill this gap. Even ES didn't
fill that gap, but the spy did. And we
are losing this. And we might well wash
all the way back down now if they do.
Very possible.
Here's the wash. There you go.
No. No position. No position for me.
Certainly not
not going to trade inside here. I've
I've made that about as clear as I can.
I'm not going to trade inside any of
this
for this exact reason. Look what they
do. They're telling you what they do,
right? It's not just telling you today.
It's telling you overnight. It's telling
you yesterday.
We can keep looking at this exact level.
Right?
This is this level.
We'd have to go back to November and
October. But this same level
has been traded so many times and it's
sloppy. There you go. Same level, guys.
getting tight now on the profile.
Okay, maybe we'll do some giveaways
because this is getting boring at this
point. 1,400 of you watching. Let's get
it up to 1,000 likes. 686 likes right
now and we do some giveaways.
Go for a coffee or bathroom so we have a
wash. Yeah.
There you go. So, Maxim saying,
"Beautiful sell of the range." Yeah. If
you're a range trader, this is what
we've talked about, right? If you're a
range trader, this should be your bread
and butter, shouldn't it? You're a range
trader, this should be your bread and
butter. I'm not a range trader. I try
and avoid the ranges.
we get this up to a thousand likes and
we'll give away some Apex accounts and
stuff and all that good stuff.
Right, I'll give you a minute. I'm going
to use uh the bathroom, come back and we
do that giveaway. Do an Apex giveaway.
All right, right back down we come.
Right, how many likes? We got enough.
Can we do a giveaway? Look at that. I
walk away and like 200 people just
disappear. It's hilarious. I haven't
done it yet, guys. Jeez. Slow down.
Nothing's been set up. I can't do
anything yet.
If you keep entering, we can't do the
competition.
Stop.
Stop. Stop.
Stop it.
I have to give away something else first
now just to like fix it. You crazy
people. All right, we're going to give
away the course first because you guys
keep typing the wrong wrong thing. So,
type course.
Just type it once and we give away a
beginner course.
Just type it once, guys. Otherwise,
you'll get booted out by Nightbot and
then you can't win it. So, just type it
once.
Give away a free course. And then I want
a,000 likes to do the Apex giveaways,
please. So, at least 200 more.
This market is uh
not doing anything. We're going to do
some fun stuff instead.
Let's
buy back down to its speed. What up?
What are we doing market? You going to
give any follow through anywhere today?
It's probably going to be a Monday.
Maybe an afternoon. You might get
something in the afternoon. I expect
they will run the stops at some point in
the afternoon.
I give you guys 30 more seconds.
It's just the introduction course, guys.
So, it's just two a two-hour course.
It's for someone that's never traded
before.
It does give you uh
does give you some money off the main
course, though, as well.
All right, going to pull this winner. 5
2 and one.
Spearhead Media Group. Why do I feel
like I've seen that name before? Have
you won before?
Spearhead Media Group. Let me know
you're here.
Still holding that New York open right
now.
Let me know you're here. Spearhead Media
Group.
Oh, nice. Awesome. Okay, same thing as
before. You can even do it to the same
email. Okay, just info@flzontrader.com,
right? And I'll sort you out that
course, my friend. You're welcome.
No worries. No worries.
You guys are nuts in chat today, man.
Crazy people. What's going on?
Right, you need to get me to
1,000 likes. 50 more likes and we'll
start doing some giveaways.
We are just stuck. This market is
absolutely stuck. You can see value area
low on the session. Value area high on
the session. We are in a D-shaped
profile. We are just in a range
rotation. Nothing is changing here.
There's no movement. We're not finding
acceptance lower. We're not finding
acceptance higher. We're just stuck on
each edge.
I would love us to just do something.
Tesla's absolutely screaming right now,
which is probably holding ENQ up pretty
well.
Look at that relative strength all the
way up into the old highs. It might come
up for one more test and then see if
they fade it.
So, I'd imagine Tesla will at least test
this. If not, wick that and then see if
it rolls over. And then once it does
that, maybe you'll see acceptance lower
if the rest of the market wants to join
in. Right now, we're just inside value
and we're basically the same levels as
we've had all days, right? 850 860s up
here is the same level that we talked
about all day where we tested here and
failed, right? We're now starting to
just build a ton of liquidity out here.
Shelf above is at 73s.
So this now is becoming more and more
pivotal
as your over under for sentiment.
Why people only a few people get
repeated prizes. It's it's done totally
at random. You can see when I pull it,
it's it's just there. Seem to be lucky.
Yeah, exactly. Inside bar daily. We're
inside the current week. We're inside
the previous days value is what we
talked about in Discord, right? We
expect rotation.
We expect rotation. It's our expectation
today.
Where do you get data about buyers and
sellers? You would need to use a
footprint indicator or bookmap,
right? You need footprint charts or
bookmap.
You would need to understand what you're
looking at as well. So, we're still
holding for now. Still holding previous
week value area high. I want to see if
we flush under this or if we're going to
rebid and rotate again.
We're just pinned. We are pinned between
5day and 20 days right now.
Willing to play lower. Again, same thing
if we move outside of range. Otherwise,
not willing to play it. Willing to play
higher if we move outside of range. I
use a 1 minute, a 5 minute, and like
sometimes I'll look at like a 30 or even
a daily sometimes just to see key levels
from the day before. But one and five
are my main areas like in this current
fiveminute bar, right? Buyers keep
stepping in over 42s and failing.
Sellers keep stepping in under that and
failing. So that's like the key level
right now is that the 42s in this bar.
If we look at the previous couple bars,
we had buyers step in at 60s
and no acceptance. So we're just stuck
right between 60s and basically this low
here, 30s. We're just completely stuck
right now.
footprint on Trading View on Ninja.
Probably a little bit better on Ninja,
but I mean
the Trading View one I I actually do
like I think it looks pretty good. I
think it's pretty easy to read. Heavy
Delta coming in here. Let's see if they
get follow through. They're trying to
step on the book here.
These 50s and 60s keep rejecting. We're
starting to get under it. But we have
now a base that we created this morning
from this little imbalance. So maybe we
fill the imbalance. Imbalance is all the
way down to 15s. 8:15 is the actual
imbalance. It's actually here. It's not
this whole thing. Actually 8:15 is the
imbalance.
There's the 20s.
Seller came in at 25s there and got
himself caught
as they continue to rotate.
What is easier to decipher at a glance,
footprint or bookmap? Um,
that's a really good question. They're
both the honestly they're both exactly
the same. Um, I'd say bookmap's easier
to see like the current momentum because
the bubbles are showing you like the
runs on market liquidity. And the other
thing with bookmap that you get that you
don't get on uh on footprint charts is
the resting liquidity. On a footprint
chart, you can't see the resting
liquidity. So maybe maybe bookm
like gaps and liquidity in the market.
They just held this rotation again back
through the 50s. Now squeeze back up
into this gray box. Now they have to see
if they reject the gray box and come
down or if they reclaim the gray box and
go again. It's just getting pretty
shitty in here, guys. Not much to do.
Yes, absolutely. Rotation is absolutely
the name of the game today. So, up to
that gray box. So far, they can't get
through the gray box. So, rotation back
down to where we just came from. There
you go. Again, they're just small
rotations now as well inside a bigger
rotation. It's very choppy area like we
talked about at the beginning of stream
going back to
November. November 5th. We're going back
to November 5th. The top of this stream,
right? We're at a thousand yet. We're
still not a thousand. Come on, guys. We
need like 125 of you to hit the like
button and we can give away some stuff.
No, imbalances are not fair value gaps.
It's the same thing, but look, the
difference is is you guys mark the whole
area. And I'd need to turn it on on here
because I don't have it on. But
uh
reset this reload
stat levels.
Okay, here you see this imbalance. You
guys would mark it out as the whole
thing. you guys would mark this whole
thing out. The imbalance actually isn't
down until here,
right? That's where they didn't get
filled.
So, the same principle, but accuracy is
different when you actually see the
order flow. And actually, it's even
better on Ninja if I'm honest.
How do I get that page on Trading View?
There's a there's a free video on my
YouTube. Just go to my YouTube. I
literally show you how to set it up and
uh what my settings are. Just go on my
YouTube. It came out like a week ago. I
think I put that out.
Yeah, I know FC Mike. It's crazy. It's
been nuts. It has been nuts. All right,
so gray box to previous week value area
high is the rotation right now. Still no
follow through either side of this.
VIX reclaiming PDC. Let's see if VIX
wants to get back up into the 1750s,
which would give downside follow through
if it does.
Yes, right into that New York open.
Let's see if it loses this New York
open. So, these 50s and 60s, same kind
of level as we had earlier. Same kind of
level starting to reject. Now, we're
coming down towards this imbalance we
talked about all the way down into 15,
right? And let's see if they bid around
these 15s. As we just talked about it
here, this is the actual imbalance which
we're coming down towards all the way
down to I actually have it on Ninja is
like 17 to 14 is like the big big level
of that. Let's see.
For footprints, yeah, for footprints I
use a one minute and a five minute.
Sometimes I'll just peak the 30.
actually that like
one and five is enough like this is my
five over here which I have up all the
time right so it's my delta build out
here I can see the key levels of where
the sellers got stuck or sellers came in
hard at 60 imbalances here you can see
we're going to come and fill this first
imbalance into the 15s there we go just
tapped him and if we fill the next one
you wouldn't even have an imbalance you
ICT guys but there is actually one down
here you go so we just filled it found a
little bid mhm
Alex doesn't know what he's talking
about. Mhm. Listen to the crazy old man,
though.
All right. So, if there's follow through
now, we'll probably come down to 801s if
there was follow through.
I want to give away two Apex accounts
today because you guys have been amazing
this week. Very, very supportive.
How we doing for likes?
Not bad. Not bad. Not bad.
Is it possible to get that template uh
again? It's on my YouTube, mate. On or
do you mean the ninja one? Ninja one's a
paid one. Um what they called? Cydi.
Okay. FZT. Type it in chat once. That's
your code for 90% off with Apex and most
the prop firms out there. That will get
you the best discount. Type it in chat
once. will do a giveaway right now for
an free Apex account. Just type it once.
You don't need to spam. If you spam, all
it does is pull you out. All right. All
it does is pull you out.
Oh, Victor, I've just seen your name.
Let me uh sort you out here, Victor.
How do I get to
All trading view is on one, isn't it?
Absolutely on one.
See if I can get to you.
There we go.
Give you guys 30 more seconds.
Get back for the 50 test here.
All right, pulling this winner then.
Five, four. Gosh, there's lots of you.
Three,
two, and one. Dopamine.
Dopamine 5578. Dopamine 5578. Are you
here? Dopamine.
Are you hear dopamine
market coming back down?
Do they come lower now? Back into this
same area where these sellers keep
trying to come in at the 25s. Remember
it was the 25 break we played lower
earlier. This is ES into its 20day here.
Do we find acceptance lower right now?
Yeah, nice. Congratulations dopamine.
Okay, all I want you to do is email me
please. info@flzonetrader.com.
Send a screenshot of yourself logged in
to your YouTube so I know it's you. I've
made a note of your of your name. Send
me a screenshot of that and I'm going to
sort you out with a free Apex account.
Any size that you want, any type of
account, any size you want on Apex.
Okay. Still no continuation underneath
these 25. Still holding that old
imbalance of 15s. Still in this
rotation. Still no acceptance outside of
any of this. If we do, we know that down
here might want to be filled. If we get
acceptance under this gray box, then
we're going to look for down here. But
until then, just being very, very
cautious about looking for anything
else. Does the shape of the previous
day's distribution give you a clue about
the next day's profile? Absolutely. But
it also matters where we open up. All
right, so yesterday was a big B shape,
right? If you go from the open, it was a
B-shape, but we were we are still
basically trading inside of yesterday,
aren't we? Right. So if we think about
yesterday,
yesterday's value was here.
We are not moving value up, are we?
We're not moving value higher, right?
We're trading in the same level. In
fact, we're trading right around
previous days value area high and point
of control. Right? This was fair value
yesterday. If we decide yesterday's fair
value is too expensive, then we can
think about these rotations down here,
which is what I'm willing to play
outside of here. At the moment, we're
not able to do that. All right. And
we're not able to decide that
yesterday's value was too cheap and move
it up. So, we're just creating more
liquidity out.
Watching this now, zooming in now to see
if we're going to find acceptance lower
at this point back to that old
imbalance. Can we come and flush down
underneath all of this now? Are we going
to get acceptance underneath this gray
box and really start working our way
into 39s and 700s, 690s, and maybe even
650s if we got very lucky? Big big ask
for the day because we've not been able
to move outside of anything yet.
Alex, can I ask what website you use to
see the sectors like uh healthcare, tech
stocks? Uh, yes. I I use Finn Viz. All
right. So, I use it for my scans as well
for swings. It's free. You can just log
in. So, it will probably freeze. It
always freezes when I seem to do it on
stream up here. Right. So, Finn Viz,
it's already frozen. It's such a dodgy
website. Come on. It really does not
like this site for some reason. Give it
a second.
Give that a second to load. There we go.
All right. So, if you come down. All
right. That shows you the breadth. As
you can see, healthcare is starting to
go red. It was very green this morning.
So, ES starting to sell off now. You can
see the sectors. And if you go here,
you'll see like all the top gainers and
the top losers. And you can actually
create some scans, right? So, if you go
to screener, if you're looking for
stocks, you can scan things like over
the 50-day or x amount of days up or PE
ratio, all lots lots of things. I go
through it all in the course.
Okay, back to the gray box. So, we're
starting to see potential acceptance of
lower prices here
back into that key area, initial balance
low. We're starting to see potential
acceptance of lower prices here. If we
start breaking down away from these
levels now, back down towards this gray
box where we found a bid earlier.
Remember, this is off previous days
profile. Right? When we look left or the
current week profile, we know that there
is a node here from 808, let's call it
down to 878.
Don't move that, Alex. If we find
acceptance under the gray box, we have
the 20-day at 750. So, we could target
750 and then we could really target 700.
So, watching this now to see if we find
acceptance lower for the short and we're
starting to come into the IV. Starting
to see aggressive selling here in this
now for a continuation. Second attempt
down here. Stop already moving down.
Let's see if how far we can move. Can we
break the low of day and get out of this
gray box?
Can we get out of this gray box? Come on
then. Nice ES starting to lose a bid as
well. I see ES sweep this low. Taking a
partial here towards this bottom end of
this wick where sellers got stuck this
morning.
And let's see if we reject this gray box
and a pull back inside. So now what I'm
now watching is to see if we're going to
do this to here and here, which would be
a nice way to end the stream. And we're
very aware that this can be a fail
break, a reclaim, and a go upside,
especially if ES sweeps this or one of
them sweeps this. So we don't see a
reaction here soon. And I'll cut the
runner again. And then I'll consider
readding if we stay Nope. If we stay
heavy at 820.
All right. Consider a read. If we stay
heavy up here. If we reclaim this. I
won't add.
So far so good.
Yes. Doesn't sweat, does it?
Spy is literally doing 5day 20-day
rotation.
Literally exactly what it's doing.
Right. Let's see if they start watching
this. Have we got any bids lower today?
Nothing under 780. Ah, 7:30. Okay. Where
what is 7:30? That is what I want. All
right. That might help if we can get
heavy here.
He's just come on the book down there.
Come on guys, just step on it. At least
wash. Watching ES for the wash here. I
want to be very careful if one of us
breaks the low and turns inside. I want
to be careful. Sellers keep getting
stuck around the sort of 79 area. So we
need to see follow through underneath 79
to continue to hold this. Here we go. Is
80 test.
Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on.
Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come
on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on.
Come on, baby.
Look.
There's that outlier. 90s.
83 is big level.
Big level. Come on. [\h__\h] do it. All
right. ES now sweeping. want to be
careful if ES reclaims IB here because
we just took the liquidity that we're
trying to attack here on ENQ. So ES has
already just taken this out.
Do not want to hold this all the way
back up to 820. Not going to give back
30 points in a rotation in case it
squeezes and read there. Willing to cut
and read there if we don't get this wash
down. I think we're going to get this
wash down. Come on.
Thank you. Right. Let's see if we get
previous week close now. Let's see if we
get previous week close now.
Oh my god, how patient have I had to be
for this today. All right, watching the
50s. We have a slight node. We have the
20-day at 50s and we're going to see if
we can get this. Let's go. [\h__\h] yeah. My
god,
how patient have we needed to be to
this? All right, let's see if we can get
this now.
We should break lower at this point.
We're into the 20-day here. 20-day is
basically right here into 53s where
where you can see my mouse can move you
to show you what I'm looking at higher
time frame. All right, here's my 20-day
this purple line. If we find acceptance
under this 20-day, right, this is mean
based on the Ballinger bands. If we find
acceptance under this, I'm watching this
node. Right, my expectation is for us to
come down here if we can wash under 50,
right? So, I'm trying to hold a runner
for this move here. And we also have
previous week close at 38. So 40 50 and
40s. We need acceptance under 50 and 40s
and then we will get 700 or 692s. All
right. So we built liquidity all day.
We're starting to use this liquidity
now. All right. Watching this little
level here and this gray box, this gray
level here. So if we can get under this,
then I'm looking for this and this.
Right. We do not want reclaims here now.
Okay. We can probably slightly adjust
this based on volume soon.
Yeah. At least we got something. Geez
Louise. Like it takes so much patience
to be willing to let the market chop for
ages and then just take what's
available.
Am I in? Yes, I'm in. Yes. Yes. Yes. I
don't want this to reclaim IB.
Do not want a reclaim of IB. We look at
um if you look at if anyone's watching
spy anyone has done the course look at
high of day on spy 5day look at the low
of day that we just tagged in spy
20-day right 5day to 20-day rotation
it's a very common rotation we talk
about it in the course a lot
back testing this gray box they must
stay heavy in and around here all right
I will not let them reclaim this and
squeeze me out back up to here if they
stay heavy here, then I'm looking for
that. If they reclaim it, I will cut
this. I want to see buyers caught into
this level. All right, we want to see
buyers come aggressively in that we're
starting to see here. This is good. So,
we want to see more of this. More
buying, please. Getting stuck. Want to
be careful. That auction at the low is
actually a very good auction of the low.
But if we see buyers caught stuck, we
will wash down. Here we go. So, there's
the buyers court. Can we get acceptance
under here now?
Let me show you in real time what I'm
trying to look for. Let's go, baby.
Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go.
50's big level. 50 is big level. Even on
the book, they're starting to try and
stack 50s. If we wash 50s, let's see
what's underneath. Yeah, still got 730
on the book. So, I would like to get
down into that 737 for me. The 730 on
the book, but 737 previous week close.
Important level for me.
Here we go. ES is really starting to
wash now.
Who's this buy that caught? What level
were you? 79. All right. We don't want
it above 80s. We do not want this above
80s.
Come on. Let's go. Come on. Come on.
Take out 50 and just wash to 37.
Come on. Let's go. Step on it. Step on
it, sellers. Get under 53. We're
outlying delta at 53. We got to get
under 53s here. There's a 235 lot
outlying delta at 53. We need to get
under 53 and then we can have some
drift.
Come on sellers, please, please come and
play. Come and pay me on a Friday.
Don't want it above 80 and I want it
under 53. I think we get continuation if
we get some strong closure under 53.
Please do not just wash it up without
hitting my last target.
We'll cut this above 80. Do not want it
above 80.
Out. Out.
out for me. I can always read
just out based on Oh, what's going on
there? Based on where they're uh where
they positioned. So, out on this can
read. I will read if we start losing
this bid. But this comes a bit of a
squeeze above 80. If they if they pull
back and hold 80 now, they can resqueeze
up. So out on this just based on what
I'm seeing on the tape.
They knock me out and [\h__\h] don't get
100 points. I will be absolutely
frothing.
ES rejecting that IB low. So ES is
actually being much much better. Came to
IB low to the tick but still holding the
20-day.
Why do I have a bad feeling they're
going to do this?
imbalance here that they're refilling.
Uh, you absolute [\h__\h] faces. You [\h__\h]
faces.
Oh, should have given it room. Should
have given it room. I can read add if I
need to.
Right. More buyers came in here. What
level are they at? 88
90s. They're selling 90s and 800s. I'm
not sure we're finished going lower yet.
It's a good reaction on ES. So, I'm out
of this at the moment.
Will read add if I can see enough buyers
get caught for the wash. Want to be very
careful if it's a break of low of day
and a reclaim just like we had earlier
in the morning. Right. So, being very
very cognizant of that. Is that the
right word? I think it's the right word.
Cognizant of it.
Right. Ray box
big level is over under
VIX into a pivot as well. So we're
looking for VIX to get back above 1760s.
Yeah, 1760s. Above 1760s we have a gap
filter 1780s on possible.
See if I left this 800
They're trying to squeeze 800 now. ES
still under its IB. They're trying to
squeeze through 800 to see if they lift.
They are offering all the way up to 25s
now. So, I' got to be careful on any
re-entry thought here. If we reclaim
initial balance, it would be a failed
auction. But this gray box is a big
level off the developing week like we
talked about.
Do we see some follow through?
Value area low on the day up at 820 for
me. 8:30 on here. 825ish
on Ninja. Buyers trying to step in for
this squeeze now. Like I said, they're
offering all the way up to 820 here.
So, reclaiming IB. ES still has not
reclaimed its IB, but ENQ is reclaiming
the initial balance and it's going to
lift up towards these 820s like we
talked about. That's why I didn't want
to sit in this for the squeeze. And
let's see if they resell this or not.
Otherwise, we go straight back inside
the range. So, it really depends if they
trap enough buyers up here and then
close back under 800. Certainly, if they
close under 790, there's another selling
opportunity. So, if this is a squeeze to
be resold, it could be fun.
This 800's key now
trying to bid the 800s. If we start
closing under 8790, I'll be reinterested
in a short again, but not before that.
It's good selling here. Nice. Let's see
if we can get under these 790s now. Big
pivot here. Back to that IB. Now, if
we've trapped enough buyers here, which
it looks like we have, we need to close
under 790 and we will get heavy.
We got to get back under the IB.
back under this gray box under the IB.
If we're going to wash, we're going to
have to do that. Not going to enter
before that
battle here. Big battle here. 800
reclaim. Still no entry for me. Not
underneath initial balance yet. So, they
can come up and test value again. So I
am willing to play short side if we trap
enough buyers in a push up which is sold
into
which is sold into if we close back
under here. Right. I'm willing to sell
that. I'm not willing to sell in this
shove up into here. Not yet. Not unless
not unless I really see buyers really
get caught offside.
ES reclaiming now as well. It's coming
back up to its New York open. So, here's
the squeeze. So, 20s is the level. 20s
to 25. Same levels we talked about
earlier. If they reclaim that, it's 50s
and 60s. Same levels we've talked about
all day, right? Same levels we talked
about in here, right? So, I need to see
buyers start to get trapped here and
closing underneath all of this to be
confident about new lows.
You guys saying
people
just made 4K from the range top the gray
box. Thanks, Alex. Give me confidence
for that. Nice. Yeah. So, you're a range
trader, which is perfect. So, you traded
from up here to down here. That's
perfect.
Perfect.
All right, here we go. Let's see if we
can get some closes under here or not.
Let's see if they trap some buyers down
here now. Still holding the level for
now. So, Ivy's still being absorbed.
Can you please show the fiveday and
20-day you're talking about? Uh, yeah.
I'd have to bring this over from the
other screen here
and kind of move you down into this. See
this? Can you see this chart here?
5day, 20-day.
That's the rotation,
right? And on Q's underneath, we haven't
quite made it, but that's the rotation.
That's how they build liquidity out.
That is exactly how they build liquidity
out on a high time frame. All
right, reclaiming or attempting to
reclaim value here. ES into New York
open in 24hour be very possible of a
squeeze back out if they get through
these levels. All right, so the squeeze
will happen. I will not be playing this
because it would be a range trade. We
should reject this and do this. If they
reclaim this, we will go back to high of
day. If they reclaim this area here,
they probably go back to high of day.
I'm waiting for confirmation. It's very
hard here while they do these washy
positions.
I'm watching for closes underneath the
initial balance to see if we can stay
heavy, if we can trap enough buyers
trying to reclaim value, which we might
well have just done. Yes, very hard
rejection of the New York open there.
Watching this now to see if there's a
short setting up. If we can start
getting heavy underneath the initial
balance,
we need to be careful of 780
and 756.
If we get closer, 780 is where a big
seller came in earlier.
still there holding the IB that gray
box.
We will see.
All right, 60 more likes for another
Apex giveaway. We got 25 minutes left to
do it.
Pass two evals on the short. Nice work,
mate. Nice work,
Chris. 800 on the funded. Calling it a
day. Nice work, buddy. Good work,
everyone. I'm just waiting for a
re-entry here. So, I've had one go at
it. Made some money. Waiting for a
re-entry here to see if we stay heavy. I
am not going to force my way in the
market. If they want to keep holding
ranges, I will not force my way.
Here we go. Starting to see some
heaviness now. So, if we can stay heavy
here, I'm interested in the short. It's
got to stay heavy here because I know
that sellers got stuck at 80, right?
Sellers got stuck at 80. Big levels, 84,
80, and then down at 56. That's where
the sellers got stuck. That low of day
auction is pretty good at the moment.
It's a shame we didn't um hit some TPS
on it or the final TPS in it.
Do I enter big and immediately size down
for TP2 and TP3? I mean, it wouldn't say
I enter big in a range day. It's not an
A+ trade for me. Um, but yes, I
obviously if we get to TP1, TP2, I'm
taking positions off. I'm not adding I'm
taking positions off. We're not in a
we're not in a trend, right? So, I'm not
adding to my winners in a market like
this. I'm just peeling off and moving
stops.
Which prop firms allows me to
immediately pass evals? Um,
Apex, you mean on the same day? Apex
maybe funded next bolt. I'm not sure.
I'd have to check.
Okay, back down to this same level.
Still waiting to see if we close under
this and stay heavy. If we can build
enough buyers trapped in here and we
close under this, I will look for a
wash. Otherwise, there's no play.
Lucid. Yeah. Do Lucid have one that
doesn't? No, I think Lucid is 50 and
60%. So, I think two days or or three
days on Two days is the is the quickest
you can do on Lucid, I think.
I think there's a wash down here. Are
they adding 17?
So choppy.
What would be my buy price? Probably
like I'm not going to buy it today, but
probably a reclaim of this kind of area
here. If they do that, then I would
expect we'd complete the rotation from
one side of value to the other because
that would be a failed auction under
value. We reclaim this, then I'd expect
we'd come back to the other side of
value, I guess. Again,
I'm not looking for that. It's not a
trade that I'm looking for. Same way as
I'm not looking to fade the top. I'm
just not looking to do that and wait and
see if there's continuation. If there's
not, I'm not going to play it. It's just
rules that I have.
What would the short entry look like? I
think we've talked about quite a few
times. It would have to be like this
right under here. Need to be a heavy
close and a rejection with buyers stuck.
If you don't get that, there's no short
for me anyway. what I'm looking for.
Now, I pin it every day. I pin the
anchored uh profile every day. So,
starting to reclaim or potentially
reclaim that previous week value high
right into that same node. ES back to
VWAP and the New York open again.
Yeah, for educational purposes. I've
just told you what I'm looking for. I
don't understand you guys who want a
signal. I've literally told you what I'm
looking for. So, where do you think my
entry would be? Like, I told you here,
I'm looking for reject of 50 and a break
of 25. Where do you think my entry would
be? It'd be here, wouldn't it?
It's [\h__\h] It's unbelievable.
Unbelievable.
You act like I don't tell you. I don't
understand. I tell you what I'm looking
for. It's not like it's like mystical.
I'm literally telling you. I draw it. I
even draw it out. I even draw it out.
Do I see value in back testing? Yeah,
I'm sure there's a lot of value in back
testing for sure.
Oh,
I know. I know they do. I know they do.
Can I put a traffic light behind you?
What? Green. What would it be? Like
green for buy, red for short, yellow for
do nothing. All right, let's see. Let's
see if we close heavy again here. So,
rejection of previous week value high.
We're still not underneath the initial
balance. Still just fanning around here.
Market doesn't know what it wants to do.
And we've got what? 20 minutes left. How
are we doing for time? 20 minutes left.
We're almost there, guys. Guys, we're
almost at 1,000 likes. Once we hit 1,000
likes, we'll do some more giveaways.
Maybe I'll give away one more
introduction course and one more Apex
account.
Oh my god, this is like so sloppy. So
sloppy.
All you got to do is like look at a five
minute right now. Have we got a five
minute here?
What is that? What is that? That is
dreadful.
That is about as bad as you get, guys.
That's dreadful.
Okay, back inside. So, if they hold
their rotation now, if they hold 23s, I
would expect that they drift all the way
up to 900s.
I would still be more interested in the
short underneath IB
at the moment. We've reclaimed it.
to value area low. This is the move that
we just talked about. Do they absorb
here? Do they now absorb here and then
go right back to the top side? I will
not be playing this long, but if you
were looking long, that's what you would
want to see. You'd want to see them
absorb 23s and start to lift to 8 880s
and then 900, which is what you're
starting to see. This is value.
If they can hold a bid here, big if,
then you're looking for that. I'm going
to look for this move here. That's what
I'm going to look for personally.
What is the Discord membership for?
I'm not really sure what that question
is.
The market's being a wally. It is. It's
making its mind up, isn't it's building
a lot of a lot of liquidity.
A lot of liquidity.
I'm I'm buying the initial balance
breakdown or waiting for the retest. I'm
not buying it. I'm I'm going to look to
sell underneath it. I'm going to look
for continuation under it. I'm not going
to buy a rotation play today. I've
decided I've already made that decision
from before we opened. Right? I made the
decision before we opened. I am not
looking to trade between these today. I
am avoiding this. If you go back to the
very start of the day, 9:15, I told you
I am avoiding this. I have zero interest
in trading this. If we base, I will
trade. If we base, I will trade. I will
not trade this. If you are a range
trader, there are trades here for you. I
am avoiding this. This is a decision I
made before the market opened. I will
not be trading this.
Like I said, it's h holding value. I
would imagine a break of 50s now is
going to lift you to 80s and then up to
the 900s.
So, if you are a range trader, it's
going to pay you pretty well by the
looks of it,
right?
Let's set
this up.
Okay, we're going to do another Apex
giveaway because you got me to a
thousand likes. Thanks for all the new
followers. Uh just type FCT once in once
in chat
and then uh we'll give it two minutes
and we'll pull the winner. So just type
it once.
Please don't spam it. It won't help you
win. It will make sure you don't win.
Please don't spam it.
So, you lifted into this area here.
Still waiting to see if my trade comes.
It probably doesn't look like it's going
to develop today.
Does not look like it developed. All
right. How are we doing? 30 seconds long
longer or so and then we'll pull the
winner.
I would love it if it gave me my trade
today. It'd be fun. But we will see. At
the moment, we're now holding value. So,
you're still holding value here of the
20s.
Alex will trade short underneath the
initial balance if it stays heavy and
we've trapped enough buyers. We may well
have trapped enough buyers now,
especially this big lot here that came
in at the last high, but we will see.
We've got to get underneath IB for me to
be interested. I am not interested
otherwise. No way, Jose.
Yes. Rejecting that New York VW. Coming
back down to its IB now. It's almost at
IB already and Q lagging behind it.
Right. Let's pull this winner because
then I'm going to have to uh zoom in.
Topseg.
Topseg, let me know you're here. Top
seg, you've won a free Apex account.
Topseg,
let me know you're here.
And all you want want you to do is email
me info@flowzonerader.com
with a screenshot of you logged in. But
just let me know you're here. I'll give
you 30 seconds to reply. We're still
holding this gray box. I'm still looking
for the same trade, folks. Nothing has
changed, right? Buyers are still trying
to bid off this. I am interested in this
move here and nothing else. So, I'm
avoiding everything else. Buyers are
still in control over this gray box. As
you can see, they're still holding it.
ES just held IB. We are just in full
rotation right now. Top seg, you've got
about 20 more seconds to reply. Top seg
21277.
Otherwise, we're going to roll it and
we'll just automatically choose someone
else.
Give you 10
9 8 7 6 5 4 3 2 1. Okay, we're choosing
someone else.
Mike Hinatx or Hinatx1212,
are you here?
Mike, are you here
coming down to this IB? I'm really
interested if we start getting under
this again.
Watching this very intently now, guys,
because I'm starting to see some heavy
action coming down towards these 790s.
Big big level here. I'm watching this
intently now,
especially if they reject value area low
and trade under the gray box, right?
like we've talked about. That's would be
preferable.
You just held a little imbalance there.
Yes. Still bidding off IB.
Yes. Nice. Thank you, Mike. Sorry, I
just see you replied. All right. Email
me, please. Uh info@flowzonetrader.com.
send me a screenshot of you logged in
and uh we are going to get you set up
with a free Apex account.
Congratulations. Don't forget guys, all
the prop firms use code FCT. Other than
take profit, you can use code flow zone.
That will always get you the best deal
on pretty much every prop firm out
there. I'm still looking for the same
trade, guys. Nothing has changed. For
those of you like, "Tell me when you're
in. Tell me when you're in. Tell me when
you're in." We got to get under this,
right? We got to get under this pivot
for me to be interested. Until we get
under that pivot, I am not interested.
Once we get under it, I will consider it
and I will be covering some of my uh
play down into low of day because we
have some sellers caught from 60 and
under. And then I will be trying to get
into previous week close which is at 40.
And then I'll be trying to get into
previous week point of control which is
basically just under 690. All right. So
we're coming down into this IB now. I'm
getting very interested now in how we
react. All right. So I'm watching this
now. So, I'm zoomed in to see if they're
going to sell through this and if they
offer me a trade or not. At the moment,
buyers are still protecting this node
here. You can see this shelf right here.
At the moment, they're still protecting
it.
Come on, baby.
It's looking good. There's a buy at
790s. There's a seller at 805. So, I
just want to see if we can get under
these and have this seller come and
chase down. Here's the 90s. Come on, you
mother cluckers. Let's have some fun
here. Let's see if we can get this short
now. Come on.
Come on. They're covering at 70. Here we
go. Here we go. Right. Watching 80s
carefully because it's where uh sellers
got stuck this morning. Here we go. Is
the 80s. Let's see if we get
continuation now.
Watching 80s and 70s. Watching for a
wash through 70s. Here we go.
Right. Ideally now we can get down into
59 and ideally now retest stays heavy.
Otherwise I will have to cut it. This is
like a few attempts at this trade today.
This might be the third attempt at kind
of the same kind of trade here.
Let's see. Already paying myself some.
So no matter what we'll make money on
this.
Come on man.
Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come
on. Come on.
I'm down to low day and snap it.
Come on.
Bids here at 70, 60, and 50. I want to
be careful into 60.
These are all levels.
All right. In here.
this delta up in here. I'm watching
these levels, right? So 80, 70, and then
60. And then if we get acceptance, then
we can really get heavy. At the moment,
we're not seeing it, right? Already
starting to reclaim IB or attempting to.
So gray box key, can we stay heavy
versus this box? Definitely versus 801s.
Right. Want to stay heavy versus 801s.
They are starting to stack 70 now. Big
buyer. Well, big is for today. Big is
for today here. Here we go. Come on.
Got to get under 70 now. Come on.
They're trying to protect it. It's that
big level we just just talked about.
Just showed you it on stream. Right.
Just this guy here. See this? It's where
that big seller is. We need to get under
that for continuation. If we fail to get
under that, we can squeeze, right? So,
be protective of profits. Make sure
you're paying yourself today, please.
back to IB, back to gray box. Probably
if we fail to break lower, this will be
fail a failure to make a new low. Shorts
will get caught. So, this is why we got
to be very careful here. We do not hold
on reclaims of 800. Certainly not.
Certainly not.
There's
IB test. They're going to come up for
800 by the looks of it. Any break of
800, I will be gonzo.
There's the 800. I'm out now and can
always enter back in later, but probably
going to call it a day there with seven
minutes left. Right. I owe you guys
another course. Right. How many have we
done? Yes, we do one more.
How did I win? I literally just entered.
I entered on the break here and I moved
stop. Right. And I take profit. I manage
my expectations, don't I? Right. That's
still 90 down to 60. Right. Still 25
points. All
right, let me set this up. We're going
to give away. Where is it gone?
All right, giving away one more course
here. So, just type course in.
They might still set this up and they'll
probably set it up without me if they do
it. Now, we just type course into chat.
We'll give one more introduction course
away
over 800. There's potentially a squeeze.
Certainly, if they go back inside the uh
value area, it's just messy right now.
That's probably me done for the day.
I've I've had a few attempts at that.
Made a little bit of money today, but
not a lot. Not great money today, but we
haven't had a lot to play with. No
continuation.
So, just type course once.
Give you guys another 30 seconds and
we'll pull that winner.
And then don't forget those in Discord.
We're going to do a uh
a live uh lesson afterwards.
Maybe just give me a minute to go and
get some uh some coffee.
All right, let's pull this winner.
Five, four,
three, two, and one.
Oh, look at that. Well, you can give it
to a friend or family member then, Nate.
Just shoot me um hit me up on Discord,
bud.
Hit me up on Discord because I know
you're already a member, but you can
give it to uh a family or friend or
something like that.
Nice to see a member win something.
Uh it' be in uh p it would be private
lessons I think. Or hang on let me have
a look. Where do we normally do it? It
will be have to do on the one we share.
If we go to voice channel we'll do it
there in general or where do we normally
do it? If we can do it in private
lessons and I can share the screen we'll
do it there. Let's have a look. Can we
do that? We should be able to I'll
announce it in the main channel, bud.
I'll announce it in the main channel.
Okay, it's going to do it now, isn't it?
Now that it's now that I'm out is going
to do it, isn't it? It's just sods sods
law. It has to [\h__\h] around in this gray
box so much that it drives me insane.
Um, we have built sufficient liquidity
now. I tell you what, we we've done the
move. We have built sufficient
liquidity. Now, uh I think that is very
possible. Now, if you're still in this,
you need a break under 70. That's where
the seller keeps getting stuck. I've
said it so many times. This guy here,
this delta here, you need a break under
70. It is a good auction at the lows,
but there is an imbalance underneath.
So, if you get 70s, you might get 60s
and 50s quick. And if you snap that,
then we're looking for 690. All right?
You're looking 690 if you can snap it
all. big if butts and maybe, but that's
what you're looking at.
Hopefully, it does it for you. It' be
really nice if it gives you if you get
from 790 to 690, that's a 100 point
trade to end the week with. So, you
never know.
Feel like you deserve it.
Did I ever DJ in Abodine? Yeah, I did.
Um,
remind me of the clubs up there. I think
I played a New Year's Eve up there like
a liquid and envy or something. I think
that was Abedine.
I'll text Steph in a minute and ask him.
If not, I did played quite a famous club
in Scotland, but I can't remember if
that was Abedine or somewhere else. All
right, here's your lower day break. So,
your next cover now is into this 38. All
right, that's previous week close.
Right, so your runners now. There's your
low of day. Oh my god, it knocks Alex
out just to take the piss out of me.
Right, swipes me out. Here's your lower
day. Okay. So, TP1, TP2, TP3, and if you
got very lucky, all the way down into
these.
Oh, you
Yeah, you you just you
you
[\h__\h] [\h__\h]
All right, they're adding at 50s and 45s
now.
What were the clubs called in Abedine,
mate? Um,
I think I p I might have played with
Ilas and Barentos down there. Up there,
I should say.
Ministry Liquid. That maybe that's what
it was then. It would have been the New
Year's Eve. I definitely played I'm pre
I definitely played a New Year's Eve in
Scotland and it might have been then all
right previous week close coming up
folks and if you get a snap under that
and then you look good for that move
towards previous week point of control
towards the 700. So you might well get
790 to 690. Uh for those in Discord,
that was like one of the trades we were
looking at today, right? If you think
about what we talked about in Discord
this morning. What did I give you this
morning?
Be flexible. Under 900 850 previous day
low possible over 900 26K 26100
possible. So we're under 900 under 850.
Under 900 under 850 under these kind of
levels here. 850
big level all day under that previous
day low. These kind of moves into these
are possible.
Here we go.
Congrats if you're in this. I think
you're going to get it into lunch.
Here's previous week close. This gray
line.
I think you look good. You should get
previous week close here.
Oh, it's hurt my feelings. It has hurt
my feelings.
Here you go. So close.
You need a rejection. Need to stay
heavy. Ideally versus 68s, but uh you
can afford to let it come up to 84s here
on based on where those buyers came in.
But ideally versus 68s and you're
looking for a 38 or 40 tag. And under
that, you're looking for previous week
point of control for your runners. [\h__\h]
me.
Cannot believe it did me dirty like
that. There you go. Right, there's your
tag. Oh my god,
what a
but but bastard.
Oh, just wicked me out. You absolute
cluck. All right, there's TP1.
[\h__\h] me. Wicked me out.
Right. And then you're looking for down
here. So you've just hit this. You could
have taken some off there, but this
level here, previous week close is
important. Next move is down at 690.
That's your next one.
Alex, why not enter on the pullback
since you missed it? Um I I just felt
like I had a few goes at it today, mate,
if I'm honest. Like I had a few goes at
it. I think I had we I traded this one
here,
hit TP, knockout runner, and we traded
maybe this one here. Took a little TP,
knock out on the rest. And then I had
another go here. Took the break a little
bit earlier. Came down. I didn't want it
to reclaim this shelf, right? Stop was
protecting this shelf. Knocked me out
and then went. It's just like three
three goes, mate, is is enough. Do you
know what I mean? Like sometimes the
market doesn't give me what I want. It's
just it is what it is. It is what it is.
Yeah. Well done everyone. And lot lots
of you should have had a big week. I
mean this this is going to go for you
now. This looks good. This looks good.
Now think about this now what we're
doing. All right. This is why it's
important to try and be patient and
position yourself for the moves. It
doesn't always work, but if we zoom out
now, right, if we zoom out,
we have a chance. Remember, someone said
we're really bullish today. I was like,
we're definitely not. We've left trapped
buyers. We sold yesterday. We have the
first pullback. They've resold this.
They failed to make a new high. They're
reselling this. If you break this low,
probability is you come down into here,
right? This is bearish
volume being built out. All right,
especially if we do this next week,
which would be fun. The bullish move
would be coming in a reclaim of that.
But that's when it gets uber bullish for
the market. Not until it's just
liquidity build out today. And it can
very easily be a bearish continuation
because we expect this point here to be
sold. And if anyone's like, "Oh, it's
hindsight." It [\h__\h] is not, mate.
Like
We talked about this here. Here we go.
There's the resell back down. That would
be the reclaim for the bullish move. All
right. We talked about it all. We talked
about it even on stream yesterday. We
talked about all of this. All of this
stuff. We talked about
65 649 for runners. Uh I would say
6590. So you can just call it 700 and
then yes uh 50. So 650. So 700 650 if
you want to make it easy for yourself.
580 and if you got very very very lucky
540.
This is going to kill me. This is one of
the hardest things with trading, right?
When you have three goes at something
and it goes on the last time when you're
not in it.
I'm only human.
How do I place stop losses, Alex? I try
and place them the other side of the
node, right? Which is why I got stopped
out here. See this node being developed?
I decided that instead of using the
whole gray box, I was going to use this
node which had been developed, right?
So, I placed my stop the other side of
this node and I got stopped out.
If id done it right based on this gray
box, which if we zoom out was based on
this node here from the developing week,
I probably would have been okay,
you know. [\h__\h] man. Like, here you go,
guys. You're almost there.
Oh, man. Well, look, I don't want to
hear any bollocks like Alex doesn't know
what he's talking about.
You're coming into the 700s. All right.
So, this is a 100 point winner for you.
This is tilt. This is what tilt looks
like. Thank god we've had a massive
week.
Uh Felix, I prefer uh uh Ninja Trader
personally, but it's a personal thing.
It's a personal thing.
Right, I'm going to have to get off
stream now really folks because I've got
to go and teach uh
my uh community now. It's been a great
week. Um fantastic week. Thank you so
much for joining this week. Thank you
for all the new subs. I cannot believe
how quick my YouTube is growing at the
moment. It's um all thanks to you guys.
I absolutely love trading with you lot
and uh it's so much fun. I know lots of
you are new. If you were new here today,
you're probably like, "God, that was an
awful trading day." It was. It was. I
can't I can't dictate the trading day.
It's one things like new new guys have
to understand. I can't dictate this. All
I can do is avoid this like we talked
about and try and fade outside or buy
above it and avoid this, right?
Understand the type of day we're in.
We're now getting that trade set up. Of
course, it's going without me after
knocking me out. It's just sods law, but
uh hopefully next week we get some
expansion modes. It's very possible. It
is very possible if we have had a failed
breakout on daily and weekly time
frames. It's very possible we have some
fun. Here you go. Oh my god. There's
your 100 point banger. There is your 100
point banger. There is your 100 point
banger. Well done folks. Uh yeah, make
me happy. W's in chat for anyone that
got that. And you can hold your runners
now. 650 is your next target. And then
uh 580s. All right. W's in chat if you
got it. Let me know who got it because
that will help me feel good as I leave
the weekend. Lots of you got it. Oh,
fantastic. Well, at least that's
something, eh? At least that's
something.
All right, big love everyone. Thank you
so much for joining this week. Um, don't
forget all the codes are underneath if
you want to give back to the community.
All right, the codes are underneath and
that's how I'm able to do this stream
for free. And uh, FZT is the best code
for most prop ferns other than uh, for
take profit. You can use code flow zone.
If you want to do the course, if you're
new here, go on my YouTube channel, go
on the beginner section, do everything
for free first. Make sure you like how I
trade. If you don't like how I trade,
it's okay. Go and find someone else. I'm
not offended. This is how I trade. This
is my setup, how I work. And uh if you
do like it, everything else is available
on my website, flowzonerader.com.
Peace and love, everyone. Make sure you
refresh yourself over the weekend. All
right? Do not sit on the charts back
testing all weekend, staring at a screen
all weekend. you will get burned out and
exhaust yourself. All right, go and have
a good weekend with your friends and
families and loved ones or your dog or
whatever it is you like to do. Make sure
you go and do it. Peace out everyone and
thanks for joining. See you on Monday.