Morning everyone.
Good morning everyone. I hope you're all
doing good. Let's move this down a bit
so you can see. Hope you are doing good.
Hope you hopefully you had a good
afternoon session if you traded FOMC.
Wasn't too much to trade there. a little
bit of chop, but the big trade that we
talked about all yesterday morning
setting up for that trap that happened
on the earnings report right into 4:00
did exactly what we talked about, didn't
it? So, do me a favor. Lots of you in
here nice and early. Smash that like
button for me and then I don't have to
keep saying it through the stream. All
right, so let's have a look on the daily
chart. We're starting to get what we've
talked about this week. You notice the
Ballinger bands, they are going to start
expanding now. All right, so we had
contracting Ballinger bands for quite a
while. The last few days we're starting
to base up here is allowing expansion of
the Ballinger band. And you'll al also
notice this 5day moving average with
this Ballinger band starting to take
effect. Doesn't guarantee a trend, but
it just means, you know, there is a
chance now that we're going to create
some room for it to move upside. Uh,
ideally, I would like to see an inside
day print uh a little bit longer into
the end of the week and give this chance
to really get moving. Right. Yesterday,
we talked about flipping this. This was
a red box right into potential demand
with that poke up, a dip, a hold, and a
drive out. We had it last night. What I
would say so far, we've had a failed
breakout. All right, failed breakout
overnight. That is all right. We're
holding this. So technically, we are
still bullish in terms of structure. We
are holding this. If we lose that and
come under it, there is a deeper
rotation like we always talk about. But
until that point, you want to be very
careful. We want to be considering that
inside bar, how we might play out today,
edge to edge. Probably unlikely to get
too much of a bid outside of this
because the bowls aren't extended enough
yet. All right, so just understand what
is likely to happen today. I would not
be surprised to see an inside bar today.
If we start losing 26,000, then we can
think about this move into the 900s. If
we lose 900s, then I would almost
certainly say that this is a failed
breakout then and we are playing a
rotation back down. Until that point,
we're watching to see if this holds.
We're going to get more clues about this
as we move into the hourly chart. So,
let's do that now.
And pull this up just so you can see it
a little bit better.
All right. This is the current week's
developing profile. All right. Here's
previous week value area high all the
way down here. Current week developing
profile. You can see this week we have
been in a constant grind from the
Sunday, right? Monday into Tuesday. That
was the dip and rip that we played on
Tuesday into Wednesday, which was the
dip and rip. And then yesterday, we
played that you played that pullback
short leg into this area. And we talked
about the trap happening somewhere under
here. Here was the trap underneath,
reclaimed, and straight back up. Right,
we've now built liquidity. The problem
is it did it when it ran out of time. It
did it when no one was really at the
desk. All right, that was the earnings.
There's the trap underneath with the dip
and the rip, but hasn't taken out this
high. Now, can this be bullish rotation?
Absolutely it can. All right, it can be
bullish rotation in here, but we are
boxed in in here. All right, the current
weak uh point of control over here
26100ish very very key as is previous
day value area low. This area here here
is key for bulls to defend. If they
defend it, they'll be looking for a
rotation back up to the previous day
value high. But you can see overnight,
one, two, two attempts to get over it.
Not doing too well. We're building out
lots of volume down here. So, I would be
watching this both ways on the tape
today. I would be highly expecting a
rotational kind of day, an inside kind
of day, which means edges are more
likely to play today than trends. And it
means you're going to have to be careful
with making sure you manage your
positions. Lock in those profits. see
money take money. So if we hold dips
down into here this morning, there's
probably a rotation TP1, TP2, maybe even
TP3 if you get lucky. But it's also very
possible, right, that we get stuck here
and we come down this way and we do
this. If we lose, right, if we lose a
bid under here, we need to be careful
that it doesn't come and revisit all the
way down here. You can see where we
building out a cluster down here, down
here, down here, down here. So need to
be willing to play the other side of the
tape. If we start to lose bids 26,100
and stay heavy. All right. So it's a big
level. As we drift into this probably
early morning, we're going to see
sentiment either fake out and bid back
up or we're going to lose that bid and
rotate. But this is your range being
developed. All right, you can quite
clearly see that they are starting to
settle in here. It is not a small range.
300 down to less than 100. So at least
200 250 points. You do not want to be
the wrong side of that range. All right,
onto the five minute. And you can see
the same thing we've talked about.
There's the dip and rip
into that key level. Dip and rip.
There's the hold. There's the bid back
up during GlobeEx. London goes sideways.
Get stuck. Cannot take out these key
levels up here. All right. So, that is a
failed break. Lower high. Lower high.
Lower high. Lower high. And we're
rotating back down towards this. Just
depends if they redip it. rotation and
liquidity building stage of the market.
Um, if you're struggling with seeing
that, all you have to do is go to the
indicator right up here. What are we
doing? Higher time frame, we are
building liquidity. Lower time frame
currently bearish, right? We're in a
sell,
but the higher time frame building
liquidity. So, understand that we're
between the lower time frame algo and
the higher time frame algo. You can see
between these at the moment while it
makes its decision.
Overall though, technically the market
is still bullish overall for now. for
now unless this becomes a failed
breakout. All right, let's go through
some of the other names. We can start
off in the ES.
Let's have a quick look here.
So, alltime high break yesterday and
trading back inside. We're not seeing
follow through away from here, but so
far still technically bullish all the
time. We're holding sort of 78. All
right, somewhere in here. all the time
we're holding this technically still
bullish. We start to lose that certainly
if we lose this then that deeper
rotation right this will start to be
sold off. So they bulls really need to
hold this and start to get going. If
they don't we're going to see that
collapse that we talked about yesterday
right they will need to see momentum at
these highs. Remember we've got Apple
earnings tonight as well.
If we go on a lower time frame just see
where we're at. We're opening up pretty
much flat.
All right. Some very key pivots here.
You can see all you need to look at ES
is this right here.
This is quite clearly a key level that
we are still currently holding. All
right, previous day low and that's your
rotation from the current high to
previous day low. If you start getting
weakness under there, that's where
we can start seeing that bigger
rotation. Right, let's have a look at
the ETFs. Make sure they're all lining
up. Okay, we start on the spies. We've
just done ES. Same kind of story there.
And same kind of rotation. Let's zoom
out here a little bit. Yeah, right into
this nugget. This cluster here still
holding dips. Can it do this is the
question today. If it can't, then we're
just going to build out the liquidity. I
think we're probably going to build out
liquidity today. That's what I think we
are more likely to do. Q's, same story.
All right, tapped through the highs
yesterday uh in the pre-market. Never
able to get back up there to that
all-time high and just building out more
of the same again. And if we start to
lose the bid here, it's very very steep
up this week. We think about from
Sunday into Monday, but we think about
from here, right? We're pretty steep up
from this open. We can expect that move
down here and still be okay. All right.
So, just be aware of that. Be aware of
it. Let's have a look at the VIX.
Starting to climb, isn't it? Still in
this big channel that we've talked
about. All right. Still holding in the
16s. It's got previous day high 7. So,
we're watching 1720 1738
and then yeah, 38 pivot might even get
us up to 1950. Quite thin in there
through that. So, we need to be careful.
We can also extend this out a little
bit. Make sure this is accurate
somewhere in here. There we go. All
right. So, we need to be careful. We're
still in that channel, but we can see
it's still bullish rotation on the VIX,
right? Everyone's saying that this is
like going to collapse. It hasn't.
Bullish rotation squeeze back into the
channel. All right. So if this is was a
uptrending regression channel, we
squeezed out, pulled back, squeezed out,
pulled back, squeezed out, pulled back.
We haven't collapsed under this channel
right now. I would still have some
certain warning signs up about this,
right? Very quickly going to have to get
through the mag now. Apple earnings,
remember earnings are tonight. Held that
dip yesterday, like little fake out
under reclaim. So want to see if Apple
can get back up to these highs. If they
start bidding it up before earnings
today, do they position themselves
before earnings or is this going to be
profit taking? They're expecting weak
earnings. Softy earnings weren't too
bad, but they sold off on the conference
call because their uh guidance was a bit
lower than expected. Everything else was
good yesterday. The other dip on Apple
be down into these 50s. Right, Amazon
gapping down into key level here. So,
big drive out yesterday. Faded it, held
the held the uh the gap and now is in
kind of no man's land while it makes
that decision into that pivot. Goo, nice
drive up. There you go. Nice drive up
into the earnings. Big peak out. holding
gains well. So Google right now I mean
we can think about this but we can also
think about this up here as another
level. So does Google need a back test
to make sure it stays firm meta big
earnings. Remember I'm long meta. This
is starting to pay really well. Now
anyone in Discord who took these longs
remember I'm long from down here 88s. We
were looking for this move back up
towards this pivot. We've got it. That
is a fantastic trade to uh sort of start
this year from somewhere down here. I'll
have to get my uh bler up to see where I
was, but I was long down here and we're
starting to really get motoring now.
That's a massive trade. Very, very happy
with that one. Gapping up and pretty
extended into some key levels here on
Meta. Want to be careful. This pivot
here is what I'll be watching now. So,
we can set a price alert there to see if
it can get through and have
continuation. Microsoft Softy, like I
said, sold off on that on the earnings
call back down into its pivot. So, the
big question here on softy, does it hold
this? If it doesn't and we start to get
weak, you'll see this market start to
rotate, but that's uh kind of the only
one right now seeing a lot of weakness.
Nvidia trying to hold its gains, opening
up flat again. All dips into 90s. If
those keep holding, Nvidia's okay.
Tesla, uh, still in this choppy
rotation. If you're trading to Tesla,
you're probably not having too much fun
right now. I would say here is is where
it's boxed in right here for the whole
of this year so far. Rotation, rotation,
rotation, rotation. All right, it's just
boxed in. We can have a quick look at
some of the broader names. Oracle still
dropping down. I'm starting to get more
and more interested in that. If we can
come down into here, it is of interest.
And
Netflix
still long in this just a tiny tiny
piece on. I still think that we've got a
chance to flush lower. So just want to
see if we retest lower and what happens
down there if we trap some shorts. AMD
starting to get boxed in here. You can
see the levels. So I've drawn it in.
Fail breakouts. Failed breakouts. Fell
breakouts, fell breakdown, fell
breakdown, fell breakdown, rotation.
That is pretty much it, folks. That's
pretty much going to cover us. Not much
else we want to look at today, I don't
think. We can have a quick look at the
uh 10 year. Starting to get going.
That looks very dangerous. Remember, we
talked about the breakout above this.
The last year or so, we based above it.
Now, we're breaking out above this. This
is not good for the market. I'll tell
you, it's really not good for the
market. I guess the last thing we should
look at is the Dixie, which is probably
still selling off.
Yeah, still got a chance to break down
lower. Is gold still pushing? Yep, still
basing on gold. So, if you're trading
gold today, you're just basically
watching this box. All right. And if you
start to lose that, you know what's
going to happen. Otherwise, it's still
bullish. Silver still going. There's the
same story here. Those are your pivots.
It's still holding until you see a
backside. Remember, we've talked about
this. We haven't seen backside in
silver. Everyone's too too keen to get
the short as it will be a crowded trade
that. All right. The more shorts that
pile into that, it's starting to feel
like a small cap, the higher it's going
to go as they get themselves caught. All
right. Couple minutes left here to the
open.
Move that from yesterday. There we go.
It's a little bigger for you all. Right.
So, starting to uh lose this bid at PDC.
Anyone who took the short up here was
really nice into VW up on the lower time
frame. Algo protecting previous day
value area high. Any of these, maybe
some of you took this short. I think a
couple of you in Discord did. This is
looking really good, right? And if you
can get the full rotation to value area
low, you're going to be a very, very
happy trader this morning. That's a good
move. Really good move to start the day.
Okay. Good morning, everyone. Um, I'm
never going to be able to get through
all the good mornings anymore like we
used to do. So, I'm sorry about that.
There's so many in in here now, which is
fantastic.
But uh I hope you're all doing good.
What about US 100? US 100 is the same as
ENQ. So it's exactly the same. There's
no difference. You're just trading CFD
for it. All right,
let me get my chart sorted out here. So
we've got some support structure down
here at previous day value area low. We
can see we actually get thicker
Um, from where's that edge? Yeah, sort
of 98s
down into Have a look at this. Is there
an old maker point control down here?
There might well be. Yes, there is.
Yeah, 98s down to 90s
and even 72. So 98 down to 90. Yeah, in
here we get a bit thicker. So I wonder
if they can come and test that today.
Um, but yeah, neutral bias today.
Overall, we're technically bullish, but
uh we are opening up an inside bar,
inside value. All right, inside bar,
inside value. More likely to see
rotation. The only thing I've got my eye
on is BIX.
Bicks.
All the indicators on the bottom of the
chart. This is delta and the bottom
one's volume.
Volume and delta.
All right, folks. Good luck here. 40
seconds left. Make sure you've gone
through your morning prep. Make sure
you're fit and able to trade. All that
good stuff,
right? Don't be taking a trade if you're
on tilt or you've got a car what I call
carryover tilt from yesterday or
anything like that. Just take the day
off or just sit here and and and learn.
Don't be risking capital if you're not
fit and able to trade. Make sure the
market conditions are something that you
like at the moment. For me, they're not
they're not my favorite trade. But we
will see if we flush down and hold or if
we flush down and stay heavy if there's
a bigger rotation that's going to take
place.
All right, 5 seconds here, folks. Let's
see what we can get.
So, into value area low to start the day
by the looks of it. Magga mixed bag
right now. The big loser uh Microsoft
8.46% down.
So, protecting in front of value area
low back to previous day point of
control. If they go through point of
control, we can look maybe for the
rotation to value area high. So this is
the rotation today here to here and just
outside of it and just outside of it to
the underside like we said inside bar
inside value rotational day today until
it proves otherwise right that can
change that sentiment can change
I've just said a million times it's a
neutral bias today we are an inside bar
we're in rotation it's probably more
likely that edges are going to play are
going to pay as we build out liquidity
unless we start to see the offers start
to print underneath the key levels or
bid did start to pe print over the key
levels, I'd be neutral. Give you a
readout on the MAC. Tesla 1.45%
up. Nvidia 0.06% up. So, basically flat.
Microsoft still bleeding, 9.33% down.
That might very well go SSR if it keeps
bleeding. Um, Meta over 10% up. Google
1.66% up. Amazon 0.23% up. Apple 1% up.
Natron is mean. Thank you for that.
Appreciate it. Glad that video helped
you. Glad that video helped you. All
right, so the rotation still in effect
this morning. New York open straight up
to previous day point of control. Can't
get through it. Back down to New York
open. That's already happened twice. And
if they keep failing, they're going to
come back down for value. All right,
this is just the rotation is where we
are.
So, probably going to try and attack
value right now as we start drifting
lower. Here you go. Here's the move to
value. So, in this short, trimming some
into value now as we start to lose this.
And we're just in a runner now from New
York. And if we reprint it, we go back
upside. I'll cut the rest out. But just
in here to value, trim some. If we get
down into here, lovely bonus, but we
don't expect that. It's a nice bonus if
we do. But two failures at previous day
point of control said enough for me to
just have a little scalp down there.
Okay, up towards VWAP again.
and see if they get stuck here.
Microsoft now SSR I think on I'm
assuming it has gone 10% because I just
saw it at 9.98%. So I'm assuming they
didn't save that 9.97 again. I'm going
to assume Microsoft would be SSR now. So
for tomorrow there might be a bid on
Microsoft as they fail to sell it. I
would imagine
IQ's coming into their block which they
keep defending.
Still in this with a runner all the
time. We're rejecting New York open.
Still in this with a runner to see if we
move lower
but already locking in no matter what
here. Locking in.
will not hold it above uh sort 44s.
Nice. Here we go. See if we can get this
runner to go for us. Here we go, folks.
Beautiful. So, still protecting that New
York open blue line. If we get follow
through under previous day value, we're
looking for these blue boxes. Previous
day high, GlobeEx. And if we get really
lucky down into this,
just don't be adding too late. We're
positioned for this in case it wants to
do it. But our expectation is a
rotation. It very well might be that
they want to bid at previous day value
low. I would like to see them bid down
here or down here because I'm in the
short already
tape. See if we can see some follow
through here.
Nice.
Some sellers keep getting caught down
here in the 10. So, we need follow
through underneath that right now.
Otherwise, they're going to get
themselves caught.
Move my stop down a little bit here.
VPO now at 22s. Really nice. Here we go,
folks. Into these next TP areas. Let's
get some volume on here.
Really good. Fantastic. Here's our
trade. Locking in money here and we will
hold runners now just in case we get
down to this gray area. Beautiful. Nice
win to start the day. So, two failures
into previous day point of control. We
lost the New York. We trade down to
value and we see how deep we can go now.
Very very very nice. Yeah. And Microsoft
getting absolutely crushed here like
expected. So now SSR over 10% down. That
thing's in big big trouble.
Right into these 150s. So coming in
towards the edge of range. Make sure
you're zooming out. Remember this is
point of control on the developing
weekly profile where we are now. This
right here is point of control on the
developing weekly profile. It's a big
level that bulls will want to defend. If
we stay heavy under here and they fail
to defend it, I will be looking to trade
all the way down to 25s and possibly
down to that 26,000. But I expect this
to be a very heavily contested level
right now.
Yeah, if you if you're in this short
with me, you should have locked a good
chunk in. W's in chat for me. And let's
see how low we caning go. Here we go,
baby. What a nice one to start the day.
Come on. Come on. Let's come all the way
down. Let's be very kind.
So I would start moving your stop down
aggressively because we are being
aggressive on the tape here and the
bounce back will be violent if and when
they do it. Gap now filled on the ES gap
now filled on the SPY as well. So just
be aware of that. We have an efficient
market. We're obviously well below the
gap on the Q's. VIX is absolutely
ripping through that 22 level 1722s or
1718s that we talked about pre-market.
We are still in this short. We're still
looking for more but we are now managing
our runners right watching this blue
box. if they can start turning this into
resistance. If we think about what this
is, this is a huge level on the weekly
profile. If we start losing this on the
developing weekly profile, if we build
into this and lose it, I'm looking for
this. It might not even give us a chance
to get any more on. It might just slide
all the way down at the moment.
Really good.
Really nice. What an absolute pear. What
a beautiful day. All right, gray box is
your next cover. Then the green line
short from here.
See if we get gray box, which we just
got.
And underneath gray box, we'll look for
this. Right, if we go all the way down,
we'll look for this. But these are big
cover points. Beautiful.
So, you should be locking in some good
chunk of change into here, guys. This is
about 100 point trade already. And this
is about the fifth day in a row giving
you 100 pointer. Let's see if we lose
this gray box and we really get motoring
and we are going to use this as an
overunder now. All right, this might be
a key level.
Beautiful. Beautiful. Look at very heavy
tape. This is what we like to see. Heavy
tape once we lost this coming down into
this big whole number of 26,000.
Still heavy tape. We're going to get
this previous day low, this wick
hopefully from overnight where they
dipped and ripped. So, just be careful
down here. You do not want much size
after this.
Beautiful.
It's still bidding down at 75. So, I
wonder if we can get a flush beyond
this. Really, it needs a pullback at
some point. We're very extended from the
flow zones now. So, just be careful. You
might want to manage your position. You
might not want to sit through this
pullback because it might be violent
back up to this red line up here.
So, if you want to take it all off now,
you can. You absolutely could take it
all off. That's a big trade. It's well
over 100 points for you to start the
day. And we're what, 7 minutes into the
day and you've just had a 100 point
banger. You are welcome. You are
welcome. VIX absolutely ripping. So, VIX
into its next pivot in towards these
1744s all the way up to 17 sort of 60s.
So, it might get stuck there to VIX.
Here comes the pullback. So, if you want
to get out of this now, you can. I still
think we have a chance to move lower,
but certainly some shorts came in under
22, but I'm expecting a pullback. Um,
and then see if they resell it in
towards that red box would be ideal.
They're still defending 50. So, I would
actually like them to lift this up all
the way up here and defend it up there
if I'm going to add on for a second
trade here, but we will see.
It's still bidding down at 6 uh 26,000
below. Here comes the lift. Can they
lift this a bit higher? I'm not going to
play this long. I want to see them lift
it higher and see if we hold this now.
Right. If we hold this now, we've moved
outside of previous day's value. This is
current week's point of control. I want
to see if sellers are willing to defend
that. If we scream through that, then
we're going to go on a squeeze. But
right now, I'm wanting to see, right?
Are sellers willing to defend up here?
They can set they can defend in front of
it. You can see this shelf here. But I'm
wondering if we just let this through
and then redefend it. Also
watching ES and Spy into the PDC, right,
Spy already there. ES almost there,
right? So they flushed under. I'm
interested. Do they defend PDC? Spy now
starting to reclaim it.
Can this have a shove up is what I'm
thinking now. If I'm going to reshort, I
want to see a shove up and then stay
heavy. We are developing nodes down here
now. Remember
this was the area that they dipped and
ripped um last night. This was the area
where we were looking for that trap last
night, right? It looks like they're
defending early here. We might get
follow through further. Yeah, we're
coming down for that previous day low
now. Shorts definitely keep getting
stuck in
and around 10 now.
I really want them to lift this for me.
Yeah, lots of you locking good in there.
Good money in there. 5,500. That's great
money. Nice way to start the day.
Alex is the best on YouTube. Thank you.
That's very kind.
Stuck in a range. Well, we will see,
won't we? We will see. Like we talked
about, we were inside bars, but that
inside bar finishes at this green line,
right? So, the daily inside bar finishes
here. We are moving outside of value.
Previous day value area low now being
left. So if we come back up here and
fade it, I expect lower here and fade
it. I expect lower. We need to be
careful of traps in this area. But right
now the tape is heavy.
This is the edge of the inside bar. And
this is down here is current week value
area low. And we have liquidity down
here the 900s if they really want to do
it. Here it comes. So coming into
previous day value, previous day low,
this is your next cover point. Do not be
a dick for a tick, please.
If I come to to Italy, you'll take me
for dinner. Oh, thank you. Sounds good.
475* 10. There you go. That's a nice
winning day, isn't it? $4,750. Nice
work. All right. Previous day low here.
This is your TP. And then through this,
we're looking down here. If we get
follow through, this is the edge of the
inside bar, right? Think about the
daily. This is the daily low. If there's
follow through under here, we will be
looking for actually down here into this
blue box really into sort of 9 920s.
There we go. It's a tiny tiny tiny size
left. Now I'm basically out of all of it
and uh we'll see if we get all the way
down here now. So the next target is
down into this blue box. Right, this is
the edge of current week value, but
there is actually a big node down in
this blue level. So if I zoom you out, I
can show you why and what I'm looking
at. It comes from the higher time
frames, comes from this hourly, right?
We just let go of this node. We traded
to this node. We let go of this node.
We're trading down towards here now.
Right? You can see this. All right? So
this is thin. We're repricing the thin.
They might very well bid off there. We
don't know, right? We don't know. We're
just playing this trade right here,
right now for this reason. And then we
can deal with what's next once we get
there. All right. So, dip and rip so far
is what they're attempting to do. I'm
not convinced yet. This gray box is key.
Relief over the gray box. We go to red
box
and we're trading back down to that 5day
on the ES as well. GlobeEx hanging out
underneath now. So 5day on ES
and previous day low on the spiders
and VIX now at that next key pivot 1760.
So, anyone who joined me in the
pre-market, we talked about these pivots
coming up on the VIX,
right? We're trading into
this next key pivot. Now, we've ripped
through this. We're coming in towards
that next block and the top of the
trend. Okay, we're coming into the top
of that trend.
All right, we might well get this move.
We might well get this move, guys. We're
almost there.
I guess you could target down here if
you really wanted to. It's quite a lot
without a pullback.
It's buy now through previous day low
into its 5day. ES through the 5-day into
GlobeEx previous day low. Still low
hanging fruit for ES. VIX is motoring
like we talked about. talked about
premarket, everyone talking about VIX
being bearish. It ain't. It ain't. It
was still holding its channel. I had
a strong sneaking suspicion we would
have the ability to do this today if we
left the range, which we did.
Still a heavy take. All of the mag other
than uh meta getting absolutely crushed.
Very heavy. Here we go, guys. This is
the edge of current week's um developing
profile. So, this is value area low on
the current week. This is the final TP
for me. If we got down in here, it would
have to be on a flush. I'm going to take
everything off into here most likely cuz
I'm expecting a rebid. So, we're coming
into it now.
Previous day low here on ES. I'd like to
see just one more little swipe if
possible. Just a little dig down into
the 910s or something. Watching the tape
here. Yeah, we've got liquidity under
900. So, I'd really like to see one
little swipe. I don't want to be a dick
here. Um, the opening range is very,
very big.
We're already at 250 points uh of that
opening range. First 15 minutes. Here we
go. They're starting to try and find a
bid into this. So, this big key level
starting to bid off it right now. You're
welcome to take it all off if you want
here. I'm going to try try and hold to
see if I can get to 900s, but I don't
really want it to lift.
Come on.
Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Just do
it. Just complete it. I don't want to
sit through a pullback.
Be very careful of this auction down
here.
Right into my key levels.
Come on, baby.
Yep. Done. There we go. Done. Out. Thank
you. Thank you for playing. Thank you
for playing. That is an absolute
monster. That is a 214 point trade to
start the stream today. There we've had
100 point plus yesterday.
Going back to bed. See you guys later.
No, I'm just joking. I'm just joking.
It's uh 6:46 in the morning for me. That
is a lovely way to start the day. Do I
ever tell you when I entered? I I'm
pretty sure I did. I'm pretty sure I
told you. All right, looking for this
now short side. If we're staying heavy
on the table, we planned it out
pre-market, especially once we lost
value.
There was only one entry for me up here.
We never retested a key level. So, I
will re-enter. Now, if if you're looking
for a re-entry, I will think about a
re-enter somewhere in here. All right.
If I see balls get trapped, I'll think
about that play there.
It was quick. It was quick today. Yeah.
I mean, I can't I don't get to choose
how quick it is, guys. I can only watch
the tape. The moment I kept telling you,
look, the rotation is happening from
previous day value area low into point
of control. They kept getting stuck and
once they let go, it was like, okay, we
can't get through the New York open,
we're going to trade down. And I
positioned for that trade down. So,
here's the squeeze back up. Why? Because
we hit the key level. We are likely to
come and retest this gray box now. And
point of control on the current day is
in that gray box, right? So, the relief
is back upside to here. And there might
be there might be a reshort opportunity
as we come into this. We will have to
see if buyers get stuck or if they're
going to do a full reversal. This is
also an big level for me. in this gray
box and then above it. Right?
So you can see the importance of
covering into key levels. Not being
greedy. Must cover into key levels.
Like them just to lift this a little bit
higher and see if it offers a reshort
here. So if we trap buys here or the red
box, I will think about the trade back
down. I won't. My expectations will be
lowered now because we've done the main
move. So I will think about only if I
see buyers trapped. All right, this kind
of move down into here now. All right,
if we trap buyers, if we trap them up
here, I'll look for the same move. But
I'd be looking for something like this.
If we start to trap buyers up here
or at least expect that pullback move
this shelf here, you can see VPO just
trading VPO previous day low trying to
be reclaimed here.
Watching the tape to see if they start
trapping by soon. Like one more little
shove up would be most ideal.
Looking pretty good here into these
26,000s. I would like a little lift up
towards 30s.
Value area high in the day 50s. That
would be ideal. Watching these 26,000s.
I would like a lift up first if
possible, but will position. Here we go.
Starting to see some weakness come in
here. We might get this move now. Might
not even make it, which would be
annoying. Would rather size up higher.
would like one leg up higher first, but
this might be it, folks.
Yep. Okay. Trading this back downside at
the moment. Taking some partials into
some of these imbalances. We have
imbalances down into 61s, which we're
coming into now. Trimming some here and
then we'll hold some. See if we can go
lower day
through the next imbalance 50s. And then
there's one down into sort of 35s.
Paying myself on this cuz we don't know
if they rebid off this, right? We don't
know. Sellers got stuck down here. We
don't know if they rebid off this. So
the trade is from here to here. I would
have loved it from here to here, but the
trade is from here to here. If they
rebid this, they can do second leg up.
And we can think about the same thing up
there again. There we go. Out of this
already. Just just filling those
imbalances on the way down.
Right? So we can make that make sense
for you on here.
I was looking at in here. See these
imbalances? All these green blocks,
these imbalances. So once these buyers
got caught,
these buyers got caught. We used their
pain to trade into here and we defended
this. So I'm all out. It might now flush
back down without me possibly. That was
the trade from here to here.
Let's see if they have follow through
for you guys. I'm out of it already.
Didn't sit through that.
All right, while you guys just figure
this out, let me just get my bottle of
water. I've left it next door.
So all those imbalances now filled
back into value area low for the
developing week. Remember this blue
cluster, this blue box underneath that
is a very thick cluster that we've
developed this week. This is a very
thick cluster and previous week value
area high is here.
Maybe they give you follow through. I
might have taken that too early.
The volume profile right now, where is
it anchored to? Uh, today's open 9:30
open.
How can you see the imbalances with just
volume profile and CVD? Um, you can't
see them with just that. You would need
footprint which is what I'm using right
so it it's on here
but it's on the screen I'm trading
remember I'm executing on ninja trader
folks I have footprint on my ninja
trader here comes follow through heavy
delta right this is where sellers got
stuck this morning into these 30s so
from 30s down to the edge of auction
into tens is where they get stuck if you
get follow through under here now you
can see this little shelf if you get
follow through under here I'll be
watching this low to get snapped see if
you can run into the edge of this this
is the thick
level I'd say into sort of 85s and if
you get follow through under that well
you might well come all the way down to
previous week value.
Having a good bloody go at it. There you
go. More sellers got caught there at 10.
Just be aware of that. They came in very
heavy there at 10.
So that you have got breakout sellers at
the low of day right now. Just be aware
of that. There's some absorption on the
tape happening but think you're going to
get the 85sish because they keep adding
bids down there lower right now.
May I please know the key level it
turned from? This is a it's the current
week uh volume. There's a big cluster
down there. If you build out if you look
at the profile from the Sunday open all
the way to today, you will see a big
cluster which is this blue box. Right?
That's what you're thinking about. If
you're thinking about the sell point,
well, we sold through current week point
of control, right? developing point of
control and the current uh and the
cluster above at 160.
The other thing to note, we've had many
many many P-shape profiles this week
without much of a rebalance.
Okay. Blue box key level.
Key level.
Q is also holding a key level. VIX
holding around a high of day right now.
I'd say next level for VIX to trade up
to will be those 19s all the way up to
sort of 1950s, 1958s.
We got to see if it rebids on the VIX
because it's it's been quite spicy this
morning. You got to expect a pull back
on the VIX and see if they rebid those
sort of 1750s. Right, starting to build
out a bit of a range here now while they
start to build out liquidity. Remember,
we've had a 250 odd point move downside
today. There hasn't wasn't that much of
a squeeze back up, right? We didn't even
hit this level here. They're building
out liquidity. They will want to trap
more buyers in if they are to come lower
for today. And obviously, they will want
to trap more shorts in if they are to
have a squeeze out higher. So, your easy
money trade for the day has absolutely
gone. It came very earlier, very, very
early.
I just are definitely not looking for a
buy or sell now. I just heard you say
that you were short and was curious. It
was during development of M1 candle. No,
it was
once these guys had got caught. Right. I
kept saying I'll be looking for buyers
to get caught. They got caught. I traded
short. That was it. It was a pullback
because after we've had a big move down,
right, we expect a pullback. The
pullback came into previous days low
into a node. I would have preferred it
higher, but I didn't get it higher
because they got stuck here. So, I play
that short and I covered into this cuz
my expectation was that shorts probably
get stuck here.
I don't care about if the candle's
developing or any of that bollocks like
candle closure. I I'm not at a level
where I need to give a [\h__\h] about that.
I care about who's trapped. If they're
trapped in one second, I'm going to play
their pain straight away. I don't need
that candle to close.
And the moment we move away from someone
trapped, I'm in.
Yeah, smash that like button for me,
folks. What settings for the order flow?
There's a free video on my YouTube. I
put it out last week. All the settings
that I use are on there.
But it comes down to personal
preference. I just look at delta. But
all I care about is delta. All right,
still rejecting this here. This is your
overunder for sentiment for right now in
the immediate future. This is your
overunder where we've just moved point
of control to. All right, buyers will
want to squeeze above that to the top
side of this range, possibly even up
here. You can see value for the day has
moved down quite significantly towards
my gray box down towards here. All
right, that is now your value. This
would be a big old B shape. All right.
So, this might signal the end of the
upside auction cuz we've gone from
Pshape to Bshape at the moment. Assuming
we close in the B-shape, that is.
You were all long, right? Today. Good
job. All long. I'm not sure what you
mean.
What determines trap signs?
Offside delta.
Offside delta at key levels. Just want
to just see if they're adding bids lower
right now. Yeah, 85 still there. 70
there. Thick level at 50. Thick level at
40. They're bidding so much lower here.
And there's a lot more weakness possibly
to come in this market now.
Oh, that might have been a really poor
cover point here.
Kind of crazy, isn't it? you get 250
points and you're like, "Oh, think I
could have get 400."
Okay, 20-day coming up for the ESP
spy not too far away. It would have to
trade 90s for that 20-day.
Next level's down here, previous week
value area high. So, this node here is
pretty big. If we lose that, you'll kind
of come straight down into here. And
this is the weekly close, is it? Are you
sure?
Previous week close. Yeah. So that big
gap fill into the previous week. That
would be giving back the whole week.
It's very possible.
Big sell there. We haven't had a big day
like this for a while. It's nice.
Maybe we have another leg up. Um well,
we will have to see. Um, we are pulling
back to potential RBS levels, but it
really going to depend. Can it can it
hold, you know, 830s?
If it can't hold 830s, then I'd expect
we will trade 700s today. And it will
need to hold that on a dip because if it
does not hold that on a dip, like I've
talked about numerous times, if this
becomes a giant failed breakout this
week, then we have a lot of pain coming
in for this market.
So if we don't hold this, we will trade
700s.
This would be another cover point here
for most people.
Nice, Greg. Glad it helped.
Yeah, flow still very bearish.
Big sellers coming in down here. Just
watch this delta here. Still follow
through. They're looking for value area
high. Now, this is previous week high.
Previous week value area high was your
next color point into 30. Kicking myself
now that I'm not in this. Here we go.
Very big follow through. Probably all
the way down into here now. So, we're
thin down into this.
Oh my days. Oh my days.
Going to kick myself. Can tell already
tell I'm going to be kicking myself.
Oh, this short that we took here could
have held it through. Never mind. Never
mind.
Never mind. Right, back to previous week
value area high. See if they defend this
now and come down into this blue box.
And tell you what, if buyers can't
defend this, it is good night market.
Heavy heavy heavy heavy heavy take.
Previous week close is 38. 738.
Previous week close is 738.
This box here and previous week point of
control is 690. So in here
buyers must defend this higher time
frame. Buyers must defend that or it's
good night.
Good night market.
It's a my two trade today with that
first one and this one.
That is a shame, isn't it, Alex? You
[\h__\h] idiot.
Just held through it. Just let it figure
itself out anyway. Is what it is.
Looks like we're going to go for a
previous week close here on the ES as
well. VIX still going. Absolutely
ripping bases right now on the VIX.
Have I considered a volume profile
mentorship? I mean, there's a there's a
course on my website.
You can buy the courses on my website.
Everything you need is in there.
There's no one ones if that if that's
what you mean. I don't have time to do
one-on- ones.
Right, big's coming up to that 19s.
Heavy heavy heavy tape down here is my
expectation.
Cluster now built at the 800. So 800
will probably be be 800 and 815 will be
a squeeze trigger higher
um just for the counter trend little
push out back and then they will
probably try and resell it down to the
lows. Just so you know this these nodes
here can be squeeze trigger highs. I
expect them to try and defend here
definitely certainly to defend up here.
But if you're in this short just make
sure you know you don't want to be
adding down here. You want to be moving
your stop to protect some of this
looking for this fade paying yourself
into some of these levels.
I would not be adding short now at these
lows. You're getting very close to your
cover points.
Here comes previous week close coming up
now. Gray line on your screen. Blue box
underneath. And I would imagine they
will want to trim down there.
Do I have a video identifying trap
buyers and sellers? Yeah, it's all on my
course. You will have to do the course
volume profile and order flow course. So
I would advise that you do stuff for
free on my YouTube first, then do the
20our course and then do the volume
profile and order flow course that you
understand structure how the market
moves, why it moves, all those good
things.
I volume node at 700. Uh yeah, exactly.
So it's, you know, six 696 basically is
previous week's point of control and
it's the weeks before that value area
low. All right, so it's multiple things
down there.
Multiple multiple things down there.
Back to this node at 800 that we just
talked about.
This is your key level 800 and 815. If
they get through that, you will see
squeeze relief.
back towards this 800 like we just
talked about. If you get through that in
8:15, you might get squeeze relief up to
value area low. The big sellers came in
at 850. Just so you know that the big
sellers, it came in at way up at 850. We
have imbalances all the way up there.
There we goes is the squeeze relief. So
28 800 to 8:15. Now if they get through
8:15, we can viably see 850 here for
squeeze relief. So if you were short,
you probably don't want to sit through
what might be potentially coming here if
we get through the 15s.
Oh, but how did Alex know? Because I'm
reading the order flow. I understand
where we're moving and how. Right into
value area low. This area here is the
area sellers must defend. Now, they fail
to defend this. This is the big relief.
If sellers defend this, they will have
one more go at coming back down. That's
why I saying you do not want to be short
down here.
I'll be honest with you, I didn't really
have any good trading mentors.
I just didn't. My trading mentors
probably taught me 90% of what I learned
was the worst thing to learn.
Okay, so defending 15s and 20s into that
imbalance back down to the 800s
buy side imbalance here at 80. I would
say a big buy stepped in at 70 and we do
have a decent auction at that low. It's
not huge access. We haven't quite closed
the gap. Tell you what, ES did ES did
close its gap. All right, so ES did tag.
We might have missed it by a tick. Let's
have a look. Previous week close on ES
was 94575. We hit 94 Oh, we didn't close
it. We hit 947.
So, we're a couple points short.
Still think they want to try and get
into it, but we will see.
starting to get tight here on the tape.
10 to 85. Starting to get tight. It's
probably one way or another is going to
get caught. Just watching this liquidity
build out very very tight on the tape
here.
Still think there's a flush in this just
to come and run everyone out, but we
will see
what what can I say about the psychology
of wanting to go long from here?
Why do people feel that urge? Because
they think it's gone down so far, it
can't go down any further. So, your
natural instinct is to try and buy it
back up.
or a lot of people's natural instinct is
to try and buy it back up.
Be very careful
if they get acceptance through here of
this back up into that
and we go back to the 15s again. We can
see this rotation to the 15s previous
week value area higher here. They go
through this, they will get a relief
because this is very very thin. Sellers
will want to defend this level here.
They will not want this going through
here because they will get run out
fairly aggressively potentially up
towards 900. So they will attempt to
defend this.
Nice.
How much more juice has it got?
Good defender 15s or 20s, but there or
thereabouts. This edge, you see this
edge right here. We're building out
profile now. We're building out volume
into here.
It's a little messy how they've done it
twice, but that's what they've done,
right? Sentiment is still lower until
they can get above that. This is still
the target.
Big buyer came in at 70 early this
earlier today. All right, that's where
the huge buyer came in at time was this
10:04.
They are still adding liquidity lower.
We still haven't quite filled that gap.
So, it's almost there.
We go. They're going to try and get
through these 70s. 70 is the key level.
It's where the big buyer came in. Just
want to see if he turns up again.
There's lots of bids here. We're going
to trade through him. We go. There's a
70s through him. Now they're adding a
45. So, we're going to snap it. We
should trade low of day here and get to
previous week close.
Can I talk about this relative to flow
zones? Well, the flow zones are in
bearish, aren't they? What the flow
zones doing? thick bearish price. Every
time we come up, we're rejecting. Come
up, rejecting. Come up, rejecting. Price
is still bearish. Look at the flow
zones. It's telling you it's bearish. No
reason to go long. Right. What we doing
up here? Multi-trend bearish.
Right. We were in liquidity building
phase before the market opened. Once we
let go of that liquidity, it was good
night. Right. A market so close to
filling its gap. Just can't quite do it.
We're at the 20-day on the QQQ, which
keeps finding a bid. We are under the
20-day on the SP on the ES. Sorry, we're
at the 20-day on the on the SPY. We're
not the 20-day on a QQQ and ES keeps
finding a bid right in front of that
previous week close. This gray line here
be nice to see that filled, but it's not
filling it right now. So, back to the
top side again. And relief can happen
over here like we talked about if they
can bully their way through back through
previous week value area high.
So, they will need to try and bid over
this. And if they can't, then all we're
saying is we're in the previous week's
value. And that rotation can take place
in previous week's value
or all the levels, all the horizontal
line, not the value levels, but
everything else previous week close like
all the open high, lows and closes of
the weekly and daily candles, all the
GlobeEx levels, all the uh opening range
and the initial balance are all on
there. Yeah.
It's stuck at previous week value high
again. No acceptance through. Back down
to VPO which is now trading around the
800.
Like to get another trade here. Just
don't think it's going to give it to me.
I'd like to see it flush lower, rinse
everyone out, and then see if it traps.
Don't really want it to do the same as
yesterday and not flush everyone out.
I'd want to see everyone flushed out.
Really?
What for a long rotation? If I was going
to look for a long rotation, I would
want to see this happen first, wash
these guys out, then reclaim this, and
then offer that rotation back up.
Not until then. Very much like
yesterday. Like if if it does this and
just does this, I'm not going to touch
it.
I don't think the auction's finished
yet.
There we go. Lower, lower, lower, lower.
Come on
into these imbalances. 70s again. We
keep talking about this 70 guy through
him. We should go to previous week
close. Now
we got to say under 70 we should go to
previous week lows.
Put that wakey wakey.
Big sellers keep coming in at the lows.
They're trying to get us down to that
previous week close. They're desperate.
Come on. One snap down to 40s will do
it.
Here we go. Here we go. 60s.
Price has to stay under 70 now.
Here we go. Come on. Watching ES because
it's about to do the same move and close
its gap. Here we go, folks.
Thank you.
Oh, baby.
Beautiful. All right, job done. So, I
just took this from here to here once I
saw them trapped and out of that. Just a
scout. Last level here. if you're going
to hold is into the 690s, but I would
imagine down here they will try and trap
sellers now.
If I was them, I would try and trap
sellers now. Uh, if they let go of this,
well, [\h__\h] me. It is good night,
sweetheart. It's all the way down into
this.
So, I'd imagine you'll see some sellers
try and get caught down.
All right, job done. Job done.
So, last trade, it was a small trade for
me. I didn't want to trade this side but
once we built you can just think about
as flag can't you once we build this
liquidity once we keep getting them
stuck above 15s then there becomes the
opportunity for the low hanging fruit to
manage this position here into here nice
and tight stop
job done
I'm not holding runners beyond that now
I might be stupid like earlier and
regret not holding runners but for me
that is enough that's a what 60 odd
point trade
here was a 40 point trade and that was a
214 point trade. So we're over 300
points for the day and we're into the
area where I think they will want to
defend it there or thereabouts. I'm
probably done with the shorts now. I'm
not interested in any more shorts.
Not interested any more shorts unless we
bleed underneath previous week point of
control. They're absolute adamant on
bleeding under that. I will show you
what I'm looking at if we're going to do
that. I don't think we will do that but
can't rule it out. If we are going to
bleed underneath this node, right, this
is quite thick. So you got to be
somewhat careful. Then this opens up,
right? So here bid bid bid. We think
about this trend line. Bid bid bid bid
bid bid bid bid bid bid bid bid bid bid
bid bid bid. Failed to move higher
failed to move higher. Two failed
breakouts. Once we lose that trap buys
and snap, right? And what is the
breakout point? It's here, right? That
was where we broke out from. This is the
pull back in. We can probably bid up
from here back towards 26,000 now either
today or tomorrow. All right, even if
it's going to be resold, we can probably
see something like that or we can see
something like this, right? But I would
imagine somewhere around here they will
try and bid back up to this node which
is why I don't want to be short anymore
now. That is it done with the shorts.
Hopefully that makes sense to you all.
We talk about those higher time frame.
What is the pullback leg? Where does it
go to? How do we position oursel for the
next move?
Now I'm pro projecting along. Are you
saying um I'm imagining that it might
take some time to develop. It doesn't
happen have to happen to develop today,
but I would imagine somewhere in here.
All right. Doesn't happen have to happen
today. They might want to dip below and
come and do this tomorrow. But I imagine
there's a retest back towards here.
That's going to happen at some point.
Where's 26,000? Towards here. All right.
So, I'd imagine this happens. It doesn't
have to happen today. Right. Unless
they're going to do this and really come
down into here, which I would be a very
big ask. I would imagine there is a
relief leg back up higher now. And then
once it gets up there, if it goes
sideways, we build out liquidity to go
high. If it comes up and they reject it
and trap buyers, then it will be the
lower high to go lower.
So try and make this make sense for you.
We don't know. All right. If this has
been the trend, let's just think about
this is the trend since last week. Boxed
in breakout retest up up up.
Here's the trap. Fail to break higher.
Lose this. That's the snap. Right. This
is what we played this morning. We're in
this back down to this area. Our
expectation is we're not going to keep
going down. We don't think it might, but
normally you would expect what? A
pullback leg, which is probably going to
go to where? Well, either here or here.
Now, once we get there, we don't know at
that point, right? If we're going to go
sideways to build the inverse head and
shoulder to go higher or is this the
first lower high set leaving trap buyers
to go lower? We will make that decision
next week probably, but my expectation
is we will drift back up.
That blue box coming in pretty good so
far. All right, so starting to see that
squeeze back up starting already. And
the big buyers came in at 800. So if we
get through 800s, there's more upside
here. Imagine they're trying to protect
in front of 800s.
Hopefully this makes sense to you all
like you especially you guys who are new
why we're trading and how we're trading
like why we're trading what direction
we're trading in I guess is a better way
of saying it why what our expectations
is why I'm done with the shorts now why
for me low hanging fruit has gone we
always talk about trading the low
hanging fruit my expectation now is
probably going to be you know shorts
will likely get trapped near the lows
and we will probably see relief back
upside to some sort It might might not
be today. Like I said, this gray box is
a big big area. Previous week's value
area high is a big big area. But I can
tell you what, if we get through this
and shorts get caught down here, this is
probably going to happen. All right, so
let's just look at the low of day
auction and see how we actually look
down there. Is it a good auction low?
It's not the best to be honest. That's
not that good. Good selling in here, but
I don't want to see buyers at the lows,
so it might not be done yet, but we will
see. The last two days has been a bit of
a messy auction at the lows.
Guys, there's well over 1,100 of you
watching right now, which is fantastic.
Stream's growing great. You guys are
making serious serious money. Can you
please, can you please, please, please
just hit the like button for me, please?
Right. It doesn't cost a thing.
Absolutely nothing. I'm here trading for
free, giving out education and some big
big trades for you guys. Okay, didn't
get all of that. I'm sorry. My bad. But
we got the first leg. Should have held
the second leg. And now I'm kind of done
with it.
So just uh smash that like button for
me. So here's the the lift up. So if you
want to play the counter trend, you can
think about this now. Maybe you got long
from the blue box. If you see the market
start to base over here, then you'll
probably get this relief up here. All
right? So maybe you go long from here to
here. If you see it base, maybe you get
this leg up here. If you want to play
the counter trend leg, that's what I
would be looking for. And just remember,
you haven't flipped the flow zones or
anything like that yet, and you're not
over previous week value. But this is a
nice squeeze from blue to gray. And you
might well, if they can base here, you
might well get a pop through sort of 30s
all the way up into 900s. It's very,
very possible for that counter trend
leg. All depends if shorts willing to
fend here or if they want to defend up
here.
Is the indicator fixed on the right of
screen? The session volume profile? No,
it's anchored volume profile. Anchored
volume profile.
What is the red box next to the New York
VW? It's just like a supply channel that
I've got, right? It's old point of
control. It's uh current week value area
low developing week and it's point of
control from the week of Monday the 12th
of Jan. So, it's a big level. You can
see we reacted off that level, right? It
was demand, we reacted off it. We
reacted off it. It was blue. We snapped
through. I now know that this can
potentially be supply. So if we get
relief, it can be into this. This is an
old PC and it's been thickened up from
today as well.
And it's also this is current weak
developing weak value area low.
So lots of confluence up there.
It seems price always looks for point of
control. Am I right? Yeah. Especially
when it's naked. But yeah, obviously
point of control, you just got to think
what point of control is. Point of
control is fair value. All right. Why is
it fair value? Because it's the most
traded price by both buyers and sellers.
So if if buyers and sellers agree on
price, it's going to spend the most
amount of time and build the most amount
of volume up there, which means it will
be the point of control on the day. So
if they agree on price, which currently
they agree that this is fair price. Now
if buyers decide shortly that this is
too cheap, we will try and auction
higher. If sellers decide this is too
expensive, we will try and auction
lower. Right? I'd imagine they will try
and get through here and do this move
like I talked about. But you have to see
if they build out the liquidity to do it
because they will need what to do it.
They need sellers, sellers, sellers,
sellers, sellers, sellers stuck who then
become buyers who then offer this and
then probably see a rejection from there
back down if they're able to do it. I'm
not going to trade the counter trend.
I've made my money today like we talked
about. Low hanging fruit's gone, but I
will sit here and help you guys as much
as I can.
What's my win rate? 100%. No, it's not
100%. I'm joking. uh it's normally
around 66 to 73%. But what I will tell
you with that, which I'm very very
honest about, lots of those will be like
break even plus one. So they won't
always be like today, right? If you were
here last week, I think it was last
week, you would have seen me three days
in a row get knocked out, break even,
and missing 100 to 200 point trades.
three days in a row, but those will all
show as positive trades on my bladder,
but they're positive by like five 10
points. They don't [\h__\h] mean [\h__\h] Do
you know what I mean? Pardon my French,
but they don't. So,
win rate,
it might it might be uh it might look
better than it is, if that makes sense.
There's quite a few break evens in
there, but the difference is I'm trying
to position myself for these moves. If
you join me on stream, you will see I
will try and position myself for these
moves. Like even here. Wow, that's poor,
Alex. That's so poor. But I just thought
we were going to hold that. But there we
go. Missed I missed this here. That's a
shame.
But there we go. Didn't like what I saw
on the tape, but there we go. It's all
right. Be kind to yourself, Alex. Be
kind.
Still haven't filled the gap yet. Uh
yes, we have. This gray line is the gap.
Cash gap is right here. So, we have
filled that gap. Same on ES. We've also
filled the gap on ES. We've absolutely
filled it. Cash gap right here. Gray
line. We've filled it. It's absolutely
been filled.
All right. It's been filled.
You see ES doing exactly the same thing.
Filled the gap. Building out profile,
building out volume. Break above here.
Probably gets relief up into that. If
you want to take the counter trend, like
I always talk about, hardest trade in
the books, the counter trend relief, but
you're adamant on trading it.
What are the benefits of being a member
of this channel? Not much really, I
guess. Just supporting me, getting more
shoutouts. If you ask a question, I will
answer it because it will show up on my
screen. I can't answer all the questions
now, especially as we get bigger and
bigger on stream. I try to answer as
many as I can, but obviously then
members will get preference. But if you
want to support the stream, that's a
good way of doing it.
How do I find where the gap was? The
close cash gap closed.
GC swan diving. Is it? Let's have a
little look. Let's have a little look.
See, have they gone risk off on
everything? Oh, they have. So GC's just
closed its gap as well. So next thing
you'd be looking at is these lows down
here. See, I haven't got any volume
built out. But yeah, you could look at
this pivot in here into 265. And if it
lets go of that, there's an old low of
190. This looks very, very much like the
same. Bid up, bid up, bid up, coming
back into key level. I'd be like going
risk off now at this point. If I was on
GC, right? All you have to do on GC if
you didn't take this break was just take
this break here, right? Take this break
here. Very thin. You can see lack of
structure in there. Straight back down
into here. Break down into here. Run us
down into there.
Same thing, same setup, same kind of
thing that you look at all the time.
Do you have trap participants? Is there
a shelf? If there is, can we get
involved somehow?
Why do I think we crashed today when the
big tech company's earnings are tonight?
Well, most of them were last night. Um,
it's not really I wouldn't call it a
crash. Not yet. But right, let's go.
Let's go over the regulars on on the
channel can tell me why we're doing
these moves. So, let's start on the
daily. Right, you regulars tell me what
did we expect up here and why, right? If
you're a regular, you tell me what we
expect up here and why. Right? What do
we expect?
There you go. Ballinger bands. Ballinger
bands. All right. Ballinger bands. So,
we were running out of room. We talked
about it. These are starting to expand,
but we can't get over these. We can't
get over these. We can't get under
these. We can't get under these. We
can't get over them. We can't get under
them. We can't get over them. We can't
get under them. There's some edge for
you. But before you do anything else,
you can look at that. Now, did we know
we were going to sell hard today? No, we
didn't. We didn't know we were going to
sell hard. I actually thought we'd
probably have an inside bar, right? I
thought we'd trade down into here and
see if they can hold the bid and go
inside and build this out, right? To try
and open this up. But we didn't, which
means what? Well, this becomes trapped
buyers, right? And now we're starting to
lose this. What does that become? A
failed breakout. All right. So if you
think about all the participants who
position net long, remember I've talked
about all week the rotation happened
here Friday, right? We started buying
Friday, Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday. You
don't want to buy the breakout, guys.
You don't want to buy the breakout. You
want to be positioned for the breakout
for this very reason. Right? They didn't
hold the breakout, which means what? All
these buyers are now becoming sellers.
And all we're doing is trading back
down. So now we've cleaned up all these
stops. We've filled this gap. Remember I
talked about this gap? We have
efficiently filled that gap. Now the
market has become efficient. We talked
about this. You can go back and rewind
the streams. I said if they're going to
be really nasty, we will do a fail
breakout. We will fill that gap. We will
lose the bid and we will now come all
the way down here and clean all this
out. That is why it's happening. It
doesn't matter what the catalyst is.
Like it really doesn't matter. It what
matters is the volume's caught, right?
What matters is the volume's caught. And
then we go from there down a time frame
into like an hourly
right this right here.
Where's your volume from the last few
sessions? If we think about this from
Tuesday, all right, from Tuesday bid up
Wednesday
and Thursday morning, right? Globeex. So
you got Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday,
Gloveex. What happens here? These are
all trapped buyers. They become what
under here? Market sellers. What do we
do? We use their pain. Where do we come
to? Next key level
confluence. Next key level. So old point
of control. Old value area low. Old
point of control. Old point of control.
This is the old balance that we just
broke out from. This can still
technically technically this can still
be a breakout and pullback like I've
talked about. If they bid off here and
come back here and build liquidity, we
will then have room to go higher because
the Ballinger bands would have moved.
But they can also come up here, lose the
bid and absolutely slam this. My
expectation, like I talked about, we
probably will come up here
maybe tomorrow, maybe Monday, Tuesday,
next week. What happens then is what's
going to be absolutely pivotal for the
rest of the uh quarter.
Tuesday, how do you say it? Tuesday. Oh
my god. Monday. Yeah. Come with me on a
Tuesday as I take you through the
market. I will show you where the
market's going to.
Doesn't mean I'm currently bearish for
the future. I think it's too too early
too early to say. I was bearish for that
breakdown to here.
If we start losing these key levels on
those like big weekly profiles.
Yes.
Previous week point of control.
Still trying to come into it. Thanks,
Josh. Appreciate you joining. That's
very kind of you. Okay. S uh ES keeps
rejecting that 20-day.
I'm just wondering, do they want to
attack the lower Ballinger band?
Because ES is already trading through
that that 20-day and it's staying heavy
there. Q's coming into 20-day now.
Why do we never see an influencer talk
like that about markets? They do it
about everything. Come with me.
Shut the [\h__\h] up.
And they always talk so quick. There's
no break. Come with me as I take you to
my best restaurant in LA. Oh my god.
They serve their absolute best peeking
back. It's unbelievable. Look at this f
stir fried rice. Shut the up. Get a job.
Get a job.
Okay. Previously point of control. Jeez,
what a trade, man. So, they still they
still held these sellers. They didn't
give that relief above it, right? They
still held this level. They've traded
down to PC. We're starting to run out of
levels here. We honestly are. This is
like probably the next spot and it's
starting to look very, very bad for this
market. Really, really, really, really
bad. Uh, I can give you a readout on the
mags. Probably a good thing to do right
about now. So, Tesla 2.29%
down. Nvidia 1.73%
down. Microsoft 11.78% down. That will
be SSR tomorrow. I will be watching
that. Meta holding its gains. Come on.
cuz I'm swing long meta 7.29% up. I
wonder if I should, while I'm talking
about that, I'm going to have a quick
look. Google uh 2.44% up uh down. Amazon
1.87% down. Apple pretty much flat. Let
me have a look. Should I be trimming
some of my meta position quite possibly
now up 15% on that
average price is 590.
Give me a second here, folks. Just want
to see if I want to manage this because
we've probably filled that gap that I
was looking for. In fact, I know we
filled the gap.
Picks this pull back. It's the close.
I'll wait and see. Long from where?
Average price 590. So I'm long from
here.
Why is I'm only up 15% then? That don't
make sense. Check that out. I want to
see if we can get up into it. I think we
can. But we filled that gap, haven't we?
Yeah, maybe I'll trim a little bit.
Maybe I'll just trim a little bit.
What day did we buy that in the in the
swing, guys?
It's last year, wasn't it? So, it was
down here. Bought in November.
Sell a little piece there. There we go.
Um,
yeah. Any of the rest of Discord? Any of
you still in that long with me? Let's
see when I bought it. I have to have a
look.
We got that gap filled. It's what I was
looking for, which is great.
Found a breakdown here.
Market's still bleeding.
I'm going to be looking at this at the
end of the day thinking, why didn't I
just hold my short all day long?
Where's the swings?
Where was Meta? What day did we get in
there? Call it
Netflix.
Oracle. Oracle.
I can see it. Maybe I did it in the
wrong tunnel. I know we like that. ND
uh what you guys saying? Does initial
balance have two levels? Yeah, the high
and the low. The low is right here, the
purple. And the high will be the purple
of the high which be high day all the
way up there. We ain't coming back for
that today.
We are not coming back for that today.
This is starting to look very very very
bad. Look at the size of these two
hourly candles.
Please don't get short down here guys. I
know it's still bleeding. Please don't
get short down here. You're you're
literally asking to get run over if you
do that.
Come with me as I take Meta Swing Long.
Oh my god.
Okay. Value keeps moving down. You can
see the edge of it here. They've
defended this now very very very well.
All right. So this is pain point for
sellers. All right. They do not want it
above this. We are still bleeding away
from this. Buyers had a chance to try
and do this. They couldn't do it. They
didn't build the liquidity to do it.
Flow zones still stay in a cell.
Multi-time frame sell.
I am uh well, I'm miffed. Uh not upset
cuz I want the long. I'm just miffed
because we would now be up Oh my god.
Almost 500 points. If we hit this, it
would be 500. Oh god, that's painful.
That is painful, folks.
I'm sorry.
Was the opening 15 minute concept still
valid? Uh yeah. Well, it's right here.
So, if you risked to the mean of uh the
orb and you faded outside the orb, yeah,
you're that that's your trigger. It's
that white line right here. That's your
orb right here which is currently value
area high on the day very much would
have worked
basically what we took here we just
didn't get the continuation when I
wanted it
and the blood is still very present in
this market things not a day to be
trying to bid on it that's for sure
I left 20k on the table yeah probably
and some to be honest there we
All right. This is the next spot, I
think, potentially.
Is that here? Yeah. 600. That's probably
the next spot.
Where's the low volume node? 540
to 513s.
Let's think about uh
that Sunday open low to the high of
week. We're now in the golden pocket as
well. You can see these orange lines.
We're now well into that golden pocket.
So, you don't want to be a new money
short down here. You really don't. That
doesn't mean you want to be long, but
you really don't want to be a new money
short, right? We're at like we've done a
70% fade since the uh
yesterday's high. We've pulled back over
70% now. Don't want to be new money
short. Blue box coming up here, folks.
And 620s on the cues.
Vick still going.
The Vicky Vicks is still going.
Alex, so more trapped buyers with price
moving down. Is 830 in play for a
squeeze up? For more trap buyers? Um,
you you need trap sellers for the
squeeze up? You need trap sellers for
the squeeze up. Right now, Delta's been
very, very, very heavy this whole way
down. It just depends if and when they
finish with the auction. They're just
dumping inventory right now. It's
probably around here. And if not, then
can keep coming lower. But like you
don't want to bid. You're going to need
trap buyers. So you're going to need if
you're going to play that counter trend,
which I always say it's the hardest
trade in the book. I don't try and trade
it. You're going to need something like
this. And you're going to need trap
buyers, you know, down here and then a
reclaim of profile and then a squeeze
back up into each level. But you're
going to need to respect each of these.
Now,
how do I get the blue boxes? I draw them
on just based on old volume areas,
right? They're just based on old volume
areas on previous week profiles.
What profile am I using on TV in the
settings? This is anchored volume
profile. All right. So, anchored to 930
and I set it to two ticks. If you don't
want ticks, you can set it to 1,000 a
row.
So, I'm going to build out a node down
here like we just talked about, right?
This is the type of thing you want to
see. And then you want like a flush
under it and a reclaim of it. If you're
going to be the counter trend long
because we're extended away. So you want
like a flush under and a reclaim. And
then if you're absolutely adamant on
playing that counter trend, that's what
you'd want to see. You But for me,
you're just bidding against the tape.
You'd need to see something like this,
this, this, this, and this. Otherwise, I
just would I in fact, I just wouldn't
touch it long anyway. We're just dumping
inventory. But each to their own. I
would say sellers have got caught now at
30s. So, if they don't get an expansion
330s, they've got caught, but you're
going to need to see it pivot over this
node for you to have that counter trend
long. I really would be very skeptical
about taking anything wrongside today.
We're in a big trend down day. We're
just absolutely melting. Ask yourself,
is there a reason to do it? Blue box
coming up here.
And then if we trade through this blue
box,
probably talk about into here maybe.
And this thin node all the way down to
534s.
So blue box now tagged.
How often do they dump inventory every
one to two months? Uh, really depends
how extended we've got and how trapped.
Um, but if you have a look, we did it in
July, did it in August,
we did it in October,
we did it in November, and then we've
been in a range since. This is the
first. I guess you could argue like
early December there was a bit of a
dump, but not not like this. This is on
a fail breakout.
Oh, well, there's your 500 pointer.
[\h__\h] That's hard to look at, man. That
is hard to look at. We had the best sell
of the day.
Trading's cruel, isn't it? You think
you've done really well with 250 odd
points
and then it does another 250 plus.
Oh god.
Oh my god.
So, you turn it on at the start of the
session. AP. Yeah, I anchor it at the
start of each session.
Starting to see these sellers try and
pile in at these lows here. There still
bids down lower into 600, but it's
getting a bit wonky down here.
Definitely getting wonky down here.
they get themselves caught there be a
nasty swipe.
They are piling in right now.
The long would happen for a base over
640 in my mind. Over 640 there's
potential for a squeeze just a small
counter trend squeeze. So here's the
move back towards 640 probably. So it
all depends if they defend this or not.
Now,
where did we tap then? 35s. And they
defended it successfully. So, still no
squeeze over 40s. The gray box still
holding up, right? Gray box still
holding up.
When I trade Ninja, do I use ATMs? I do.
Yes.
Uh I just trade I I use a minute chart
but I have a third party um
uh city for my profiles. All right. So
like this.
All right. So come back to these 40s. If
they can base over 40s, there's probably
some relief back up towards 90s, but not
unless they base over it. This is very
much like earlier. Remember every time
they've tried to do that, the same
stories here. They pushed and pushed and
pushed and kept getting sold into. So
there will not be a trigger long and
that will be bottom picking by the way,
but there will not be that counter trend
trigger long until
you see this move here. All right, until
you see that and pull back and hold
until that all the time they're doing
that, they're going to keep digging
lower and lower and lower and lower
until they're done with it.
What's the next trade long? I think I
just showed it for you. Right. It's over
40. It will be a trigger over 40. Here's
the approach of 40.
Sellers trying to defend this. If they
can't defend this, we will see a squeeze
up. There is an imbalance all the way up
to 64. And it's very possible we'd lift
all the way up to 90 if they can base
through 40. So, come on. Catch up,
please. There we go. Not you guys. I'm
talking to But she keeps pausing on me.
So 40 is the level. This gray box the
level. Can they base over it and forces
squeeze up
a chance to do it now? It's now or never
if they're going to do it. Nope. So they
just failed there again.
Oh, someone's just come in. Some big
boy's coming in there trying to absorb
the tape. I'm not convinced.
What's your game, mate?
I would say sellers are caught under 20
at the moment. So I guess that's their
pain point. If if it bases above 20 and
holds between 20 and 40 and then
squeezes through 40, they can use their
pain. But if we come back under 20,
those sellers are in control of this
last I don't know 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 minutes
or so, eight minutes.
just I'm just talking about uh what I'm
seeing here
this level
here
is 20. If they sell through this
obviously we move lower
and starting to sell through. So, no no
base over 40s, failure over 40s again,
just like we talked about up here. No,
no bid over 40 and down to the 600.
Let's see if they're adding liquidity
lower.
Just full dump of inventory. 80 is
coming up here. You can see them adding
on the book really low now into the edge
of this next blue box.
There is a low volume though down to
523s. Now I am like starting to get very
very upset at this point.
How much money am I going to feel like
I've left on the table by the end of the
day?
It doesn't matter about the news, guys.
News doesn't matter. You got to
understand news is just a catalyst. All
right? This is a dump a dumping of
inventory based on who's trapped in the
market. Don't worry about it. Like all
we're really doing what's actually
changed, right? Maybe we go down to this
apolog by the end of the day. But all
we're actually doing is coming back into
mean. I mean, we have gone past the
mean. But if you look at where we've
traded really from the highs, the
all-time highs that we put in down to
that sort of November low, and then you
look at the range that we created
before, all we've done is a failed
breakout. We've gone over it so many
times. It's a failed breakout. That's
all we've done. Failed breakout. Trading
back inside. I am starting to like look
at this chart thinking are we actually
coming for that lower ballinger band
today? Are we actually going to trade
top bowl to low bowl? The last day we
did that was October the 9th. October
the 9th we did that exact trade. We
traded top bowl to low ball
on a daily which is a four sigma move
which is insane. It's absolutely insane,
but it has happened.
Yeah, it would be four standard
deviations, Brandon. Yeah. So, if you
look back on a daily chart with your
Ballinger bands on, go back to Friday
the 10th of October. That was the last
time we did it. It's a very rare
occasion to do that, but we have done
it.
Previous week open, by the way, is uh
470.
down here is previous week open.
Be mad.
mad if they come for that
straight up 50-day next stop for the
cues probably.
Oh, Alex.
Um,
just do an expansion of IB just to see.
I feel like it's doable then.
161 into here. 470 is the previous week
open. Oh my god. Wild.
Very, very wild.
I'm going to be left a very upset man
today.
How would you know when a big move like
today happens? Um, well, you don't. You
just position for it.
There's no guarantees. Like, you have to
position when we leave volume and you
have to take partials by looking left
into each key level. Um, you don't know
that it's going to come down and do
this. There's no way there's no clear
way of saying that you know that. We
don't know where it's going to stop. We
have ideas. You can see each blue box.
We find a bid. We find a bid, but we're
trading through it. So then it's like
next level, next level, next level. Let
me just put 470 on because that's
previous week. Um,
open. Just make sure I get it on.
In fact, I can just turn it on my flow
zones. Hang on.
Previous week open. Let's put that to
gray.
should have gone on. There we go.
Yeah, just a normal normal uh Ballinger
bands. They should always be set then
normally they are always too standard.
So whenever you put it on a screen it'll
be two standard from your 20-day moving
average.
What a bleed. What a bleed.
Microsoft approaching 12%
down on the day.
What do you reckon? Apple save the day
and we rip rip it right back up.
What's my strategy, Alex? Um, close my
eyes and guess.
My strategy is ju just to play the
protrend where possible. And so like
when we left value today, the protren
became down for the day.
That's my that's my uh strategy.
And then finding ways of joining up
Every flag is working. Yeah, it is. They
keep selling off. It's just like you got
to understand like if you're playing
these these like breakdowns,
you're
play you're playing like deep discount.
You're selling deep discount to go lower
is so risky. It's not how I like to
play. I like to position myself short in
premium to get to discount
based on value.
Big seller came in at 560. That's like a
big level now. Big seller came in at
560.
Here's the move back to 560 where they
were. Are they going to refresh here? If
they don't,
big relief
through that 560. That's the squeeze
watching now. We did trap now. So 560 is
a big big big level.
They're starting to offer a bid now and
try and walk it up. I'm interested in
this for a little upside squeeze here.
Thank you.
Let's see if they hold 60s
and come and revisit 37s. Here they
come.
What a flyer.
So, probably going to revisit the 600s
and possibly the 37s. I'm going to make
too much [\h__\h] money on this.
My next problem, right, got to sell
that. Made too much money. Only buy a
little bit.
This game.
So, why was I interested there? The big
seller got himself caught.
There's the relief through it. The
seller actually came in at 60s. I'll try
and show you him here. All right. the
seller. Big seller here. So, selling at
the lows. Good auction at lows. 60 was
their trigger point. Right. Once we got
through 60s, there's the relief up into
this imbalance. So, you should be taking
partials now. I wasn't going to trade
it, but once I saw him have that much
size at the lows, I just thought, you
absolute idiot. What are you doing? Um,
so now it's very simple. Pullbacks need
to hold into these imbalances for that
rotation higher. And you'd be targeting
the next level of 640s.
Right? All right. So, remember they got
trapped here. We can do this trap level
right here. This is where they're stuck
from. They got stuck here and under.
I'm actually going to
leave this on for a second and see if we
get over 40s. Now, I'm going to have to
switch accounts here. There too much
money on that account.
Yeah, I went long just for the squeeze
up. Once we reclaim that 60s, I'm
already out of it.
And I'm watching this node here into 40s
to see if we get over that, I'll
consider an ad. And if we dip down and
hold,
we'll see. It won't even be an ad. It'll
be a fresh position because I'm already
out on that first account. Made too much
money. It was
well over the uh 30%.
Let's see.
Remember 60s is the key level here.
Buyers will need to defend 60s here. We
are still in a trend down. I want you to
remind you that. I'm just interested how
we act into here.
still holding it well so far. Well in
front of it. There are imbalances all
the way down to 48. Downside there
imbalances upside up to uh 626.
I really want to see if we can live
through 40s or or come back and test
40s. At the moment, not.
How do I figure out the seller down
there again? Delta bookmap and
footprints showing me the delta. I can
see when they're offside.
I know that 60 level is massive right
now.
Doesn't mean we can't move lower. It
just means that's currently where
they're trapped. That's all it means.
It's currently where they're trapped.
This gray box. You can see we haven't
It's not like we've shifted, right? We
haven't done this yet, right? So, we can
build liquidity out into here and they
still use that for a sell off.
Understand that. So, I played this
relief to here. If they hold this,
there's possible relief to here. Squeeze
will happen over here and we can still
just build liquidity there that they
resell down. It's very possible. I won't
be taking sales now because we're so far
into discount, right? So, if I'm going
to take trades, they're going to be
scalpy long trades based on trap
participants. And really, I probably
should be done for the day.
So, see if these 60s hold. It's the big
level right now. They trade through it
then probably a new lower day. If they
hold in front of it or at it, there is
relief. So, so far holding in front of
it.
Here we go. So, can they lift this now
up towards these 40s is the question.
It's tried. Not getting very far here.
So, that gray box holding that we just
put in, that's where that trap seller
is. He's there. We just need to see this
light lift now.
Going to try these. 600 is big
psychological number.
Here we go.
Here we go, folks. Come on. You got to
lift. You got to lift. You got to lift.
You got to lift.
They're still stacking these sellers.
95s and 605s.
They're still trying to force this lower
at the moment.
I keep telling you why 60s, guys. I
can't keep like saying it a million
times. Just do do the course, guys.
Like, I'm not even trying to sell it,
but I I keep explaining it. I'm not
going to give you any more edge. I've
said a million times why the 60s. I even
dragged it onto the screen to show you.
You've even got the node lined up there
for you. I've told you he's all sellside
in there. There's a seller stuck at 60s.
I couldn't say it anymore if I tried.
See if they left.
I don't know how you don't know when I
like I'm literally verbalizing it so
much. This is what makes it hard with
chat. Like don't do me a favor. Don't
flip between like me and some other
shitty trader. Either stay here with me
or go there because I don't want to
explain myself 10 times of the same
thing. That's not me being an [\h__\h]
but like
I don't know. If you want to watch top
set TV, I don't know what to tell you.
Learn how to lose money probably.
Right, back under these 60s now. So
buyers not defending those 60s. Not yet.
Well, there there there or thereabouts.
ES looking like it's trying to break
down to make a new low.
This area very very key now for
sentiment. Failure to break down will
cause short more shorts to get trapped.
And they do have targets down here. If
they want to come for this gray line,
they can. That gray line is previous
week open. Is that right? Previous week
open, is it? Yeah, previous week open.
What indicator is that? It's the blow
zone pro.
Yeah, I'm already done with it. I'm
already done with it, Josh. Just small
scalp from that 60 relief. We haven't
based and held above the uh 40s yet. So,
I'll consider something back up here.
I'm watching it just in case they trap a
lot. Like, I know it's a big level down
here at that 60s.
We'll see. If there's something to play,
I'll play it. We've already had that
first trade which was what from 60s all
the way up to 20s. So what's that? 60
points. Here we go. They're trying to
they're trying to hold these 60s and
force this squeeze. I'm watching this
now as we go back towards these 600s.
Yeah. Okay. Let's see.
Watching these 600s and if we get relief
through that 40s. Got a tiny tiny tiny
piece on
right above the 60s.
Failing 600s again. So still washing
those 600s. Still no confirmation above
this blue box. So that higher time frame
level still holding us down.
Break even on this.
There we go.
Oh, Lucid website's down. Is it? Sorry
to hear that, folks.
How can I find the heat map? It's called
bookmap. You can just buy it on bookmap.
Right. More sellers coming in again
there at 53 and getting caught. There's
definitely some form of absorption
happening down here, but it's too early
to say about a protrend or like a big
move up. But there is 100% I'm seeing
absorption on the tape down here at 60
and under 100%.
It doesn't mean they can't flush them
all, but every time they're coming down
there, there is a buyer nibbling at it.
Yep, there's a bias trying to step in
and force this up to 605s right now.
Here we go.
seller coming in at 80s. They got to pop
through 80s to get that move to 605.
This is getting to do to do to
Yeah, we had 175 lots stuck at 550. 127
lot stuck at 560 and that's just in the
last leg down. So, someone is trying to
absorb 60s to 50s. Doesn't mean we can't
move lower. All I'm saying is I can see
in here we are starting to see
absorption under these this level. Look
at all these sellers, sellers, sellers,
sellers. Someone is absorbing under
here. There you go. They're trying to
absorb it again. I can see it on the
tape. It doesn't mean we move higher. It
means that there is a buyer sat here
right now absorbing this. He does not
want it under there. If he gets his way,
he will get this move here. But if
sellers get their way, they will crush
him because he keeps trying to absorb
it. And you'll get this move down to
here. That is the battle right now.
There is a two-sided tape, but I can
tell you right now there is a buyer sat
here trying to absorb everything he can.
I'm out of this at the moment.
What's the easiest prop firm to get
payout from?
I don't know. TPT or Funded Next
probably.
Whitly pivot. Yeah.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Right, still half of you have not
smashed that like button, folks.
1,150
of you watching, half of you haven't
smashed that like button. We've had some
bangers on trades on of trades on stream
today and I want to do some Apex
giveaways and some course giveaways. So,
smash that like button. This seller,
this buyer might get himself caught
soon.
He's come in many, many times. If they
reject 60 now, you're going to probably
get this move down here.
This is a big overunder now. If they
reject this, you will probably get a
swipe because he's come in so heavy
there. That's why I cut the trade. So, I
nibbled at it here to here and I nibbled
at it here to here and I was like, "No.
You say buyer and protecting an area.
Can you see how much they put into cause
to the move? Are we talking hundreds of
thousands of millions? Yes, we are.
We're talking about institutional
buying. We're talking about multiple 200
lots in here. Right. This is failure to
break down here again.
Divergence to ES which made a new low.
Reclaiming these 60s. Still sellers
trapped at 60s and low of day. Oh, it's
tempting. Oh, it's tempting. Imbalance
here into 70.
Still flow is bearish. Flow zones are
bearish.
Would love one more decent trade. I'm
not going to trade downside from here
though. So, I either need an upside
squeeze or I need to let the squeeze
happen and fade that upside squeeze when
it's done. See, you can see this node,
this 60 level so big. It's so big.
Back through the 60s.
Do they force relief now? Because
they've done a failed breakdown. Shorts
have failed to break the lows now.
Um this edge here 80s is an interesting
level through 80s. Then I think there's
possible for a lift all the way up to
40s.
That's like a base over 80s. Not just
like a tap into it. We need to get above
and hold above it. And then there's
probably a move all the way up to 640.
Here's the move to 80s.
We can see if we can hold here.
Back to 60s. Probably see if they test
this 60s and hold it.
No hold of 60s. Still no trade. Then no
hold of 80s. No hold of 60s. Still no
trade. I tell you what, while they do
this, cuz I reckon I can give it a
couple minutes. I need to pee and I'll
be right back.
No, [\h__\h]
Oh, no way. No way. You [\h__\h] did it
when I used the bathroom.
All right. Hopefully some
Oh god. Oh, you just got to laugh.
You've just got to laugh. All right,
guys.
Hopefully you guys got it. I mean, I had
it planned for you. Reclaim of 60s, held
above 80s. There's the squeeze back to
the 40s. All right, there's your
squeeze. All right, if they find
acceptance over here, they get going.
Oh, you absolute bastards getting that
without me.
Was it literally as I walked away? Oh my
god. All right, so in here you can see
this 60s level. How key is this 60s
level? They kept getting trapped
underneath the 60s level. Look at the
sellers at the lows and once we reclaim
the 80s, you can see this shelf, then we
squeeze right back up to the top side
towards 40. So that's your trade done.
You should be locking in because your
counter trend, right? You want to be
aggressive with your stop. So if you
come up here, you want to be taking a
lot of this out. All right, if we start
basing here, all right, you want to be
careful and then we can think about a
base above and and a lift. But remember,
this can still be sold into, right? Can
build out liquidity be sold into. We're
playing this leg here. You must take
some profit into it. You can hold
runners for all the way up here. If you
get if it's a gift, you'll get all the
way up there for it. But it's too late
for me now. Unfortunately, I've missed
it. Used the bathroom at the wrong time.
Yeah, lots of you getting it.
So, this is why when you guys are like,
"Oh, can you tell us when when when
you're entering and you're telling us?"
This is why I teach you. Because if I
didn't tell you what was happening, you
wouldn't know that we're looking for a
60s to 80s move and from 80s for squeeze
up to 40s. From 60s to 80s, from 80s
squeeze up to 40s. There you go. TP hit.
And anything above that now is a bonus
back inside. All right. So, if I just
said, oh, I'm entering. You wouldn't
understand when to take profit, when to
do this, when to do that. That's why I
try and teach as I go.
So, another winner on stream. Here you
go. So, you might well get relief all
the way up here. It's very possible they
lift this aggressively now. It's very
possible you get a giant squeeze in this
now. So, hopefully you're positioned
well from it from 60 or 80 and you
should be up 100 points now already.
How's your luck? How's your luck, Alex?
Oh,
it's cruel. It's cruel.
It's cruel.
Nice. Nice work, Dave. Great work, mate.
And just bit move your stop up. All
right. So, what you will want to see now
is bulls base over this for a second
leg. All right. If they're going to do a
second leg, bulls will need to base
here, right, for the next leg. And you
expect that will probably be sold. Um,
but you know, we can afford to come all
the way up here. You might get lucky on
your run out. There's lots of stops up
here. You never know. You might get
lucky and get that. You might. You very
well might. We might have just had the
perfect trade down there at that 60s.
So the 60s call was good, wasn't it?
Like everything under 60s was excess. If
we go to here,
everything under 60s was excess. So if
we mark 60s out with a horizontal line,
I've called 60s right here. All right,
sellers kept getting trapped. Sellers
trapped underneath it
here. And I kept telling you in here
there is someone trying to absorb the
tape. I could see him trying to absorb
the tape and he didn't let it break
down, which meant anyone who entered
short here, remember their takeprofit is
under here. they get squeezed and their
trigger for that squeeze is the 80s
break and the 20's break to get you to
the 40s. The 40s break now is causing
the squeeze ups. Think about the stops.
You're running all the stops, filling
the imbalances, trying to probably get
up into this next cluster. All right, so
that was the trade thesis.
But again, what do I know?
What do I know? I'm a just a stupid
40-year-old with specs on on YouTube.
This is am I going to reenter? I mean,
it's it's going to be very hard for me
to get an entry now. All right. The the
optimal entry was down here. This gray
box, we kept talking about it. Gray box
and the 80s reclaim anywhere here was
optimal entry. If it pulls back here and
holds, yes, potentially, but you have to
understand that this right, maybe we get
one more leg out of it and then they can
fade that. If we get lucky, we get that
leg all the way up to here. But I've
lost optimal entry. All right. I hate
entering after I've lost optimal.
Optimal entry was here. You're up 110
points right now. And you just let it
[\h__\h] squeeze. Let everyone get get
taken out. And you take your money, you
risk off as you move up, and you hold
your runners.
Nice baited. Yeah. Hopefully it's
helped. Don't forget the top knot. Yeah.
A 40-year-old Arsenal supporting idiot
with a top knot wearing glasses and a
patchy beard.
A has been DJ.
How long did it take me to get here? Um,
quite a while to be honest. Like I it I
had some bad mentors. I learned some bad
habits. Um, getting rid of those bad
habits was flipping hard work, which is
why I created the flow zones for for
myself for a long time. Um, it took me
longer than probably most uh to be at
the level I'm at now. I've probably I
feel like I'm improving every day, every
week, still got lots to learn. I don't
think you ever stop learning. you know,
when I talk to um family friends of mine
who are, you know, 60s and 70s and
retired, some of them ex uh
head of like emerging markets and stuff
at Morgan Stanley and stuff like that,
they, you know, you never stop learning.
So, I think I'm getting better every
day. I think the last few months have
been some of my best trading yet. Um,
but who who knows? Maybe maybe the
market's just being kind to me at the
moment and I've got a good read of it
and you know maybe the market changes
and adapts and then I will need to
change and adapt. All right, we're
holding this low volume node here. I'd
like to see a retest of here somewhere
in here if they're going to actually
offer a rebid up. Remember deep pullback
flow zones and IB are right here and
previous week point control. This is a
big level here. Big big level. This is
uh not like this. This is like this. All
right. Big big big big level that we're
coming into.
big node on the developing week profile
as well. If I move you down, all right,
don't be expecting too much. Right? If
we're thinking about where we're trading
back to,
back into here. And if we zoom out and
look left down here, this old point of
control from the week of Monday the
19th. All right, we're coming back into
this huge node here. So don't expect too
much. If we get over that node, then
yes. If if we start breaking over 700s,
then yes, I think there's an argument
that we might trade up to 860s or
something. It's not pulling back for me
to join in.
Just got to lick my wounds. Give you
guys the best call possible there. I
think
I didn't have a mentor, man. I like I
don't want to bad bad name people that I
learned some bad stuff from. Um, I don't
want to bad name them. I had some bad
mentors. The only room, the only room
that I was in which was
useful and I wasn't in there for too
long was Investors Underground. I think
Nate's a great trader. Great trader. I
think there's some great traders in
there. But, um, a very small cap
focused.
Will I put the course on discount? No,
not right now. It's such good value.
Here you go, guys. Your squeeze is on.
So, next level. If you're lucky, you're
going to get all the way up to 800s,
right? So, you should be Where's my
long? This is what we talked about.
Anywhere from sort of 80s and 60s. You
might have entered lower. You should be
long from here, right? Taking profit
into here. And if you're lucky, you get
up up into there. That'll be 200 points.
But you must be locking, I'd say, a good
70% into this area here. This red box
here, you got to be locking most in. If
you're lucky, you're going to come and
run these stops up here if you're very,
very lucky. But lock most of it into
here. 70 80% whole 20% in case you get
that lift.
Are there live sessions on Discord? In
Discord in the afternoons, it's more I
will type in levels and call what I'm
seeing. Most most my trading happens in
the New York session. Uh like in the
morning, I think we get the better moves
in the morning. If we get [\h__\h] moves in
the morning, I'm more likely to stay at
my desk all afternoon.
Okay. It is possible we come for these
stops up here.
You know, spy finding a bid at that 685
gamma level as well. It's still on my
screen from a while ago.
And come straight back up all the way up
towards the 89's initial balance.
If you're trading options today, you're
probably making a lot of money. Do I
trade Asia and London? No, I am asleep.
I need to I guys, I'll be honest. I try
and trade this session here and I try
and be done with it. Otherwise, I'm my
screen's too long and it's not great. I
want to be fresh as much as possible. If
I think there's a big trade setting up
in Asia or not London, I'm not awake,
but Asia, then sometimes
Alex, I'm new to your channel. Question
on the anchor volume profile. Is it
based on ticks or what settings are you
able to share? Yes, it's set to two
ticks. Two ticks. If you don't like
using ticks, I would say use a th00and
rows, but two ticks.
Take care. Take care, mate. Have a good
day. All right. So, like I said, you
should be locking most in into this
initial balance. Like I said, this was
target. So, we actually had like target
one hit, target two hit, target three is
all the way up here for a runner. But,
you know, we might very well defend this
red box. That's why it's red because
it's going to be supply. It's a big big
big level. It's not just the initial
balance. It is also the point of control
dating back from last week, right?
That's why it's got that red line here.
Previous week point control. Hard to
see, I know. And this is the thick area.
and also the week before its value area
low from the week of Monday the 12th of
Jan
Monday the 12th of Jan. So you can hold
runners if you're willing to hold
runners looking for this. Starting to
hold flow zones, but you know this is
the counter trend leg right now.
Re-enter buy for me. There's no like I
wouldn't really want to reenter buy up
here.
Doesn't mean you can't. We are holding a
shelf.
We are holding a shelf. But for me, like
I prefer the buy down into this or this
somewhere into here if we're going to
have another go because if you're buying
here, you've got to understand that you
might only get to here and fail and
collapse. So the RR for me doesn't work
out. If it continues to squeeze up, then
it works out for you, but it's too high
a risk. I think this node here and down
here is more important. somewhere in
here,
the edge of this, this 40s that we
talked about, and even this down here,
maybe one of these. But you have to
understand that we've just tagged into
the key level. It might very well be
that they do this for the rest of the
day. It's very possible
because we're counter trend, right? You
are on squeeze up counter trend right
now.
What year did I start trading?
I actually first started trading when I
first left university when I thought I
was going to do it as a job. So what's
that? And it's 20.
Yeah. 20 years ago. 19 years ago. I
graduate 18 19 21. Yeah. 19 years ago
when I was interviewing everywhere to go
and do it as a job.
But uh I didn't trade for a long time
after that. and just had like some
investment pieces.
>> It came back to the markets uh probably
a couple years before co
did we formed some kind of lower high
for the alltime high?
Um I mean it's possible it's possible
but
we've swept the stops. We've filled the
gap.
It just now depends if there's
continuation,
right? So, we're just back into the
range. Depends if there's continuation.
But yes, you could argue that we swept
all the stops. If you joined me earlier
this week, we we talked about the gap
fill on the QQQ especially. All right.
If we go to this, it's why so important
to look at the cash gap markets. We go
to like a one day on the QQQ. We had an
old gap which needed to be filled right
into here, right? Which we have now
successfully filled. That is job done.
Um that gap on the NQ
was into this block right right here.
Right. We had to fill this right into
this right because this was a gap down
on this day here Tuesday. So we had New
York session here. So all we've done run
these stops, fill that gap, become
efficient, come back into the range.
We're we're back into death chop, guys.
I know it looks really bad, right? We're
back into death chop. Hello, Mr. death
chop. Doom doom. Failure outside.
Failure above. Failure outside. Failure
below. Failure above. We're back into
death chop. When does this get
quantified as a lower high? When we
start breaking down, right? We start
doing this. Where are we going to come?
200 day moving average and wash everyone
out. Very possible. But I don't want to
say that's what's going to happen
because it's too early right now to say
that's what's going to happen.
Okay. So, we can move this up. Your next
target is up here. If you get lucky, you
will get this. We're getting 30 minutes
away from lunch. And how many likes?
We're doing pretty well here. We'll do
one giveaway now.
I lost the shorts, but I took the long
now. Appreciate you, Alex. You always
give me extra confluence and edges that
I miss. Thank you, brother. You're
welcome.
What did you take this trade based off?
the trapped sellers down here at the
60s. Right? Go back and rewind this to
I'd say rewind it to 10:55 in the
morning all the way to 10 11. I kept
telling you that there was trap there's
a trap seller at 60 right at 560 and
that there was someone absorbing the
tape non-stop down there. Could see him
doing it
going high of day. Can you imagine? Can
you imagine?
That's why I said Apple for the win. Do
they come out with monster earnings and
we're back at alltime highs? I mean, it
would be absolutely hilarious. It would
be so funny. I don't think that's what's
going to happen, but I'm just saying it
would be funny.
Two ticks. Volume profile. Two ticks.
So basically the course will educate us
on how to read what you're reading. Yes.
The way I trade, every way I trade, I
explain in the course. The course is no
joke, guys. I I need to explain this to
you. This is not some like
three minute course. All right. The
beginner to advanced course is 20 hours.
Is over 20 hours. Right? So that is like
all the principles from someone who's
never learned. I'll build you up to
understand all the key core principles.
Then you can do the order flow and
volume profile course if you want to
understand more about how to identify
the nuances of trap players in the
market which is why the market moves. So
if you want to understand auction theory
volume profile delta delta divergence
footprints bookmap that's all in the
orderflow course right like I always say
not trying to push it. Go and do
everything for free on on my YouTube
first or join me on stream. Make sure
you like how I trade. Make sure you
understand how I trade.
Okay. How much is the course? It's uh
$699 if they've adjusted it correctly.
Otherwise, it's still $649 for the
20our. And the volume profile and
orderflow course is $399. But the 20our
one does come with a version of
Flowzones and with Discord, right? So,
you get Discord for life with the 20our
one. Okay, here we go.
Apex is on sale right now, 90%, but if
you want a chance to win a free Apex
account, just type code FCT in chat now.
Only type it once. Please don't spam or
you get pulled out,
right? Just type it once and we'll do a
giveaway. So, FZT, Flowzone Trader FT,
type it once in chat and use that code
for all your prop firms. It helps me do
stuff like this for you guys for free.
Means I don't have to charge, which is
nice. It means I get to give back to you
guys and you guys get
get the money that you guys want. Right?
Looks like we're going to break out
here. So, your next target, remember,
you're looking to lift all the way up
into these 800s, 840s if you can. You're
going to have to get through the initial
balance. So, you should have already
locked in like we talked about 60 70 80%
of your profit into this. And you're
looking to see if you get lucky to run
these stops up here. You're going to
have to respect this move into like we
have some spikes here, 750, 790, and if
you get lucky, you get 840s.
guys. A couple of minutes to do that.
Did I forget to have my coffee? Oh, I'm
going to warm this up, guys, cuz I
forgot to have it.
Same story for those of you trading ES
and SPY, by the way. It's all the same
stuff. We're coming into the same key
level, same initial balance, right? So,
you got to be locking in most your money
into that.
Okay, give you guys 20 more seconds,
then we'll do the giveaway
and hopefully
you guys should have made some good
money with me today. The other trade we
had, I did take a small scalp on this,
my first attempt on it once I saw them
caught.
Should put this on. So
transparency. Where is it? Long. Long,
long. Where are you? This one. I took
this first attempt here.
Same level. Sawing caught it 60 again.
So those are the trades I've taken off
stream. Well, I haven't taken this one.
I've called that one for you.
Unfortunately, I have not taken that one
cuz I went to the toilet at the worst
time.
All right, let's pull this winner.
Five, four. I'm just letting Nightbot
catch up. Three, two, and one. The fresh
trader. Fresh. It always reminds me that
word of uh
uh
what was the character called in phone
jacker? I want it now and I want it
fresh. for all you Brits out there.
Nice. Fresh trader. Congratulations,
Fresh Trader. Um, all I need you to do
for me is send me an email
info@flzonetrader.com.
Just send me a screenshot of you logged
in so I know it's you. I've made a note
of your name and I will sort you out
with a free Apex account any size that
you want. All right. Congratulations.
Happy for you. Let's go. Let's go.
All right. So, as long as you guys have
locked in, you still look good.
But I would say you would not want the
dips to come under 35s. And if you're a
scalper, you probably don't even want to
let it come back down here. So, if
you're already long from 80, you
probably don't want it to drift all the
way back down, right? You've probably
made 120 points on this already. You
probably are unwilling to sit through
that.
What did I do before this? What do you
mean? Oh, do you mean as a career? I was
a very average music producer and DJ.
Just very average. She just play like
empty bars.
Um,
do you have one course or two? There's
two courses. The 20our course will give
you the Discord and a version of the
flow zones. Right?
So if you want Discord, you want a
version of Flow Zones, you want to learn
everything from scratch, so you get rid
of slightly bad habits, that's the one
to do. If you already know how to trade,
but you're just looking to understand
volume, order flow, delta, that stuff,
just do the volume profile and order
flow course. If you want to do both,
there is a bundle, so it will save you
some money.
I didn't leave London for me. Actually,
I left London for my wife.
It was time for me to
do something for her career because, you
know, she put up with me traveling the
world for 10 years.
What instruments do I play? I'm actually
currently learning to play the guitar.
I'm okay on the piano from producing.
Not great, but um I'm currently learning
the guitar. I'm at like day 10. My
fingers are flipping sore, mate. They're
so sore.
You have a chance of a long up. Yeah,
you do. You do. Look, they're still
Look, this sellers keep getting stuck at
70. Like, if you look at bookmap right
now, it's the same story, right? See
this guy here? He's come piling in 74
lot, 71 lot, and he's just got squeezed
out for this rip back up to 710. But we
can't get through the initial balance.
So if you want to see that auction at
the low this morning on bookmap
right into the 60s.
Zoom this out.
560s
right. Look at this.
Can I move this? I'm going to have to
delete the drawings.
Drawing tools. Clear drawings.
Right. Remember we said 60 was the level
horizontal line. Can we do a 60? Where's
60? 50 55 57
60 was the level. Okay, that was the
level.
See earlier in the day we sold through
it at I don't know what time this was
10:54. They came piling in here at the
low. That's a nice auction low of the
low of the day with sellers at the lows.
We go back over. We hold. They try and
sell through once, twice. This is why I
told you there's absorption happening.
If we're seeing this much selling,
right? This much selling here. This is
market order selling and we're not
moving lower. What does it mean? Someone
is is absorbing. Where's the pivot?
Pivot. We tried to see someone hold it
here. We squeeze through. We come back.
We back test. We back test. Little flush
over. Little flush. And then look what
happens. 118 lot. 173 lot. They come
piling in here. 106 lot. 41 lot. low of
day 139 lot. Then we instantly reclaim
and then what? Everyone who's a seller
is now caught. And what do they get
forced to do? Well, their stops would be
above each of these swing points and
boom. All right, that's the pain.
There's the pain point. You're seeing
the same here now, right? Of liquidity
building up here,
right? That's the build of liquidity.
Selling keeps happening into this level.
they're still trying to absorb it to
complete the rotation. I would not
personally be wanting to bid that. I
would be more willing to let them sell
through it and come and retest either
this
like this kind of area here, right?
Retest that and hold that W. Doom dum
dum dum dum. That would be really nice.
But it's counter trend. There's no doubt
about it. It's a counter trend trade.
It's the hardest trade to have in the
book. I always talk about it. The best
trades, the easiest trades to master are
the protrend trades. When the higher
time frame and lower time frame want to
do the same thing
average DJ that travels the world. Yeah.
Well, I was I was lucky.
You can teach me how to play guitar,
Matt. Thanks, Matt. Have your fingers
gone flat yet? I don't know. Like what
I'm struggling with is the
you might get a squeeze on the flag
here. So leg two might be happening. So
leg one, leg two. If we get a measured
move here.
How many points we looking at?
Move that.
If you get lucky, you're going to get
this move. That would be the measured
move. You might get this move to target.
It is the correct measurement. So there
is confluence right now for this to
happen. There is confluence right now
for this to happen. It doesn't have to
happen, but if they have caught enough
shorts under here like we've talked
about, I would much rather it comes down
into here for me to bid. But if they
have and they can do this, the measured
move technically, if that is leg one,
technically is leg two. I'd be very
cautious with it because it's counter
trend. But if you are positioned long
from here, you can try and hold a runner
to get up into here. That would be a big
big big trade. How much would that be
for you? That would be 250 point trade.
That would well at least I' I'd make up
for the uh the 500 pointer that we
missed this morning when we only got 250
out of it.
Yeah. What was I saying? What am I
struggling for on um I'm struggling to
move from I really like uh E minor. Is
it G? G is fine. D is fine. C I'm really
struggling with that like three. What's
that? First fret, second fret, third
fret. I am struggling to do that. That
is killing my fingers. I'm really
struggling with that. If anyone plays
guitar, they'll they'll know. And uh
they'll probably be like, "Mate, you are
[\h__\h] if you can't play three fret on a
C. What is wrong with you? But I'm only
eight days in or something, guys.
I don't understand how the 2,500 trading
draw down in Apex. If our position goes
up 1K and then takes a stop loss at 500,
it counts 500 draw down. No, it it would
count more than that. So, it's a trail,
Fernando. So,
right, let's say you're long here.
All right. And you're a,000 bucks up,
okay? And then you give 500 bucks back.
So you only lock 500 in. You've now
eaten $500 of your draw down. If you
were a,000 bucks up and it came all the
way back to break even, you have now
eaten $1,000 of your draw down because
it's trailing draw down. So the best way
to do it with Apex, there's two ways of
doing it. One is to size very small so
that you can sit through the pullbacks
and not worry. All right, which is what
you should definitely do on your PA
accounts. Two, which I do not advise
doing, but I do do this if I need to get
more accounts. I will be aggressive with
my evals because I do not want to take
long to do it, but I also know that I
have ability to do it. Is I will be more
aggressive with the sizing so that I
know when I hit my target, I'm making
sure that target takes a good chunk of
the change for me. Like, so I I want to
try and pass it, not necessarily in one
move, but I want to get a good chunk of
it done. I'm not looking to hold through
the draw down. So, the other way of
doing it is being more aggressive and
then trail your stop. All right? Move
your stop up up up and you're out. And
then you wait for a reload on the second
trade. Move your stop up. Take some
partials. Take So, you want to be taking
partials at the highs of each move,
right? You don't want to let it pull
back on you on Apex when you're dealing
with the trading draw down.
Oh, really, mate? Yes, I might need some
help.
First of all, I need these to stop
hurting because I'm like a little [\h__\h]
Like, I didn't play yesterday as the
first day I didn't play because they've
been so sore. I think they are feeling
better today. Like, I'll tell you how
much it was hurting, mate. I I've
overplayed so much that even typing on
the keyboard was hurting. Here you go.
You might get the lift here, guys. I
really hope you get this. It would make
me so happy, but also so jealous. Like,
talk about timing. Alex goes to the
toilet. He tries the trade here. He goes
to the toilet. He comes back. It's here.
He's missed the trade and he doesn't
want to buy here because he wants a
deeper pullback and now he's probably
going to watch it hit the target. Well,
thank you very much, Mark. Aren't you
fun?
Do I have monthly P&L targets? No. I
used to do that. I like really try not
to do that anymore because the problem
with doing that is conditions change.
Um, this month will be a good month for
me. I can tell you it'll be a good month
for me. Why will it be a good month for
me? Because the markets move from a
rotation market to a breakout and even a
failed breakout. So that we have
opportunities like today. So these are
my A+ opportunities. When we start to
leave volume trapped, right? When we
start to leave volume trapped and we
leave volume, we have an A+ opportunity.
When we trade inside, which is what I
thought we'd do today, that is very
small amounts of trade for me. So, if
you think about the trades we've had all
week this week, uh they've pretty much
all been in breakout, haven't they,
which has been very, very good for us.
So, if we go back to the trades we've
had this week, yesterday was good, but
it could have been better if they did
the move that they did in earnings for
me during the day. So, yesterday
is where is yesterday? So, yesterday we
bought this dip again, I think. Trying
to remember.
Was that yesterday or this is Tuesday?
Tuesday we bought that dip.
Wednesday we faded it back inside.
Wednesday we played
this down and I wanted to buy it back
here but it didn't happen until the
earnings call. So lots of my Discord
bought that back up which is the right
thing to do. That was the trap level.
Anyone that joined me yesterday will
know we talked about this as the trap.
So yesterday we played the pullback leg.
Tuesday we bought the dip. Monday, we
also bought the dip for the breakout, I
think. Where was Monday? Yes, we also
played this on Monday. Right. So, we
went in breakout from Monday. So, this
week's been good. Monday upside, Tuesday
upside, Wednesday, we played the
pullback leg. I wanted to buy the dip,
but it happened in earnings. And then
today, we left all that volume. So, if
you just zoom out,
we go to like 15 minute here. We just
zoom out. I can take this off to make it
really easy. What have we done? Well,
we're coming back to where we broke out
from. It's where we broke out from. This
is where we started bidding this week.
Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday. We
leave it. That's my A+. Leaving volume.
That is my A+ scenario. This was eight
on the way up because we're also leaving
trap volume on the way up. Right? And
now we're coming back to repric it. If
we do a dance in here next week, it will
not be an A+ week for me. It will be a
very boring week for me and how I trade.
But I know what my edge is. I think
that's the other thing that a lot of
traders struggle with like uh
identifying the trade that you're
looking for, the prime
setup that you like to trade. Mine are
protrending markets, right? Which means
either in breakout or in a failed
breakout. We've had both this week. It's
been fantastic. Um Tyson, for example,
is an IB trader. So Tyson will be
looking for that or looking for this.
Right. So, understanding we talk about
all the time, one play at a time. So
many people come to the markets and they
want to play every single candle, every
single setup in front of them. You can't
do that, guys. You can't do it. Like I
said, read golf is a is not a game of
perfect. I think it's the best book for
traders to read. I know people will
laugh at that, but if you are new to
golf and you want to go and play an 18
hole with the pros and you get out your
driver on hole number one in front of
everyone watching in the stands, well,
what are you going to do? You're going
to absolutely [\h__\h] it up. The chances of
you driving 300 yards straight down the
middle are probably 0.001%.
So why do you think coming to trade that
you can come and take this like
wonderful setup that you've never taken
before? What's the easiest setup? You
want like a little layup or an eight
iron, right? Nice. Something nice and
easy. Nice and easy layup. So get used
to that layup. That layup for you might
be IB to VW up, right? It might be IB
expansion. It might be opening range,
right? It might be opening range
expansion. It might be flag breakout.
Flag breakout. might be a rotation of
value. It's up to you to define what
that is. Get good at that one trade,
then add a second trade in, then add a
third trade in, then add a fourth trade
in. And once you've been trading for
years and years and years, you will have
a plethora of different clubs that you
can get out depending on the
environment.
Thanks, cat. No, I appreciate it. anyone
you play golf and love the analogy.
Yeah. Well, which should make sense to
you.
How many moves are viable to play each
day?
Are there always usually always around
the first hour of New York? Uh that is a
good question and there is no answer to
that. Right? There is no answer to that
I'm afraid. Um moves become dependent on
setups. setups they become dependent on
what's happened on the previous day,
previous week, current week, previous
session, right? So, we we cannot
guarantee how many moves we're going to
get a day. It it really depends on what
that setup is. Is there a catalyst? Is
the market moving? Is there someone
trapped in the market? I would love to
say to you, oh, I'm going to get three
set setups a day. Usually, the market
offers at least something, but it
doesn't have to. And if you become rigid
on that, that's another reason why lots
of traders fail. All right? They become
rigid on it and think that we have to do
something. We have to do something each
day. I'm just going to take you to the
higher time frame just so you can see
what we're doing now. You can see this
hourly has rebalanced the last hour.
We're coming into what's this right?
This is profile developing this week.
This red box, you can see we keep
getting stuck up here, folks. Like we
have not lifted into these 90s yet. So,
we've rebalanced. So, just be careful
here. Please be careful. Right. We will
have to flip this to do this move here.
We haven't got above the lower time
frame yet enough to do it. That would
mean doing something like this to do
that. We haven't seen it yet. So, you
better be paying yourself here as we
come into lunch 10 minutes. You don't
want to give this all back right on the
dunk. Do not give it all back on the
dunk. Please be very, very careful.
Remember, this is a runner. There is no
guarantee. You've hit your main target,
which is here, right? This is a runner.
This is 20% of the trade if it goes for
you.
There you go. See, Rob nailing that.
Yeah. After three years of strategy
bouncing for me, finally taking payouts
consistently. Big part was sticking to a
system. Bingo. Right. Bingo. Most people
don't get enough data and don't trade
one setup enough to validate whether it
works for them. And also, you got to
know your personality. Like, do you like
playing flags? Do you like playing
breakouts? Do you like playing ranges? I
hate playing ranges, right? I hate it. I
hate trading edges. I just feel
uncomfortable doing it all the time. I'm
uncomfortable doing it. But some people
love it. Absolutely love it. And good
for them because most of the time we're
in a range.
Um,
if I understand market conditions and
everything, which course shall I get?
Uh, depends if you want discord or not
or not. I guess if you don't, if you're
not bothered about the discord and you
just want to understand orderflow, then
just get the volume profile and
orderflow course.
Pass my first email today. Have learned
so much here. Had learned a ton here.
Thank you for your help. You're welcome.
Control Supply Co. You're welcome.
Welcome. Welcome. We will do some more
giveaways as we get towards the end.
Please review the NQ tape again. What do
you mean on bookmap? Well, we're coming
into like we're basing up here, but like
I said, it can very easily come and
flush. We've got lots of stops down
here. You're coming into lunch. Do not
give back this whole thing is what I'm
saying. Make sure you've taken some
profits. You are looking for this move,
right? That's what you're looking for.
You're looking for this move, but you're
along from here, right? You do not want
to let this happen. It can happen into
lunch. They can absolutely come and
swipe this and then come back for this
later. So, all I'm would say is if
you're positioned at 60 or 80s, you look
good, but I would not be letting this
break down underneath and coming giving
all this back. All right? You'd be very
upset if you have not locked in here and
it comes back down to here into
lunchtime.
Don't let that do it. It's very possible
to do it, especially how it's built that
liquidity right now. Very, very
possible. We haven't really run anyone
out. If they want to do this, they
absolutely will do that.
Okay.
Out of the long, JJ, nice work. Well,
it's a it was a great long. So, now you
probably got almost 150 points.
Great. Like, who's moaning about 150
points? There's YouTube is giving you
five point trades out there
consistently.
I trade mean reversions. No, definitely
not. Only if it's a failed breakout
would it be a mean reversion. If it was
a continuation trade leaving balance,
that doesn't necessarily mean it's a
mean reversion. If we've got balance
trapped, like weekly balance like we had
like four weeks balance trapped and we
break out upside and hold above, it's
not going to be a mean reversion. It's
going to be expansion. Right? It only
time is a mean reversion is like today
when we go above balance, we create
balance, we fail, we get stuck at the
top bowls, then yes, mean reversion.
same trade setup. It's a it's a breakout
or a fail breakout. It's a use of
liquidity.
We did one giveaway. We will we will do
some more giveaways uh shortly. We're
almost at lunchtime.
I have a 50K Lucid account and I just
bought a 50K Tradeify evaluation using
your code. Thank you. And I was just
wondering if once I pass the Tradeify
evaluation, will I be able to copy trade
them? Yes, you will. Absolutely will.
What do you get from Discord? I can show
you what you get from Discord if that
helps you.
First thing you get is traders who are
supporting each other looking at the
same setups like they've been doing all
morning calling stuff out. There you go.
Look, all my traders making a ton of
money in there this morning, right?
While I'm on stream, looking after each
other. There you go. Absolutely crushing
it all morning. All of these traders,
fantastic. Love it. Right. and you get
all the calls that I'm looking for in
the afternoon. So, this is still in the
morning. There's Ben taking a short
pre-market, right? They're all
supporting each other.
And even up here,
these were the guys getting long.
Yeah, getting long on the trap we talked
about. I'm assuming Nathan's gone now,
but I think this was what we were
looking for. Yes, this right here. this
kind of play here for that trap long to
go all the way back up.
Uh, which is what we talked about on
stream yesterday. So, you get any of the
plays. See, that's me coming in in the
afternoon telling them what I'd be
looking at.
And then what else do you get? Well, you
get new student questions. We do
reviews. We do every two weeks we do uh
private lessons all together. I say
private, but it's everyone in stream.
You get my swing investments. So
everything that I'm looking at on the
swings, what levels I'm looking to get
uh entries on, what I'm looking for. Um
we did very very well last year on the
swings. And then you get Coupe does a
twoe call every two weeks with everyone
trading that way. And then you get um
lots of discounts which we don't do on
here and giveaways as well and a ton of
other stuff, right? But it does it's it
comes for free when you do the 20our
course. There's no monthly sub on it,
right? No monthly sub on that.
Trump speaking. Is he really? Well,
that's good to know. I mean, I'm out and
we're done now anyway. Coming into
lunch.
The hard thing to realize that one big
runner basically guarantees your
profitability as long as you keep risk
in check unless you get really unlucky.
Yeah. I mean, look, if you took this
here, any of these longs here, 1680,
right, and you got TP1, TP2, and you've
locked in like 80%.
All right, and even if you've just got
one left, right, that one left can do
another 100 plus points,
right? If that's a micro, it's another
$200. If that's a mini, that's another
$2,000 per account, right? On the
runner, and you've protected profits
anyway, and you can move your stop up,
right? So that's why trading in good
locations is key. It's why I'm like once
I lose location, I'm so less interested
in trading because I want to minimize my
risk. Lock in. Then I'm playing with
house money. All right. If my risk is
here and I lock in and I move my stop
up. All right. Now I'm playing with
house money. If that goes, it goes. Bit
like the one this morning. So you can
see where I fluffed my lines on the
second trade this morning is because I'd
lost position. So that was first trade
this morning all the way down. Second
trade was the bounce short. So that was
the first bounce since the drop. So if
we think about how this looked, what
what we were talking about, you can
rewind the tape. Here's the fade. We're
looking to fade this. I wanted it up
here. Ideally, they trapped themselves
in here. So I play that short. If they
get caught here, I cover. I cover too
early. There's the continuation. That's
my fault. All right, that's my fault.
Bounce short. Should have held for
continuation. But this was a big demand
level, remember, at the time. So I was
very, very proactive. But the reason I'm
more proactive on that than I am here is
because I understand we now have
structure. This can hold and do this if
it wants. All right. So, I've lost
positioning. What I should have done was
held some, added on, and left my core up
here. And then I could have sat through
that. And that's my fault. That needs a
review. That's where I'm can still
improve. Can still improve. But it's
hard when you've made 250 points on a
trade. It's hard to convince yourself
you're going to do another 500.
I struggle with the early moves like
this in the morning. Is that something
that comes with experience? Yeah, just
with experience. If if you're newer, I
would just avoid that opening. Just
avoid it. There's so there's such a rush
of blood and you'll feel like you have
to do something. Be very careful about
this dropping down now. You do not want
to get stopped out here. It's very, very
possible coming into lunch that they
wash this out. Be very, very careful,
please.
Did you catch 600 point shorts today?
Okay, I lost 1,600. Only 400 left. Uh, I
didn't catch 600, unfortunately. I
caught this first trade. So, we got 215
odd points out of that. I caught this
second trade, which was what, like 30
points. And I caught
this, which was a 60 pointer. And then I
caught this long, which was a 50
pointer. And then I missed this. I
called it, but I went to the bathroom
and it went without me.
Any
tips to get out of draw down is size
right down because you haven't got much
size there left. Size right down and
just work your way out of it slowly.
You're going to have to be willing to
dig your way out of it which is a good
skill to learn to possess. If you can
dig your way out of draw down will serve
you well in the future.
Where am I getting orderflow data from?
Well, all data is from CME. It's
centralized exchange. But if you mean
footprints, I have footprint on my
ninja. I have footprint here.
And as you can see above my head on the
screen, I have bookm
TP2 would mean taking a partial, right?
So the way I would do it is that I I
have multiple contracts. The best way to
do that to start with is micros. So
let's say you enter
let's say you're on a 50k account and
can I draw this? There we go. And you
enter three micros long here, right? So
you take one off there. You take one off
there. All right? And now you're holding
one for up here. Right? So you've locked
in profit. No matter what, you're going
to make good money on this trade. And
maybe you've moved your stop. No, maybe
your stops now moved to here as well.
Joanna, I've purchased both courses.
Nice. Looking forward to working with
you
before that long took off. How do you
judge how long you need to wait while
the liquidity builds? Um, this long
here. Well, you can see I I had an
attempt straight away. I saw he was
trapped at 60 straight away. All right.
So, I did not wait long once I saw him
trapped and we got the relief instantly
and then I stopped out. I think I might
have had another go in here and stopped
out. I can't remember. I'll have to
review it. Um,
but
once we fail to break lower, you need to
understand this.
Once sellers
fail to break us lower, think about if
you're selling here, right, versus this,
what's your target? It's this, right? We
think about structure, right? If you're
the structure is this, right? The
expectation is this here. That's your
TP1. If you're smart, if you're a
pullback trader, that's your TP1. If
you're a breakout trader, you're
shorting the lows. We don't short the
lows, right? So, once they fail to go
lower, what does that mean? Well, no one
has got their TP. That's how I see it.
Also, by the way, at this point, ES had
divergence. ES did this. So ES did it
for you ICT people and you would call
that S&T for anyone normal. It's called
divergence. All right. So and we knew
60s was the level where we had them
trapped. 60s was the level where he was
trapped here and here and here. 60s was
his big order. And we can pull that up
for you guys.
Right. 60s right here. You can see this
big red outlying delta. Huge seller here
at 60. Right. So that was what I was
looking at. I knew that was the pain
point. So I used his pain point
here. I used his pain point for the
relief. And if I was here and didn't go
to the toilet, I would have used his
pain point again. And we said 80s was
the pivot. All right, 80s. We had
imbalance over 80s squeeze happens. And
then you go target one. And then you're
looking left for the squeeze trigger. So
if you were short in the hole, where
would your stops be? You would have
stops here and here. So guess what
happens? We run that over. They become a
market buyer. Squeeze. They run that
over. they become a market buyer
squeeze, right? And now you're into TP
and now it's just how far can you go?
Can you get the last lot of stops? Where
are the last lot of stops to aim for?
Right here. Think about all these stops,
right? If you were swing short up here,
where is your stop? It's right here at
825. So, if we lift up there, that's
your last target for your long,
right? That's how the market moves. It
hunts liquidity, then it creates
liquidity when there's no left nothing
left to hunt, and then it goes and hunts
the other way. Right? So, it
it hunts liquidity, it creates
liquidity, then it uses liquidity to
hunt more liquidity. It creates
liquidity, then it uses this liquidity
to hunt more liquidity, then it creates
liquidity, and it's nothing else to
search for down there. So, it goes the
other way. It hunts the liquidity. It
hunts the liquidity and then it will
probably create some liquidity and then
it might come down into a range. Yeah.
What's another way of doing that?
What's another way of doing it? It goes
for looks for it auctions lower. It
finds an area of price acceptance for a
bit. It leaves that and auctions lower.
It finds acceptance. It leaves it at
auctions lower. It finds acceptance.
We're now too deep into discount which
is why I say don't short the lows. And
now we're going to go back into fair
value. Fair value on the day is right
here. Right point of control. This is
fair value. So we're coming back to fair
value. This is deep in discount value
area low. We're coming back to fair
value.
So any way you want to look at it, it's
the same bloody thing. The market only
moves in uh does one thing really. So
we're trying to trade up into here. Now,
for those of you who are long, you can,
you know, you can trim some into this
shelf like we talked about, sort of 80s
and 90s and VWAP. And if you get lucky,
you will pop these stops up here.
Just catching up with everything you're
asking and then we'll do this giveaway.
Sorry.
How many monitors do I have? Four. Four
big ones right now. And then one for
your stream.
Do you need bookmap for success? No, you
don't need anything. Mike, you just got
to do what you do.
Yeah. Four, four big monitors. So, here,
vertical, vertical, horizontal,
horizontal, and then a small screen
there for the stream.
I took a swing long from 25,500. You
would keep it open for a couple days or
close it later in the day before market
closes. All depends where we trade into.
I would be taking some of your size off.
If we can trade up into 87, like up into
here, I would be trimming some because
it's possible they put a lower high
there. If they find acceptance over 920,
then I think you will probably get
26,000. So, where would if you're long,
you said you're long 550s, I would be
probably taking some off or or
definitely move my stop break even for a
start because you've lifted well away
from that. So, make sure you're going to
be in the money. I'd be trying to trade
some into here. Look, just go to an
hourly.
This makes sense for you, right? You've
just said you're swing long from here,
right? I like the level. Makes sense,
right? You need to find acceptance over
this to get to here. This is the big
level. All right. I'd be taking some
partial into there. If you're swing, if
you find acceptance over that, you're
going to trade into here. I would be
taking most my position off into that
because we now have trapped people up
here. The expectation is here or here
will probably fail, right? If you got
very lucky and you kept like 5% on on a
swing and we did this in for next week,
then you might get all-time highs. But
my expectation now would be like
probably drift into here and sell or
here and sell. Definitely one of these
will offer the pullback and then have to
see if they reby this for that move or
not.
Yeah, for me like I always talk about
hourly is what I call like god god for
decision- making, right? God for
decision- making on charts.
Uh Joano, you purchased the course. Can
you get access yet? Just go to the end
of the course, the 20our course. There's
like a module on how to get Discord.
Just go through that, tell you what to
do, and I'll sort you out.
Base my setups on liquidity builds.
Everything I do is based on liquidity.
Market only moves based on liquidity.
What time frame is this chart? This is a
one minute chart that you're currently
looking at. One minute chart.
How do you get access to bookmap? You
have to go on their website and pay for
it.
Can we trust footprint chart from
Trading View? I feel like data is wacky.
I actually quite like it. I mean, I
don't execute on it, but I think it's
pretty good. I actually think it's
pretty good. It's pretty good. You can
see at the at the moment you're seeing
some buyers caught up in these highs.
All right, so we're filling in these
imbalances. I think it's pretty good.
Again, you can get my settings for free
on YouTube. I posted last week.
Do you use indicator with bubbles to see
orderflow? Uh, yes. Bookmap it's called.
Uh, I haven't seen one yet, Dylan. No, I
haven't seen one. I have looked. There
was one I was uh looking at. They didn't
look as nice. I'm trying to remember
what it was called. Um, there are some
paid ones, but I don't think they're as
good as the one on Ninja.
After your Ballinger band video I
watched yesterday, buyers seem to be
defending the 20 SMA. It would be 20 SMA
on a Ballinger band. If we're building a
bare flag for spring on woff
distribution for a seasonal marcher it's
possible. It is very very possible
Fernando um we've gone from top bowl to
mean if we build out here and we fail
and we go expansion under bottom bowl is
very possible that it gets nasty but far
too early to say right now.
What inches are the vertical monitors? I
don't actually know. How can I find that
out?
I think they're probably like 34 or
something like that.
And I've got a wide screen in front of
me. Um
I don't know how to see.
Yeah, I'm not sure. I think they're like
they're widescreen verticals. Maybe 34
inch, I would guess.
All right, let's do a absolute beginner
giveaway.
Okay, type course now into chat and
we'll do a giveaway of the absolute
beginner course. All right, not the
20our one, it's just a 2hour one.
It's just a 2hour course. It's for an
absolute beginner. If you already know
how to trade, you can give it to someone
else.
Give you guys a couple minutes to do
that. You're almost there, guys. You are
almost into this final TP. So, I'll just
move your stop up with it because you're
getting quite grindy here into lunch.
Volume's going to dissipate greatly.
Almost there into VWAP and the final
target into these stops, guys. Into
these stops if you get lucky. If you get
lucky.
Nice. I'm just catching up with Discord.
Really nice, Scotty. That long. Great
work, bud.
Great work. What a beauty.
What a beauty.
Right. You're almost there, guys. You're
going to get a 250 pointer. Can you
believe it? Can you believe it? Okay,
pulling the winner here.
This winner. Five, four, three, two, and
one.
D Carson Davis. Congratulations,
guys. Move your stop up. You're starting
to extend into this block now. All
right, so hopefully you squeeze through
into these stops, but move your stop up.
Be protective. D Carson Davis, are you
here? Let me know you're here. What a
trade, guys. I'm absolutely devastated.
I've missed this by going to the
bathroom, but there you go. There's an
absolute banger for you guys. What a
banger.
All right, nice. D Carson Davis. All you
need to do, email me
info@flzonetrader.com
and I will sort you out with a beginner
course. All right,
info@flowzonerader.com.
Here you go, guys. Here you go. Keep
moving this stop up. Here's point of
control. This is fair value. I would
like to see you run these stops at 825,
but you are getting very aggressive here
on the squeeze. This is everything we
wanted to see. Oh my god. How How has it
done it the moment I go to the bathroom?
How close would I trail stops? I'd
certainly move it up to the 50s if not
into this shelf here at 87 at this point
because you're basically there. I'd
probably protect somewhere around here.
All right, because who cares if you
don't make an extra, you know, 10 20
points, but you'll be very upset if you
give back 50. So, I'd probably be moving
my stop to this shelf here at around
88.90. All right, I'd want it to protect
here. You're very, very close. I think
these will get run, right? I think these
will get run. But it's possible it does
this before doing it. And you will not
want to give that back, right? You will
not want to give back 50 odd points,
will you? On your runner
to have access to order flow. Do I need
a funded account? No, you don't.
You don't. There's a video that I've
done on it on YouTube. you. It's for
free if you're trading with most prop
firms with trading with uh trade of
eight. You get orderflow for free.
This is current session. Orderflow on
the right is current session. Uh volume
profile on the right is current session.
Here you go guys. You're very very
close. It's going to come now. Here you
go. They're lifting. They're lifting.
They're lifting. Keep moving that stop
up with it. Hopefully you hit the top of
this these stops where we're looking for
this. Remember this is your target for
this runner.
This is your target for the runner.
You're very close to doing it.
ES, by the way, has just done it. It has
just wicked them out. So, ES has done
the move into its mean into the 20-day
SMA again.
That's it. That That's it. Stephen, if
you stay here, I will give you big
winners. You've just got to be willing
to sit through all the bollocks um and
not flip onto
top [\h__\h] TV.
I'm so mean. Shouldn't say that.
Top [\h__\h] TV where you should just fade
everything that they do. Um
pass two more Apex Evals. Is that nice
work? Nice work.
Anchored volume, guys. This is anchored
on the right. We're going to have to get
a section out, aren't we? Because lots
of new people are coming and asking me
the same question. Anchored volume
profile to the 930 open.
You have an 80% win rate since watching
me. That's pretty good going. Green on
the day. Thanks, Alex. Nice work.
Nice work, everyone.
Right. You don't want this to flush
under here, guys. You do not want this
to flush under here. Like I would have
locked in there. You You don't be a dick
for what did we hit there? A high of 16.
We were looking for 26es. You were 10
points away. Don't let this flush you
out 60 70 points. Right. Just move your
stop up. Lock it in. Who cares about
that extra 10 points if you don't get
it. Do not let this collapse on thin
volume all the way back down. Right. We
did really well there. You should have
locked in and hopefully you'll still get
it. But that's 230 points and we are
looking for 240 points. So, there's an
extra 10 points here if they keep
holding this shelf. At the moment,
they're still holding that shelf at 90.
Look, they're still holding the shelf at
90. So, hopefully you get it.
I love that. Great kitty. I watched
Topep for a year, no payout. Watched you
for a week. First payout.
There you go.
you're new to trading. What should you
learn first? Uh, I'd say learn structure
first. In fact, go on my website um and
there's a free course in there. You can
sign up there. There's your first lesson
completely free. Then go on my YouTube
and do everything for free there.
There's there's literally a section on
my YouTube called like um I think it's
called like beginners beginners trading
or something like that. There's like a
whole part of my YouTube for that. Just
go there. All right. There's like I'm
telling you there's a lot of edge just
in that alone. That's not me
blowing myself. That's me just being
honest with you. Like you can just go
there. What's it called? Trading
strategy and education for beginners.
All right. There is a ton in there for
free. Start there. Start there. You're
brand new.
Nice work everyone. All you guys
locking. I'm just waiting to see if we
can just pop these stops here and then
I'm going to call it a day and get out
of here.
As you take partials, do you move your
stop loss up? Yes, absolutely.
If you were long here, you don't want to
leave a stop loss there, do you? So TP1,
TP2, my stop now would be right under
this, somewhere under this. I'd want it
to protect this volume because my last
target is up here. Like you could hold a
tiny piece in case we go ballistic on
the day, but like really I'd like you
want it all most of it out into here.
You would not expect basically once we
run these stops there might be a little
spike. It's possible that if all these
shorts get stopped out, you get a little
swipe up, but you want to be selling
into that, right? You want to be selling
into that. This is the counter trend.
Remember, here's your leg down. This is
the counter trend. This is probably
going to get sold into and come back
down into this range. All right. So, if
you you need to be taking profit into
this drive, you get long up here, you
are asking to get absolutely murdered,
right? Absolutely murdered.
I watch your EMA videos and you
suggested a range of 35 to 50, but you
don't seem to use it any or was that
replaced with 21 to 34? They're all in
here. It's the same. It's the same
stuff. I might have like tweaked it
slightly, but I don't think so. Like 45.
I might have changed 50 to 45, but like
I still use a 50 on the day on a daily.
What's my Discord? It's just for just
for members who've done the beginner to
advance course. It's it's free for
members who've done beginner to advance.
Are we shorting from the top of fair
value zones? Um, well,
you could argue, all right, if they poke
through here, trap buyers, come back
underneath, there might be a short back
down, but I'd say the easy money's gone.
Prrisca 3K payout. Thanks so much, Alex.
Nice work, Prrisca. Love it.
Love it. Nice work, Prrisa.
Here we go. Here we go. Stops going to
get popped. Right. Once they pop these
stops, there should be a spike. Please
lock in your profits in that spike. When
it pops through, please lock in the
profits on this spike. Anywhere through
26s is what we're looking for. There
should be a spike through that. Please
lock in like 90% of your profits through
that spike and be done with it and be
happy. If you want to hold a little bit
in case we go higher, great. But here we
go. Trading into 26s here. Very very
close. This is the level. Tap tap tap
tap tap. We should do it. We should lift
through it and then you should be very
very happy people. All right, you
basically hit it here. We're just
looking for this like last little spike
through 26 to try and line this up right
here. That's a 242 point trade I just
gave you.
We go. Three, two, come on. Spike it.
Three. If I count it down, will it do
it? Literally tapped it. Tapped it to
the tick. 26 to the tick. Don't be a
dick for a tick. Remember, I would like
to see them just run through it. One
little spike and then be done. One
little spike.
This is where the stops are. We just
want one little poke through. They're
trying again. One little poke through.
But just be done with it. If If you
don't want to sit through this [\h__\h]
while they do it, just be done with it.
It's a It's a mega trade.
And I don't want any nonsense of people
saying when to enter, when to this, when
to that. Shush.
I told you when to enter and I went to
the toilet and I missed it. Imagine
that. I have to sit through watching you
all make 240 points while I had a pee.
None of that.
I don't want any of that [\h__\h]
God damn it. Man's got to pee. You know
what a cruel market. What a cruel
market. I am cursed by the to. You're so
right. Every time I go to the [\h__\h]
bathroom, the thing absolutely rips. And
it's always after I've had like one or
two attempts and I'm like, "Right, I'll
have a pee. I'll come back freshminded
and go again." And then it's already
[\h__\h] done it.
All right. Right into towards this value
area high. And you can see they're all
front running it. I would imagine we
will pop these, but ES has already
popped it. It's one thing to be aware
of. ES has already popped it
and Vick's trading block to block right
now. Like right into my key levels.
Block to block. Here you go. Here we go.
There you go. Boom. You should be done.
Be very happy. There's the spike.
There's the stops getting run. You are
done for the day. That is a 250 plus
pointer. If you got very lucky, it would
lift all the way up. But you should be
done. At the very least, you can move
your stop right up here now to make sure
you protect all those profits on here.
Thank you very much. Name another trader
who's giving you, you know, we have
nailed over 500 points live on stream
today, both sides. I would love to know
someone else who has done that and given
it to you for free ahead of time with
explanation. Answers on a postcard, I'll
take it. All right,
George. disc if if you've done the
beginner to advance course, George, if
you've paid for the beginner to advance
course, if you scroll to the end of that
course, it will be there. All right, it
will be there. The Discord will be there
for you if you've done it. You'll have
to uh send an email to what it says to
do and you will be granted access. So,
if you get very lucky now, you get all
the way up here. Absolutely incredible.
I cannot believe it.
Cannot believe it.
How do I spot absorption? I think we
went over that. uh earlier.
Is that what you use in the trucker,
Scott? Oh, I love it. Are you still long
ES, Scott, or are you out now? Cuz that
I saw you posted in Discord. That's a
great trade. Great trade, mate.
Great trade.
What a monster day.
What a monster day. All right, guys. I'm
gonna have to get out of here, take
myself to the gym.
What would my expectations for the rest
of the day be? Um, I'd be very careful
now. All right, we've been in a huge
sell, right? This is a pullback leg to
that huge sell. I would imagine we will
get a continuation. Let's just measure
New York out. We go I be high to low of
day. This is printing back to the 50%.
This is why you do not want to be long
anymore. I would imagine that that we
will now start to create a range down
here unless they're going to go risk on
into Apple earnings, which I cannot
imagine they're going to really push.
I'd imagine there'll probably be some
failed look above somewhere in here at
some point and they'll probably do a
little dunk back down into here and then
you probably get a build out in here for
the day. So, I doubt there's going to be
too much to play for the in the
afternoon unless you want to play these
rotations. I mean, there's plenty of
room. The rotations are 200 plus points.
Um, but seeing as we have absolutely
obliterated it, I don't think there's
much reason to hang around. Do you guys?
I don't think so.
What is my Discord, guys? Okay, I'm
going to say this one last time. All
right, Discord is only for people that
do the beginner to advanced course. All
right. So, that's not me trying to
gatekeep you, but if you go to Flowzone
Trader, I'll just show you now because
lots of you are newer who keep turning
up each day, which is fantastic. It's
great to have new people on stream. You
go to the beginner to advanced course,
right? So, you come to my website. It
will look a little something like this,
right? Trading course. You can see
everything in the trading course here if
you want to look at it. If you buy it,
should be $699. If they haven't put it
up, look, you still got $50 up. I'm
going to have to absolutely bollock my
guy. So, it's $649 for that. It's 20
hours. There's 20 hours in here and a
version of the flow zones for free and
discord all included in that one price.
If you want to upgrade with the volume
and order flow, all right, if you want
to put the volume and order flow course
as well, you will get like $100 off
that. All right, cuz that is $499. If
you just want the volume or order flow,
you'll have to go over here. We'll show
you everything in it here. And this is
well over 6 hours. And I think this is
399. There you go. 399. All right. But
there's no Discord in volume and order
flow volume. It's only in the trading
course. This course here, this is
everything in here. Okay. You can see
everything in here.
Am I going to be on tomorrow? Yeah.
Every day, guys. Monday to Friday. Every
day. Monday to Friday. 9:15
all the way until lunch. Right. 9:15 all
the way until lunch. That's it. Every
day I will be here unless I've got some
personal stuff going on. We will do
scam. Yeah, it's a scam. Ryan, what a
scam. It's an absolute scam.
Absolute scam. He doesn't know what he's
doing.
Literally pay for it tfold in what I've
given you today. Anyway,
all right. But like I say, do everything
for free on YouTube. All right. Big love
everyone. And um we will be back
tomorrow closing out the week on a
Friday. Um we've had a fantastic week.
Let's see where we close the day out. Um
for those who are going to trade the
afternoon session, I want to warn you.
All right, it is Apple earnings into
close. The last hour will start to get
wonky. You saw what they did yesterday.
The trap we talked about the trap that
they set yesterday, right into FOMC.
They didn't use the trap. They waited
for earnings. Right? Here's the trap.
Wash shorts trapped pump. All right.
This is the type of move they can do in
earnings. Why? Because the tape's thin.
All right. The tape becomes thin and we
tonight we're going to become a one
stock tape. So, just be careful. You've
got big MAG7 earnings in a day where we
have big big range, right? Do not be
surprised to see some [\h__\h] nasty
moves. Maybe not that high, but like
some nasty moves as we get into closing
and and on earnings, right? So, please
be careful. You do not need to overstay
your welcome. All right? Lock in. Be
happy. Get off. Go and go and do stuff
that makes you happy off the screens.
This is just a job. That's all this is.
It's a job. Don't make it bigger than it
is. Last three things here while I read
through. Discord and the weekly
newsletter are worth their weight in
gold. Yeah, newsletter's free by the
way. Links are down below. Thanks, Alex.
Can't say enough. I'm sure speak for
most. What you come here and do every
day is changing lives. So, thank you
very much. Appreciate that.
75 away from passing Apex.
Congratulations. Just take your time.
Don't force it now because you're going
to now know that you're very close.
Don't force it. All right. Just one
trade at a time.
One trade at a time. All right,
everyone. Big love. If you want to
support the stream, all the links, as
always, are down below. Code FCT for all
your favorite prop firms. Other than
take profit trader, you can use code
flowzone and I'll see you tomorrow
morning. Trade safe, use hard stops, all
that good stuff. Be kind, be humble, be
patient, peace and love.