All
right, morning everyone.
Good morning everyone. Lots to go over
this morning. Um, if you didn't know,
it's FOMC day. All right, so Fed rate
decision coming this afternoon. 97%
chance no rate cut. Uh but what you need
to be aware of is the tone. All right?
Do they change tone? Do they start
talking about more rate cuts than they
had previously anticipated? Very very
possible they might be doing that today.
If they start talking about that market
might like that news, maybe we go risk
on. If they're unwilling to pivot on
anything, then you know it's possible
that you continue to see like the market
not be too sure what it wants to do. But
right now we are absolutely in breakout.
Remember, every day this week since
Friday last week, actually, we've been
long, right? So, since Friday last week,
Friday, Monday, Tuesday, and we're
through all these parts of liquidity
that we were talking about yesterday to
the top side of the Ballinger band,
filling in the gap on the QQQ. We can go
over that shortly. Only thing left right
now is for a drive higher. We're
actually a lot closer to that than uh it
looks based on the cash ETFs, which is
what, you know, is going to become
important. So, what do we need? Well, we
don't really want to be buying up here,
do we? All right, we don't want to be
buying up here. Remember, we're buyers
Friday. We were buyers Monday, we buyers
Tuesday. We don't want to buy up here.
The safest place to buy is very simply
going to be a retest of this sort of
area down here where we've built out
liquidity this week. All right, if this
is your breakout, we need a pullback to
hold to go higher. Now, there's no
saying that the pullback happens right
here today. All right, it is possible if
they're net long, net long, net long,
unless they take profits and allow this
to happen, it's possible we go on some
horrible squeeze. The Ballinger bands
not giving us much room. But we just
need to be aware if it's going to go
without us, it goes without us. We don't
fight the tape. We have to play momentum
and location. Right now, uh, momentum's
fantastic. Location's not so good. If we
move over to the hourlys, you can see
right in here overnight, we got that
extension through. Remember the key
levels yesterday? I think it was 26,045.
Right. So once we came into the new
session,
where are we now? Down here.
Once we came into that new session
overnight, we built liquidity and then
we went for that breakout through all
that liquidity driving higher. So
watching for a retest of this kind of
area here. All right. Previous day value
area high, previous day point of
control. It's also where we had all
those stops built out on the daily.
Remember the daily we just went over all
that liquidity was basically all in
here. All right, all those stops. Think
about the daily wicks that we had up
here like this. Okay, can we come back
and retest that? Do we hold it for a
buy? Very much like yesterday. If you're
interested in the sell
might not be too late, but we can have a
look. There might be that counter trend
move down to here. All right. And then
they have to make a new high. failure to
make a new highs will they start to get
stuck. If we start to lose this there is
a rotation that can happen in here but
if we start to lose this then this
becomes possible uh today tomorrow
Friday all right so if we start to lose
these areas if this becomes a failed
breakout of lots of buyers chasing here
and we lose this area that rotation down
to here can still happen that's still a
very normal pullback and healthy
pullback so just be aware of that okay
as we move into the fivem minute you can
see above what we had
a big shove up
early in the session. Big shove up here.
Early in the session, we go sideways. We
get another shove up. Here's your retest
of this core level here. Failing to make
a new high back to here. This is the
current range. All right. If we fail
underneath uh Asia, then probably that
rotation back down to previous day value
area high and point of control is
possible. We built out lots of
liquidity. Remember this, all of this
from 4:00 and then we had earnings. All
of this is very thin and light on
volume. All right, so it won't take a
lot to repric that if it really wants to
in a New York session. I' got to get a
bit of a move on here. Lots to go
through.
Okay, let's just have a look and pull
you out so you can see the ES exactly
the same where alltime highs on the ES.
There you go. New alltime highs were
made. All that squeezed through. Ducking
down back inside currently. See if it
can hold against previous pivots. very
much the same thing. What's really
interesting is this though, right? The
Q's. This is what you want to keep an
eye on, right? So, we can set a price
alert right here
for alltime high on the QQQ. You can see
we're not quite there yet. So, we filled
this gap. Remember yesterday I said the
efficient market will fill this gap on
QQQ. Well, guess where we got stuck. All
right. So, anyone that joined me on
stream yesterday, what did we say? The
32s, right? See this gap here on the
ETFs? We talked about this gap being
filled. All right. The obligation's been
done literally to the tick. It's been
done in pre-market. Look at that. 32s
pretty much to the tick. So, if you
joined me yesterday, you understand why
I said this will probably get filled in.
That is an efficient market. There is no
obligation for it to go higher. Now, if
this is going to be a failed breakout, a
gap fill come inside. It's possible. I'm
not saying it's probable. I'm saying
it's possible. So, you need to
understand location to buy here is not
good because we've just filled in a big
lowhanging fruit on a daily time frame.
All right. So worth understanding this
on the cues of where we are. We've
filled this in, right? We're opening up
up here. It will need to now hold this
gap. It needs to hold this gap for
continuation. If it cannot hold this
gap, doesn't have to be today, then it's
going to be a problem. So we're looking
for pullbacks to hold really unless you
want to fade it and be the counter trend
play for the pullback also possible.
Spiders, same thing. Breaking out
alltime highs. You can see they are
above alltime high. So Q's have got a
little catch up to do but not too far
away and uh they look pretty good. All
right, Dixie continuing to get
absolutely smacked. All right, big drive
down lower. Jeez, it's not a good time
to hold the dollar right now. Honestly,
not a good look. VIX um is starting to
find a bit of a bid. All right, you've
seen it's starting to try and find a bit
of a bid here. All right, so this is the
same pivot we're going to be looking at
as yesterday. Can it bid and hold over
sort of these 1625s? If so, we're
looking for this move up here. I don't
know why it keeps not putting my
drawings on from another chart. But this
move here on the VIX will allow
weakness. Any dunk under here,
obviously, then we're going to see some
strength come back into the charts.
Let's have a look at the mag.
All right, Apple pulling back into that
area. All right, remember it's got
earnings tomorrow. It's a big drive up.
We're coming right back into this key
level here. If we let go of that, then
next one's all the way down here. These
can still be back tested. It's a bit
like QQQ. This can still be back test
down to here if they're taking profit.
And this is a run up into earnings if
they were starting to lock in some
profit before it.
Same kind of story here on Amazon. Big
drive up. All right. Huge breakout. It
can afford a pullback to hold. Can
afford to come all the way back down
here. But it's gapping up again this
morning. Google gapping up again. Same
kind of story. Has a bit more structure
here on Google to hold and otherwise
failures back down into here. So we just
see if it can hold this three drives. We
talk about three drives, right? One,
two, three. It needs to hold this kind
of area or fade and then reclaim it.
Getting stuck under here will allow this
move into here. This is very thin
but still holding okay for now. Tech has
been strong again. Meta gapping up
again.
See if it can hold its base. Starting to
base out versus this old pivot now. So
can it get going? Microsoft looks good.
That's very very strong again. Thin
under here. This is the problem with all
these stocks at the moment. If you're a
swing long from Monday or Friday, you're
comfortable, right? You can sit in it.
You don't really want to be a new money
long here. You don't really want to
start a new long position here. You're
out of position now if you do that.
Nvidia, great reclaim of the 90s. Super
strong. Let's just zoom that out for a
minute. I need to remember where we're
at on that. All right. So, it's looking
to get above 93s and 96s. Really 93s. 96
is a big level. You can see both sides
of this on the way up. That's your
level. Reclaim that. We'll leave sellers
trapped and then we will go for new high
alltime highs if we can reclaim that.
Gapping up again on Nvidia. It's a
strong gap. And Tesla starting to try
and find a bid down here. All right. So,
it's been washing down the last few days
in a range. There you go. Washing down
in the range, but coming to back test
this level where we first found bids.
All right. Coming back to it. Can we
hold it and start getting going? Equally
weighted mag
wakey wakey. There we go. Equally
weighted mag gapping up. We do look a
bit steep here. All right. This is my
worry right now. My concern in this
market. Here's the base. The failure to
break. But this is a big drive. We can
actually, you know, we could do with
this setting up here. Unless they're
going to do it up here. We could do with
something like this,
which would work nicely in the cues.
Let's have a look at some broader names.
Netflix starting to find a bid, which is
good. Still just got a starter position
in that. Not proved anything yet. I want
to get through this week in earnings.
AMD
starting to try and claw back. So, if we
can get a new base here on AMD, it's the
same story for chips. If it can base, we
can make new alltime highs. And ABGO
starting to get going. So, a little bit
better.
Just want to have a look at this. 10
year 30.
Still basing. Very dangerous.
Very dangerous.
You going to show me the 30 yet.
Okay.
Right. Don't have huge expectations this
morning, please, folks. All right.
People have been riskone, like I said,
since last Friday. The positioning
started last Friday and we've got FMC
coming this morning. So no, don't be
like aggressively risk on this morning
and we've got lots of stuff coming.
Okay, lots of people saying they've got
issues on Ninja and uh trade. Let me
have a look. 2050s. Yes, I have the
same. No data.
Okay. Well,
not a lot we can do then, is there?
Not a lot we can do. Trader bait down
for some reason, is it?
Yeah, ninjas are also locked up. All
right, folks. So, we'll just chart on
here for those of you who are not
trading the trader bait on Ninja.
Hopefully, they get it sorted. Not
seeing a notification. Let's have a
look.
Can't believe this stuff, can you?
But just be careful. Don't be forcing
in. If there's no data, we can't do
anything.
Okay, trade bait down. There we go. All
right, folks. So, we'll just chart on
here. I can't execute trades without
that. So, we will chart on here together
and we'll just have to see what we can
get.
Right. So, you'd be watching these
pivots here. down here is the the real
interest level. All right. So, we have
the GlobeEx pivot right here, but other
than that, you're looking for there's
your range. It's quite a big range as
well. In fact, we can Let's have a look
at what we did overnight
on the new print. Very rarely do this,
but because the range is so big, it will
be worth it.
Okay, that's your cluster.
So this level, this guy here is key
to lose this edge. There is a bit of a
dip I might hold in here. 218s.
I'd say this gu is pivotal.
We'll leave that on just for the start.
So we can see the overnight range
because the gap's quite big from
previous days.
Why is previous day point of control
showing above?
91s. No, you should be down here, mate.
There you go.
All right. Yeah. So, we've got like a
200 point gap
from the previous day value to overnight
value. All right. So, this this is a is
a huge imbalance here. Right. So, if
they let go of value
and they stay heavy, this rotation here
is very possible.
Well, don't worry guys, if it's a if
it's a outage everywhere, um it won't
they will refund you. They will have to
refund you because if it's a trade of
eight issue, they can't have you in a
prop and not do anything. So, you don't
don't stress about it. They will refund
you any any problems because if it's if
it's not a singular issue, which it
clearly isn't. Everyone's experiencing
it. They will have no choice but to give
everyone their money back. So, don't
stress. Don't stress.
What's the plan today? I would say
potentially being a buyer down here.
Potentially fading this here to TP1, TP2
or this here down here. I don't really
want to be a buyer up here and then down
here. I'd like to be a buyer.
Um, but obviously right now my plan is
to do nothing because I don't have any
data for uh Ninja unfortunately.
Same as everyone else.
Yeah. Nothing. I got I got another
I got nothing. Can't do anything. So,
I'll just read out and call you what I
can see.
Don't worry. I know you're calling
trading vote, but you got to understand
they'll be they'll be under the caution
everyone. If you're trading prop, they
will fix it. All right? You'll get your
money back. Don't it's not worth
stressing about. Don't get yourself
wound up about it. Honestly, I'm talking
from experience here. Okay? So, current
overnight value is right here. This is
your key level. If they hold this,
they're going to look for the rotation
all the way if they can get back through
uh 62s all the way up to these 300s.
And if they fade 300s, that's your
overnight point of control.
And then we can see what we get develop
after that. Let's put this on here.
There we go. No, it's not what I want.
Yeah, lower your expectations today,
folks. And FOMC day after such a big run
up as well.
Lower those expectations. Uh, smash that
like button for me nice and early. Would
like to do some giveaways on stream as
always.
ES looking strong. I'd say look at the
spy pre-market came down held previous
day high held that pivot looks very
strong. The spiders right now they
probably want the 700s on the spy.
Right. So relative weakness in NQ today
versus SPY uh in the morning open. Not
in the gap up, but just in the morning
open.
Could be a dad day anyway. Could be very
easily be a dud day or a dud morning I
should say.
They're
trying to find that bid to VWAP. If they
get acceptance through VWAP, they will
look for all the way up here.
That's what they will attempt to do is
to get up to there for the retest.
There's quite a few nodes on the way up,
but they will attempt if it's a big if.
If they can't break down o underneath
under overnight value, right, and they
hold current PC, they will try and force
this rotation. They will need acceptance
through here. If they lose this, then
GlobeEx
and down to here is possible. All right.
So, you're at a battleground right now.
So, you need to wait to find if if we're
going to have acceptance or not of
holding this gap. And if so, this is the
target, which they're trying to do right
now. All right. They can't get under
here. That morning dip so far is held.
They'll break underneath value and
they're going to try and come up for
this. There you go. Starting to get
going. So, if you are able to get long
in that, this is now your target up into
310.
It's a shame. It's quite a nice setup,
but what can you do when the network and
everything's down?
Morning, Scott.
So, if they hold VW up now, 310 is where
they're looking for.
And if they let go of point of control
and let go of here, then the rotation
all the way uh 91s and then down here is
possible. Both are possible. Uh for me
personally, I wouldn't like to be net
long today unless we come down into
these areas. For me personally, we're a
little bit frothy up here, especially
after we talked about those cues,
closing that gap.
And we've left that gap open actually
because we've we closed yesterday, the
high of yesterday was basically right
into those 32s, right? And then we
pulled back and then we've gapped up
above it. So, we have a gap back down to
that old gap fill level. It's just
nasty. Nasty.
Yeah, I can't do anything here, folks.
I'm really sorry.
Yeah, I won't be touching mobile app
either. Okay, back down to value. If
they lose this, then we'll come right
back down for this GlobeEx level. So, if
they stay heavy under here, right, we
built up a node here. There's a node
down into this. There's a little node
here. If we lose 20s, you're into
GlobeEx. And if you lose that, you're
right down into here. This is a very
possible trade today. That would be your
your counter trend long pullback. Think
about what we've been doing. Think about
this just pulling back to here, right?
This fade here is possible that they
scoop it back up. I would be interested
in being a buyer down there if we come
there. That's very much like yesterday.
I don't know that they're going to have
the juice to do it, but if they did,
that's an area I'd be interested in
being a buyer in today.
No, no. Like, yeah. So, anyone joining
late, trade of eight is down, guys. So,
I've got no data on Ninja, no data on
trade of eight. I'm completely unable to
trade today. Um, I'm not even stressed
about it. Today is not a day that I'd be
uh excited to trade about.
Um if we think about what we've had this
week, why why I don't really care too
much, right? Let's just look at this
five minute chart, right?
Let's think about what we've had this
week. We have been long on dips all week
long. All right, from the Sunday open
was the flush down into the key level to
hold. All right, Monday off offered the
long opportunity back up. Then we got
long again Tuesday for this opportunity
back up and then overnight
they have ripped it higher. All right,
because we're in breakout. If we zoom
out or if you just look down here on
this chart can just do it here. We're in
breakout, aren't we? These were the
targets, right? Remember this yesterday
in the last few days, these were the
targets. We're in breakout. Do I want to
buy up here? No. All right. Remember,
when we look at the charts, we're
thinking, what is the location? What is
the momentum? Momentum is fantastic.
Where's the best location? It's going to
be a pullback, isn't it? Pull back into
here is going to be the best location to
be buying or where we're buying early
early week. One, two, three. Those three
buy opportunities we had, right?
Unfortunately, we're day traders, not
swing traders, right? So, I don't want
to be adding that long up here. Very,
very dangerous. I want to be adding that
long down here on a pullback. So, today
might be the counter trend move this
morning down into some of these regions.
I don't know how far they come down. Do
they get to the 26, 150, 120s? Do they
come below? I don't know. Um, but it's
why I'm not too bothered because I'm I'm
not missing a protrend trade. Pro trend
trade will be if we come in here and we
do something like that, right?
Hopefully that makes sense. So, I'm not
it's not a it's not a huge miss today.
If the if if the networks were down and
we were missing yesterday, I'd be very
upset, right? If we were going into
breakout with a squeeze on, I'd be very
upset. So, if you are net shorting this
now though underneath here, if you're
net short versus 40s now, you'll be
looking, remember I said 20s is your
first target just based on a node. Then
you're looking for this level here into
192s.
Uh let me just measure this out.
Yeah, where we are here. And then yeah,
under 192s, we get very thin under 192s
all the way down into uh these areas
down here where I'd be interested in
being long around here. Right. So I
would say TP1 we've already hit right
now. If I move you to higher time frame,
you will see why. Right? We have this
node here that we developed in Asia.
There you go. All right. So that's your
TP1. If you get acceptance under that,
look how thin we get underneath 192s.
Look at this volume. Non-existent
volume. All right. So, unless they do
one of these, if they close that gap,
we're going to come all the way down.
All right. So, 192 is big, big level.
All right. Either they will fake it and
bid it back up or you will get a
complete snap from 192s probably all the
way back down to 26,100.
There's a 100 point snap under 92s if
they let it go.
a close trade and relaunch with an
update and it's working. That's good.
Well, I've tried a few times on uh
Ninja Trader. Got nothing. I'll try can
try again.
I can try again.
So, back to back test this level.
Sellers need to sell versus New York and
point of control. And if they don't,
we'll go back into range. Like I said,
I'm not too worried about missing today.
If I'm going to miss a day, this is the
day to miss. You might all say, "Well,
there's going to be loads of
opportunities later in FOMC." I wouldn't
be surprised if FOMC was a bit of a dud.
Earnings are what going to really
matter.
Just reboot. Get the data.
H. I have got some data. Is this live
though? 40.
Yes.
Frozen again.
So, it's showing me what happened, but
I've got no chart moving. Yeah, it's not
worth the risk right now until it's
smooth.
Yeah, I've got I've got I can see. So,
I've got historical prints, but I've not
got anything moving. My charts are just
not moving.
Wish they were so I could help a little
bit more.
Try that one more time. Maybe.
Okay. Reclaim value. So, same story
again. If they hold this, so we hit that
first node. If they hold this now, if
they are able to hold this and get
acceptance over here, back to this. All
right. This is the rotation. This is why
I'm like less fussed. We need to build
out liquidity one way or another.
They gave a fade into that first level.
TP1 hit and it did it straight back up.
Should talk about the MAG. Tesla 1.11%
up. Nvidia 1.73% up. Microsoft 0.14%
down. Meta 0.05% up. Google quarter% up.
Amazon 0.37% up. Apple 0.89.
And now Ninja won't even open for me.
Fun and games.
fun and games.
VIX stuck in a range as well. So, it
keeps finding bids down into those uh
1637s. That uh pivot really is down
towards 25s if it wants to come down
there. Same one yesterday, right? We
couldn't get above it yesterday. It had
numerous attempts. Same pivot.
No data this time. Log out. Log back in.
Dreadful.
You've never seen candlesticks like like
that. Like what?
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. We know, Mr. Slim.
Yeah. They're all down. We're just
testing to see if uh they're coming back
on. Some people saying they're able to
trade. I'm not able to trade. Can't I've
got no nothing. I got another nutter.
So, my footprint's stuck. So, I can't
really help too much. Okay, squeeze is
on now. Back to 310s. Then, if they're
going to test overnight of control,
right, so they dipped and held uh the uh
Asia session, that node that we talked
about into the 220s, right? They held
220s and now they're trying to get
acceptance back up.
So if we just think about this zoomed
out, right? They held this 220. This
here is what we were looking at. That's
why it was TP1. If you took the short,
no acceptance reclaim. They're now
trying to get acceptance over current
point control back to overnight point
control. And this is the danger, right?
This is the danger to go higher. I would
rather they built this out down here.
Right? I would rather they offer this.
This is a much safer trade where I'm
buying closer towards fair value rather
than deep into premium.
Deep into premium right now. We're right
at that top daily ballinger band as
well. We are running out of room to do
anything.
How does one get these indicators? Um,
you can do the course.
It's on the website
flowzontenttrader.com
and uh a version of these indic
indicators comes free with the course or
you can upgrade to the pro which is what
you see on my chart right here. This
right the pro system.
You can get that on my website as
welltrader.com.
All right. So, the question is, can they
get up into these 310s?
V-shaped recovery. No, no dip back down
to uh confirm it's going to hold 60s
yet. So,
you'd want to really see something like
this if it's really going to get going.
You have to be careful. You're still
inside the uh opening range for the
first 15 minutes. We're just building
that liquidity out.
Please explain TP1. what the downside
TP1 or the upside the downside TP1 was
this see this node right overnight value
we draw it out because it's a big gap up
here is a big node right so that's where
we expect price to come to we go to this
node we find a bid there that's your TP1
on the short it rebids it holds right if
we're going to find acceptance tire
we're going to come up for this now
right which is why I keep saying if
you're long your first TP is 310 Then
not too far away. Where did we get to
there? Coming up towards the 300s.
Unrecognizable trade. Yeah, I've g I've
literally given up. I'm not even looking
I'm not even looking at it. It's
completely pointless at this point. All
right, so you're coming towards this TP.
Let's have a look at liquidity on the
book.
Yeah, you've got some guys here. 300
310s, 325s, 350. It's all possible. So
once you get acceptance through this,
this is a big level to take some profit.
If you did get long, this is a big level
to be taken some profit off. Once we get
through that, you're looking for 325s,
which is overnight value area high, and
then uh 350s, which is the overnight
high. Those are the levels to the
upside.
Hopefully that helps, folks. I'm sorry
I'm not trading live with you today.
There is nothing I can do about it.
What is the range volume on the left? On
the left, it's uh the overnight. It's
the volume from overnight.
I very rarely put that on, but uh we had
a very big gap up today. So, it became
important to know where people were
trading, where they were positioned
overnight.
S&P. Yeah. 70,000 right now. I see it.
I see it.
Spy trying to break out to get up
towards that 700 probably.
But the best I can do is call the trades
for you today and try and teach you. I
will do my best to make sure you guys
who can trade make some money today even
without me. So I'll sit here even
without me. I'll try my best to help
you. Right. So developing a little bit
of a node here now. See bulls will want
to hold this here into 80s.
Right. this right here,
edge of current value. Balls will want
dips to hold versus that. If they lose
that, they're going to come straight
back down to the midpoint, which will
not be ideal. So, if balls are going to
complete rotation, they would want this
to hold and to rip this, right? Or like
something like this. Otherwise, they're
coming down into this point of control,
which would not be very nice. It's
probably near the midpoint. If you think
of one R one R, it's not a very not a
very nice session.
So back to mid, back to point of
control. Same thing can work here. The
moment we haven't finished a rotation
either side. So we haven't completed
this rotation to back test. Oh gosh. To
back test and we haven't completed this
rotation to back test this. So we're
just building out, which is what we've
pretty much done all night long, right?
We're building out versus here.
So, I'm saying if you're going to miss a
day's trading, today is not a bad day to
miss, folks.
Trade event users can actually trade on
Trading View. How? If there's no data,
how how can they do that?
There's there's no data, I don't think.
I don't think they'd be able to execute
the point control from alltime high is
299. Is that relevant from the week of
alltime high or from alltime high to
current price? I mean it's all relevant.
Yes, absolutely Indie. Absolutely. It's
all relevant.
If you pay for data on trading view,
well, I pay for data on trading view,
but I still don't understand how you
could how you could do that because you
would need to execute
uh via logging into trade of eight and
trade of eight data is down and it will
be pulling its own data. I don't know.
You guys do what you want. I would not
be touching it. If if look, if my
broker's down, I don't trade. If a data
provider is down, I don't trade. Right?
This is a job. This isn't a joke. Don't
be like doing something and hoping,
right? Just don't do it. It's It's
seriously It's not worth it. It's one
day of your whole trading career.
It's just not worth it. In my opinion,
you guys do what you want. In my
opinion, I wouldn't be doing it. I won't
play I wouldn't be playing, you know,
American football without putting my
pads on. It's the same thing.
All right. We need everything working.
All right, VIX starting to spike here,
folks. Just be careful. Starting to
break out here on VIX.
So, next pivot for VIX is going to be up
towards 1670s. So, it's getting going.
So, it might add weakness into this
market if it can really drive. If it
finds acceptance through that, then uh
maybe. But again, here's your orb. We're
just boxed in.
Almost completed the rotation. Didn't
quite make it. We're just boxed in right
now doing nothing.
It's very possible that we do this for a
long time and there something shifts
before we get to FMC.
Why do my candles look different? Um,
they're based on momentum. At the
moment, this is not a momentum setup,
right? Everything's flat.
So, you got print prints above and
prints below, right?
What these are great for are when we're
in breakout trends
like here,
right? All the time with blue. White is
an inside bar. So all the time we're
blue or white, we're just building
upside. It's it's telling you not to
fade it, right? So it's built to stop
you fading it. Again, the day before
don't try and short when we're just
constantly green, right? But when we go
red,
right, there's chances of fades, right?
So they're just based on the momentum
basically to stop you picking tops and
bottoms. Bet everything that I built in
the system is basically to stop you
trying to pick a top and bottom
on a trend day.
Okay, my Ninja Trader has just woken up.
Do we have
gaps in it? 51 50 42. Okay, so I do have
a gap in it. So, let me just save this.
Close it down. Try opening back up
again.
Trader's back. There you go. You guys
are saying the same. I just saw data
come back on, but I need no gaps in my
chart. I need to see what's happened.
It's the same level up here. The
rotation to 310 is where they're trying
to get to still.
market trying to find a bid. Apple the
only one red now. The Tesla now 1.14%
up. Nvidia 1.71. Microsoft 0.20. Meta
0.43. Google's just gone green 0.04.
Amazon 0.78%
up. The only one red. Apple 0.66%
down. It's trying to claw back.
All right.
Do we have data? I've just logged back
in. We do. Okay. Give this a minute or
two just to make sure it's steady
and then we will see what we get.
Thanks, Miguel.
Yeah, it's crazy, isn't it? Stream's
growing fast. It's cuz people are
starting to realize that you actually
learn on this stream.
I actually teach.
Okay, same pivot here as before. Can
they find acceptance through this? If
so, 310 is the target and then
acceptance over that. You're looking for
25s and 50s. Basically,
the squeeze is currently on. So, they're
trying to get back towards that opening
range high.
Yeah. Smash that like button for me,
folks. We will do some giveaways on
stream as always.
Still in rotation here.
Just keep comparing NT to uh Trading
View for a bit to make sure. We are
starting to get some cleaner data, which
is good. which is good. All right. ES
stuck at VWAP. Can't find that bid over
VWAP quite yet. Spy, same kind of story.
Just stuck in a range. Q, same kind of
story.
Is that Q?
We did have an alltime high on Q.
pre-market faded back. All right.
What futures am I trading? ENQ. ENQ. The
NASDAQ
actually learn more. My first two live
sessions Monday, Tuesday, than one month
of research on YouTube. Well, that's
good. That's good to know.
Is a short bias valid since we're near
alltime highs? I wouldn't have a short
bias because we're near all-time highs.
I don't think that's uh a reasonable
explanation, you know, to have a short
bias. You need a short bias when there
are sufficient amount of bulls trapped
or when you're looking for that high
time frame pullback, which could happen
today. Like we said, we are, you know, I
am I am bullish on this chart and on
this market right now, but today is not
a good location to be buying in.
Remember, we've been buying Friday,
Monday, Tuesday. every session I've been
buying. I ignored all the shorts every
session. I told you why. Right now,
we're still in that breakout, but uh it
gets more and more risky the higher and
higher we go because we're not pulling
back. We need to be buying around the
26,100. Somewhere around there, even
26,000 is a reasonable area to buy off
up here. We're about 300 points too high
right now.
Go charting for orderflow charts. What's
go charting? Is that a software?
Is that who emailed me the other week?
Pricing USA.
I don't see why you need it.
30 a month on sale. I don't like I don't
see why you need it. You could just pay
a onetime fee for Ninja Trader or invest
in your account on Ninja Trader or pay
for the pro on on Trading View. So, I'm
not familiar with it, but it it doesn't
I don't see why it would be needed.
Why are we too high right now? Uh just
because of the move that we've done
here. Uh
right, hourly chart. In fact, let's go
daily to start with. So, you can see
this, right? Daily chart.
We've broken out from here, right? We
haven't pulled back to make sure that
this base is firm. All right. Once we
pull back and hold this, this would be a
breakout retest. Then we can think about
the drive. Remember this week we were
buying uh Friday last week, Monday this
week, Monday New York open, Tuesday on
the dip, right? Think about where we
were buying this week. We were buying
from the 500s looking for the lowhanging
fruit up to here. We've had a 600 point
move that we wanted this week. We are
now also at the top Ballinger band. All
right.
Chances of going beyond two sigma is
very very small. Look what happens. Top
Ballinger band, top Ballinger band, top
Ballinger band, bottom Ballinger band
back to me. Bottom Ballinger band,
bottom Ballinger band, bottom Ballinger
band. So what we actually need to do,
maybe we have a black swan kind of day
where we close outside it. But what we
need to do is this and the fiveday.
Anyone who's been here this week will
know I've been talking about this, which
will look something like this, right?
Something like this. See this between
the fiveday when we go into strong
trends, you'll see it again, right? We
build out liquidity like this is a prime
example.
Think about this here.
Pivot, breakout, retest, right?
Breakout, retest, breakout, retest. 5day
top bowl, 20-day trend. Okay? We need to
have room to do it. Now, that's not to
say we can't squeeze higher today and
not and and never do the retest. It's
absolutely possible. Right? I want you
to understand the difference. It's
absolutely possible. This thing wants to
do this today. It will do it. It will do
what it wants. But our job, our job is
to understand risk. I don't want to buy
here hoping we get up here. What I want
to do is wait for the market to come
down here in here, trap a load of
sellers, then offer me the buy to
complete that rotation higher. Right?
That's what I want to do. That's how I
can manage my risk. Right? Because
that's our job. Right? So this up here,
very risky trade. This down here, much
better. We've got a base, right? So
anyone who didn't stop out, anyone who
was a belligerent short and didn't stop
out when we return in you best believe
they will stop out and they will become
market buyers. And that can happen. If
we fail this, all right, if we fail to
hold this and we do this, we want to be
very careful, right? If this is a look
above and fail with the QQQs and ES
taking out alltime highs, look above and
fail. We want to be very careful for
this move here, right? So this is why
I'm waiting. I'm waiting.
I don't mind missing, you know, a little
bit of action every now and again. Even
if we look at the hourlies,
where's my houries? Right? If we think
about this week, this was the Sunday
open. All right, think about this from
Sunday open. Right, we are
almost 4% up and a,000 points up. And
this trend is, I would say, pretty
bloody steep. All right, that's pretty
steep, isn't it? Right? This is not
pulled back. Right? A healthy trend will
offer this move here which might come
today would would offer this move here
back into the developing profile and
then we can move this somewhere like
this. Build out some liquidity reclaim
this and that offers a nice squeeze to
alltime highs at that point. Right? So
that's why hopefully that makes sense.
Right? Always ask yourself when you come
into the chart, what's the location?
What's the momentum? What am I looking
for? Where do I want to enter? Where is
an interesting location to enter?
Yeah, I'm having the same by the way,
folks. So, I'm my my Ninja Trader is now
down again. All right, so I can show
you. So, I will not be trading this.
I've made the decision. That's why I
said I'm going to wait to see if it
matches up. You would have heard me say
that like five minutes ago. It is just
not worth it. And I am not going to blow
all my work because people uh can't sort
out their data centers properly or
whatever it is.
So, we can just keep those of you
trading, you guys can trade. I'll keep
calling levels and I'll keep teaching
you what I'm looking at. You can try and
understand.
Yes, two sigma is the two standard
deviation. So, a standard Ballinger band
on a daily, if you understand how
Ballinger bands work, your middle line,
a lot of people don't understand this,
your middle line, your middle line, your
mean on a Ballinger band is your 20day
SMA, right? Two standard deviations
above that is your top B ballinger band.
Two standard deviations below that is
your bottom Ballinger band. Why do I use
a five-day? How many trading days are
there in a week? Five. How many trading
days are there in a month? 20. So, I'm
looking for what's my weekly bias versus
my monthly bias on a rolling time scale.
That's why I use the five and the 20.
All right. So, hopefully that makes
sense. They like they're just they stop
you buying in bad locations. That's the
best way of me putting it. If we're up
at the top Ballinger band, you really
need to ask yourself, should I be buying
here? Answer is probably no.
Hey, Alex, I'm new here. Welcome. Thanks
for joining. Thanks for joining.
Is the uh Ballinger band equivalent to a
standard deviation? Yes. only versus the
20-day only not like a rolling
regression trend or standard deviation
that way which is how I used to trade
that was the first way I traded but
those who have been with me since day
dot will know that it's the first way I
used to trade back in uh 2019 and beyond
yeah not not based on uh like a
regression channel standard deviation
but yes based on your 20-day SMA
no discount on the course right now. I'm
sorry, my friend.
Thousand people watching only 100 uh 300
likes. Yeah, that's that's just not good
enough. Come on, folks. Smash that like
button. We will be giving away Apex
accounts on here today for sure.
I was in here the other day asking about
funded accounts, but I recently seen you
had Apex Coupon and I popped some evals
and appreciate you have been teaching me
so much. You're welcome.
Yes, I for me personally, I only look at
Ballinger bands on the daily. I'm not
interested in them uh on lower time
frame charts. That's not again that is
not to say you can't use them, right?
Lots of people use them on like 15
minutes or hourly charts. For me, I
don't use them. I like them on the
daily. I like using them on the daily.
That's that's how I get my bias on the
daily of like where I think what we need
to do and what's possible.
I'm not I'm not Eba's brother. He's a
bit of a legend though.
Good morning. Good morning. Good
morning.
How do you frame your trades? Uh top
down analysis. So daily daily down into
like hourlies into five and and one
minutes. And all I'm looking at is what
kind of condition. Remember the market
is only ever doing two things, right?
We're either building liquidity or we're
searching for liquidity. We're either in
fair value or we're searching for new
fair value. So we're either auctioning
up or we're in a range, right? So if we
think about the conditions of the market
and the market and normal market will
look something like this.
Maybe we build some value out. We search
higher. We have one more search higher.
And then they go nope. There's no value
there. Maybe we build out. We search
higher and they go no. Okay. That is a
pretty standard looking market. All
right. So we need to understand what
condition we're in. If we are in a
breakout at this point, right, then I'll
be looking for longs. The protrend at
this point is up,
right? This is how I decide what I'm
looking at. This is up, right? And if
we're moving point control and value
higher, that's confirming that I'm
trying to trade upside. What else could
we think about? Like a P-shaped profile.
If we have a Pshaped profile in this
day, and it gives me the opportunity to
get long at like a value area low on
this pullback in here, right? If this is
a daily chart, then lower time frame,
what am I looking for? I'm going to look
for something that looks a little
something like this. All right, some
kind of trap down here to get long and
then I'm TP1 and see how far we can get
up. Right. And then we do the same thing
the next day. We're going to assume
pullbacks hold. And when we fail to
break out and we do this, we are now in
a range. So in a range, I'm trading the
edges. So I'm fading this back inside.
I'm buying dips back inside. Or if I'm
really honest with myself, I'm leaving
that alone, right? Because I hate
ranges. So, or I'm at least using small
size. And then once we break out of the
range and we hold, then I'm looking for
upside until we come to targets. Now,
let's say this is a top ballinger band.
This is very similar to what we've had
recently. All right, we've broken out of
a range this week. We've come up to the
top Ballinger band. It might be that we
need to retest this level. Now, what I'd
be hoping for this week is actually the
continuation higher. If we don't get
that, this collapse is possible. So,
it's all about understanding what is the
higher time frame doing, right? what are
we doing higher time frame and then
moving down. That's why it's important
you guys join me from 9:15 Eastern time
because every day you will notice my
process is exactly the same. Every day
we start on the daily and we move down
the time frames. We look if value has
been moved up, what type of shape we
have. Is there a big gap? Are we likely
to see a fill on that gap? Are we
holding value?
The source boss, I don't know, maybe I
don't know if you've been joining me
with with me this week. You you mustn't
what you've done. All right, so source
boss says, uh, I've nearly blown my
funded on this bullish move up. I keep
thinking it's going to go back down, but
it hasn't. What you've done is what a
lot of people will do is they just go,
it's too expensive. It shouldn't do
this. It's got to come down. It's got to
it doesn't have to do a thing, right? It
doesn't have to do a thing. It will come
down when too many bulls are caught and
not the fallout. And right now, all that
we've had is shorts caught in it every
single day and and we're now breaking
out on the daily, right? So, unless we
start collapsing, there's no reason. So,
there might be a counter trend. This
would be the counter trend. If we let go
of this, there might be this move to
here or here today, right? But if we
think about if we zoom out, right,
that's just a pullback, right? You will
only want to play that pullback when all
these bulls are caught. So if you keep
guessing tops, right, and hoping, right?
All you're getting is these micro
pullbacks and breakout. Micro pullbacks
and breakout. You if you're going to
fade, the best fades come when bulls are
stuck and we start going through key
levels, right? And not before then. So
even those who joined me yesterday I
gave you one short yesterday which I
even didn't take myself
which was right here and you can see it
hit the target
right so yesterday I gave you we were
long yesterday and we were long on this
move here we played
this long to here and you had the chance
to play this long to here and this was
the short into lunch just before lunch
wasn't it? Yep. short here down to this
gray box. That was the opportunity you
could have actually had it again, right?
Because this was the first time we had
bulls trapped. You do not want to get
short before you have a significant
amount of volume trapped
above you. That is overhead.
You're just doing a dance here this
morning. Nothing to do here, folks.
How much does bookmap come into my
trading? Uh, yeah, it does. Especially
when we're coming into a level I'm
interested in. All right. So, definitely
if I if I'm looking for track
participants, bookmap and footprint. So,
between that and here, but I actually
have this on ninja, but obviously it's
not working right now. Between these two
things, right, quite a lot. Quite a lot.
So, take that last push. You can
starting to see buyers are starting to
get caught here. Buyers are starting to
get caught here. So if we start closing
under this, I think you're going to see
weakness for an imbalance fill down into
this. And if we get under that, this is
your target. And if we get under that
gap fill is possible.
You can see buyers are starting to get
caught over that New York open in the
last, I don't know, 5 10 minutes. So if
they keep rejecting that, there's
potential for a wash here.
I just have to see if we can get
acceptance underneath this little ledge
here at 37. And if we can, you're
probably going to get a revisit of low
day. What was the auction like a lower
day?
Yeah, I think there's a chance to
revisit that. Here we go. So, it's doing
it already. There you go. So, we just
saw those buyers caught. So, there you
go. That's bookmapping footprint.
So, it all depends now. Can we get
acceptance under 37s? This edge right
here. Sellers need to find acceptance
under that. If they find accept this
move here. So, you've got buyers stuck
up here. If you get this, this is
possible. If you get that, then the next
orange line is possible. Remember, this
is a huge level under here. We are very,
very, very thin. Imagine this. We've got
like a bump here and then it's just like
this down to here. There's nothing until
we get down into these.
Looks good. The short looks like it's
going to play out for you guys if you
took it.
You got some covering here on bookmap
into the twelves and the 200s. Let's see
if there's a guy down at 92s or not.
Yes, there is. Yeah, right here.
So, yeah, they want it down into there.
They want to see if they can protect
that shelf. No, I don't use range bars.
No, no, no.
Why NASDAQ over SPY? Uh, just cuz I got
I like the volatility. I got used to how
it moves.
Can make really good money in it once
you understand it. Here you go. So, here
comes the lower day test.
I wish I had
better uh availability to look at this
more detail with you with my footprint.
Try one more time for Ninja.
Okay, so lower day test coming up. So
I'd be like taking a partial into that
and then see if you get uh into 92s and
then if you get acceptance under 92s
then you can probably see a wash in this
back down to those levels that we said
we could be interested in buying off
today.
What other volume on side candles called
is footprint footprint? There's a video
on my YouTube for it and show you how to
do it.
So yes, under previous day high spy
under previous day high. They had gap
fill potential if they start staying
heavy here. They're into key levels. So
it would be a partial kind of place
right now. And then if you get under
here,
there's potential for the wash. But ES
already coming on the previous day high.
Yeah, VIX doing that breakout that we
talked about. Remember we said trade
into once it started to break through
50s and basing above those 25s, the
moves into 70s. We're there now. So,
next stop for VIX is probably the 83s.
If we break through 83s, it's 95s. If
break through 95s, it's 1712s.
I've still got nothing on Intrader,
folks. I can't I can't do anything here.
I'm really sorry. I'll try my best to
help you. In fact, let me
maybe I move this
right into that buy side imbalance at
this low of day. I still think you're
going to get a lower day here and you're
going to get an auction lower. Looks
good.
It's really good.
Those buyers getting stuck through the
imbalance. There's your lower date.
There you go. So, that was the key was
right here. Once we saw those buyers get
stuck, someone asked, do I use bookmark
or anything like that? Once we saw the
buyers get stuck here, that was the sign
and there's your low of day. So, now the
next targets that's TP1 here. TP2 is
here. All right. If you get that, that
will be TP2. Otherwise, this is the same
level that becomes important, right?
Point of control on the day where those
buyers got stuck. Remember where
those buyers got stuck. That was a good
auction at the low. Sellers coming in
down there. So, sellers will kind of
want to defend these 50s. If they can't
defend 50s, there's a squeeze back out
to the upside as we are in a range.
Doing my best to teach you today, folks.
There's nothing else I can do.
Uh Cladio is asking, "Do I mind set
sharing my footprint candle uh settings
for Trading View?" I don't, but it's on
YouTube. It's there's a free video. I
put it out like two weeks ago. Save me
going through it all right now. So, if
you just go on my YouTube, I'll try and
find it for you. In fact, a second
print chart. I give you my settings in
there. share with beta.
So you're now looking for 92s if they
can find acceptance lower. There you go,
my friend.
So that last link I sent,
what's my bias for today? Uh probably a
I'm probably expecting the pullback leg.
It's just depends where they stop it,
right? So, do they defend GlobeEx
or do they come down in here and then do
we bid off this into FMC?
So, that's what I'd like to see for
today is that kind of move there. If we
fail this, all right, if we fail
previous day value area high, obviously
there's a rotation debt down into the
lows. If we fail that, we have to watch
the current week developing value
underneath 88s or definitely underneath
well yeah definitely underneath previous
day value area low I'd be very very
concerned because from that point if we
start finding acceptance underneath
26,044
then I think there's very probable that
we move down to 25,900
right but I I'm would be looking to bid
either around this orange line or even
more preferable down here. So if they
can trap sellers here, that rotation,
but ideally here is better. So on a
lower time frame, I'd be looking for
some kind of nonsense down into this and
then base and then maybe a wick and this
move here. I think it's possible. At the
moment, they're protecting GlobeEx.
You got remember it's FOMC day. So
anything they do now is just building
liquidity for later. Anything they do
now is just building liquidity.
Yeah, I've tried connecting. It's it's
it opens and then it just freezes.
Yeah, first I think that's first time on
stream. 1,00 uh viewers. Thanks, guys.
It's amazing. It's amazing. Thank you.
Smash that like button for me, guys.
We're only over half of you not hit the
like button.
Nice. Lot lots of you getting that
short. Nice work,
Joe. It's definitely It's definitely not
like GameStop that I mean that they
should have gone to jail for that. That
was dreadful what happened there. It
worked well for me. I did take that was
one of the biggest trades of my career.
I got short uh the morning after that.
Why am I able to pass evals heavily but
never get paid payout when funded?
Probably psychology by the looks of it.
Uh, two ticks, Fernando. Yeah, they're
tick based.
Take care. Take care.
We're growing. Yeah, we are growing. All
right, so come back to test that 50.
Remember, we just talked about the 50.
This is the level sellers must defend,
right? They must defend 50 and they must
now get follow through. If they fail to
get follow through now, they will get
caught. Why must they defend 50? Well,
there's a shelf there. It's point of
control. But I'm going to get rid of
this now from here as well. We don't
need that anymore. But there also where
the buyers got stuck. Remember here we
talked about where did the buyers get
stuck here? Their buyers got stuck. Look
at all this aggressive buying.
Aggressive buying. Aggressive buying.
Aggressive buying. Did price move
higher? No. So all the buyers in here
are currently caught. So we came up.
This gave them a chance to stop out
break even. Right. Sellers now need
continuation lower underneath this. If
they don't get that continuation, it
would be a pullback which fails to move
lower with sellers caught these lows.
You can see the sellers are caught right
now at 215. So sellers must get under
that otherwise this is your rotation
between here this 30 points acceptance
over this will be a potential squeeze
certainly over 65s.
Hopefully that makes sense. You can play
both sides of the tape today if you're
uh quick enough on the trigger.
Nice. Lots of you making some good money
already.
Trade rate seems okay now.
We trading at 30s.
19 18 17 16. See I keep getting gaps
though. There are gaps in my chart. Let
me try one more time on trade. I'm not
convinced guys.
Try one more time.
Still inside that lowex range. Orange.
Orange to orange.
Let's see if this opens up this time.
It's a good start.
Good start. Can it open the footprint?
There we go. Right. Give this a minute
or two just to see if it's able to stay
open.
So far looks good though.
disconnect sim then live work. Okay,
I'll try. It seems to be working now. I
just want to give it a minute or two to
make sure it's smooth.
It seems to be doing a bit better now.
All right, ES back inside previous days
high. Still no gap fill on ES.
Spy the same back inside previous days
high. It's got VWAP and New York open
above it. Q's the same. VIX just came up
to that pivot. 17's failed in front of
17 so far.
Big block there.
That's the long hair. Thanks. It's
actually short. I actually just had it
cut. It was very long.
Okay, so back to these 50s. And you
know, if sellers can't defend this,
remember sellers got caught from here.
16s.
Yeah, sellers are caught from 16s here.
And buyers are caught in here. This is
the rotation between these. and
acceptance might allow that squeeze,
especially if we get through this 63
shelf. And under here, this is the
target. Right now, there isn't anything
that I really uh want to take.
Market's asleep, isn't it? Market's
asleep. I tell you what, we give it
another eight more minutes and we'll do
a giveaway early today. But you guys
have got to get me to thousand of you
watching. Let's get to 700 likes and and
we'll do a giveaway. There's 481 likes.
Let's get another couple hundred in
there
and uh we'll do an Apex giveaway. Maybe
some other stuff.
Breezy. No, wasn't able to trade uh
today. Not even because of the range
because trade of eight and ninja trader
or trade of eight data has been down. It
looks like it's only just coming back
now. I know other people saying they're
still having problems with it. There you
go.
At the moment looks okay. I'm bit
dubious about taking a trade. I'll be
honest. Even if there was a setup.
Okay. Big buy has just come on the book.
All right. 800 lot down at 26,200.
26,200. So he's kind of said, "Hey, this
is where I want to absorb it." Let's see
if he's a spoofer. If we come down to
him, big coming back down into where we
broke out from
into these 50s again. That's a huge
buyer. 800 lot. That's some proper size
down at 200 right now. Huge buy down at
200. We will just have to see.
See what he's saying.
Back to value area low on the day.
No, I don't think trade's working. Still
still keeps pausing versus what I'm
seeing, guys. I'd be very careful.
Not worth it in my opinion.
It's a leave alone day I would say if
you're on trade of eight
silver at lows. Did it reject those tens
I talked about yesterday? Someone asked
about what the trade was yesterday for
it and I said the tens
it was tens.
Was it this move? Where are we? Was it
Monday?
Remember where we were?
Tuesday. Yeah, it was here. So, it was
this play yesterday was this fade back
down. We're building out a range though.
Like I said, a high time frame. Silver's
very bullish. All right. It can afford
to come all the way back down here and
be scooped back up. They can build
liquidity.
One, two, three, drop down, pick it back
up, have loads of shorts pile in all the
shorts here, build it back up, hold
this, and expand. They can [\h__\h]
easily do that if they want to. Would
not surprise me. It's just what gold did
a couple months ago. If we look at gold,
same kind of story.
Where's that blush on gold? Everyone
thought it was over. There you go. Build
out of liquidity,
flushed back down, held, and gone. And
it's done it a few times, right? We
build our bases that way. Here it was.
Looks very similar. Build out liquidity,
flush down, failure to break lower.
gone. If you compare that, it's very,
very, very, very possible they can do
something like that if they want.
Macro environment says we'll probably go
higher on silver. Just might need to
cool off for a minute.
Very possible.
Okay. Still think this wants to move
into that GlobeEx at the moment.
That 92 is still absolutely key.
He's a spoofer down there, by the way.
He spoofed that 800 lot. He's not legit.
first profitable day on my email because
of you. Learning more each day. Nice. Am
I from the UK or Australia? I'm from I'm
from the UK, mate.
Are you likely to trade follow uh
following FOMC today? Well, not if we've
got no data.
Probably not anyway. I'm probably more
interested to be honest, I'm not even
too worried about FOMC. The chances are
that, you know, 97% chance we're not
going to do a rate cut. What's going to
matter is the tone, right? Is he still
belligerent
or is he talking about more than two
cuts this year? If he talks about more
than two cuts this year, maybe the
market likes it because we need to get
moving. Um, what I'm more interested in
is the reaction to earnings. That's
actually what I'm more interested in
because I think we have positioned early
or early from last week into this week
for the MAG and you have uh Microsoft,
Meta, and Tesla earnings at the bell
today. So, three of the MAG 7 today and
then you have Apple tomorrow. So, I'm
interested in first of all what the
earnings look like. Um, then I'm
interested in in the forecasting, the
earnings calls, and then I'm interested
in what the reaction is to those. Um,
have we priced it in already, or is
there a bigger move coming for tech?
That's what I'm really interested in.
Once we get through, once we close this
week, I think we're going to have a
really good understanding of what, you
know, the next two, three months are
going to look like. It's a big, big week
right now.
Still think this is the target to the
92s. The rotation is still remember we
said that where did they say the trapped
16s still the same level right here. So
we just came right back into it. So you
can see this level right here where the
sellers got trapped. Rotation is from
here 250. I think if we come under here
the 92s is the big level. Right. So
we're still building out liquidity
between this.
Right. No acceptance above it. no
acceptance below it. But I still think
once if this snaps, this 92 is a massive
level.
Whereas if we zoom out, I've got rid of
the profile. But basically under here,
there is no volume. This was a straight
squeeze up. So there's no volume. This
was very, very thin.
Do I prefer Trading View or Ninja
Trader? I prefer executing on Ninja
Trader, but I prefer charting on Trading
View. It's much easier for me to teach
you guys on Trading View, that's for
sure.
Sorry, trying to catch up on uh all
these comments. Sorry, sorry, sorry.
what prop firm anyone recommends for
futures. I've got a video on that. Five
five top prop firms. All all depends
what your trading style is, but go and
check out my video on them. But they are
simply put um Apex, Funded Next, Take
Profit Trader, Traderify, Lucid. I
should say Funded Next just launched uh
Bolt today uh permanently and it looked
pretty good. Uh
need to uh do a post about that. Did
forget to tell you guys. I am sorry. Um
let me find it.
So
started today.
It's $99 for 50k. Profit target 3,000.
Um max loss limit 2,000. Daily loss
limit 1,000. Is end of day draw down.
You can use three minis or nine micros.
40% consistency only in the eval. no
consistency in the uh um funded stage of
it. You can trade news.
Um
you need $250 profit in in your current
cycle and your end of day balance must
reach 52,100 and then you can pay out
and you can withdraw profits above the
buffer.
Minimum payout 250, max 1,200 day daily.
So they're going to do daily payouts.
That's pretty good.
So they just launched that today. Looks
good. I will do a deep dive into that
later.
Okay. Still think they're trying to find
acceptance under here. So all we've got
is some sellers stuck in here. Once they
get through this, right, this is where
the sellers are stuck.
Do it as white. Once we get through
this, this 92s is the big level. I think
you should get it. You should get it.
There we come.
Looks good, folks. It looks good for it
in my opinion.
My humble opinion.
And they're adding liquidity down to 95s
now. We've got lots of guys to fill down
here. One big swipe will do it. One big
swipe will do it for you.
Wouldn't have minded being able to trade
some of this. There we go.
Here it comes. Here comes low date
and swipe down to 90s is looking very
probable through here. They're trying to
stack fires. I think you're going to get
this move to 92. I think you're going to
get it.
And then we just see if we find
acceptance under that or not. That's the
next thing.
Here we come. There's IB low. Can we get
acceptance under it for 92s? So if you
took the short any of these shorts TP
here, like just a partial here, but
you're looking for this, right? And
under there, if we find acceptance under
there, you can get a deeper move. But
it's very possible that they trap at
this level down here. So just be
careful.
Why is 192 such a big level? If you look
at GlobeEx, if you look at the volume
during GlobeEx,
that was basically the shelf. Um
yeah,
if we
look at GlobeEx
Tuesday,
Wednesday,
Tuesday
here
into 9:30 30.
Make sure that's not extended. Correct.
Okay. Right. You see this?
Sure. You guys can see this. Move this
down a bit.
Right. Look at this under here.
Think about this volume.
Right? Where do we keep finding bids?
Here. Look under here. Under this low.
There is nothing. Look how thin that is
down into this. All right. So you've got
this move from 148. You got 50 points
here with nothing in, right? We can if
we if we fade that, if they find
acceptance, we can do this. They can
also use it as a trap, which is why I
think 92s is a big level.
Here you come. You're coming for it now.
You're coming for it now. So another
trade setting up really nice. Here we
go, folks. Here we go. So here's
GlobeEx. So TP2 now hit.
And let's see if you find acceptance.
they can trap here, but if not, there is
a drift all the way down like we just
talked about. So, I'd be watching
there's a little bump in the road at
158. So, I'll be watching60,
140s, and then lower day uh lower day,
old day value. So, we can put some of
these in just so you can see them.
These would be my next levels. All
right. So, if we find acceptance,
remember, you should have taken decent
chunk off here. If we find acceptance,
we're looking for these gray levels
below
consistency is based on your profit,
right? It's based on profit. Sorry,
someone just asked that. What features
is this? NQ.
I don't know. No, I've not tried it tra
traded CFD props. So I couldn't tell you
why. Been short since 26 250 250. Yeah,
that's that was the level to short. That
was exactly it. So you should pay
yourself into here. That's a 60 point
trade in case they use this as the trap
level. Remember we've talked about this.
It can be the trap level. Once they come
under here, you're starting to find bids
like we talked about. Like I said, it
finds acceptance or they will use it for
the trap because they know under here is
very thin down to here. All right? So,
you must pay yourself into that because
you do not know if it collapses or does
this. So, if you've got this to here,
that is a good chance to pay yourself
some money and then hold runners.
I can't trade right now. No, sorry. Not
cuz I don't want to. I would have loved
to be in that. I can't get any data.
Trader down. Hey, how are you doing? Do
you need some design thumbnails? I'm
looking for work. I already have someone
that does mine for me. Thanks. Thanks,
bud.
Yes, actually JJ, that that happened to
me during my um unfortunately during
that time I my personal time I had off
um for unforeseen circumstances, I did
lose a few of those accounts. It's uh
it's a shame because they had built up
some nice money in them, but I had some
stuff happen which I wasn't ready for.
Thanks for doing this, Alex. Trading is
lonely sometimes and it's nice to have
someone to listen to. I agree. That's
why we do it. That's exactly why we do
it.
It's not a bad, it hasn't been a bad
session. If we draw out what we talked
about and the only trade that I've said
is valid today is this to here.
Right? That's your first trade. And if
the runner goes for you, you're looking
for this and this and maybe if you got
very lucky down to here. But you should
have taken TP into the orange line. So
now you can see why the 92s are
important. Why I kept saying 92s is a
big level. There you go. So testing edge
of value. Now do they reject this?
Remember 50s is still important. If we
come back to the 50s again, I'll be very
very careful because we've been there a
few times.
Where am I from? I'm originally from
London, but I live in Los Angeles
currently. Been here six years.
What made me say that today is sleepy
trading day? Meaning choppy or
relatively low volume? Did I say it's
sleepy? probably just because we weren't
moving.
It's more that the range uh if we think
about that opening range and we weren't
moving outside of it, right? How big is
that opening range? 81 points. Not very
big. Initial balance 81 points. That's
not very big, right? So sleepy because
they probably need to build liquidity
and everyone's waiting for later.
Everyone's waiting for later.
Traderate says, "I have an open trade
and I can't close it because data is
down." Cam, I would not worry. Honestly,
if you're with a prop firm and you're
having that, they will reset them all. I
would almost
I don't want to say guarantee it, but I
would be fairly sure anyone that had
issues during this time, they will have
stuff reset. Do not stress about it.
No, I don't think so, Evan. They don't
give a [\h__\h] about retail.
In fact, if anything, they want retail
because they can take positions against
them. That's definitely not what's
happened. What's the orange line?
GlobeEx,
Asia low,
Asia session low, and the edge of
volume.
I need to do a uh sheet here that tells
you everything. What's the volume
indicator? It's on the right hand side.
It's anchored volume to the New York
open anchored volume profile.
Is there a reason that moved to LA? Uh
yeah, I moved with my wife. She took a
job here
London and LA aren't getting overrun by
homeless or are
where I live it's not a problem but
certainly downtown it's pretty bad
as someone from Sweden. When's the news
coming out? I assume it's FMC. Yeah,
FMC. You get a 2:00 print and then 2:30
he'll start talking for an hour or an
hour and a half and then you've got
earnings. Remember you have mag seven
earnings into close. That's also a big
part to play in this.
I've tried it CB. It's It's not working.
It works and then it freezes for me.
I've tried. I've tried. Thank I
appreciate you looking out for me
though.
Mine keeps freezing. I don't know why
but maybe it keeps trying to reconnect.
which part of LA I'm imply Vista west
side
if we trade FOMC can we start a new
volume profile at that time you could
that's not a bad idea you could do it uh
what I'd be what I'd be more interested
in is use the current profile and I
would look at the uh anchored VWAPS. I
would use anchored VWAPs for FOMOC on
the print. Okay. So, still rejecting
this node here, which is a good sign for
you guys in short. So, failure to get
back up to the 50s. So, we're starting
to make lower highs. If we think about
this, we've broken down away from this
now. We've trapped buyers at 50s. We're
not letting those buyers out. We're
starting to see continuation. We're
starting to reject this now. This is now
another lower high. And 92s is coming.
And the big question is, can you get
down into any of these? These gray boxes
are some of your cover points. It looks
good. I will tell you now. It looks
good.
So, the next target would be Oh, don't
do that. Would be down here if you can
get it. So, you should have already hit
TP1. You don't want failed follow
through here. You want continuation
underneath.
Need to get under this guy here at 92.
You can see where he got stuck right at
92. Breakout seller. You get under that,
we've got room.
234 to 92s. I mean, you almost had it.
Sorry. I might be a bit late on chat
here trying to catch up. It looks good,
right? So, the next target I'd be
looking for 60s and then I'd be looking
for 40s and then I'd be looking for
26,120s.
Basically, you do not want to fake out
on a reclaim. I'll tell you that much.
You do not want this. If this comes back
in value, do not touch it short. If you
trade back inside here, you're done,
right? Don't let them trap you. You're
short from here. Maybe some of you got
short on this flow zone here against
this node, your TP1. You're looking for
that. Do not let it reclaim this top of
gray box. Okay? Do not let it reclaim
that. All the time you're in this and
it's holding you. Look good for that
next target.
You can really think about an IB day. Do
we get IB expansion or an IB rotation?
Yes, Asia low. Sorry, Josh. Sorry, Josh.
Sorry, guys. I'm trying to catch up with
all of these comments.
You called that 92 level. Nice. Yes.
Well, you can see it's uh market is
respecting stuff recently very well.
What does your wife do you for? Do me
for? I don't
know what you're asking there. I have a
wife.
Some amazing comments in here.
Uh, have a business. Yeah, flow zone.
Weather weather definitely played a
factor into it into the mood. Yeah.
Before I started trading, what did I do
for work?
Uh, believe it or not, I was I was kind
of a big deal.
I was a a DJ and music producer. Had a a
very a very good career. Very fun.
Actually spent LA last week or early
this week looking back at it 10 years
ago. VIX really starting to get going
now. 1680 breakout coming up on VIX. ES
coming for this gap fill. SPY coming for
the gap fill. So you're watching SPY
into 95. ES is almost there. It's about
to fill its gap. So you'd be watching
the cash gap 708 on ES if you're playing
that. That is a cover point for you if
you are short on ES. If you're looking
for continuation on spy, you're looking
for 9550s and the Q's got a long way to
to go to play the to play catch up. But
you look good so far.
What's my strategy in simple terms? Make
money. I'm joking. uh is to is to try
and play the protrend where possible.
Try and play the higher time frame
protrend where possible.
Alex, would you be able to help me out
on an issue? Dashboard on top step shows
52,000, but my balance on my main screen
says 53,000. Would this be an issue? I
would I would assume I don't know why
that's happened. Yeah, I would get in
touch with to get in touch with Topstep.
Couldn't tell you why that's happened. D
get in touch with their support team and
hopefully they actually answer to you
because I know they haven't been too
good recently.
Am I a [\h__\h] or am I a blood? What are
these comments, guys?
Uh she's a yoga teacher. Breezy,
what was my DJ name? It was Tough Love.
And then I had a solo project which I
still do now called Alien. Tough Love
was my big my big project. Had a couple
big hits back in the day.
video dock on my life as a DJ.
I don't think you want to see images or
videos of me. There's a messy DJ
traveling the world. Here we go, folks.
So, you're looking for this breakdown to
160 is your next TP. Then you're looking
for 140s. Then all the way down here. ES
has almost filled that gap. It's just a
couple ticks short on that last push. It
came to 709s.
70950. It needs to trade 70850. So, it's
one tick short. Uh, sorry, four tick
short, one point short. Here we go,
folks. You're almost there.
Congratulations. Any of those of you who
have been able to trade this nice trade
from these 50s down. So, you're going to
get almost 100 points here. Again, this
is another day where I've given you 100
point plus trade and you can hold
runners. You might well come into this.
It's very possible. This is the higher
time frame pullback. And then down here,
we might see some absorption.
Do I still make music? I do.
The music business was so good to me.
Why did I leave it? Um, that's quite a
personal question.
I feel like I actually have to answer
that.
Was very good to me. If you don't
believe me, you can go and look at the
billions of streams that I have and
artists that I remix. There's more to
life than just money. It can also come
down to lots of personal stuff.
You know, tough love. What? Yeah, then
you know me.
What's the name of the cell indicator I
have? Do you mean these these waves?
These are my flow zones. It's my system.
You can get it with the course, version
of it with the course, and you can
upgrade to this pro version on the
website as well. All the links are down
below, guys.
Do I like House and EDM? I don't love
EDM, but House yet.
MG Miles, I'm stuck in a short and I
still can't close. Well, let's just hope
it keeps fading for you all the way down
here and then it lets you close out down
down there.
What is my entry method? And what do you
mean? I look for trap players. We've
gone over this quite a few times today.
Right. So the short today, why was it
50s? We kept calling it a 50s. When we
were here, I said if we leave 50s and
hold against 50s, it's a short, right?
Because of the trapped players up here.
We've gone over this quite a few times
here and here and all we are doing is
rejecting the trap buyers right now.
Maybe you've joined a bit later which is
fine. Yeah, we have gone gone over this
a few times today.
Do I still tour? No, that's the main
reason I I quit. I didn't want to tour
anymore. I was done. I spent 10 years
touring the world. I was I was done. I
took every drug there is to take. I
parted in every city there is to party.
I had a lot of fun. I was done. I didn't
want to get on another flight. I
couldn't bear the thought of getting on
another flight and another hotel and
driving countless hours. It was enough.
I had a good career. Enjoyed it.
Did Tyson change his name? Yeah. Uh
well, he didn't change it. It's just
that it it's changed. What's his name
now on here? I can't remember what it
shows up as, but it's not Tyson.
This 92 is still key. Remember, if we go
back inside 92s, I'd be somewhat
concerned, but it's still rejecting it.
You can see they're using this as a
rejection point now and they're trying
to trade into this, this, this, and
ultimately this.
ES now has filled its gap, folks. So ES
has now filled its gap. Cash gap on ES
has been filled. It's not quite been
filled on uh SPY yet. It's very, very
close. So if you're trading the ETFs
today, you're looking for a fill of 9550
on SPY. Be taking a little profit there
on your short if you're trading the ETS
today into 9550s like we talked about.
Looks good. So failure of previous day
high all the way down towards 9550.
You're a dollar in the money. If you're
in options, you should be making good
money right now.
Alex, how often you meet on Discord for
trading? Well, I've said I want to do
one this week. Every two weeks I want to
do like privates with people on Discord.
Did I play any big festivals? I did.
Yes,
a lot. A lot of big festivals.
Favorite city? Um,
I don't know what to travel or to DJ in
or to live in.
What time frame do I use? This is a one
minute you're looking at currently.
That's it. There you go.
Darth Darth Nugette. That's Tyson. That
one there. All right. So, ES finding a
little bit of a bid off that gap fill.
Still not inside its initial balance. So
all the time we're outside of IB on ES
maybe we have some more downside. VIX
did just spike up through that 1683.
Hasn't found a bid through it yet. So it
might pull back down to the 1670s here.
You you can just keep holding this as as
long as you're taking your profit.
Remember your TPS have hit TP1 here,
right? TP1, TP2. And you can look for
this on your runner and then all the way
down here if you get very very very
lucky. I'll give you a readout on the
Mac because they are all starting to go
red. All right, so the stronger one
today is Nvidia 1.34% up, Tesla half%
up, everything else red. Microsoft
quart% down. Meta quart% down. Google
quarter% down. Amazon half% down. Apple
0.90% down.
So, some profit taking for you guys
here.
Did I ever go to a club in Sheffield
called Gate Crasher? I did. I went to
that club. I didn't play that club. I
used to play tank in Sheffield a lot
with Jamie Dugen and those boys. And I
also used to play what was the [\h__\h]
massive warehouse they used to have over
there? Used to do like Halloween
festivals there. Huge. I used to like
playing Sheffield. I used to stay in the
hotel in the uh uh football ground.
Yes, trade's down, guys. Trade's down.
Everyone joining late. Trader is down.
still listen to Radio One. I love Jack
Saunders. That's how touch I I am. I
don't know who Jack Saunders is, but uh
still friends with a lot of the Radio
One guys, Danny and Target and all that
lot.
How do I know 60s and 40s are the next
support zone? Just based on volume, by
the way, I don't know, right? I don't
know. But based on volume, these are
target areas, right? Based on overnight
volume. So based on overnight,
um here we can see these nodes,
right? You see these nodes
here and here, right? And once we get
through that, this is current value area
high for the developing week. Okay. And
then we have previous day value value
area high and point of control down
here. Right? So this would be a really
good level to trade in. I would be
interested in buying this market
somewhere in here. Right? I don't know
if we continue to all-time highs at that
point, but this if we come down into
this, like I've talked about, if we come
down into this, if they fade this into
FOMC and they do some nonsense like
this, right, this is a great buying
opportunity to trade back up.
Maybe they set that up for tomorrow.
Maybe they set up for next week. I don't
know.
But we talked about that premarket. All
right, this was planned out premarket.
We talked about maybe having a fade down
into here today and maybe scooping it
long. Obviously not been able to do
anything, but there we go.
How are we doing for the likes? We're
still short on the likes. We need to get
those likes up. I really want to do a
giveaway in the next 5 minutes.
Definitely not from Turkey. I am part
Lebanese though, so that's probably why
he's saying that.
I don't trade Bitcoin. I don't trade
Bitcoin. I will I will pick up IBIT.
Like I said yesterday, when I bit comes
into good levels at ETF, I'll pick it
up. Is liquid enough to trade
the museum one in Sheffield? No, it's a
bit further out. It's like a huge
warehouse. Um, it's like a very
industrial space with a big car park.
They do like Jamie runs the the raves
there. I assume he still does them all.
Let me have a look.
I can't My brain's so bad now that I
can't remember stuff like that. Jamie
Dugen still Facebook, I'm sure. Yes, I
have.
Wired. No, that's his event company,
isn't it? Basefest. Was it that Magna?
That's what the venue is called. Magna.
Taking me back, mate. It's a long time
ago. Do I know Craig David? I I actually
do. Yeah. And I've remixed Craig David.
I've done I've worked with Craig David a
few times
and I know the original Artful Dodger. I
know all that crew guys. I was I did it
for a long time. Long long time.
And Ez
Matt Jam Lemon I'm good friends with.
Jordan saying Trader Vape just blew two
of your accounts. If they're simfunded
like accounts do not stress about it.
I'm sure they will correct everything
end of day. Do not. It's not even worth
stressing about, honestly.
What time do I trade from 9:15? We do
pre-market 9:15 Eastern time into 9:30.
Then we trade all the way until lunch.
We got another hour left together.
Every day, Monday to Friday. The niche
crew. Yes, OJ knows. Yeah, that's it.
That's literally it. All that those base
base boy crews
warehouse project. Yeah, I played uh
warehouse project maybe four four or
five times normally on New Year's Eve.
Normally did main room New Year's Eve.
Actually post I posted it up the other
day.
Um that day I actually did we did f four
or five shows five shows on New Year's
Eve
and I had to get from Tank in Sheffield
to Warehouse Project in Manchester in
like 40 minutes and we flew. We
absolutely flew at a driver
foot down mate. It was good fun. Just
about made it on that set. Can't
remember who else was there that night.
Danny and Hannah. I think
you're making me go way back in my
brain, guys. It's crazy. Let me see if I
can find it. Might have it here
somewhere.
There. That was it. That was the view
from my booth for warehouse project. I
don't know if you guys can see that.
Long time ago.
See that?
Long long time ago.
That was a midnight set. Good set.
Enjoyed that. Good fun.
No, I don't know. NRA, I don't know.
Like, I'm so out I'm so out the loop,
guys, with all that stuff. Right. Look
at that. There's your TP. So, the next
TP's just been hit. Gray box.
Congratulations. anyone who's in this.
So, you're now looking for the next TP.
So, you're looking for a continuation
now down to 140s. It's working out very,
very nice.
What does it actually mean to remix an
artist? So what happens is is all sales
uh and all all streams get can go
towards uh the the single. So let's say
let's say
I don't know Ed Sheeran's got a song
coming out in like a month, right? So
what he'll want is that song to be
played in on as many radio shows and as
many clubs and as many festivals as
possible. if his song, he's a very big
artist, so he won't not necessarily
always do this, but if that song has an
appeal of like it's it's a slow jam or
something and they want it in a club and
they're gonna want a club DJ or a club
producer to do a remix prevalent in the
club scene and then everyone starts
playing that in the club scene and then
they want like a drum and bass mix and
they want this and this and this and
this. So I was very fortunate. I was
quite prolific. So I pretty much remixed
well a lot of people a lot of big guys.
Everyone from like Jiraquay to
just like like everyone literally
everyone spent like a lot of my time
doing it. It was good fun. Jess Glenn
trying to think of the big ones we had
which were hits. Megan Trainer,
um, Chasing Status,
uh,
Sigma,
what else did we do? We did some like
legendary old stuff as well.
Clean Bandit.
Cracking my head.
Long time ago. Anyway, reason we're
talking about this is we're we're in
this short. Well, you guys should be in
this short and you're just holding now
the runner to see if we can get
acceptance. All right, we're through.
We've hit TP1, TP2, TP3 is this gray box
and then all the way down here if we get
lucky.
Did I ever find some of the music party
scenes soulless? I've been to IBA a
bunch of times and some people were so
fake or a lot of people were very fake.
It got worse and worse and worse. I'd
imagine it's pretty poor now. I went
back to IA this year. I actually quite
enjoyed it. Um, but I mean I had a
residency there every year for 10 years
and I would say it definitely got worse
and worse and worse. The early days were
really good. I've been going there since
I was 13. I was quite genuinely going
out clubbing at 13 in IA to club called
Elderino which is not there anymore.
And Pasha Paka,
how does one start attempting to make
beats or house music? Uh, or if you want
to make it, you you're going to have to
choose if you're on Mac, just get Logic.
Lots of people now just use Ableton.
They find it easier. I'm a Logic guy.
That's what I use. Find a tutorial
online and just start slow. Start with
probably sample packs and one VST and
then just start slow.
What was your music promo? I've been
lucky enough to work with some of the
best artists all over the world for
music promo. What was your promo
company?
Yeah, there you go. I knew people would
take care of your losses. Favorite city
to party in or to party in? Um,
God, that's hard. It probably is. I beat
it to be honest. I have some amazing
memories there.
Berlin as well. Right up there.
No, it didn't work with Prodigy. Would
have loved to. I They They never did
official remixes, I don't think. Shame
about Keith. Would have loved to before
he passed.
No way. You made so so freaking tight. I
did. I did make so freaking tight. Yes.
Taking you back there, eh?
Could one suggest a level to get short
in this or is it too late? I'd be
somewhat careful now because you're
coming down to target. So, you would
need to see a rejection here, right? IB
and here, but I'd be I'd be somewhat
careful. um you'd need a push into here
that is significant bias trap to know
that we're coming lower. I would be
somewhat careful. The reason I'm saying
that is if you look at the divergence to
ES. All right, ES has already done the
move we would look for for the gap fill.
All right, so if we think about this,
here's your gap fill. All right, so ES
has just filled the gap. It's trading
back at IB. All right, if ES starts
putting in higher lows here and
reclaiming IB, then it's going to go
back up here and that's going to be a
problem. and it's going to drag and
queue. I would assume SPY's now filled
its gap. Well, it's a a tick or two
short. So, SPY, the cash ETF, got very
close to gap fill as well, right?
Whereas the Q's, we're lagging behind.
So, we've got relative strength in the
Q's because Gapill's way down here.
I would be skeptical about an ad on the
short now.
Not the safest bet. It would be more
about holding it unless you see a spike
up, you know, unless you see a push up
here
and we see You know, let's say these
these imbalances filled in.
Jesus Christ. These imbalances filled
in. We see trapped buyers. Then maybe
you could think about it. But I'd be
somewhat skeptical about trying to get
an ad this late in the day.
Genuine. Yeah, I work with Genuine. Good
old Elgen. I've got his still talk to
him. He's a good dude. Shot music video
with him with him here in LA in 2015,
I think. 2015. Yeah, 2015.
Who's the best DJ in your opinion? Like
personal favorite? Um,
so hard, man. That is so hard. Uh,
Roger Sanchez was like how I fell in
love with house music and he became one
of my mentors. So for him, for me, he's
right up there watching this now guys to
see if you see a spike in buyers
trapped. ES starting to reclaim initial
balance. So you will need to see buyers
get trapped here. If they do not get
trapped here, it means we're going to go
right back inside and trade back up to
these levels up here. So you want to be
very careful. Um EZ, of course,
there's t like there's so many all the
older guys, the legends. I I don't like
it now how people mix between songs in
like 30 seconds. I hate all that [\h__\h]
In your humble opinion, the reason price
is falling is because ES hit a major
resistance level and NQ following ES. Am
I correct? You are not correct. You're
not correct. It might be why ES is
falling. ENQ is falling because we're
trading into thin volume. So, it's not
about necessarily a major resistance
level, although we did hit major
resistance. It's more about this, right?
We've got supply and we've got buyers
stuck. So, we fall all the time. Buyers
remain stuck. All right. It's just a
pullback. It is a pullback leg until
proves otherwise. We've gone over this
so many times. Here's the trend. Here's
the pullback. It might very well
continue higher.
ES does not and ENQ does not follow ES
and vice versa. They are different. All
right? It depends what the stocks within
each index are doing.
Uh, chasing status. Yeah, they are
legends.
20 years, man. This guy's doing it. I
mean, I'm 40, right? I was going I was
going to watch Roger when I was 13, and
he would have been going even longer
than that. So, he's been going 30 plus
years. All those guys like Todd, Roger,
um,
uh, Louis Vega, it's incredible. Tongy
That's awesome. Um,
that's awesome. Three music channels
that over 800 million command views.
That's awesome.
What was the channel called though? I
might have missed it. I want to know if
I know the channel.
Unless your name's Nick, you're not
selected. So,
I wonder who you are.
Short flight to Vegas. Yeah. Is it short
flight to Vegas? I go I still go to see
guys quite a lot. Still remember Sister
Bliss playing my record. What a feeling.
Yeah. Legend. Same for me, mate.
Same for me.
Shame about Maxi a few years ago. Love
Parade. End of 90s. Yeah. June.
What gap do I speak of? Previous day
high. No, previous day close. Cash gap.
Four o'clock close. So, I always trade
cash gaps. I'm always interested in cash
gaps because cash is where most of the
money is traded, right? So, 4:00 cash
gap is here. But again, we've closed it
on ES. We have relative strength. We're
holding up. Okay. It doesn't have to
come down here. Remember this right
underneath this. This was a high volume
node here. This can be still be a failed
auction and a reclaim and a trade
upside. It doesn't have to come down
here. It'd be preferable if it does
because it offers a better bid up, but
it doesn't have to do it.
Where do I want to go long? For me, I
want to go long down here. That's where
I want to go long. I'm There's not going
to be a trade setting up today. It's
going to have Well, there might be this
afternoon. Like, let's move you to high
time frame quickly. Right. This is these
are the areas. Look at these nodes. this
back to fair value back to here.
Somewhere in here would be lovely. It
might be that it holds it and reclaims
which is fine. If it does that, we can
join later on. We can join on this dip
here once it's proven itself. But if we
can come down here and trap into here,
great. We can get long here. We can add
on here and we can get that continuation
trade. If we let go of this, all right,
and we stay heavy, then we will be short
for that rotation down into this load
here over the next few days. So, we're
setting up well. Look, we're extended
up. We would expect a bounce at some
point, but ideally we find that first
bounce from here. And if they're too
trapped here, then we're going to a
range here for a bit. And then we look
for acceptance above or below when we
get there. But we got to let it build
out for a little bit. So this is why I
say I wouldn't be short down here.
And as you come upside now, back to
these key levels.
Back to these key levels. All right,
let's do a giveaway. We're almost there.
I would love it if you guys would just
smash that like button a bit more, but
let's do a giveaway. We'll do a uh one
now. Maybe one later as well towards the
end of the stream.
Artist name tough love. What's tough
love?
Going to see Coxy in Brussels. Nice,
nice, nice, nice. Yeah, I am 40. Yeah,
I'm 40.
Are we still waiting for a long? I mean,
auction here is not too bad. If you
like, it's just a bit awkward the way
it's setting up better on ES. It's still
a short because you're still under IB.
But if you start to build out liquidity
here and keep trapping shorts down here,
then this can be a relief long. I would
much prefer, like I've talked about, I'd
be very careful about trading for FOMC.
I'd much prefer the longs down here,
guys. Right. This is a much better node
to be trading off, but technically if it
reclaims this, there can be relief, but
much better down here if possible. Much
much better.
Okay. I haven't even done it yet. Well,
everyone was getting ready for the uh
didn't even get a chance to put it in.
We'll do the course giveaway first,
guys, because otherwise none of you will
get uh
get entered now.
What's just gone on here?
Let me set it up.
There we go. So, just type course once
in chat. We do the course first only
because you already did FCT before I got
to set it up. So, it's just a bit it's
the introduction course. It's not the
main course. Just type it once in chat.
We we do Apex afterwards because I want
you guys to actually be entered.
Give you guys a minute. Right.
While you do that, I'm going to get a
cup of tea and I'll come right back. All
right.
Okay,
I'm going to pull this winner for the
course. It's just the introduction
course, two hours long.
Don't worry, spammers have all been
pulled out. Winner in five, four, three,
two, and one.
All right, ZM Solutions
or Ze Solutions,
let me know you're here. Zes,
yes. Nice. Okay, Zams, I'm going to make
a note of you. It's a very beginner
friendly course. So, if you already know
what you're doing, you might want to
give it as a gift to a friend or
someone, but it's totally up to you.
Making a note of your name. All you have
to do, email me
info@flowzonerader.com.
Send me a screenshot of you logged in,
please, and uh I will sort you out with
the course.
I'll sort you out of the course.
When I buy Apex accounts, do I need
Ninja Trader or another app to trade?
No, you can trade on Trader 8. Lots of
different ways to do it. Is it back up
and running?
Let me see if we got data 14. Yeah, it
is matching. Okay, that's a good start.
It's a good start.
All right, I want 40 more likes and
we're going to do an Apex giveaway.
40 more likes. We do an Apex giveaway.
It's great. It's back up and running.
Thanks for letting me know everyone.
Appreciate it.
I don't think it's that bad. Like,
what did this offer? How many points was
this?
It's 75 point trade. It's not that bad.
It's slow, but it's at least being
respectful. And it might be, you know,
if we hit final target down here, it
will be a 150 plus point trade if any of
you were able to get that. It is a
pretty good trade.
Big if, but if it does, that's what you
will get.
It still won't let me place or close an
an order, but the information is
correct. Well, there you go. So, still
problems. Thanks. Let me know.
How can we enter the giveaway? I'll tell
you what to do as soon as we get 12 more
likes.
Yeah, I think the best options were
probably on the spy, man. You took that
morning morning uh push which got stuck
into the pre-market level. If you look
at that like shelf on pre-market on spy
at like 98 97 98s
and then we let go previous day high at
9650s and you basically about to close
the gap again at 9550.
So you you could have got one to $2
there on spy which I don't know what the
uh premiums were like this morning but
no the course is like only a twohour
long course. It's a very beginner
friendly course. But I'll tell you what,
if you win the course and you do the
course, you do actually get like a $100
off or something something like that off
the main one. But Discord is for the
20our course. I don't give that away for
free. I give enough here for free as it
is. Even when I'm not able to trade, I'm
I'm I've been able to give you this even
today when I'm not able to trade.
I'm coming from top step to Apex. Which
charting plan should I use? Wealth chart
versus rhythmic trade of eight. I'd go
with trade of eight. Go with trade of
eight because then if you trade on Mac,
you can trade on web platform. If you
like using Ninja or something else, you
can do that as well. I would go with
trade of eight. If you trade on mobile,
you also have that.
Alex, could I ask you a complicated
question or should I wait after the
market close? Ask away. I'll do my best.
Yeah, info Z info@flowzonerader.com.
info@flowzontenttrader.com.
You re-entered sell at 192. It's a good
level. Still rejecting it. It's the same
level, right? It's the same level we
called talked about earlier. There was
no reclaim of it.
Didn't get a chance to look in here. Not
too many bars caught. There was on this
wick though, 88 to 95. That was a good
wick. Okay, so into this next level.
They must get through this now. Sellers
will want to get through this now and
then trade to 140s. All right, so
sellers are in total control. So your
next TP will be down here if possible.
So you're just managing this trade. No
long trigger until you reclaim all of
this.
Do I use rhythmic account has more or
less issues in trade of eight? I haven't
had an issue with trade of eight for as
long as I can remember. This is the
first one today, but it's obviously some
global outage.
What do I see the market doing for the
rest of the day if you haven't recapped
already? Well, ideally, my friend,
ideally, we are going to see the market
coming to somewhere around here.
And what I would ideally like to see is
in here
sellers get trapped. All right, that's
what I'd ideally like to see something
like this in here. And I want them to
use FOMC
as a way of like trapping them and then
rip it back up. That's the ideal world.
If we don't do that and buyers try and
come in and they get caught and we
reject it, then we can play that
rotation back down into here.
Ideally, we want to play upside where
possible. But if it needs a deeper
rotation, right, if it wants to let go
of uh you know these 100s and 26,000,
then it is welcome to come to 900. We
cannot rule it out back down to 900. It
will still be a breakout pullback, but
it would be much stronger if we can just
fade into here, trap sellers, and then
bid back up. That would be the best
possible scenario in my opinion.
Say theoretically you were trading with
funded accounts and counter counter
traded so got banned
and other prop firms required the
standard million 56 day evaluation if
there was cash pool.
Did I miss the first part of the
question? Sorry mate. Let say
theoretically you were trading with
funded accounts and counter traded. So
traded like instruments against each
other and got banned and all other prop
firms required the standard minimum 5 to
six day evaluation phase if there was a
crash
bull run and you didn't have time to go
through the week long eval phase. How
would you go about theoretically using
your own 10k to bypass the prop pending?
I'm not really sure what you're asking
there mate.
Are you asking how I trade 10k cash or
or what what are you what are you
actually asking?
Thank you. Hit my target for the week.
Nice.
Any trade available? I mean the one the
one you're in now. That's it. That's it.
Until until you see a pivot now, I
wouldn't be entering short. Right. The
the move's happening. You're managing
this position and you got half an hour
left for lunch. VIX wants to break 17.
It does. 1698 came right up there. Uh
next next point is 1712s. Right. So if
it gets through here, 1712 starting to
hold those 1680s very very very well.
Reversal at 26k there or thereabouts.
We'd actually prefer it above there.
Somewhere in here. 26100.
Somewhere in here would be more ideal.
Somewhere in here. Gap fill is here.
Previous day value lows there. But
somewhere in here would be ideal. If we
get stuck here, I'd be very worried
about that.
What's the yellow line number? 26080.
This one here. 2673ish
26073 that's the cash gap
es by the way uh sorry ES spy actually
just finally filled its gaps remember it
came very very close a few times it just
filled its cash gap the yellow line
right all right so spy now has done its
move it's now closed its cash gap which
is great so the only thing left for spy
really is if it wants to stay weak in
the cash market right it's going to have
to let go of these afterhour lows and
these pivots here I'd imagine 95 is a
big level just based on gamma. I would
assume they're all pinned at 95 right
now. 95s and probably 92s again.
Who is this guy who keeps spamming about
Binance? You are getting banned, mate.
Get out of it. Report.
Bye.
I only know how to trade by buying 100k
accounts. How would you use your own 10k
and not buy accounts through prop? Oh, I
see what you're saying. Just write size
right down, mate. Be realistic. 10k. I
wouldn't even be using minis micros.
and just build it, build it, build it,
build it, build it. It's all you need to
do.
It's honestly all you need to do.
If you if you used a 10K account, right,
and you use micros, let's just say you
use one micro and you hit $100 a day,
after one month, you'd be at
$2,000. That's a 20% gain on your
account,
right? Right? Cuz you only got 10k in
there. It's a lot of money. Need to
understand that. I wouldn't be going
full send. Bill build bill have you got
to earn the right to go full send.
I do not recommend a sell right now. No.
Okay. Let's do this.
Okay everyone. Apex currently 90% on
sale. The code to use is FZ FZT to get
you 90% off. But if you want to win a
free account, just type FZT in chat
right now and we'll pick a winner at
random. Just type it once. Please don't
spam. Just once
Oh, sorry. Who's this Hunter? I've just
seen your email to spam. So annoying.
Keeps doing that. Reply to here.
There's
another minute or so to do that.
right? Starting to see that relief. So,
yellow line still key level. ES starting
to reclaim. I'd be out of all the shorts
now as well. We start to reclaim it's up
here as squeeze potential. So definitely
no ads if you get very very lucky, but I
would not be uh adding up here now.
We're starting to build out more volume
here over and over and over again. And
ES is starting to reclaim, so I'd be
somewhat careful if ES starts to bid
back in front of IB. We see it's
starting to get like volatility starting
to move through here a little bit.
Right, let's pull this winner. Make sure
you guys are all happy.
Linda Brown.
Linda Brown, are you here? Linda Brown.
Are you here? Linda Brown still
rejecting this. Wow, it's impressive.
Maybe you get very lucky. Those of you
in from the 50s,
you need to see follow through. There
you go, Linda. Okay, same story. I've
made a note of your name. If you can
send me an email, please.
info@flowzontrader.com.
Send me a screenshot of you logged in so
I know it's you. And uh free Apex
account on its way to you.
So, next targets for those of you
holding from these 50s will be down here
into 138s and then all the way down into
here. If you get very very very lucky.
Did I just delete that? Need to delete
that. Where's it gone? Hello. There you
are. Right. This is your next target.
The 40s and then the teens. And then all
the way down in here if you get lucky.
Just manage your position. I wouldn't be
adding on anymore.
You're getting closer and closer.
What are the indicators? Uh these are my
flow zone pros.
Pretty much all one indicator that and V
news. Um I'll see I I never really like
trading uh FOMC. I like the next day the
reaction afterwards better.
I still don't understand what you're
saying, Matthew, but I'm asking like if
you only knew how to trade via prop firm
accounts and you got banned from one and
a massive movement was happening and you
didn't have time to do the 5D eval, what
do you do? I don't understand that
question. What is your question there?
What's the actual question there? It's
like cryptic.
What are you asking? So, if I got banned
from a prop firm, okay, and there was a
massive movement happening, as in
there's volatility, which happens all
the time, and you didn't have time to do
a 5day eval. So, what you're saying is,
how can I gamble big on volatility by
using 10K? That's what you're actually
saying, right? And I told you, trade
micros. trade micros and earn the right
to trade more than one or two micros.
Do I use TPO Rick? Yeah, I do look at it
occasionally. Um, most of the time I
don't feel like I I need to look at it.
I can kind of see from my eyes how long
we've spent somewhere, but I do I do
have it on my charts when I need it.
I would never advise buying a CFD
account ever.
What's the equivalent ticker to SPX to
MNQ?
I have MEES1, but the candle volume
footprint bars are super thick compared
to MNQ1. If you're looking at volume,
you just want to look at ES, right?
Don't look at me. Just look at ES. If
you're looking at volume, trade mees,
but use the levels of ES because you
want institutional volume.
Previous day value area low, previous
day point of control is better for a
swing long. Yeah, that's what I'm
looking at like because if we come into
here, right, and hold,
right? Now, if we come into here and we
hold somewhere in here, right, even
here, and we trap and do this, the long,
the protrend long is all the way up and
we're expecting a breakout of the high.
But at the very minimum, right, even if
we don't get that, we're probably going
to get this trade up into here, right?
So, it will offer profit no matter what.
We were probably looking at 100 to 200
points no matter what. And if you get
lucky, then they'll let it rip.
But we just have to be careful based on
the dailies. Do not forget the dailies.
I keep going over this. At the beginning
of the show, we talked about the
Ballinger bands, like where we are on
the dailies right now. All right, look
at this long wick above the daily
Ballinger band. Surprise, surprise. Who
said that? It's very unlikely we're
going to get above that, right? The
statistical chances of getting above
these is small. Tomorrow and the next
day, once we have this this doing this,
sure, we would like a pullback into
this, right, to be absorbed to then go
long. Maybe it has to come down into
here. Like I said, it's possible it
comes for the 900 check. It is possible.
We cannot rule that out. It is possible
we do something like this. It is also
possible. We cannot rule this out that
it does that. All right. If this is all
[\h__\h] and this is a giant stop hunt
and you have institutional selling,
right? Institutional selling into this.
This is possible. When will we know? I
would say after earnings Thursday,
Friday. I don't think that's what's
going to happen. I think the reason
we've rotated
back into tech
is to position themselves after a long
period of consolidation. We talked about
this long period of consolidation. If we
hold either 26,100 or 25,900,
if we hold it, we have every single
player for three months trapped. We have
an upside squeeze possible. All right,
that is the most probable thing to
happen. The second thing to happen will
be a failure and a collapse and they use
this for institutional selling. All
right? Because if lots of people are
bidding up and they can sell, they pair
it off and sell against it. This is
still untested. Is possible. It's less
likely in my opinion, but it's possible.
Cam, thank you for that. Very kind of
you.
How can I connect trade of eight to an
Apex account? It it will literally show
you how to do it. Go on to the Apex
website and just walk through it or just
go on YouTube. There'll be lots of ways
of showing you how to do it. It's very
very easy.
Linda info@flowzontenttrader.com
info@flowzonetrader.com
any trade available bro you can tell who
like comes in here and then leaves and
then comes back in leaves the short that
we're in is the only trade right now
right
you can argue that we're rejecting this
I do not like the add-on short right now
I will be honest I think it's very very
risky as you're getting closer remember
the short was from 250s right each of
these gray boxes has been a cover point.
We can use this as like I'm not even
going to do it as red. It's too risky.
Right. So, you've hit TP1,
TP2, TP3, as long as you weren't a dick
for a tick. TP4 will be down here into
the 120s. TP5 will be down here into the
90s. All right, that that will be the
trade. So, the next TP will be here, and
the next TP after that will be here.
Matthew, like your question still
doesn't really make sense, mate. If
you're going to use 10K of your own
personal money, obviously nothing
changes, right? You trade the same way.
You trade technical setups the same way.
You just lower your size because your
risk is 10K. I would be using one to two
micros if I had a 10k account and I'd be
trying to build out let's say at 20% a
month. You need to go slow, right? You
build 10k to 12k during that first
month. Prove yourself you can do it.
Then you can start slowly slowly slowly
doing more. If you're experienced trader
and you want to put risk on, [\h__\h]
sure, put risk on, right? But if you put
a mini on and you are wrong by the point
of 100 points, you've lost 20% of your
account instantly. So that's it. Nothing
really changes.
Correct. Correct. Yeah. Microsoft,
Tesla, and Meta earnings today and then
you got Apple tomorrow. Correct.
Oh my god, Alex is the best of the best.
That's very kind of you. Thank you.
What's the obsession with high candles?
Candles. See a lot of people in my other
discords using it. I don't know.
I can actually just momentum candles.
That's all they are. They they should
make you able to see trend better, but
they don't print the actual price. All
right. So, if we we move to a highashi,
all right, trend becomes easier to see.
All right.
But they won't show they won't always
give you the actual price. All right,
the way they deliver price is slightly
different. All right, so the wicks on
them will be slightly different. The way
it's calculated, but it can become
easier to see trend using hyenashes.
Maybe that's why people who trade trend
with uh EMAs often like hyenashes.
They're not they're not for me. I have
tried using them before many many many
years ago.
Okay, so gray box to gray box. you might
get down into here and hopefully you get
that flush all the way down.
I mean, it's a simple question. Yeah,
just trade normally with 10K. Just size
down. There's there's the simple answer
which I've said many many times. Nothing
else changes.
Thanks, Nick Bob.
You're answering you're answering your
same question. 10K was an example of
like how I've learned everything I need
to via safe proper. I still can't
understand what you're saying here. Most
you loses 100k a time. How do I bypass
all the rules and stuff and just use my
own? That's how you bypass the rules,
right? You open up a brokerage account.
You put 10K in. There you go. You bypass
the rules. Now you play to your own rule
book. But you better be good at managing
risk. No zero DTE for me. No.
So many questions trying to catch up
with here.
Yes. Uh, I would always watch like any
So, anytime you're looking at Here you
go, guys. You're going to get it.
Anytime you're looking at anything
volume based, guys, anything volume
based, look at the main contract. Look
at the ENQ. Look at the ES. Here you go
into your next target. And then the last
one you can look for is all the way down
into this blue box, which is where I
would love to be a buyer from. All
right. So, this is a fantastic trade.
So, TP3 into here. here. Now remember
TP1 was 92, TP2 was 60, TP3 was 40, TP4
is into these like 20s here and then all
the way down here. Maybe even gap fill.
You never know, you might get the gap
fill, folks. So this is the higher time
frame pullback legs starting to play
out. So some covering in front of these
sort of 25s and 20s that we talked
about. Yeah. So when what was I saying?
Anytime you look at volume, always look
at the main contract. Why? Because
institutions, they're not trading
micros, right? We need to follow the
whales. So, we need to see the
institutional money.
Oh, literally asking how to open a cash
account.
Um, well, you can just go with uh AMP or
anyone that provides futures account.
Just have a look, see what you can look
at um Trade Station.
Just check the fees. Make sure the fees
are good for the round trip.
if that's what you're asking. Yeah, that
that sorry, maybe that's what you're
asking. You just need a brokerage
account, right? So, the main future ones
are like Iron Bean, AMP, um, Trade
Station is very good for absolutely
everything.
Almost there, folks. Oh, this is
fantastic. What a trade. I really hope
some of you are in this. What it would
have been a gift if uh we could have had
this all together. Beautiful, beautiful
work.
So, TP's in into here and then really
you're looking for previous day value
area high, maybe even gap filled if we
get really lucky. So, we've hit most of
these. One, two, three, four. If we get
five and six, I would after that, I
would not be touching it. All right. I
would really not be touching it. We get
very, very, very, very, very close now
to where we want to come. This is
ultimately where we want to come. If
there's a full rotation be down here,
but I think this blue box, it'd be uh
coming towards the edge of where we're
likely to come. Like we talked about,
very thin. To remind you all why. All
right. Once we let go of 92s, for anyone
joining late on stream, once we let go
of the 92s, where was that? Was it 92s?
I'm sure it was 92s here overnight.
There we go. Once we let go of this 92s,
we are very thin all the way down to
this shelf. Okay, so this is why we're
likely to fill in all of this down
towards this shelf and then we expect
probably there's some buyers hanging out
here to try and bid it back up at least
to this point here. All right. If they
fail to bid it back up, there's this
rotation down here. I would imagine this
happens no matter what. And then if they
want to rotate, they will do that. If
not, we will build out liquidity to move
higher because that is how the market
moves.
So the higher time frame pullback leg is
what's in effect right now.
Alex, did you say you would never
recommend a straight to funded account?
Yeah, I I don't think they're worth the
money. I think the rules the rules Nick
for most of them is like 20%. What? Why?
Why? Why? You're paying so much money to
skip a one day pass or a two-day pass so
that you are constricted far too much.
You're better off sticking six or 700
bucks in your own cash account and
trading that.
Honestly,
you've helped me trading more in 3 weeks
in the three weeks I've been following
you than three years of following
others. Oh, that's great to hear. I'm
I'm glad. That's why I turn up each day
because I like helping you guys. The
emails and direct messages I get from
people whose lives are massively
changing and benefiting is the most
rewarding thing for me. Right, shelf up
here into 150. Let's just have a little
look down here. Haven't had a look at
the footprint for a while.
Not convinced that auction's over yet to
be honest.
Yeah, 150 is key. 150 158. I'm not
convinced this auction's done yet. We'll
see. Okay, so gray box to gray box
rotation again.
Don't worry though, cuz ICT said, you
know, volume profile doesn't matter. It
matters so little that it's price is
reacting to it perfectly. Don't worry. A
[\h__\h] delusional old man said it
doesn't matter. We should listen to him
instead. Um,
sh Alex, don't start.
a good UK broker. Um or trade station uh
does UK. Um
I have to go through who I used to be
with. Give me a second. I will have some
of them down here. How do I get those
up?
Saxo is UK based trade station. I I
really liked I used to trade with them
even for small caps. Interactive pretty
good as well.
Was good for small caps.
I don't think IB was UK based. Trade
Station is though. Trade Station and
Saxo are UK based. Um but you have to
check if they do futures. I know Trade
Station does. I can't remember if Saxo
does. I used to trade my uh ETFs on it.
I trade on PC. I like you can't for me
if once you get serious about trading,
you got to leave a Mac alone.
Trust me, it was very hard for me to do.
I've spent my whole life on Mac.
I will not stream FOMC. No.
What volume indicators do I use? Um,
well, profile. So, anchored volume
profile and footprint and volume and
delta. Okay, gray box to gray box still
holding in above this is previous days
high, right? Yeah, still holding above
previous days high. This is a big big
hover point here. I would love to see
one more flush down into this. We have
liquidity on the book all the way down
into
12680s,
but we'll see. It's been a big trend
down. You do not want to get caught
shorting the lows, right? Look at this
like grind down. They will very, very
likely come back for all of this later.
The way that they've built this out,
think how many stops are in stops and
stops and stops and stops and stops. And
Alex would love something like this to
get along and rip those faces and be
beautiful. We'll see. Doesn't have to do
it today. Could do it tomorrow. Could do
it next week.
You've helped me too. Thank you. I knew
volume was where it was at. No worries.
Have I used IG? I actually have an
account with IG. I've got like hardly
any money in there. I It's the first
thing I traded on when I was like 20, 19
or 20 playing spread bets
like a long time ago. I haven't used it
since. Tasty Trade. There you go. Tasty
Trade. People saying Tasty Trade's good.
I see that advertised a lot. Where was
that guy from that set it up? He used to
have another brokerage, didn't he? Sure
he did.
I execute on Ninja
FMC. 2:00 will be the announcement. It's
likely to be no change. 2:30 will be the
uh Fed talk.
What is the orderflow window next to
your book map on screen? Uh it's just my
DOM. That's the level two. Yeah. So
price delta bid and ask um volume
profile sell volume profile buy session
volume profile. It's just my dom. Here
we go. Come on, baby. All the way down
you come. Let's come.
Think or swim. There you go. Thanks,
Eric. See, look. You guys are smart.
Deep charts. I have looked at them
briefly. I don't I don't need them, but
I think they're very good.
Here
we go. All right. You got to be
covering. If you are short into this,
you have to be covering into this move.
Now, this is the overextension as we
come back into the area where I would
expect the market very, very likely to
start finding bids around this area. So,
you better be 90% out of this trade if
you were short. This is a big winner on
stream again. You are now
120 or 130 points up. Yeah, 130 points
up. What an absolute banger. Another 100
point trade again on stream for free.
Is there a bookmap type program for
think or swim? I don't know. Maybe some
others can answer that. I I don't know.
What would I be looking at to go longs?
So, what we'd be looking at the same
kind of thing we had here, but the
opposite. All right. So in this area
here, you want a good auction, right? So
we want an auction where inside a candle
inside here, we see lots of sellers. All
right? And once we see that, that will
let us know that the auction's finished.
Ideally, we fill this gap and then we
start pivoting above maybe something
like this where we have trapped volume.
We'd like a node down here to be
developed of trapped sellers and then
we'll use their pain to go back upside
and then we're going to run all the
sellers out. That's what I would like to
see if I'm going to be a buyer. That's
what I want to see.
It's very It is possible we come down
for this, but I would be taking 90% off
into here. Did I take it? No. Uh it's
not because I didn't want to take it.
It's I'm ready to take it. It's because
trade of eight is down for me. It's it's
not because any other reason other than
I have no data, right? Trade of eight is
down currently.
How the best way to set up the anchored
volume profile
or how yours just 930. Just click on
930. It's all you got to do. Change it
to two ticks a row. Um two ticks or a
th000 rows.
It's just one day, guys, with trade
bait. It's It's okay. It happens, guys.
I don't know if many of you have traded
like elsewhere, but I can tell you like
I used to trade on [\h__\h] trade zero,
right? and I'd have like 5,000 shares
short on a Chinese stock getting
squeezed and that whole [\h__\h] thing
would go down. I'd wake up like 20 grand
in a hole, right, with real money. It
happens sometimes. It just happens,
guys. It It honestly, it happens. It's
shitty. It happens. Very rare, but it
happens.
So, you're seeing some covers in front
of this now.
Some covers starting to happen in front
right down into that level.
There are some guys still bidding down
into 85. But like I said, if you were
short, I would be 90% out of the money
now. Just holding a very small position.
The damage has been done. We've done the
move. Remember, we talk about the
lowhanging fruits. Like we've got a
couple of bits left, but you definitely
don't want to be forcing your way in
down here.
See if we can get Ninja Trader open. Now
you guys are saying it's working, so I'm
going to see if we can get it open.
Do I have an Apex account discount code?
Yes, FCT. Everything's underneath, guys.
So, FCT for all your favorite prop firms
other than uh take profit. You can use
code flow zone there for 40% off. There
are some big sales on right now. So, 90%
off for Apex is a big sale on uh Funded
Next for uh the Bolt. You can use FCT
there as well. Massive, massive sales
going on right now.
Front running in front of this back to
this profile. All right. So, just keep
remembering the higher time frame. Why
did we think we would trade down to here
today? We're coming back back testing
this. This is the area where we expect,
you know, some buildout to probably hold
somewhere around here down to maybe even
the 70s. You can see this right here. We
can thicken this up a bit. This right
here is an area of interest for us to
potentially buy back. We might go under
it and reclaim and the buyback could be
on a reclaim. It's definitely an area of
interest.
Would I recommend yellowing Apex? I
mean,
I don't know if I'd recommend it. It's
definitely a way a way that you could
trade, but I don't think I'd recommend
it. I still can't do anything. And I'm
even just trying to put a limit order
out here just to see if it can come on a
screen and it just says error. So still
no way I can trade with trader eight.
Guys, you're starting to see a bit of
relief here.
Just be careful. Remember, you've hit
most of your TPS. Like I said, you
should be out 90% of this move. You
don't want to be holding through
everything.
Thanks DS. Looking forward to you
joining every day.
So if you're looking for the long now,
starting to see these imbalances push.
That's not the best auction at the low
yet if I'm honest. But here is
definitely where these sellers started
to come in in this candle. So this is
kind of a key level to hold. I don't
love that low of day auction yet if I'm
honest. But if they start to build in
here and hold, there might be relief.
But I don't love that. But it's not bad.
So I'd be watching 21s to 10. So 20s to
tens again. The low of day doesn't look
too good for me yet.
I can't trade it anyway because this
[\h__\h] thing, but there we go.
But if the 10 to 21 start to hold, you
might see some relief. There's lots of
stops that can be popped. There's
probably likely to be relief up here to
75 to 90 at some point, right? It just
depends. Is it going to do it now like
this or does it need to come and take
this out and then go for it?
Like I said, 20s to tens are important.
I don't like the auction at low of day
right now. There's not enough sellers
caught down there yet. At least not from
what I'm seeing on Trading View. Let me
see if I can get any data here on Ninja
to see a bit more. Does Ninja look a bit
better? Ninja does look a little bit
better to be honest. The tick data there
is a little bit better. So yeah, 19s
down to tens, 20s to tens. If that holds
as a higher low,
that's a good sign.
But we came very very close to this.
It's kind of might as well come and
finish the auction, take it all out.
There's a buy still at 85. There was a
spoofer at 70. I'm looking lower to see
if there's much. A little bit of 50 and
40s, but not a lot. So you'd want this
to hold down towards tens. Now that
doesn't mean you enter there. It's just
like if buyers are going to step in,
that's where they're going to need to
step in. But again, the low of day
auctions not the best looking right now.
I would say
imbalance here down towards 10. They are
trying to bid in front of that. That's
not a bad sign.
So there's a good hold of 20s down to
tens and there's possible here that they
can get going for a squeeze. Counter
trend squeeze is possible here
especially up into 37s. Over that you're
looking 56s and then into this node up
here. Right up here is where we get
thicker 75s.
Are there any reasons why you would do a
second session or do you always do open
till 12? It's also just like I need to
have a life, right? I've got to have a
bit of a life. I I do I do trade in the
afternoons when they're setups, right,
in Discord for my community in Discord.
Like when they're setups, we we talk in
there, but recently the afternoons have
not been that good. Today might be
different. All right, so let's see if
they lift this now. So if you've got
long in this in this hold here, you're
looking for a lift through 37s and then
you're looking for 55s and then all the
way up into 80s. All right. So if they
hold here, it's very very very early,
but uh it is possible to offer relief.
You're into lunch as well. I still think
they haven't finished down here, but we
will see if they're going to take it.
Right. They're going to be looking
wants to hold. You'd be looking for
this, this, and this for this would be
the start of the pro trend, but I would
rather see it build out some liquidity
for a little bit, but you might see some
relief here into lunch.
Which firms have sales? TPT is 40% off.
You can use code flow zone there and no
activation fee. Apex has 90% off. You
can use code FCT there. Um, Funded Next
has a big sale as well for the uh, Bolt
accounts.
I would be careful here, by the way,
guys. You're into lunch as well.
Uh, no, I manually mark all these. I
manually mark everything here.
I have global plus but um I don't use I
don't use any added stuff. No iceberg,
nothing like that. I just have it very
very simple.
Take care, Mark. Take care, Mark.
Here's the relief. All right. So, you're
looking for this
into here. This is the next wick. So if
you get acceptance over 40, you should
lift into 60. Same levels and then 78.
Where's my thing gone? [\h__\h] hell. So
here. So here's TP1, TP2, TP3. And if
you get really lucky, you get all the
way up into here. But I'd definitely be
looking for this to trade 81s if you
find acceptance or 70s, 75s if you find
acceptance. This can be a stop hunt up
here and trade back down. So you I would
have break even already on this because
I don't like the uh low of day auction.
So it' be TP1 into here. So TP1 into
here. You hit TP1, TP2, TP3.
And I'd already been moving break even
because I don't like the lower day
auction.
Why is 37 a level? Uh it it's again it's
from uh Globeex session.
Tra's back up and running. I mean, for
me, I can't I can't even place a limit
order. No, still I can't do anything on
any of my uh
prop accounts. I just get error
messages. It's probably a no trade for
me, unfortunately.
I'll give you a couple minutes and see
if you get this. So, let's see if you
get acceptance through here. But even
this
there's another 20 points.
So you probably got you probably just
missed this uh target at low of day. I
don't know. You probably only got into
here. So we got 128 points downside move
and then see what what we get as upside
relief.
I'd love it if it would just manipulate
a bit lower first and hopefully they fix
all the accounts and I can pick scoop
something up for next uh the next
session.
Uh off the chart for me um TJ I' I'd
never execute on Dom. It's just a habit.
It's just a habit.
Guys, clean up the chat, please. Like,
stop all of it. Don't want any
negativity. Just stop. Just stop it
completely. Stop it.
Trend lines can be used as confluence.
Yes, great kitty. They they can be used
as extra confluence.
But what what I would say here, right,
we went over this a little bit earlier.
What you actually want here is like a
buildout of some volume. All right, if
we can start poking this out and some
good volume and then a failed break
below. All right, so let's say we come
lower, we sweep, we clean out all these
levels, institutions get long, we come
back, and then we build above that
volume and we leave all the shorts
stuck. That is the better move, right?
This is a very early long. Like I said,
it's very early. I'm not convinced we
finished the low of day. I don't like
the auction at low of day. Remember, I
kept saying that it's very, very early.
But there are some sellers stuck between
20 and tens which we went over right
here. Right this right here. But it's
not significant at low of day. I don't
like that. All right. There I want to
see big red and I'm not seeing that. But
you can see 20s to tens keeps being
absorbed. Where's 20s? 20s to tens. This
level here keeps being absorbed now. And
there is a chance for relief back up.
But it's not ideal. It is not like an A+
setup, but we are coming into a very,
very good area where I said I would be
willing to look for buys if we can trap
shorts. This is the first time we're
seeing this. I'd much rather it does
this, builds out, and then does that for
FMC. That would be a plus. But right now
it's still holding.
Yeah. Trader [\h__\h] again. Yeah, there
you go.
Alex, were you able to stay green each
month last year? How do you keep
yourself from tilt? Um, I think I had
one red month last year. I have to go
through which month it was. I had one
technical issue on stream where I got
absolutely [\h__\h] smoked
um on the trade copier and I spent the
next few weeks making it back. How do I
keep myself on tilt? You would have seen
me go on tilt on stream. Um, but I don't
like go mental when I go on tilt. You'll
see me verbalize when I'm on tilt. So,
what am I? I can tell you my big tilt
factors. Too many break evens in a row
or like calling a really good trade and
like not having it go for me. So, I
think it was last week.
Last week there was like three days in a
row where I got knocked out. I had three
attempts at a short two days in a row
for the rotation and I got knocked out
for like 20 points, 20 points, 20 points
and it would then on the fourth go it
would do like 100 point move. One day I
left stream and it went for like a 200
point fade. Um,
so it happens, but you what you'll see
with me is I verbalize it and I note it
and I come back to the stream the next
day and I'll be like, "Okay,
my tilt's up. My anxietyy's up. I'm
pissed off that I haven't made this much
money, so I need to be careful now. I
need to be very, very careful with my
sizing." And that's how I try and avoid
it. Um, you can't people that like
control your emotions, control you
can't. All you can do is control how you
view life, how you view things. You
can't just There you go. So, trader doc
saying, "Yeah, I remember you kept
warning yourself." For me, if I
verbalize it and say it out loud, that
for me is part of acceptance, right?
It's part of acceptance. Trading, much
like life, and I'm going through this a
lot at the moment, a lot of life is
about acceptance. Can you would have
seen I did a post on YouTube. Can you
accept a loss? Can you accept someone in
your family's passed away? Can you
accept a relationship's ended? Can you
accept
your lifestyle isn't what you thought it
was? Can you accept that you've just
taken a bad trade and you've lost on it?
All right, that might sound like really
simple. It's actually not because
acceptance is what allowed you to move
forward. If you cling on to the fact
that those things have happened and you
can't accept they've happened, it
doesn't mean it's okay, right? I'm not
trying to make an excuse for it, but if
you cling on to the fact that I'm so
pissed off that that's happened or I'm
so upset and I'm so devastated, you are
clinging on to a tag, a a a form of
tilt, an emotion. If you can just accept
that it's happened, okay, that's
happened to me. It's unfortunate. I'm
not happy about it, but this is how I'm
going to move forward. That is how you
move from taking a loss to moving
forward. So let's say I took a loss.
Okay, I accept that's happened. I've
moved forward. What's the next trade
setup? Okay, I've taken another loss. It
hasn't worked out for me. Okay, what's
the next trade setup? Okay, I've taken
another loss. Okay, three in a row.
What's the next trade setup? The next
trade setup for me at that point is to
walk away. Come back with a fresh face
tomorrow cuz I want to get punched in
the face five times in a row, right?
Three times is enough to be punched in
the face. So it it's just finding
acceptance and knowing your tolerance,
right? If you're going to sit here and
you can't find acceptance for it, what
does not finding acceptance for
something look like? Tell you what it
looks like. It looks like this. All
right.
I'm buying this now. [\h__\h] you. I'm
buying more. No way. I'm buying more.
Yes, it has to go up. No, [\h__\h] you. I'm
buying more. No, [\h__\h] off. I'm buying
more. Oh, I just blew up. And then the
trade goes and then you go, I [\h__\h]
knew that was going to happen. That is
what not finding acceptance looks like,
right? Fighting fighting against the
markets. If I'm trading well, I'm never
fighting a market. I'm patiently waiting
for it to come into an area or I'm
waiting for someone to fight the market
and I'm trading their pain point. Okay?
So like so much of
becoming proficient at trading is about
knowing yourself. Mastering the market's
one thing. Understanding how the market
moves, why the market moves, waiting
like understanding the key levels. We
can all mark out these key levels,
right? We can all mark out these key
levels. Do you have the patience to wait
for it to get there? All right, to offer
you the best buy. Think about yesterday.
Those who joined me yesterday, we bought
the dip yesterday. We took the 40
trigger long, right? Where was
yesterday?
Here
we go. All right. Yesterday, look at
this key level down here into my key
level. Same key level, right?
We didn't trade all this,
right? We waited. I said to you, I'm
going to ignore this short and I'm going
to wait for the long. Very much like
today, I'm going to ignore this short,
wait for the long into this key level.
The trigger was 40 from what I remember.
Shorts were stuck here under 40. This
was the trigger. That's the patient. The
patient guy wins. The disciplined trader
who's willing to let it come to a level,
let it show you it wants to move and
then take the trade. If you can start
doing that, that is called knowing
yourself. Because marking levels is
easy. Waiting for the levels, that's a
whole new skill. It might sound really
simple. Most traders cannot wait. They
cannot wait. They have to click. They
have to be in a trade, right? They
cannot wait. Look, if you waited now and
the hold of 20 and 10s that we talked
about. Look, we're there. We're almost
there already. This is TP2. TP3 would be
up here for acceptance. We're going to
run out all these stops, right? It's
literally doing everything we've just
talked about. Why? It's not cuz I'm a
[\h__\h] genius, guys. I'm not a genius.
It's just patience. It's patience.
I can have accepted big loss as my wife
is a different story.
Acceptance does not mean I can't do
something going forward. I accept the
weather is what the weather is and
there's nothing I can do about it.
However, if it's raining, I can grab an
umbrella. That's exactly it, MJ. That is
such a great way to put it. That is such
a great That is acceptance. It doesn't
mean you have to like it. It just means
you accept it's happened. I'm learning
this. I'm genuinely I'm still learning
this. You don't have to like everything
that happens to you in life, but you
have to accept that it's happened. If
it's in the past, it's already happened.
You can [\h__\h] and moan and scream and
shout all you want, but all you're doing
is causing yourself in pain, or you can
accept it's happened and try and find
the most comforting or best solution for
you to move forward. That's trading. You
can accept it, right? If you can't
accept a loss trading, you're going to
really struggle. You're going to really
struggle.
How you know that was the level? Um what
was your name? Alan Alanis there. Uh
it's just based on value. All right.
Previous day value area high. Previous
day point control. Previous day high.
Previous day close. Lots of confluence
down here. We are likely to come under
this level and find a bid. And you know
right under it we did. And we trapped
like we said 20 to 10 was the trap. And
here we go. So, this is the move.
Friska, I'd wait for the pullback now.
If you if you didn't take this dip in
here, I'd wait for the pullback now
because you want to be careful. Think
about the uh the amount of legs, right?
We we don't want to long at the top of
this one, two. We don't want a long up
here. We don't want to long up here. So,
what you want, let it build out some
volume now. Let it prove to you that it
doesn't want to go low and then you can
think about trading back upside. I still
don't love this. I'll be honest, but we
will see. This is just squeeze relief
back to this shelf.
It definitely happens, trader doc. It
definitely happens.
Do I think that the balance the trade's
going to go back upside? Yeah, I don't
know if we wick this out. Like, I'll be
honest. I don't know if we wick this out
still, but my bias is as long as we hold
this area, I think we will trade back
upside. It doesn't have to be today, but
as long as we hold this area. I think
this has been built this way for a
reason. All right, trap. Right.
Comfortable, comfortable, comfortable,
comfortable, comfortable, comfortable.
Drip, drip, drip. Ideally, we do
something like this, this, this, this,
and then this. I think that's possible.
If we lose this area, though, you can't
look for that trade. If we lose this
area, the rotation is back down to the
900s, right? It's very very possible if
we lose that area, but all the time we
are holding down into sort of 26,000 and
50 is the max. But ideally, we want to
hold 26,100, 26,73 somewhere in here. As
long as they do this, this this if they
build out this and reclaim it, then I
think there's a great upside shot. If
they're going to do it already, it's it
is what it is. If that 20 to 10 hold was
it, it's not the best auction at the low
of day, but if that was it, that was it.
I'm going to have to get off soon. I I I
have an appointment soon, so I I will
have to get off soon, but I'm just
trying to help. Alex, can you go over?
Yes. Yes. Sorry. Sorry, my friend.
Sorry. Sorry. Sorry. You did put that a
while ago. Same kind of story. All
right, you're watching PDC.
This is a better look here. This is
actually a better buildout. All right,
underneath higher time frame algo,
there's your higher time frame algo dip
underneath it. Reclaim. If they start
holding this and reclaiming, this is
your big area PDC to IB. If they if
they're able to reclaim this, this has
got a shot. It has got a shot back into
it. It's the same kind of story, right?
Let's zoom out on an hourly.
Sunday open. It's a nice flag pullback
into the 30s,
right? And the last chance would be into
60s. So, I think dip buys, if they're
going to hold it, will be either where
we are now or down into these 60s. All
right. So, either they're going to do
this or they do this move here later in
the week. That's what I would be looking
for. failing to hold 60s or if you come
under this I'd be very concerned
especially under here but same kind of
same kind of story on ES exactly the
same kind of story you can see they're
trying to get that relief now so PDC
here acceptance through PDC gets you to
IB acceptance through IB gets you to VW
acceptance through VWOP gets you to New
York open and you've got all these stops
to run out remember this is just a
higher time frame pullback guys I cannot
explain this enough right
is a higher time frame pullback back.
Failing to break lower. Build liquidity.
Break out. Pull back. Break out. Pull
back. Break out. Pull back. Break out.
Pull back. Somewhere in one of these
levels. We expect a bid here or here.
Right? Same story. This is the pullback
leg, higher time frame to build
liquidity to go higher. If they want to
do a deep test, they will. This is why
we have to wait and see. At the moment
we are reacting, right? We are reacting
should should sorry should I who live in
Europe win mark PD value area zones use
based on time zone instead of Europe
depends what session you're trading Tony
So always use the New York session, you
can use the whole session if you want to
look at if you're trading Europe, you
can use you can use the Asia, you can
use developing session since that uh
6:00 open and you can use the previous
days. You can also do one on that
European session
global plus global plus for uh bookmap.
I'm in Los Angeles
in Los Angeles.
Gold.
Going to have to get out of here in a
minute, folks.
Yeah, gold still looks good. Like we
talked about, pullbacks are going to be
absorbed. Look at that. Jesus Christ
almighty.
All right, so that liquidity day, all we
did, remember I said gold, none of these
are a short. Everyone's talking about,
oh, it's a big short. No, it's just like
a pull back in. There is nothing in
here, right? Until we go backside at the
moment. This is straight straight move
upside. Uh
we can go to a five.
Same kind of story down to IB low into a
double top high. I don't know how go
gold trades technically like what it
likes to do but technically you're
bullish all the time. You're holding
above this. This is the same thing,
right? Built liquidity for a couple of
sessions. Breakout, pullback, breakout,
pullback. breakout is still bullish till
it proves otherwise.
You're going to have to lose all of
this. Same on silver. I would imagine
no here.
Pull back absorbed. Yeah. So, the same
thing. Remember we said it's no
backside. Everyone's talking about this
big short on silver. Okay. Yes, we're
overextended, but where would the
backside be? Well, where are the pivots?
There's your breakout. You could argue
there's a little one in there. Until you
get under all this and you leave buyers
stuck up here. It's always the same
thing. Until there are buyers stuck up
here, there is no backside move. Yes,
we're overextended. Yes, we're probably
past two standard deviations, but look
how we absorbed it. Bye.
How many shorts? What you need to ask
yourself now is how many people position
themselves swing short in here saying
this thing has to die. Well, painoint
number one is there. Painpoint number
two is there. And I'm telling you what,
if it gets past pain point number two,
they're [\h__\h]
Best way of me putting it. They are
absolutely fooked. All right, if it gets
past painoint number two, I just want to
have a look at that on a daily chart for
a second.
Bring you down so you can see it.
see where we are based on standard
deviations
on these.
I mean look look look look
everything we talk about. What is a
healthy trend? Top bowl 5day on the
breakout.
This is a healthy trend. Top bowl
fiveday. Top bowl fiveday. Top bowl
fiveday. Top bowl overextension through.
Big flush. Oh, guess what? Fiveday. Top
bowl. Top bowl. All right, this is fine
right now. It might be that it does a
blowoff top and a rotation, but this is
still bullish. It can come all the way
down here and still be bullish.
If I was swinging long, there's zero
reason to sell right now. Zero macro
reason. Zero reason.
Okay. Got stuck at that TP2. And like I
said, this auction under here, I would
be very, very careful. All right.
Because this under here,
there's your last trade. I'd be out of
this. out. Let this build out volume.
Now, I don't like this lower day
auction. I've said it a million times. I
don't think there's enough shorts
stucking down in here. The shorts got
stuck 20 to 10. You can still watch that
level 20 to 10, but if they don't hold
that, there's highly probable that you
get new lower day. Right, last few
questions and then I've got to get out
of here, folks, and get on with my day.
Yeah, SP I agree. I agree on NQ as well.
I don't like the auction lower day
auction. I said it's probably squeeze
relief. I would much rather it comes and
digs into all of this and traps more
shorts.
Netflix.
It's holding up. All right. We just
We've done one undercut of this. I'm in
a very small position here, but
it's possible we fade a little bit more.
watching this pivot here on Netflix.
Right, this is the big one
16.
Yeah, there's a little undercut in here,
which is why I positioned long, just for
a starter.
Into here would be great. anything in
there, I'll start scooping up and then
we'll be looking for that long term. But
we're like, it depends what you're
looking for. I'm looking for an all-time
hold. Like I'm not looking for or a
trade when I'm looking in this. We're
already down what, like 40%.
Yeah, 40% off the highs
and I'm very very small size, but you
know, we we could do with a big big old
flush like and a trap and a reclaim,
right? That would be really nice if we
can do it. I don't know if we can do it,
but certainly if we come into there and
we trap shorts, I will be uh swing long
starting to add with more size.
I'm not worried longterm. Not not in the
slightest.
40. I'm 40.
What's the most reliable strategy or
confluence that you work with? I would
just say volume and like flow zones,
right? Momentum and volume. So like
volume,
momentum clouds,
right? Don't fight them. Simple as that.
this anchored volume profile on the
right hand side anchored volume profile.
Okay folks, time for me to get out of
here. Thanks for joining today. Good
luck with FOMC if you're going to trade
it. Hopefully trade's back up and
running properly for them. Just be
smart, be careful. All right, be smart
and be careful. Um, again, I don't think
we finished the auction. We're still
holding the 20s to the tens. That's
still the same level. But I don't think
we finish the auction at the low. It's
the only thing I would say. I would be
looking, like I've talked about numerous
times, I'd be looking to see if we trap
under here, anywhere in here, here,
maybe even that, but ideally not. And
then reclaim and build out volume, which
we can use to reclaim. And that will be
what I would be looking for in an ideal
environment. All right. at the moment
still holding the tens and 20s, but
that's what I'd be looking for this
afternoon in an ideal environment. FOMC
likely to be volatile. Remember, you've
got earnings afterwards. Don't need to
force it. It's just one trading day. All
right, there's a new trading day
tomorrow and we get Apple at the end of
day and we get Friday close and then
next week we will know if we're
sustaining bids outside of breakout or
not. Thanks for joining on the stream.
As always, if you're new to this stream,
go and check out everything on my
YouTube. Tons of free education on
there. Go there first, right? If you
like that, you can head over to my
website, flowzonetrader.com. There are a
few courses there you can look at. If
you're interested and you like how I
trade. If you want to support the
stream, you can become a member, $5 a
month, or you can use my code FZT down
below for all your best prop firms. I
will see you tomorrow morning. Those in
Discord, I'll try and pop in and give
you some advice coming into FOMC. Peace
and love. Use hard stops, all that good
stuff. Take care.