Happy Tuesday, people.
We're back. We're back again. Good
morning. Good morning, everyone. Hope
you're doing good. Hopefully, some of
you caught some of those overnight
longs. What a beautiful move for
continuation, right? Once we reclaimed
that nine sort of 20 level that we
talked about yesterday, old uh naked
point of control, we're now basing over
it and you can see where we're
attacking. All right, so we're going to
go over all the charts now all the way
top down analysis
and then I'll trade with you live into
lunch. Okay, so as always starting on
the daily,
what do we have? Well, yesterday
gap down, opened up, drove higher,
closed near the highs. We expect what
continuation? What are the targets? You
can see all the stops here dating right
back to the 5th of November. Right back
here, we have a gap fill in here. All
right, especially on the ETF. So, I'll
go over it on QQQ. There is a gap fill
there that it might be looking to do to
be an efficient market. It doesn't need
to do it today, but it might be
something it wants to do. So, we have
all these stops. One, two, three, four,
five, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13. Even
this guy here has now been taken out 14.
All these stops here, these are daily
stops. All right, lots and lots and lots
of stops. Every time we come up here,
we've rejected. We've come up, we
rejected. We've come up, we've rejected.
But this is one, two, three. This is
time number four. All right, so imagine
if there are passive sellers, all right,
sat here unloading. How much more
inventory have they got to unload? I
would guess not very much. All right.
They've had three months, right, from
November 5th, November, December,
January coming up to so December,
January coming up into Feb. Three months
of unloading inventory there. It doesn't
mean it has to break through today, but
I would say it's a very, very good
chance at some point we're going to get
some form of breakout. Whether that
sustains or not is another thing. All
right. So, what we're looking for today,
we have this top Ballinger band. You can
see starting to point upside. Look at
the 5day turning around, starting to
come up through the 20-day. and we might
get one of these channels if we can
sustain a break and hold here and then
we can start to do this move for Q1. All
right, it's not what anyone expected,
but it's very much looks like how we're
setting up. The only other thing on the
daily we could potentially will look for
is a fail break, a gap fill, and then
this to be the false break and this move
here for the rest of Q1 and beyond. So,
lots to play for. This week will be
telling as we get into especially from
tomorrow onwards. All right, FOMC 97%
chance of no rate cut, but what's more
important is actually the MAG and what
happens afterwards. All right, let's go
down into the hourlys. We can look at
the profiles that are starting to
develop here. All right, so those of you
traded me with me yesterday will know we
were taking these longs. All right, we
were long yesterday for the push towards
this old naked point of control up into
here. I think it was 890s. That was it.
Was it 920s? It was 890s. All right. So,
our long yesterday was from here up into
this move into this guy here. We
completed that and then we were risk
off. And what you've had is a pullback
overnight, right? If we think about
previous week's value area high, this
guy right here, pullbacks overnight.
Surprise, surprise. Held previous week's
value area high. That was also previous
days value area high. So, you've got
confluence there. So if you were playing
in the uh Asian market, well there's
your long trigger and there's the
expansion. All right, you've taken out
all the key levels. Now we're start now
su successfully basing above that 890,
aren't we? All right, so we pulled under
it. We've got back above it and we're
starting to drive higher and we're
coming into supply here. So we don't
really want to be long here at the
highs. Unfortunately, what we've got
here setting up in the market is anyone
who was swing long, right? Anyone who
swing long from down here or even here
or even entered with us yesterday here.
All right, they have both things on
their side. Remember, they have location
and momentum. All right, we always talk
about that. Prime location, discount
location, great momentum. If we're long
today up here, unfortunately, we have no
location, but we have great momentum.
All right, so we don't have both these
things. So, we need to wait really for
some setups to come in. Now what that
will those be? Ideally it will be a back
test of some of these key levels. All
right so anything into here where we can
see some buyers stepping up some form of
absorption. This by the way is current
developing week profile. So you can see
we get thick in here from sort of 9:15
down to 865. Right? Anywhere in here
where we see buying absorption taking
place, sellers getting stuck, we can
look for this continuation higher as
long as it hasn't taken out all the
stops. If we fail in here, all right,
the next spot is these previous day
value area lows, previous week value,
area highs. All right, same kind of
thing. Looking for this. If we give this
whole thing back under here, you want to
be very careful. All right, if we do not
see absorption here, we can rotate all
the way back down. This can still be a
breakout retest, which can still be
absorbed. So, these are the areas I'm
interested in looking long in here,
potentially in here, but more likely on
a reclaim here. So this level here is
big for me. These sort of 920s and then
down here underneath that I become far
less interested in the bullish play. All
right. When will I be really
uninterested in the bullish play? If
right if we go and pop all these stops
if we I'm going to have to zoom this
back. This block up here. If we go and
pop all these and it hasn't given me an
entry right there's only something I can
wait for is a retest build out to go
higher. If we don't see that, if we see
this move, then I become far less
interested in it because it means we've
had a failed breakout and then a
rotation is probable again. All right,
so have to be aware of that. It's all
depend what do we take, when do we take
it, what's available. All right, moving
up into the five minute. You can see
this is the move we just talked about
the Asia move. There's your double
bottom, the reclaim and the drive.
London sideways. So we're waiting now.
Can we get a retest here? Do we see a
break and retest to buy? Um, I do want
to go through the ETFs and the cues
because they're going to be important
today.
Right. So, let's just take you on to the
cues up here.
Okay. One thing I want to be aware of is
this up here. All right. 632 is a gap
fill. Uh, move you out into an hourly.
You will see it.
Right. This is a big gap fill from I
think it was 5th of November. Yeah.
Right. So this mark here, this close,
we've never filled this gap. All right.
The highest we've got is up into here
into the 26 or 276 27. All right. We're
comfortably inside that right now. This
is the gap fill. This was after hours.
The gap fill, the cash gap is to 632. So
I am aware of that as we come into it.
Hence why I've got a uh price alert
there marked out because this might be
it might be right that this is all
they're trying to do and that can be the
failed break. I'm not saying it is but I
need to be aware of this. It's a big
level for the market to be efficient. So
that's one thing I'm watching at
watching for for the Q's. It's not quite
so obvious on ENQ, but it's a very
obvious gap on the Q. So be aware of
that uh as we roll down these and go
through the ES and the spiders. Right,
ES getting very close for the breakout.
Right, not too far away right now. All
I'd say is check your sectors. Right,
healthcare very very weak. Uh, UNH was
weak off earnings. We saw healthcare not
really get going yesterday and this
morning as well. It is showing some
weakness. So, it might drag the market
not necessarily down, but it might stop
ES moving as much as it would want.
really depends if those other sectors,
obviously tech's worth a lot, but like
finance and stuff like that, if they
start to pick up some of the weight. Um,
SPY, same thing. All right, SPY, you are
very, very, very close to this all-time
high breakout. You can see I've got it
marked out here for alltime high. It's
worth setting price alerts for these
guys just so you can then see if it's a
fail break or not. Dixie getting
absolutely clapped like we've been
talking about for a long time. This is
the expected move coming right down back
inside. And uh the more this collapses,
well, the more rotation you're going to
see into safe havens like gold and
silver. I told you yesterday silver was
just a flush to be probably scooped up.
And well, look at that. All right,
there's no breakdown yet. Now, if we
have failed follow-through in the next
few sessions and we start to see, you
know, failing to make new highs, then
you can think about the backside move.
But yesterday was nothing more than a
pullback, guys. So, everyone got very
excited. Yes, there's a lot of
volatility, but until it proves
otherwise, all right, we are not
backside of the move. You're going to
need to see a failed break and starting
to see a collapse down. Same story on
gold. Still looks good. Still holding
all the time. Dixie's rotating off.
You're going to see safe haven moves
back into this. Are they due a pullback?
Absolutely. Of course they are. Full
Sigma moves yesterday. But, uh, you
know, we can only play what's in front
of us like I always tell you guys. VIX.
All right. VIX opening up in the mid
teens right here into some sort of old
support system here. Still sort of
holding this channel. We can probably
move this out a little bit. Something
like this. Right. Still in this channel,
right? We've had that big swipe. And
really, this is kind of no man's land.
This is grindy area. So, we'll have to
see what gets going on the VIX. Uh if we
look at the previous few days levels,
yeah, there's probably a pivot here. You
can see this was the gap fill we talked
about yesterday. I' I'd be watching a
break on VIX above 1620 1625. Maybe then
it gets going. Right, let's have a look
on the MAG.
All right, nice gap up on Apple. You can
see that red bar was resistance. So,
we're now going to use that as a
potential support mechanism. Remember,
I'm still long Apple on the swings,
right? Long from way down low in the
200s.
And we'll see we'll see if we can get
going. Now, this does now start to look
like what we've been talking about the
last few weeks. There's your build out
of liquidity. There's your fail to break
lower. If we can base out here, then
guess what we've got? And obviously this
week we have earnings season. So if we
can get going off good earnings, it's
got a shot. It has definitely got a
shot. Amazon,
same kind of story. Nice gap up. If we
zoom this out a little bit on Amazon,
right now holding above this gap,
building out the same kind of liquidity.
As long as it holds dips into 35s,
there's potential rotation higher.
Collapse 35 and it's a different
different story altogether, but 235s
will be a key level on Amazon for dips
to be holding. Goo another gap up there.
Nice drive higher. You're seeing the
same story across the tape here, folks.
All right. Failed to break lower. Build
out the liquidity. Can it break higher?
All right. This is story of the tape.
We're starting to see, remember we
talked about it November last year, we
saw rotation out of the MAG into, you
know, some of the Russell and uh more
speculatory kind of broadening of the
market. Now we're seeing rotation back
into the MAG. Why? Because we have
earnings this week. They're positioning
early for earnings. Look at this
position early for earnings. Big
position. Look at Meta Go. I'm glad I'm
long in this one. This is an absolute
steam train that actually could do with
a healthy pullback here. All right, we
could do with a good pullback in meta um
before it gets going. We've got some
pivots up here. So, something like this
would interest me to add. Uh I'm long
from down here, folks. All right, those
in Discord will know I'm long from down
here. Sat through all of this. If we get
another pullback for an ad, I will add
on.
And let's keep going through these.
What's next? Microsoft,
same story here on Softy. All right.
dips yesterday held or the day before
held. All right, pivots down here.
Failing to break lower. Looks good. Just
need to build out a bit more liquidity.
This is pretty expansive here. We need a
pullback to hold or just base in here
for a while. Looking strong so far. Tech
on this rotation until we see failures.
We're looking strong. Nvidia, same kind
of story. actually a little bit more
messy here on video because we built out
a huge amount of uh liquidity here last
year. If we zoom out of this, you can
see across here. All right, so needs to
get back in this range and do the dance
to open up. That's uh a little bit
messier to be honest. All right, because
you could argue that this is backside
here, right? So failures under here will
be a problem for Nvidia under 75, but
it's holding up all right right now.
It's not the prettiest chart, though.
Tesla.
Zoom out of this. That is a little bit
messy as well.
[snorts] This is your pivot on Tesla.
Here to here. Here's your box. So, they
want to hold above 30s and then they
need to get a break above 50s and a
hold. That's your pivot. It's actually a
bit messy. We're just boxed in. So, it's
probably if people are trying to play
momentum in that, they're probably
getting clapped both ways, right? as an
equally weighted mag. Let's have a look.
There you go. So, equal weighted mag
having a good January. All right. Up
into here. So, this is what we'd look
for on the mag and then this. It doesn't
have to be like that. It can just be
here and then go. But a little bit of a
buildout would be healthy for the mag if
we're going to get going. Right. Let's
have a look at some broader names. We've
got a couple minutes left. APGO
week
Netflix
still holding. Okay. Okay, might need
one more attempt to flush and a and a
hold. AMD pulling back after that big
big drive out.
Dangerously close to a backside move. Uh
40s is the kind of level 38s and 40s.
All right.
Uh again, if you're trading uh ES today,
just make sure you understand how weak
healthcare has been overnight, right?
UNH and stuff like that off the
earnings.
Okay. So, I'm not long and strong out
the open here. re really don't want to
be long and strong out the gate here.
What I'd love to see is dips. All right,
I would love to see before we come and
take out the top of this red box. I'd
love to see some dips into sort of I
don't know 935 down to 8.85, this kind
of box down here. Uh I would be
interested in I definitely don't want to
be long at the top. If it goes on a
squeeze without me, it is what it is.
Unless I can see something I'm really
interested in, it's going to be hard to
draw this high.
Does my indicator generate those buy and
sell arrows? It does indeed. Yes.
All right. Just under a minute here.
What's the plan for today? We're above
previous value high and overnight close.
Looking for continuation sweep or fail
rotation. Yeah, exactly. We just went
over it, right? Dips into here. If they
hold somewhere into here. If they fail
that level, then possibly rotation back
down into here. But really somewhere in
here, right? I want to see something
like this. I want to see passive buyers
step up. I want to see aggressive
sellers get caught. If I don't see that
and they don't step up, we watch
previous days levels and if we've
collapsed under that, then we're going
to come right down into here. This would
be a short that I'd consider taking for
the counter trend
on a higher time frame. That would be
counter trend.
Let's see how we go, folks. Hopefully
market offers us something. Good luck,
everyone.
See if this can flush down a little bit
for us for us to scoop something up.
Uh ES letting go of previous day high by
the way. I think that's previous day.
Yes. So gap fill on ES would be down to
981s. Gap fill for us by the way is all
the way down here. 850s. Long long way
away.
Mag all opening up green. So Tesla 0.11%
up. Nvidia 09%
up. Microsoft 0.71% up. Meta and Google
both quarter% up. Amazon just uh about
third of a percent up, giving some back.
And uh Apple 150% up. So coming back
down towards previous day high right
now. And let's see if we can get into
some of these areas for us to start
bidding on. We'll be interested. Already
seeing some buyers try and step up here.
It's a big drive up already.
Buyers stepped in nice and early there.
So, held the 55s. There's a seller here
at 95 and then all the way back up. So,
here comes the squeeze. So, they're
already trying it. So, it didn't even
get into our level. They've already
tried to absorb it.
I'd be watching ES into VWAP and
previous day high here. If it starts to
base above, it's got squeeze potential.
Here we go. Right back to the upside.
Amazing. Didn't get anywhere near where
I wanted to participate down here.
looking for dips. But, uh, we actually
need a dip, not just that first little
thing. We'll see.
If we buy the orderflow course, do we
get Discord? No, you do not. It's only
in the 20our course. Okay. Some sellers
were here uh up into the 15s and 20s.
They've just left the tape. So, we got
some early spoofing here.
Yes. projecting that VW up and previous
day high right now.
Relative strength in the cues
like we talked about. Expecting relative
strength in the cues today because of
the mag versus healthcare continuing
higher here by the looks of it and we're
trying to see if these sellers come back
on the tape. At the moment they are long
gone. So dips are holding here. They're
looking to accelerate through and take
out this GlobeEx at the moment.
See if we can come up all the way up
into this now. See if we can grab a
piece if it's going to start to base and
hold.
Really want to buy much much lower than
this. Just not going to give me the
opportunity today.
VIX starting to get going. I want to be
careful here of the divergence. VIX
coming up to those 1620s. So if VIX
starts to break through these 1625s,
there's an upside move to 1650. market
will get weak or at least the ES will.
Let's see.
Is there a day trade on silver? Um have
a look little look. Might be if there's
failed follow through.
you're just stuck in GlobeEx. I mean,
I'd say if there's failed follow through
at 110s, maybe that's all all I would uh
consider playing off right now. But I
think, you know, that would be a counter
that would be looking for that early
move counter trend almost.
Watching this New York to see if it
holds. I really want to be a buyer down
here. It's just whether they're willing
to let this go. Meta just gone red on
the day. Tesla just gone red on the day.
They're still absorb obser absorbing
that uh level. Come on. Come all the way
down. It' be really nice. I was very
tempted to buy up here, but nothing I've
seen on the tape yet. Really want this
breakdown into here. Not for me to play
short, for me to scoop long.
Vicks trying to get through this break.
This 1625 break is what you need to
watch on the VIX. So just whipped the
low of day there and they got absorbed
again. Sellers currently stuck
underneath 67 on the day. Big seller was
at 73. So you could even say under 73,
but definitely under 67. It's where
sellers have come in heavy. You can see
it right here. This one. This one.
Right. They keep coming piling in down
here
under sort of. There you go. Under 70.
I would say it's well 73 and 68 is where
they they're marketing very very
aggressively in here. So hopefully we
get a move lower. I'm not going to play
the short. I'm going to wait to see if
we absorb down here. I'm going to try
and avoid that counter trend at the
moment.
Some absorption here again.
This moving lower.
Come on. Come down, baby.
Interesting ES finding some strength
here when ES uh ENQ starting to make new
lows. A little bit of a mess out here.
I'm just going to have to wait for it to
figure itself out.
So, coming down to previous day high,
this red line. This is the area of
interest down here. Previous day value
area high, previous day point of
control, and this big block. Anywhere
down here where I start to see
absorption on the tape, I'll be
interested in getting long, especially
if we can trap and start to curl and go.
But want to be careful if we stay heavy.
Obviously, I won't bid on it.
Here we go. This is better. So, if you
did take this counter trend short,
you're looking good. Down into these
boxes are your targets is previous day
high, this red line. So, you would be
cover one here. Previous day value area
high be cover 2, previous day point of
control. Anything beyond that is an
absolute gift for you guys. I'm looking
to get long in these areas if I see
sellers get trapped. All right. If I see
sellers get trapped.
VIX going for that uh 25 break. It's
currently trading at 1623. So you want
to be careful if VIX starts to get
going. There'd be a bigger flush in this
market. ES now starting to join in for
this move downside. How low can we go?
Can we come down and offer me something
to trade here please?
So into previous day highs. They are
offering bids down at 98.95. So
hopefully we can trade a little bit
lower first in towards this blue block.
Gap fills all the way down here if they
really want to do a gap fill.
Come on. Almost at previous day value
area high. So this is your TP2 if you
took the short.
I'm going to wait to see if we can trap
some sellers now.
They're still being aggressive on the
tape. They're still offering bids down
to 8.90 right now.
So, it is previous day value area high
now tagged coming into my level of
interest. [snorts]
And now it's all about how we act when
we get down here.
VIX going for it. Still at 1624. Still
not fully confirm that breakout yet on
the VIX. Just right into a pivot.
Lots of sellers coming in down here.
Still don't think we've swept enough.
Still think there's one more leg down.
Come on, give a swipe first. Don't go
and drive straight out of the gate. Come
further down.
Buy stepping up here. 940 is the level.
I'd say the big sellers came in at 38.
40s is the level, but I want us to move
lower first. Really, I would write
really like some sort of nice auction
down here where we trap lots near the
lows.
So, I'd be high from yesterday. Not too
far away for a spy either.
Come on. One more leg, please. Come
down. Not playing this short, by the
way. Want to make that clear. I'm
looking to play the long back upside.
All right. Watching these 40s. See
sellers redefend 40s. It's a big level.
We can see them trying to offer at 40
again.
Value area low on the current session is
42. So I guess if we go back inside all
of that. I want to see more excess
though. I'd like to see more sellers
down here. C before I think about this
long. We are starting to build some
volume around here.
So, Meta, Nvidia, Tesla, all gone red.
But we're coming into that level, this
box where I think there's potential for
us to bid on if we can trap sellers. If
we don't, then they're going to come and
reflush down here. And if they let go of
this, then there's definitely a short
all the way down into 725. That was the
level we broke out from. But watching
this level again, they're tapping into
40s again. Watching for a trigger long
if they're going to let this start to
really get going now. 40s, 40s, 40s.
Here we go. They're now rebidding.
Trying to force the squeeze through the
40s in a small piece here.
And we re offer through here and come up
to 55s. Here we go. Starting to join
this for the squeeze. Peeling some off
straight away in case they defend 55s.
Nice.
An imbalance here up to 55. So buyers
now have got to step in and hold 40s.
Here we go. Right. All right, let's see
if we can get up to the New York VWAP
into flow zones. Make sure you pay
yourself. They can come back in and
defend this if it's too early. We
haven't had a pullback that's held yet.
Remember, this is just a straight
squeeze. So,
ES up as well. Nice nice bounce there.
Watching the New York open on ES. If it
trades through that, we'll get a giant
squeeze out. But this is the four the 55
level that we just talked about. Sellers
just reoffered at 55s through this. The
next imbalance is at 62s
and then we're at VW.
Let's go, baby.
Come on.
Get your ass moving.
Imbalance coming up here.
Let's go. Let's go. Little piece left
now. And if we continue to squeeze and
then firm up, I'll start to add. Right.
If we can continue to squeeze and start
to firm up here, I'll start to add.
[snorts]
All right, ES into that New York open
and VWAP. Big levels here, folks. Big
big levels here, folks.
Let's go. Let's go.
Let's go.
All right. All given pre-market.
Remember, this is what we were looking
for. All right. even in uh Discord. The
first thing we're looking for this
pullback here to hold and for that
expansion higher. All right, hold
towards 900s. We got a lower there at
918. Yeah, let's go, baby.
You nice and easy. Two days in a row.
What a gift. What a gift. Right, this
New York open going to be key. [snorts]
Beautiful.
Beautiful. The trap at the low was not
that good, I'll be honest. But that 40
trigger was the key, right? The 40
trigger was the key. Once they got stuck
at 40, that was it. So tiny tiny tiny
size left. Now that's uh 40 50 point
trade there.
Nice. Yeah, let's go. Let's go, guys.
Let's go. Nice trade to start the day.
Remember, we have not held a pullback
yet. I want to be that clear. Be clear.
I don't love the auction at the low.
There wasn't that many call, but a
pullback can come down here and hold. So
if this is just leg one and they want to
do a leg two and then do this, they can
also do that. But so far we look good.
You just hold hold a runner now. Should
be long from this trigger. Selling into
the New York open. No, selling into the
New York open. Have to see if they hold
or not. I will reload if we can get up
here and hold up here. We start to
flip this over otherwise I'll stop out
on these runners.
New York open. Absolutely pivotal. Same
on ES pivotal pivotal area.
Nice guys. Well done everyone. All
right, coming back to down towards this
sort of 40 area.
So we did have sellers uh earlier in the
day, 47 down to 43 and then the next
block was down at 30. So, I'd say 47
down to 43. If buyers absorb that,
they've got a shot. Otherwise, it's
going to be these 30s.
Otherwise, it's going to be the 30s.
ES looks strong here. It's trying to get
through its uh New York Open and V up.
So, let's see if they're going to rebid
this or not.
Let's have a quick look at the MA. So
Tesla half a% down, Nvidia third of a
percent down, Microsoft 1.53% up, Meta
half a% down, Google 0.78% up, Amazon
0.40% up, Apple 2% up. So mixed bag in
the MAG as we approach earning season.
VIX failed that breakout of 25 by the
way, hit a high of 1627, traded right
back inside, back down to PDC now.
Nice, Rob. Great work. All right, we're
still holding these levels where those
sellers got stuck. So, these 43s still
holding where the sellers got stuck. So,
as long as they're holding this bulls
are in control, potentially early in
control for the squeeze back up. Here we
go.
Can they get back through point of
control now for the day 66s? So, we want
to get back through PC, back through
76s, back through the New York high,
rebid over that, and then I'll consider
adding up there for a squeeze. ES now
starting to get through VWAP and New
York open. Want want ENQ to start
joining in. Need Tesla and Meta and
Nvidia to start finding an aggressive
bid here. Here we go. Let's go.
Come on. Let's get back up there.
Here we go.
But I want to leave this point of
control. I don't want to hang around
these 66s too long. I want to move away
from this. Let's get this volume on. Do
it for you guys this morning. I'm sorry.
Here we go. Want to move away from this
point of control. Here we go. Here comes
value area high on the day and VWAP.
Let's go. Let's start being aggressive.
Let's move away from this level, buyers.
Let's go. Let's go. Beautiful. Let's go.
Really nice hold there of this key level
right where those sellers got stuck. So,
we talked about these sellers stuck in
here. All right. Right here against
these 55s. We held it really, really
nice.
[snorts]
Morning, Ken.
Can you buy the flow zones by
themselves? Yes, they're on the
website.com.
All the links are down below.
What is the alltime high of NASDAQ? Uh
48.
Right. Let me just check that on this
new contract as well.
Oh no, new contract. So the new contract
level is 26670.
Yeah, on the current on the NQ 26670
48 would be the adjusted level. That
means
okay sellers coming in there
aggressively defend trying to defend
this New York open. That's your key
level right now. If we start squeezing
through that, the sell is going to get
caught out.
So, still in a rotation of value.
I think we can get going here.
Uh, the lines are the boxes on. I draw
the boxes by themselves, right? But the
all the lines are on there. Everything
else on the screen's on there.
Okay, back into this level again.
ES at its opening range high. Just hit a
new high of day. Trading back inside its
range right now. So, no follow through
yet on ES.
Come on, market. We want to just get
going. Hive day here. Come on. Thank
you. Be kind. Why can't you do what ES
is doing? Let's find that strength.
Let's find that strength.
Just want to get through this New York
open and start squeezing up here. We
can't get through it soon. I will
consider a cut because we're building
out a lot of volume. You can see this
here. Building out lots of volume here.
This is not what we want. We want to do
this and move away from it. All right. I
don't want to get caught in this
rotation here for hours and hours on end
if they're going to be really silly
about it.
Just been doing the section of the 20our
of course where you explain this making
more sense now. Nice. That's awesome.
Glad it's helping. Yeah. News at 10:00.
Thank you guys. Still got 10 minutes for
that.
Yeah. Consumer confidence
previous 89.1 median forecast 90. So,
expecting very similar stuff. Here we
go. Back up now. Can we get going on
this runner? Come on. Let's get up to
high day. ES is going. I' I really want
to get up to high day and then take out
all these stops. I'd love to get up to
basically 26,50.
It's where I'd love to get up to. So, if
we can get this trade to go, which is
what I'm looking to do here. Partial's
on the way, obviously. Where's my long
trigger? Right from 40s, right? If we
can get up to the top side of this box,
it would be fantastic. Partial's on the
way, of course.
We got to get through this value area
high on the session. Let's go. We've got
an imbalance here into 90. Lower time
frame now. Go a little spike into 94.
Let's go. Come on, baby. Let's go.
That's why I said I'm bullish today.
Protrend is bullish. I want to buy dips
off the key levels once sellers get
stuck.
Hey, I love it. I love it. I love it.
Two days in a row. Market being kind. We
love it.
Okay, so into what is this here? Is this
developing profile? Yeah, current week's
developing edge is basically 26,6.
This right here is current week's
developing profile. We want to expand
this. We want to move this blue line
higher with us now, right? And if we
look at the hourlies, you can see why I
was looking at and what I was looking
at. We went over all of this pre-market,
right? We were looking for dips to hold
versus this key level here. Dips to
hold, right? The old naked point of
control, this big bump. All right. And
we're looking to take out these stops
here now. All right. These stops here.
And if we get a squeeze, those will run
us up all the way up to 26,100.
And what's the very top of this? and
we'll just call it 26,150.
So, if we squeeze through 26,50, we've
got another 100 point higher potentially
setting up. Here we go.
How many other channels were telling you
to short this today? I reckon lots of
them.
Here we go, folks. Here we go, folks.
All right. So, you can take partial into
this current New York hive day if you
want if you haven't paid yourself enough
already. My expectation is that we can
move higher hopefully. Well, just
remember we've got that 10:00 print. So,
you will want to move your stop at least
to protect you break even at the very
minimum. Here we go. Let's go. Are we
going to get 112 points here? And if we
can get 112, then you know if we can
squeeze this is possible today, folks.
145 is possible today. if we can get
going. So that's ultimate target.
[snorts]
Can we get long here? No, I would not
advise getting long here. You need now a
breakout and a pullback that holds. You
don't want to you do not want to get
long, right? Think about this move here.
All the dips have held. You don't want
to get long into high of day. Yes,
there's an argument. It will squeeze
higher. But your location there is not
very good for the longs. It's the same
reason I didn't long at the open. We
waited for this, didn't we? I said, I'm
not going to play this short. I'm not
going to play this long. There's a move
down to here, but I'm going to wait for
the long down here. I said to you guys,
if you want to play a short down to
here, that's for you. But I'm going to
try and play the pro trend long. All
right, the protrend long. The easier
move is the long.
Okay, here we go. So, back into where
these buyers got stuck at the beginning
of the day. Want acceptance through high
of day. Now,
come on, guys. You better be smashing
that like button today.
You better be smashing that like button
today and telling all your friends that
this is the stream you watch when you
want to learn how to make money. Tra
[sighs]
GlobeEx hit. We're just looking to run
these stops now. We're just looking to
run these stops up here now.
Let's go. All right. ES hit GlobeEx as
well. Come on. Give me 47s, baby. Let's
get a limit order out there.
Give me 47s, baby.
Another 100 point trade here. Let's go.
We got a little bit of an imbalance. You
want buyers to absorb now into 26,07.
Ideally 26,09 but 26,07
and you know down into this shelf. You
do not want them to let go of the shelf.
Ideally, we just squeeze out and we hit
our target before we get into this 10:00
candle. Here we go. Go, go, go, go, go.
Give me the target before the news and
then we can just hold a tiny piece in
case. Remember, I'm trying to get into
here. Squeeze above this. I will look
for this next red box. Right. We now
want buyers must defend this. We do not
want acceptance under this. We want
this. Ideally, just take this out. Don't
be a dick for a tick, by the way. All
right. If you want to take like most of
your profit here, like 80%, take it off.
And then I'm going to look to see if we
use these stops. If we get all these
stops run, we might get an absurd
squeeze out into here, which would be
fantastic. All right. So, but my stop
now, I will be defending this level
here. I do not want to see 26,7 go. So,
at least move it to 26,000. Here we go.
You you Let's go.
Let's go. Job done. Thanks very much.
Thanks for playing, you [\h__\h] idiots.
Trying to short the lows. You absolute
wallies gifted me the trade today. Let's
go.
Let's go.
Let's go. All right. So, we're in bonus
territory now. If we get up into here,
it's bonus territory. That is absolute
gift if we get up into there.
I know. I know. I know. I know, guys.
This is beautiful, beautiful trade. When
when when the market's operating clean
like this, it's so nice. Protrends are
so nice. I kept telling you guys, when
we're in a range, you think we're
trading well now, wait until we get into
a protrend. And yesterday was the first
day we got protrend on the breakout, and
today we're getting the same kind of
move. So much easier. I cannot tell you
how much easier it is.
So TP's hit. These are your next blocks
now. All right. If we get lucky, uh
26,100 and then up here on the runners
if you've got anything left.
My phone blowing up.
All right, guys. There you go. I love
it. I love it, everyone. Second 1K day
in a row. Nice,
nice, nice. Thanks everyone.
Hopefully you're just learning with me
as well. All right. My my ambition here
is not just for you guys to make money.
I want you to understand how we move and
why we move. All right. That's that's
all that really matters. Even if you
didn't catch this today, you understand
how we move and why we move.
Inside bar trigger. It wasn't really an
inside bar trigger today. um because we
were actually opening up outside, right?
So, it was a continuation. All it was
was,
let me just move this up and try and
manage it if I'm going to teach you. All
right. If you were here the last few
days, you will know that we talked
about,
right? If a daily is starting to do
this,
an hourly is doing this,
and like a five minute or one minute is
doing this, right?
Does that make sense? Right? We were at
this point. We were here today. Right?
So, we were opening up here. The morning
pullback was this. We were looking to
buy this, buy this, buy this. Right? We
wanted this pullback, this pullback to
continue higher. All right? That's what
we were looking to do today off a key
level. All right? So, we had a support
system here to buy off, right? Based on
the previous day, there was a support
system here to buy off based on the
previous day. So, we were playing the
lower time frame. Pull back in, get
long. Let's go. All right. What did that
look like?
If we zoom this out to like an hourly.
Let's draw out what this hourly look
like.
So, where's the pullback long? Here it
is. Where did we get long? After we
confirmed and held that, where are we
looking for? break a structure into
these. Right? It's super simple, right?
We get long here for this move here. If
it didn't hold there, we'd get long
here. If it didn't hold there, we would
have probably got short there and then
got long here for the protrend. But the
protrend, look how we're moving. Doom
doom doom. We're going to expect higher
until it proves otherwise.
Right? So, if they base over this now,
the last chance is a squeeze up. You've
got news coming in here. I would move
your stop nice and tight now if I was
you. You do not want to get wicked out
on news.
We have just had the low hanging fruit.
The only thing left is all the way up
here. Either way, we're locking it in.
Let's go. Come on. Come on. Come on.
Come on. I would love it if the news
just absolutely gives us a 100 point
ripper up to final target.
Love it.
[clears throat]
So, a seller here into 60s. News coming
here, guys, in about 20 seconds. Move
your stop nice and tight. I will tell
you now that a uh big seller came in
earlier at 34s, right? Huge seller at
34s or around here. All right, so we
want to see this protected,
right? You want to see this guy stay
stuck. You want to see that stay stuck.
If he doesn't stay stuck, there's
probably a move down here. Here comes
the news. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go.
Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go.
Let's go. Let's go. Not going to hold
this underneath 34s.
Getting close to stopping out here on
the runner, which is fine.
34s to defend. I can show you this guy
right here. This guy right here. Looking
for this to be defended. 34s.
holding nicely here. This is a good
auction. I will say there are buyers
caught over 53s right now. So, you know,
the rotation can happen between high day
and 35s or 34s if it wants. I will cut
underneath that.
Uh if we can get over 53s definitely and
and then start squeezing through high of
the day, we'll let those buyers out. But
buyers are caught currently from 53 to
high of day. Sellers keep piling in here
at 50s. They're being absorbed every
time there's a dip into 40s right now.
You can see it on the tape. They keep
being absorbed. Here we go. Can we get
acceptance through? Here we go. So,
they're refreshing at 65s through that.
We can go 75s and 80s. Just seeing
what's on the tape here. So far they're
refresh selling into 60s and 65s.
Every time we've dip down into 40s
there's been a buyer stepping up
absorbing the tape right but 34s 35s is
the key level. If I don't see what I
want soon I will just cut the runner's
trying to get aggressive here. They're
really trying to step on the gas and get
this snap.
Still a buyer sat here at 47s.
Here we go. Come on. Come on. Come on.
Come on. Let's get all the way up there
for the runner. Come on.
Refresh. Selling up here again into 65s.
Oh, thank you for the super chat. Very
kind of you. Very kind of you. Thank you
very much.
If YM is red and ES is fully green, does
that mean could be high taken? I don't I
don't understand what you're what you're
saying there, my friend. Could be high
taken. What do you mean? It just mean
we're seeing a rotation, right? I said I
said it a few days ago, right? November,
December, early Jan, we were rotating
out of the MAG and we're rotating into
broader markets because we've been very
narrow. We've gone to broader markets.
In the last few weeks, you've seen the
rotation back out of the RTY and back
into some of the MAG. Why? Because we've
got earnings this week. So, they're
putting some risk on into earnings.
They're positioning themselves into
earnings in case we have blowout
earnings. Because if we do have blowout
earnings, then there's a good chance NQ
will take out this pivot of 26,150
140 and come all the way up. Remember,
the other thing to consider is that gap
fill on QQQ. We went over it pre-market
this morning. All right? Even if we're
just going to be an efficient market and
fail, there's a reason for the market to
try and come up to 32 to fill this old
gap dating back to the 5th of November.
Maybe the market then fails there. Maybe
it's just trying to be efficient and we
get an alltime fail, a huge stop hunt,
fill the gap and fail. I don't know. But
all I do know is we are positioned long
for this move to here because that's
what we expect right now to happen. It
doesn't matter anything beyond that.
like
you know don't get caught sort of
bitching and moaning about it's doing
this because of this. It doesn't matter
what it's doing. Your job is to make
money. All right? So understand what it
is doing and join for that move. Don't
worry about anything beyond that.
Is it just me or does the market seem a
completely different person since the
new year? It's not it's a different
person this just that you're seeing
rotation back into tech into in in front
of earning season, right? That's all it
is. Hi from Switzerland. Hey, how's it
going?
Just bought your course. Looking forward
to learning more. I just found your live
stream and I feel like I'm drinking from
a fire hose, but I'm loving it. Thanks
for joining.
Good night from Asia. Night, night,
night. All right, ES pulling back. I'm
getting ready to stop out the runner
here, folks. If we can't absorb in front
of 34s, I'm going to stop out of the
runner.
900 watching over only 300 likes. Come
on, folks. We've just hit a 100 point
banger again or over 100 points. If you
took the high 125 point banger again,
this is what three or four days in a
row.
About to stop out here. This is where
the seller came flying in at 34. So, if
we don't absorb here, I'm out. Very,
very, very close to knocking me out
here. Literally a tick away. I'm out.
There we go. Out on the runner. Can
always join back in. All right. So,
great trade there.
This was our main target. Remember, this
was just a runner target. Main target
was right here. top of the red box and
we're starting to see this trade back
inside now and they can come all the way
down to these 26,000s if they want. All
right, so we can get rid of these
because these are stops now and we can
put some volume in here of what we'll be
looking at. So we can have this right
here. I will tell you in this block
here, buyers are caught over 55s. All
right, so sellers can defend all the way
up to 55s right now. All right. So,
sellers, if they're going to look for a
rotation, they will want to defend in
front of 55 for this move down here.
Buyers will want to absorb this big fat
block here. Remember when we were here,
I said, "Come on, I don't want to be
here too long because in here, we can do
this." But again, what have we done
today? Lowhanging fruit. Boom. Boom.
Just like yesterday, low hanging fruit
trade.
Money's made, right? Most of you should
have made your money. And we can see
what else we set up with now.
only verbal abuse because that's what
he's into. I don't know talking about
Alex, you showed the trapped sellers
when they entered the trade. I think you
mentioned that it didn't look great, but
it was good enough. What was the trigger
at 40? The 40 was the trigger because
that's where the uh sellers were caught,
right? So if you if you look down there
at the time, we had a big big selling
coming in underneath. Well, at the time
it was like 30 and under was big
selling. In fact, let me just get you on
here and then just show you.
All right, this right here, right, this
was the aggressive selling delta
all here.
The reason I didn't like the low of day
was I would have rather this been sell
as well with a passive buyer rather than
just a turnaround. But you know they
obviously got caught. So if we look at
here 40s right all of this most of this
is sell volume under here. We're
absorbing the tape once we broke over
and held. That was your confirmation as
well. Selling here got caught again at
the low of this candle. So trap sellers
here. some trap sellers here trying to
force that rotation back down in and
then we trade away from it. All right,
we're coming right back up to those 53s
that we just talked about.
All right, this imbalance, you can see
where they stepped in 53s. There you go.
We just talked about it. So, here's your
sell side imbalance into here. Sellers
will want to defend 53s. If they fail to
defend 53s, all right, then this is
possible up to the 26,000 and 26,045s,
is it? or 49s, can't remember. I'm going
to have to look on the other chart.
Right. So, sellers will want to defend
this area here. If we make that make
sense with volume, the gray box, right?
Sellers will want to defend up to 53s.
We can do it here. There you go. Up to
53. Sellers must defend this. If they
fail to defend that, there's a bigger
squeeze for 26,100,
26,45s.
All right.
Do you anchor your volume profile to
9:30 every day or just let it rip? So 9
9:30 each day for the current developing
profile and then for the daily
developing profile and then I do the
Sunday open uh each week for the weekly
developing profile. So if you have a
look right now,
here we go. Squeeze is on here folks. If
you have a look right now, right, this
is your probably should have traded off
that. I've only just noticed that. That
is my bad. This is the current
developing weekly profile, right? And
we've just held that dip into the weekly
profile value area high. So, they're
trying to come into here now. Probably
should have just added in that. That is
actually pretty poor for me. I didn't
notice it until just now. Anyways, is
what it is. So, they're trying to Now we
we got to be careful because you're in
three drives here. One, two, three. So,
at some point you might see that repull
down again, but these these are the
targets now. Red boxes are the targets.
Here's the resqueeze. Here we go. All
right. So, it's on. It's on like Donkey
Kong today. It's on like Donkey Kong.
It is on like Donkey Kong. Yeah, you
could have gone long down here in the
flow zones. You could have gone long on
the reclaim. If they especially if they
hold now if they now hold this level I
think they're just going to squeeze this
high now. Every the shorts are so caught
here. They're trying to fight the tape.
[snorts]
This is the best process focus stream
I've landed on today. Thanks again. Oh,
thanks for joining. Thanks for the kind
words. Alex, is there a way to recognize
trap participants on a candle chart or
does that require reading of the
footprint? Yeah, not really. um Rome
very hard to see that on a candle chart
because you don't have the information
within it. Um so you can understand that
like we pivot over this you can make the
assumption but you can't see the
specific levels within it right so but
like candles are still useful but you
just can't see the specific levels you
see a lot of sellers stepping up here 75
80 85s you can see it on bookmap above
me right now all right lots of sellers
trying to defend this area right right
here you can see it but we if we keep
adding liquidity let's have a look above
if we're into key levels yet they're
still up there let's see if there's
anyone at 145 5s there is right 135 145
even above. So we're trying to drive
higher today but you can see these
sellers here starting to stack up. So
next push into there you probably
wouldn't be a bad idea to take profit if
you just retook this long. Not all of it
but like lock some in. I'm not in this
anymore folks. Like I said if this dip
holds you could argue there's a reason
to get long here if this dip holds. But
we are we would be buying very very high
in premium now.
bit like yesterday if you remember
yesterday. Same kind of story.
Um,
it's all right. It's all right.
There's another naked PC. Is there on
ES710? Okay, that's good to know.
Thanks, mate. I haven't got that marked
out. Nice one. Good. Good eyes. Good
eyes.
What time frame is the footprint chart?
I normally use a one and a five minute
and occasionally I'll look at a three
minute or sometimes I even look at a
daily for the day before just to look
there was a big area.
What's my opinion on Friday's potential
shutdown? I don't have an opinion on
stuff like that. Like
who knows? Who knows? I I hope they
don't. I really hope they don't because,
you know, I don't want to go another
three months with them cooking the books
and putting out [\h__\h] data. It just
doesn't help us trade. We're going to be
in a volatile environment enough as it
is. We could do with uh some data
points.
I did not enjoy the government shutdown
last year, losing all the data points.
It's just got ridiculous. And then them
coming out afterwards saying we're not
going to go back and give you half the
information you required. You know, I
think it's less than ideal. But look, we
will just see. We don't know what
they're going to do, right? Let's just
deal with it when it happens. We don't
want to speculate.
So, over half of you still not smashed
that like button. Let's smash that like
button. We can do some giveaways today.
Again, I'll give away some Apex stuff.
All right. Still holding this point of
control starting to move up. Dip still
holding here. There's an argument for
this to trade higher. Like if you're
already in this and you're adding
probably and didn't cut where I cut on
this drop, makes sense to be uh firming
up here for an ad. But otherwise, I'd be
very very very careful starting a fresh
money position up here.
Best type of plan for bookm
the cheap one is um global global plus I
think it is for futures. Global plus
just make sure you've got data. Um,
yeah. But go global plus I think is is
all what all you need.
Can you please let me know how I can
learn everything you've taught this
morning? Uh, yes. Well, start on my
YouTube. There's a lot of free stuff on
my YouTube, right? not everything, but
there's a lot of good content there on
YouTube, like key levels and initial
balance trades and all those all that
good stuff. Start on there and if you
like how I teach and you're starting to
absorb it, then you can go on my website
and there's a 20our course on there that
you can do and with that you get Discord
as well. Comes for free for life. So,
onetime fee. I think it's if they've
updated it, it's $699. If they haven't,
it's $649. And then if you like the
volume and orderflow uh course, you can
do that as an add-on. So it's it's all
on my website. Every everything's there.
But like make sure you like how I teach.
It's really important you like how I
teach.
There are people that live stream book
on YouTube. I know there's a bit of a
delay, but it's still helpful. Yeah, for
sure. Like if you can get it for free,
um it's not as accurate. You can't zoom
in and zoom out, but if you're just
looking for the levels of where passive
participants are, it can be very useful,
especially if you're just starting to
learn.
Weeble just added a footprint feature on
desktop app. Oh, nice.
Yeah, I think I still like Weeble. Like
I want to buy them cheap. I think uh
there's an argument to buy them.
Currently trading at 762s today. I've
always got them on my watch list.
All right, still holding here. There is
still an argument for this to base and
go higher. All right. So 26,100 26,55.
So again, I'm not buying up here. I'm
out of position now. We we got this long
from down here to here. We just wait now
and see.
But if if you're if you're interested,
there's an argument to take here. I
would just be somewhat cautious. If we
lose this gray box, right? If we lose
this gray box, this is where all the
volume will come in. And you'll see this
probably into low volume node. And if
they really want to pivot down into
these, they will these shelves down
here. So, this is why you got to be very
careful. If they lose this, there's a
quite a nasty drop in it. But so far,
they've done it once, they've reclaimed.
Momentum is still bullish. Flow zones
are still supporting. I am not going to
get long now. We've hit my targets. I
will need uh need to see a lot of
participants trapped to convince me to
get long. Now, VIX getting absolutely
crushed. So, remember 1625 we said was
the pivot pivot for VIX to break above
and hold. This is why it's so important
you understand all these key pivots.
1625, we went over this in the
pre-market right here. Look what
happened once we got through it. All we
did was sweep it and then get completely
crushed. All right, this is helping the
market go risk on. All right, risk on
when we do this on the VIX, right?
Helping the market go risk on.
just passed 10 Apex evaluation accounts
only trading live with you for less than
10 days. Thank you so look how kind you
are. 50 bucks. That's very kind of you.
Thank you very much. I really appreciate
that. I'm glad that my teachings are
helping you. It's fantastic.
Fantastic. Still holding here. Still got
a chance. Still holding here. Still got
a chance. When you say passive but it's
seller in the market, is that watching
put map? Yeah, exactly. or you can watch
the DOM. Either way,
chance of a resqueeze here, especially
if ES can catch a bid.
And just be careful because we are in
this is obviously the third drive on the
hourly. Doesn't mean it can't go higher,
but we just want to be a little bit
careful here.
Yeah. So passive seller, it's like it's
just these guys above above me. You see
the horizontal lines,
right? These are limit orders. If you
see horizontal lines, the limit orders.
Bubbles, these are market orders. This
is delta, right? So bubbles are are
delta.
The horizontal lines are limit orders.
The bigger and darker the line, the
bigger the size. You can see the size
down here on the current order book.
Right. And this is just my profile for
the day.
Oh, I've got you on the wrong one. Here
we go. There we go. All right. So, these
are the passive sellers. See how we keep
coming up? The passive sellers here and
passive buyers down here. Well, he keeps
coming on and off and on and off. And
the blue is also passive participants,
right? So, anything horizontal is
passive. The darker the color, the more
size. You can see they're adding
liquidity. Someone's trying to drag the
market higher. So, you can see he came
in at 70, then 75, then moved to 80.
He's trying to attract the market to
come higher at the moment. And we had a
spoofer up here at 95. So this guy at 95
has moved down to 85. You can see he
came off the book and a couple seconds
later came on the book at 85. So he was
hoping to get filled at 95. He's lost a
bit of confidence. He's now looking to
get filled at 95. Same with this guy
here. He's hoping to get filled at 80.
You can see he's moved down. Same size
now. Come on the book here. Just over
70. Is he? Where is he? Like 71
72s.
>> [snorts]
>> I was under the impression that ESNQ YM
kind of follow each other. Why is YM
continuing to dump while ES is pumping?
It will be because a sector that is in
YM is weaker. You got to remember ENQ is
techbased.
All right, and is only 100 uh stocks. So
if we have a look in here
right this is the breadth of the market
today all the sectors we should say
right so if we look at these sectors
what is what is heavy in NQ Microsoft
Nvidia AVGO MU INTC all of these green
ones down here Apple all of these all
right strong Oracle the only one weak
one in ENQ Google looking good Amazon
looking good guess what's not in NQ
which is elsewhere financials and
healthcare I talked about it this
morning be careful with healthare The
sector ES will probably lag because of
UNH. U unh down like pretty
significantly right now uh off earnings
yesterday. 19 almost 20% down on the
day. All right. So healthcare and
finances lagging behind. Let's zoom this
in.
Fin viz website is quite buggy.
It's not going to let me move it. This
is like the other day. Oh no.
Let that catch up. Finn viz website. My
uh server does not like it. All right,
here's the move to 75s.
So maybe the resqueeze here. Still
passive seller there on the book at 75s.
Where's that website gone? Here we go.
Let's just zoom this in.
I'll move this uh website on the other
screen. It's stuck on my screen.
There we go. Right. So, this is why ES
is lagging. Finance, healthcare, right?
Finance and healthcare. This is why ENQ
is pushing tech. Right. think about
this is how prepared we were for it this
morning folks.
Uh
tech strong again today healthcare weak
so might drag es that was at 5:23 this
morning I told everyone that. All right
so it's just understanding how and why
the markets move [snorts]
on bookmap. How do you tell someone's a
buyer or seller? Uh, well, if they're
above you, if they're above price,
they're a seller. And if they're below
price, they're a buyer because you it
means they're a limit order on the book.
And you can only put a limit order on
the book that way.
How do you know if the same player
pulling re-entering? It is an
assumption, but you can kind of see it
because they come off and they come on
back on at another level with the same
size, right? So, it's like jostling of
size. So, if I show you
here, right? If you see this player
here, he comes off and he comes back on.
So, he's like 15 lot here or something
and he comes back on here with like a 15
lot. There you go. So, he comes off for
like a couple seconds, he comes back on,
he gets filled here, right? So, these
sellers are holding price down at 75. We
talked about this and now you're
starting to get the break below here.
You need to be very careful here. Now,
this is where the sellers need to now
defend. They keep coming in. They're now
attempting to defend it. This is the
gray box and they want to see a break
away from this level. This is where they
came in earlier. So, if we make that
make sense on here, this is where
sellers came in earlier. Remember the
53s? They got stuck. We dipped below,
they got squeezed out. They will try and
get under this again to get this move.
Buyers will just keep wanting to absorb
this. The more sellers that get stuck
here without this, the more squeeze
potential this market gets.
How do you see weights price come down
this morning instead they pull up price
yesterday openings pull up I don't I'm
not sure what you're saying there um
Moni maybe try type that again for me
I'm not I'm not sure what the question
is how much credence do you give to
historical daily levels 26120 looks like
a big daily wick top from some days back
in December found you a couple weak So
go learning tons. Um I give a lot a huge
amount especially for the higher time
frame levels. Right? So the high
remember today why were we long the last
few days. Right? Even if we start off
right these levels here are massive
aren't they? Right? Why are they
massive? Swing shorts. All right. Swing
short. Swing short. Swing short. Swing
short. Swing short. All right. If swing
shorts get stopped out, what do they
become? market buyers. Oh, can't draw an
M now. Right, they become a market
buyer. Right, if a swing short stops
out, they become a market buyer. What
happens when they market buy? Well, we
get increased energy upside. All right,
it's not to say that we don't do that
and then institutions sell that. All
right, use the market buyers to sell
into and rotate back down. But we we're
not going to be the guys picking the
top. We let the institutions do that. If
they want to do that move there, we're
joining it after a failed breakout.
Well, right now what we know is that we
ran stops down here. We reclaimed this
week. We reclaimed SMAs. We are heading
for these stops. All right? And if they
get above and base and we are going to
go because we've got a huge amount. We
talked about it yesterday. Think about
this market as boxed in basically in
let's just call it here. All right?
We're boxed in in there or certainly to
here. All right. Since November. Look
below, fail, reclaim. Look below, fail,
reclaim. top side, bottom side, top
side. If we break out over here,
everyone who's short in here is going to
get stuck, which means we are likely to
get some upside energy. Now, the only
way that will fail is if institutional
sellers, right, position, let's say we
have all three months worth of energy go
buy side on a stopout. Let's just say
that happens. If there is huge selling,
they will pair off against that and
that's when you will get like huge
aggressive buys and and price not move
higher and then and only then will we
get this move here. But if that doesn't
happen then we are likely to just
continue this right main trend.
Those are the opportunities in the
market. But yeah, I I watch these. These
are very important. That's why we've got
the red box. You can see the red box is
right to the high of these. very very
important how we act in them.
Probably the most important thing daily
levels. All right, back to the bottom of
the gray box. Sellers still trying to
defend these 53s. You can see it's a
huge huge level. Let's have a little
zoom in into this. So, they've defended
it again here. You can see they've come
in flying again here. They just want to
keep this heavy and if they can start to
pivot underneath this, they've got some
uh buy side imbalances to clean up. If
we start reclaiming, then obviously
squeeze is on. So, I'm leaving this
alone right now. Like I said, I don't
want to buy in premium. We got to We had
to buy in premium today anyway, but we
bought as close as close to yesterday's
uh fair fair value as possible.
Remember, this is yesterday's fair
value.
This is yesterday's premium, and this
would be overnight discount. So, we
bought as cheap as we could today to get
up into here. But I don't really want to
buy expensive to sell more expensive if
I can avoid it.
This was the trade today.
[snorts]
Will you consider short down to 40s? Uh,
what are you saying? Down to 40s. If it
comes down to 40s, um,
I'm not,
but this
is a valid trade.
All right. If you move away and you fail
to reclaim and buyers get stuck in
there, that is a valid trade or at least
into this pivot here. But just remember,
right, we are bullish in momentum. That
can be a counter trend that is scooped
again to go higher, right?
Anyone who joined me yesterday will know
like I I avoided that same kind of trade
yesterday.
The heat map on Trading View accurate. I
could not tell you, Rick, I've never
used it, my friend. Never ever used it.
Uh, my the way I have footprint is I
only care about Delta is how I have all
my footprints set up.
Apex just released a 90% sale, did they
really? They didn't tell me. Well, there
you go everywhere. 90% sale. Apex, you
can use code FCT right now if you want
to get a sale on.
Good chance to get all your accounts if
that's the case.
looking for a reaction down from uh
point of control at 710. So you're
you're looking for that naked PC trade
down. It's already coming down into that
VWOP now. So you got GloEx taken and
then it can't get back up there at the
moment.
What future NASDAQ you trading? I'm
trading NASDAQ futures like NQ contract.
No discount on the course. Sorry. We
just did a big big discount all through
november and December. There's no
discount at the moment. I'm sorry.
Two-leg move down is most of the time
they do or even three leg down as
possible. Yeah, they can do multiple
legs, but two leg is a very common
trade.
If you think about it as well, when we
think about
trading markets, right, we want one of
the first two pullbacks, right? These
are these are very probable. Once we get
to here, this can happen very often,
right? So, you want to be looking for
the first and second leg on the
pullback. They're the safest entries.
First and second, the third leg, but
they don't get anywhere with it even on
a lower time frame. Doesn't mean it
can't, but the first and second leg are
like the main parts of the wave. Even on
higher time frame, the same thing. It's
why we had to be a little bit careful.
You could argue the breakout was
yesterday. Yesterday's pullback or
overnight pullback was the first leg.
Today's pullback was the second leg this
morning on an hourly chart after the
breakout. So, the next pullback you kind
of need to be careful.
Would you use zero DTE call options for
the move we took? No, I don't trade
options.
Can you explain when green bubbles in
bookmap become misleading due to stops
and take profits? How to recognize them?
Misleading? I don't think they're
misleading. It's just understanding what
they are. If there's a big what you
don't want to assume, right? If there's
a big green bubble, all that means is
there's a lot lot of market buying
activity. What matters is what happens,
right? So, if we've got a lot of market
buying activity, it means there's a
passive seller the other side. If price
doesn't move higher, it means that big
buyer just got caught and price will
move lower away from his price. Right?
It's always it trading is about the
reaction. Whether you're looking at a
key level, whether you're looking at
delta, it's about noticing something but
then going, okay, so what's happening
now? What's the story? So, if we look at
bookmap right now, what's the story
right now?
Where are you guys? Right, we've just
talked about all these sellers keep
trying to get the force away, force
away, force away. This big buyer comes
in 154 lot. He gets caught. He gets
forced to stop out. We drop down. We
absorb 40 again. 40 was the level I gave
you all morning. Right? That was my
stopout was 34s and 40s. We're now
reclaiming. This seller is now caught.
We're going to try and take out this
pivot and come up to these highs into
this limit order of 75. If we break 75,
what's going to happen? probably some
con kind of squeeze because oh that's
not the line I wanted because we have
right the top of the auction here
sellers will try and defend this so if
we get over this level you will probably
see a squeeze out and search for
liquidity up to 100 probably all right
so it's it's about telling the story
who's involved so we just had lots of
market buying activity here price at the
moment is not moving higher so we know
passive selling keeps happening at
around these 65 levels Okay, so these
guys here are still defending. Do I have
an arrow line here? I don't know if I
do. These guys here are still trying to
redefend price here. And if they get
squeezed out, we will probably lift and
come up to 75s.
Right. Other thing we should note now
folks is you are now inside your initial
balance. You can see this uh shelf is
getting thicker and thicker and thicker
and thicker. This is your sentiment for
the day is this shelf right here. All
right. So price starts to move away from
here. We talked about you might get a
squeeze out.
Can you quickly go over your settings
for AP once more? Yep. Just here.
Row layout ticks per row. I have it set
to two. If you want to do number of
rows, I would do this to 1,00. Right?
And then it will look like that. Right?
So either way, however you want to do
it, either work. I've just been doing
ticks per row. This matches my
footprint. That's why I have it like
this. Right? And then I have it. The
only other thing I change.
Everything else stays the same. I just
have it moved to the right hand side.
Where's that input?
Can't even see it now. Placement.
Placement. Right. That's the only other
thing I changed. And then I just have
point of control up and down volume gray
and value area blue. Right. Here comes
IB high. So the squeeze is on. They're
coming back to those 75s. We just talked
about this on bookmap. So if we think
about what we just went over, if sellers
can't defend here and we get the squeeze
out, we'll revisit this up here. And we
should now squeeze through and come and
clean out all this liquidity which is
being added above into 85 and possibly
up into these hundreds. This is where
sellers are sitting looking to get
filled. So these are probably buyers to
be honest just looking to fill and uh
take some profits on this squeeze up.
So gray box defended and here's the
squeeze up. So here's your initial
balance high. Yes, trying to join in.
So, here we go. Here's 75s.
So, they've just taken a load of stops
here. And the question is, can they lift
this any higher now?
Is there a lift any higher?
And through 85s and 90s, and then you're
looking for 100. And then 100 is the red
box. Yeah. And then through 100, 150.
All the stops, the last lot of stops are
at 145. I think it actually is.
It's trying to get through that or
trying to approach that high of day. Um
I forget your name, but one of you
pointed out there's a naked point of
control at 70.10. So it's worth watching
that. You still have gap fill potential.
Remember spy trying to fill that gap up
to 696.
So spy is trying to fill a gap up to 696
and Q's are trying to fill a gap up to
632s. Right? If we're going to do that
today, it's a big if, but if we're going
to do that today,
Tyson's just absolutely on a heater
right now. Just locked in another $4,000
today. Nice work, buddy.
Here we go. So, squeeze is on. So, let's
see if we can lift out to the hundreds
and then if we get through hundreds,
150.
So, this is your target here. If we can
get up to the hundreds, then 150. I've
got my eyes on the ETFs as well for you
guys. Uh, you're getting very close to
that naked point of control on ES that
one of you pointed out. You were just
three ticks away there. So, maybe some
resistance there on ES. Worth noting.
So let's see what if we go back to boot
map so you can see what we were looking
at.
Defended traded through sellers came in
got absorbed at that same level this
horizontal level and we will will now
try and lift up. So sellers are out of
money. All right. All the time we're
above this 75s, they're out of the
money. And the targets here are 100.
Let's see if anyone's on the tape at
145. Yeah, 125 and 150. There you go.
145, 150. So they're looking at the same
targets as me, these guys on the book.
So all the time we're above 75s. Now you
actually want to see buyers just come in
here and just defend this. You don't I I
wouldn't want to see this roll back down
to 60s. If I if I was long, I'm not
long. I'd want to see sort of 70s 75s
defended for a resqueeze
because it's also your initial balance
area, right? So, you got to be careful.
Do I have experience people getting
banned buying Apex Ess? Uh, they will I
think they'll let you trade again. It
normally takes like three months or
something, but I mean if they've done
that, don't worry about it. Don't buy
anymore. There's plenty of firms out
there. So, just use it should mean that
you've got lots of PAS in the money. So,
just lock those in and then uh use some
other props if you need.
What are my indicators? Uh anchored
volume profile and my flow zones. So,
this is all one indicator,
my custom indicator.
So, dip still holding hundreds not far
away.
Uh for me, Nick, the dailies and
weeklies, uh only because I'm a day
trader of this stuff, but I'm I'm sure
the uh I do use a yearly in fairness. Um
I don't really check the monthly. Here
we go, folks. Here comes the 100. So,
here comes the 100. Congrats if you're
in this. You should get up towards these
hundreds
and then through that 150s. And look at
VIX trading downside now approaching its
previous day low.
Says your naked point control now has
been hit on ES. So really you're talking
about can we get through that spy gap
fill remember is up to 96es. So you're
almost there on spy. You need 40 cents
more on spy.
No, I'm not. I'm not in on it. I'm not.
Probably could have traded it from here,
but like I said, hit my low hanging
fruit. Stopped out on this. It's a shame
I stopped out on that. I wanted it to
defend. Was it 35? So, ran me out there.
Um, but it's okay. It's recovered. Maybe
could have re-entered here. Just simple,
isn't it? Like it held gray box.
I would imagine if I have a look at this
candle here, what time is that? 10:30. I
imagine there's some sellers trapped
around there.
10:30. Yep, there you go. Sell is
trapped at the low right there. All
right, there's your pivot and there's
your go and 100 and then 145s is your
target.
[snorts]
You'd want this to hold at IB certainly
to hold the top of that gray box if you
were long. Remember, if you've bought
this, you are buying premium to sell
premium. You're not buying discount.
Now,
what do I anchor anchor volume profile
to? 930 opening print.
Here they go. They're going to try and
lift this. Can they get up to the
hundreds? Here they go. They're stacking
100 now. So, 90 95 100 105 110.
Naked point of control. Just an untested
level, a fresh level.
Yeah, it's definitely stuck there at
that 10. It's tapped it now. No
acceptance through it.
>> [snorts]
>> Sorry guys, it slowed down a bit. So,
you know,
can't do much. Just calling what I can
see at the moment.
And they lift this. I think you're going
to get it. They're now adding liquidity
higher at 115. I think you're going to
get it, folks.
Just don't be too aggressive at the
highs though. Just manage your position.
Your trade to downside. If you are
adamant on trading downside, I would I
would say you need to leave this volume
shelf. I would not be thinking short,
right, until you get under here. That's
your short. I really would not be
thinking short above that unless we like
come up here, spike, leave volume
trapped here. Right? If we have
something like this,
right, then maybe there's a short from
here to here and the rotation would be
there. And then if you found acceptance
lower, there'd be an add-on. But
otherwise, do not fight this tape, guys.
Please don't fight the tape.
There's nothing in here. Look, we've
been in a buy. Blow zones are up. We've
got targets above, right? Do not fight
the tape.
my footprint settings for Trading View.
They're all in a video on my YouTube. I
posted it maybe last weekend.
Just just go on my YouTube, go to recent
videos. I show you everything in there.
Understand everything beside volume
profile. So, I'll buy the volume profile
course. Thanks so much. Hey, you're
welcome. Look forward to working with
you. Right. Still buyers still trying to
absorb here in front of 75. They're just
looking to get this shove up and fill
all these sellers up into 15s at the
moment. They've got to absorb over 75.
I'd feel somewhat uncomfortable if they
can't do that. Even though there's a
shelf, technically they can hold all the
way down here. You know, if you bought
this break from here, you just want them
to resqueeze this above the IB. You want
them to shove it up. You don't really
want them to collapse back down into
here again.
Like we talked about, you need to be
careful because we're on a three drive
on the hourly and we're also on a three
drive on lower time frame. So if we
think about this lower time frame one,
two, three, if we go to an hourly
since the breakout, we're going to
consider this the breakout.
One, two, three. So you want to be
careful. You want to be careful. Doesn't
mean it can't go higher. It just means
the probability starts to become lower.
Uh, they're rolling fibs.
They're rolling. Rolling fibs. The flow
zones.
Here we go. Here comes your 100. Here
comes your 100. And I would love it if
you get 145 today.
Here you go. Very close. Refresh seller
here. stepping on at 95. He's now been
filled
and now bidding 80s.
Someone's flashing 80s. Fifth time he's
flashed it. Now he's moved up to 91.
Flashing 80s again. Someone's being a
bit of a bit of a you know what. All
right, let's see if we can get through
the hundreds here for you guys. ES now
finding acceptance or trying to find
acceptance over that uh point of
control. Very close to a gap fill here.
Here comes the gap fill on the spy. All
right, spy about to fill its gap. Oh,
it's not a gap fill. Sorry, it's an
alltime high break. My bad. Gap fills on
on QQQ. So gap fill on QQQ is to 31.
Alltime high break is what you're close
to on the spy. My bad. Come on, Alex.
Get with it. Get with it. Here comes the
100. Check. 94s. Trading 94s. One swipe
up and you should get it. It's an 84 lot
sat at 100 looking to be filled.
95s, 96s. Probably a bit of front
running here. And then maybe a little
swipe. 96s. 96s. 97s.
Come on buyers. Go and fill him.
So close. So close to that big guy at
100. He just trimmed some though.
He was thicker and he moved down to sell
some. I think they still get through
him. Here they go. One more attempt.
They should get him. So remember, lots
of stops here in this red box. Uh spy
alltime highs. So ES spy now alltime
highs. Is it ES alltime highs or is it
just spiders? Let me have a look. Uh
yeah, just the spiders.
So new alltime highs for the spiders.
Not on the futures market yet, but on
the spiders, new alltime highs, right?
So options traders comfortably in the in
the money and this thing should keep
lifting.
How are we doing for likes? Can we do
some giveaways yet?
Is [snorts] the pull back towards IB?
And how much short were you of that 100?
97's traded. 9850s.
Ah, what buggers.
What a bunch of buggers.
Come on, guys. Over 800 of you. At one
point we had 900 of you. Only 500 likes.
Get your likes up. And I'm going to get
ready to do an Apex giveaway for you
guys now. Coming into the top of the
hour, we'll do one now at uh when we get
into the next what's this? In 15 minutes
time, we'll do a giveaway.
Rick's just getting absolutely clobbered
now underneath previous days low.
Looking for the next pivot on VIX.
Probably down here into 1563s on the VIX
is the next pivot.
>> [snorts]
>> still looking for it.
So that's where all the sellers stepped
in. 93 to 96 imbalance there. Through
that we can probably squeeze again.
No, I'm not giving away volume and order
flow course, guys. I give you so I know
you guys don't want to spend any money,
but I give so much stuff and edge for
free on live stream. So much stuff.
So much.
I've watched other people's live
streams.
There's not that many I respect. So,
I'm not going to give away all all my
edge in my courses [snorts] for nothing.
[laughter]
What time of tea would I recommend for
better concentration? I I prefer like
stress relief tees than concentration
tees. I don't know. Uh if you want to
know what I have, I just have like a
stress relief tee and I have here's the
pullback into this shelf here. So just
be careful here. Especially if ES
collapses back down under those tens. Uh
is it tens? Yeah, tens and sevens for
the ES.
So flush coming back down to this gray
box. Maybe remember the shorts will
happen. All right. If we lose this,
right, if we lose this area, you want to
be very careful of a fail break like
here. But if we lose this, that can
happen. But we're very bullish overall.
We got so close there. We missed it by
six ticks. They missed the 100 by.
[cough]
Q still haven't filled their gap. The
gap on the cues is still up at 632. So,
we hit a high today of 631.63. Still not
filled the gap. Here's your IB.
Here's the IB.
Do I use ticks for my chart? Uh, no. I
just trade off the minute chart.
Yep. Live stream every day, Monday to
Friday, 9:15 Eastern time. time we do
pre-market prep into the open and then
trade into lunch.
Uh Evan, yeah, I don't when did you win?
If you won recently, it will be uh next
month. If you won like back end of last
year, there's normally like about two
months on them.
[laughter]
Love that comment, Sean.
Nice, man. I'm glad I'm glad we're
aligned. All right, so support systems
down here. Here's your initial balance.
This is the support system. If buyers
lose this support system, then there's
an argument for lower prices. Again, the
big sellers today came in at 47 and at
34. 47 and at 34. Those are the big
levels for um Vpo today is at down at 48
right down here. So how we act in around
this gray box will be will become very
very important
and I would not be back. So remember we
said three drives one two three. So I
said be very cautious trading this third
one. It's the same on the hourly. If we
start to get under here there is an
argument for a backside move. There's
also an argument to do very similar to
what we did yesterday which is just to
trade around a core for a bit. All right
if they want to base up here for a bit
and wait for earnings tomorrow they can
also do that. Here's the gray box tagged
into the top of this shelf.
This is just this volume profile,
anchored volume profile.
It's not an indicator. It's a drawing
tool. It's it's here. Uh yeah, it's just
a drawing tool. So, gray box being
defended so far. Back to IB we go.
They might rotate for a bit here while
they make their minds up of what next.
It's very possible.
Do I think we still get 26,100? It's
possible. It really depends what happens
in and around this core level.
Not like there was a huge amount ex
excess at the high day.
Looks so much like yesterday. It does,
doesn't it? I agree.
It's coming for a back tested previous
day low by the looks of it. Trading
under it.
See if they give one more leg down and
if they scoop it for another go or not.
You got remember they can be done with
it. Like we hit low hanging fruit. My
target was hit here earlier today. Right
here. The runner I got knocked out.
Runner. Next target would have been here
and the final target would have been the
top of this red box. All right, so we
hit low hanging fruit hit runner runner.
You almost hit runner. I mean, you're
six ticks away. Like I always say, don't
be a dick. 40 ticks. Six ticks is
absolutely nothing.
How do I determine the position and size
of the box on the chart?
You see this profile? Where do we get
thick here? So where's the box on that
shelf? Right. Nice hard shelf, right? So
this is where
we have had a lot of volume building
out. So buyers will want to defend this
volume. Sellers will want to get under
and use the volume to go lower. So
that's why the box is this thick. It's
based on the profile.
[snorts]
Nice, Tyson. Great work.
I'm not in a trade. No. No. Haven't been
in a trade since here. Since this. That
was the trade I took. I got knocked out
on the runner
at 35s, I think. Somewhere around here.
Here. I got knocked out on the runner.
Trying to I was trying to hold it for
this move into here. We talked about it
the whole way through the session.
Currently not in a trade.
and five minutes until the new hourly
bar.
We are trading right back down. Right,
the current developing week profile is
down into uh into this level here. It's
right at this PC. This is like a big
level.
If we let go of that, where's this next
shelf on the developing week here? Okay,
if we let go of this, this trade here is
is probable. I don't think I'm going to
play the shorts today, but I'm telling
you now, if we let go of this, a
rotation from 50s basically to 26 flat
is very probable. There's a 50 point
trade there if we do it, if you want it.
I'm not saying you have to take it. It's
the counter trend trade. It's the
hardest trade on the book, right? It's a
counter trend to what's going on, but
it's very probable if we let go of that
shell.
What are the red boxes? Uh supply,
potential supply.
Yeah, just that one trade, mate. That's
all I took.
Yes, volume profile on the right hand
side starts at the 9:30. You have it
anchored to 930.
Can we use high volume nodes as support
and resistance? Yes, you can. You can.
They can act as support down here. You
can also use low volume nodes. By the
way, it can also actually act very nice
if it's like a first dip in especially
if you think about a low volume node as
like an imbalance, right? Let's let's
imagine like we hadn't done backside,
right? And we just had this node here.
Let's imagine this. This dip in here can
be really good because the buyers are
waiting to be picked up.
Not now. Well, it's actually it actually
is a really key level now, but not
because of that. Actually, because of
the higher time frame.
Thanks, Jay. Okay, back to that IB. So,
I would just be careful here if you're a
buyer. If they have failure to follow
through here, it's a big if.
Sellers will try and hold this here or
this rotation like this. This this is a
much safer entry than this here. This
can still absorb off this and try and
complete the rotation. Absolutely can do
that. But you are now in a battle of
premium. Right. This is your battle.
Buy still defending this gray box for
now.
We have a sellside imbalance all the way
up to 87s.
Just zoom this in. Where did those
sellers come in? They came in at 80 and
87s. Yeah. So, sellers will want to
defend 87s. Through 87s, they will start
to get caught potentially.
Take care, Graity. Yeah, it's not been
nice since we broken out. It's been much
nicer since we broken out.
much easier trade setups once we're
outside.
Did ES just hold those tens? It did.
Yes. Just hold that old naked PC. Just
went wick to wick and held. You might
get it here. It might go for you.
You might get a squeeze here. ENQ
is my bread and butter that
much love, Alex. Made 1,000 bucks with
the entry long. Appreciate it. Nice.
Okay, we're coming up to the top of the
hour. So, new hourly bar incoming here
in 5 seconds. I might get a bit of
injection of liquidity into this. Here
we go. See if they do anything with it
like lift it. And they try. They are
trying. And we said imbalance is up to
87s. ES looks like it wants a new high
here. ENQ might very well join and you
might get that 100 now if they can get
through this. You what you will not want
to see as a buyer is it fail this level
here, right? The 87s, right? Because
that will be failure to follow through
and that can lead to this move here.
Here we go. 86 87s. This is testing the
imbalance. we just talked about
right up to here. 87s.
Can they lift through 88s? They can.
They are trying. They want to get to the
100. New alltime highs on uh SPY again.
New high high day breakout
into this imbalance here. Here's the 88.
Can they lift this for a new alltime
high? Can you get any more through here?
So, this is the level that sellers are
trying to defend.
And if they get through here, you'll get
100 and then maybe 150s.
This is a big big level for sellers to
defend here. Huge level. If buyers
cannot get a higher day break here, this
will be a fail failure to follow through
in my mind.
Will I announce when I get in a trade? I
mean,
I I don't know if I could have made it
more obvious today. I told you where I
was looking to buy pre-market. I told
you where sellers were stuck and I told
you through 40s would be a squeeze
trigger. I mean,
there's literally like I'm telling you
when I did it like
there's nothing for me to do up here.
I'm not looking to buy in premium for
the rotation up. It's not a trade that
I'm looking for today. I was looking for
this trade today. That's what I prepared
for. That's what I hit. I would have
loved to been holding a runner for the
continuation. But remember, I bought
today at 29 25,940.
I don't want to be buying all the way up
here. Now,
it's not a trade that I'm looking to
take.
Doesn't mean it can't go higher. It's
just not a trade that I'm looking to
take.
Can I show bookm? Isn't Is it not on me?
You want it bigger, you mean? There you
go.
These same levels of interest, right?
This was the breakout they held. This is
now looking like failure to follow
through. And underneath this will be a
problem if they come underneath that.
back to this like mini shelf here. 70s
again.
I would be very very careful if they
start to rotate this and let go. Very
very very careful here.
Is it a dangerous point here?
It's messy. VIX keeps approaching
previous day low. If VIX starts trading
inside previous day low, we might
struggle for a bigger breakout. If it
keeps rejecting it, might be all right.
Yeah, all the bookmap setups all in the
volume profile course, right? So, volume
profile and order flow course. So, go
over a bookmint volume profiles, how to
trade them, everything's in that course.
Sorry, I wasn't in chat earlier. You
mentioned your play before the open. No,
no play before before. There was no play
before the open. Just the just this
drive. I was saying we talked about why
I was looking for this before the open.
This is what I was planned out for
before the open. Right. So, we talked
about it on stream and
right here. Talked about it right here,
right in Discord. Right. This is what I
was looking for. And possibly later on
in the week, if we can find acceptance
above 26,120, which is what we're trying
to get up into here, above this, maybe
there's a continuation trade.
What did I use for confirmation? Just
the sellers that got trapped at the lows
today. So down here, sellers got trapped
underneath the 40, right? So, they got
trapped.
It wasn't the best. I would have liked a
better a better auction, but you can see
where I've marked it out, right? These
sellers got trapped. There's there's
your 40, right? Big sellers came in.
Delta flipped from negative to positive
and then we held and we held the
pullback. That was another seller got
trapped again here at 45. So, that was a
confirmation.
It's what I always want to see. If if
we're coming into a demand level and
sellers get trapped down there, that's
when I'm like, "Yeah, we're going."
Right. This thing is trying to break
out. It's trying to get up to the 100.
Yes, it's trying to get going
back to that key level again. Can we get
acceptance? You should really squeeze
through the 100 now and start going, but
it's struggling. They keep unloading
inventory up here.
You do not want a failed breakout. If
you're a buyer up here and you do not
want a failed breakout, you want to see
it come and rip through and into this
red box. And if you do that, you might
have some fun here. You might even get
the 50s.
Where am I from? Um, originally from
London, UK.
Here they go. So, they're going to try
again at the hundreds. Is the liquidity
above? Yeah, liquidity stacked all the
way up to 10, 15s, and even 25s now. So
hopefully you get a lift straight
through a nice stop run. Lift you up
into 25s would be fantastic. And
remember, we're watching for gap fill on
QQQ into 32. 632 on QQQ. Here you go.
High day should be coming up here for
you folks. Here's the 100 check. You
should just pop straight through this
and get a nice like shove through it at
this point. Shouldn't
be too hard.
Come on. Give it to the guys and the
gals. Give it to all of them.
You should get it. So much liquidity
resting up here. You should just get a
swipe.
They reloaded 100 again. 100. You should
come and take him out.
Come on.
I think you get it, Serge. I hope you
get it. I I know a lot of you have got a
TP up there. You should get it. There is
liquidity resting above it. It should
come and swipe it all.
It's very very close to doing it now.
Just remember, don't be a dick for a
tick. You You missed it by four ticks
earlier. You should get it now. Here it
comes. Here it comes. 100 lot. 100 lot.
100 lot. 100 lot. 100 lot. I'm just
watching to see if it gets filled. Is it
starting? So, you get very close.
Come on. Put that. Move down. I got to
see you trading 95s. We're so close to
filling him.
They're rebidding at 85s now. You just
want this to squeeze. You don't want it
to stall out and pull back. You just
want to squeeze out at this point.
and rip like another 10 20 points higher
would be nice on the squeeze.
Cannot believe that's it. Come on.
VIX right into previous day low. That's
a big level as well on the VIX right
into PDL.
Need VIX to let go of that and trade
lower and then you'll get more juice.
It's coming, mate. It's coming. Don't
worry. It's coming. It's coming.
It's just going to make it really sweaty
and hard for you. But I think it is. I
think it's coming. I hope it's coming
for you.
[laughter]
It's funny.
They're still stacked there, but you got
liquidity higher.
Just watch the VIX. It's the only thing
I'd say right now. VIX trading right at
previous day low. If it's VIX start
squeeze through that, you might see a
bit of weakness coming to ES, which
would not be ideal for where we are
placed timing wise on MQ.
You were trying to short 630 QQQ.
I mean, yeah, I don't like no reason to.
There was no reason to to be short down
there.
Okay, back down to these imbalances.
Still absorbing. Hopefully
for you guys who are long, you build
some liquidity out in here and you
complete this
and then hopefully
one can hope
you get this move up here.
Buying delta coming in here. You're
looking a bit better. I think it's
coming, guys. You're looking better now.
You're looking better. Some strong
buyers stepping in here. Once you clear
100, there should be like a 10 to 20
point like little ripper.
Here you go. Here you go. Here you go.
Three ticks away. fill them for their
partial. For goodness sake. For goodness
sake.
[laughter]
Oh my god. Three ticks. The edge of the
red box. It's holding up. Well, once you
get through that, we can look up here to
the top side of that red box.
[laughter]
What's the gap on QQQ? Uh 5th of
November. JD, go back to the 5th of
November. And it's like trading at about
around 6:32,
right? So, uh, QQQ
go to a 4 hour.
This right here,
this old close. It's actually a tiny bit
higher.
3209.
3209 up here. That was the close and
we've never filled it to the cash gap
close.
And they are being a [\h__\h] tease, aren't
they?
We want a happy ending here. [laughter]
We don't want some edging. Can we get a
happy ending here for chat, please?
Jeez.
[laughter]
Oh, it's funny.
One last attempt. It's trying again.
It's there. It's It's not even big size
up there to fill. They really shouldn't
be struggling this much. Vic starting to
pull back off the previous day low.
That's what you want to see.
You are one tick away there. You just
traded 99.75. You're a tick away from
filling that guy.
[laughter]
The options on Apple will you'll get the
volatility once the earnings come out.
Is that Wednesday night or Thursday
night? I forget which day Apple is. I
think it's Wednesday. Is it? It used to
be Thursday. Hang on, let me have a
look. I put it in the newsletter. Can't
even remember.
uh
Thursday.
So after close Wednesday,
Microsoft Meta Tesla
after close Thursday,
Apple SanDisk, but Apple's the main one
to be watching.
Forgot after the post today. Anything
important?
Not really anything I'm interested in.
Still holding. Dip. Still holding. Here
they come. One more time for 100. One
more time. They're edging you so hard
today.
It's coming.
Thanks, Super Prime. Appreciate it. I
want to do a giveaway. I forgot. We'll
do a giveaway once we hit the 100. If we
can get 100, we'll do we'll do this Apex
giveaway.
What are my visions for today? Um well,
we've already hit my first target.
Second target is 120. Third target um
go to like a 4 hour or something. Uh
yeah, it will be these up here.
We can put some lines on these.
This block here,
that's what we're looking to trade to.
These are all the stops. So there's one
lot of stops here at 100 and then
through that into 20s then through that
into 30s and then through that into 45s.
Right? These are all stops. All right.
So swing stops are here here and here.
Ultimately here over here. All right. If
we base and hold then over this the rest
of the week we are going to be very very
bullish. If we do a fail breakout and
start losing I mean depends how we build
out profile then we can think about a
rotation later in the week. But this is
where we're trying to get to. If you
read the weekly newsletter, you will
know where we're trying to get to. You
absolutely know already where we're
trying to get to.
This is making it ridiculously hard to
move that extra T. It's only 125 lot.
Getting stuck here. The longer you're
stuck here, the worse it is.
How to use imbalances on the footprint
for your trading? Well, you just got to
think all in imbalance is where is where
we got very we got very very aggressive
very very quickly. So, if we think about
this, right, this big move, it means
there'd be limit orders still sat there
waiting to get filled. So, they got
filled and then we trade higher. So
that's how you would use an imbalance.
I'm just using that as an example
assuming there's an imbalance in there,
right? So they can be areas of
attraction where the market wants to
move to where where they're resting
orders still waiting to get picked up.
Come on, just swipe it. Jeez,
happy ending. Yeah, please. Happy
ending. One tick away again. Did we just
get it? We hit it. Woohoo. Happy ending.
That guy just got taken out.
All right, so you've hit next TP. We
hopefully should squeeze up here to like
15s and above. Here you go. That's what
you're looking for. All right, let's see
if you can get price acceptance over
100. So that's all you're looking for
now. Price acceptance over 100 for a
continuation of a squeeze, but you
should have locked most yours in. So
that's TP2 hit. If you held from this
morning, all right, if you held from
this morning, that was TP1. This is TP2
and this is TP3. Okay, so you've hit
TP2. Now, did any of you hold from that
move this morning? Did any of you get
that?
Any of you still long from this like 140
trigger? 940 trigger. Sorry.
Big trade up over 650. Nice.
Took all at TP1. Yeah, same as me, mate.
Got out and got back in. Nice
profit at TP1 and run. Hey, it's still
still a good day. Still got over 100
points.
So, 120 points was TP1. And this is uh
where would you now have got up to? How
many points is this? There's your 1604
165 point. you get hive there, you'll
get over 200 point trade if you if you
get this move up to the 45s.
All right, so this is how we try and
trade here. I try not to scalp unless
we're in a range. When we're in a range,
I will happily scalp. When we're moving
out of a range, I look to try and hit
those targets.
Yeah, [sighs]
the yen Harry trade is a very
interesting.
It's yet to unfold and it might very
very well unfold.
very possible.
There are some big amber signals
happening in the market right now, but I
don't think we're there yet. But we will
see.
We will see. You're starting to squeeze
now. I'm telling you, watch watch QQQ
into uh 32s, right? It's where Q's is
trying to get to.
Can I review ES? Yeah, you'll be looking
at the same kind of thing, mate.
Right. Squeezing out. Beautiful squeeze
out. What are your targets? Looking
left. You've just taken target one. Your
next target
is probably here. 20s
and 27s and then 36s. All right, that's
it. That's your target. Look at the
[clears throat] expansion.
Where is this low?
Very similar to what we did on ENQ. Same
kind of setup. Buying the dips this
morning.
You're at the 1618. So it's TP1 24s 24s
25s next. So liquidity here 1618 is the
same level as this liquidity here into
sort of 17s big TP here. Next level for
a measured move will be into 24s and
then liquidity sat there at 27s and then
look 2618 is the all-time high. All
right, it is also set up there with
liquidity. So the fibs are matching very
very well with where resting stops are
right now. Very very well.
I mean, what do I know? I I don't know
anything.
I have no idea what I'm doing. It's just
It's just pure luck. I just I just hope.
I come to the market each day. I don't
do any prep. Close my eyes and I just
hope that I get it right.
It's been unfolded. Well, I mean, in
parts of it, you're talking about the
the yen carry. parts of it has, but we
haven't seen the weakness.
Obviously, uh we're seeing it in the
Japanese market.
It's just do we do we start selling in
the US holdings?
Am I from Barlona? Why do I sound like
I'm from Barlona?
I'm not Catalan.
I wish I was. Beautiful part of the
world. Love it there.
Okay, I tell you what. We've hit target.
Let's see how many of you on stream.
We'll do an Apex giveaway. I'll make a
little tea or cup of coffee and then
when I come back, we will announce the
winner. So, how many of you are in here?
Almost at 600 likes. Give me two more
likes and we're going to do this
giveaway.
There we go. Beautiful. Well done,
folks. That wasn't too hard, was it?
AI told me to long hair. [laughter]
It's hilarious.
What copy would would I recommend? Um,
affordable indicators. They're about to
have a sale though, so I would wait a
week if I was you. Okay. Code FCT.
That's your code for uh 90% sale on Apex
and for most the prop firms. All right.
Code FCT. other than uh take profit
trader, you can use code flowzone. Type
it once in chat and when I come back
from making a cup of coffee, we will
announce a winner of a free Apex account
and I'll be right back. Just type it
once, folks. You don't need to spam it.
If you spam it, Nightbot just banned you
and you don't get a chance to win. So,
just type it once and I'll be right
back. Let me get a refill.
All right, let's pull this winner.
Five, four, three, two, and one.
Dead Eyee Dave.
Dead Eye Dave. Are you here? Dead eyee
Dave. What a great name. Fantastic name.
Let me know you're here in chat. Dead
eyee.
Uhoh. Dead eyee. Dave, are you here?
Give you a couple more seconds. You got
to let me know you're here, my friend.
If you're not here, we're going to roll
it.
[laughter]
All you guys hoping he's not here.
I'm going to give you 20 more seconds,
dead eye.
Okay,
just in case he comes back, guys, we're
just going to give him a couple more
seconds.
Okay, we're going to reroll in five,
four, three. You don't need to type it
again. Two, one.
Russian 497.
Are you here? Russian 497.
Yeah, there you go. Russian 497 Windsor
free apex account today. I'm going to
make a note of your name.
If you could please just send me a
screenshot of you logged into your
YouTube so I know it's you
and you send that to
info@flontrader.com.
All right, info@flowzonerader.com.
Starting to see a little bit of weakness
at these highs here, folks. So, still
bullish overall, but definitely seeing
some weakness here as you start to lose
this level. All right, there is
potential for a rotation back down at
some point. I'm not playing shorts
today. I want to make that clear. Right,
so email me info@flzonetrader.com.
Right. Info@flowzentrader.com.
What time frame am I on? This is on a
one minute time frame.
Dave, you were here. Why didn't you
reply? Dave, what happened?
I tell you what, Dave, I'll honor it,
Dave. I will honor it for you. I'm
making a note of your name.
I will honor it for you. Even though you
were you didn't answer. All right. So,
if you do the same thing, just send me a
screenshot of you logged in
to uh info@flowzonerader.com.
You're welcome. No worries.
You're welcome.
What do I think of 26,077
just around the IB? I mean, it's a it's
an interesting level.
It's definitely
a pivot.
The short will come underneath.
We might we can very easily do this for
the rest of the day. Look how we bu
building out volume here. Look how thin
we are under here.
We can easily do this. If we start to
lose that that rotation under can
happen. I certainly don't want to be
long up here.
Certainly not.
But we're starting to see
what was the top of that auction look
like. It was probably quite good, I
would imagine.
It's a pretty good high auction up
there.
Some buyers caught up here.
So, if they can't reclaim that,
just came down to that imbalance. They
can't reclaim that and you start to see
a backside fade
under here is what's gets important.
Until that point, not really, but uh we
will see. You just got to remember if
you're going to try and short today, you
are trying to play the higher time frame
pullback leg. It's the literally the
hardest thing you can do, but it is
potentially going to set up.
Dave paid a sub as well. Yeah. Well,
Dave's winning one. He's winning one.
We we will honor people who are who come
back.
It's the short scenario. Now, it's only
if Yeah. I mean, one thing I would say
is we are running out of room on the
daily, right? Those who have done the
course will understand this.
Look where we are on the daily. Forget
the red box. We're very close to this
top ballinger. There isn't much room
left. Now,
arguably, we can poke outside of it like
we have done down here. Like, this is
quite a big move outside of it.
The best thing that the market could do
would just be to go sideways for a day
or two and let this Ballinger and five
days start to do this and then this can
actually help the market.
We've hit the targets. Look how big
these candles been the last two days.
We've hit our targets. We can come
outside of this. Really fun.
And go I would say go back and uh look
at the newsletter. I think in the
newsletter I would have put all these
key levels in.
See what I get for the bullish scenario
this week in newsletter.
Let's see what Alex said this week for
Bulls.
Bullish scenario from weekly
perspective. Despite value migrating
lower, bears fail to establish sustained
control. Bulls will look to defend
25,700
or quickly reclaim it following downside
flush. The prior weak point of control
25890 remains untested, which is what we
did yesterday. And acceptance above that
level could act as a catalyst for a
squeeze towards 26,000 to 26,100. It's
exactly what we've had. Beyond that that
zone, sustained acceptance and
development of new structure will
provide the foundation for more
meaningful bullish expansion, which is
exactly what I just drew out for you on
the daily. So, it was all there in the
newsletter. It was literally all there.
Anything below 700s which flushes and
reclaims right which was
Mondays
under 700
overnight or Sunday Monday under 700
reclaims is bullish and then you're
looking for a rotation towards 890 which
is what we tried to do
uh on Friday and we did on Monday.
There's the 8.90 take and a hold above
that. We're looking for 26,000. Ding,
ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding,
ding, ding. All right. And then 26,100.
Ding, ding, ding, ding, ding. All right.
So, we've done everything that we look
for on the weekly newsletter. Now, it's
just about acceptance. What do we do?
Literally hit hit those targets nice and
early this week. Beautiful.
Do I trade only on the one minute after
finding high time frame? Yeah, like so I
look at dailies and then hourlies and
then 5 minutes and I execute on the one
minute. Just execution. You don't have
to do that. You can execute on whatever
you're comfortable with. Five minutes
fine.
What setting do I use on Ballinger
bands? Standard settings on dailies.
It's all I'm looking at. Where can you
subscribe to the newsletter? uh it will
be down below or if you click click the
link at the top that's pinned to chat
right click that link that link tree it
will be in there it's completely free
doesn't cost you anything
USA waking up is it
put that in the swings
we put that in the swings this morning
thank you for that had a notification
yet. Want a little bit deeper if I can.
I want it back into a retest of this if
I can.
Would be very greedy. Or at least let me
out.
Getting close to 50. I I'll watch 24s
and 22s. We can get down into there. It'
be really nice.
plenty of time. Don't need to rush that.
I mean, remember, they only announced
the uh government investment yesterday,
Alex, do we have a gray box node up
here? Yeah, one here.
No, just just one. Just one. None. None
overnight. I slept overnight. I missed
all of this which is annoying. Just this
trade. This is it. This is it for me
today, folks. Is all I've taken. Maybe
could have, would have, should have
re-entered here. It's I think I think we
were looking at that and I got caught
teaching. If I can remember correctly. I
think we were looking at this and I got
caught teaching. There was someone in
chat apologized for making me making me
miss it but got it themselves. So So
[laughter]
that one cost me. That one cost me.
Well, I would have got out at 100,
so it cost me another 50 pointer. But
it's like it's all right. These are the
trades we talked about.
Besides being free, it's clean, clear,
the news worth newsletter is worth a
shot. It really includes useful
information. Yeah, it's it's pretty
simple. I just tell you like what
happened in the previous week, news to
be aware of or earnings, anything like
that looking at the week ahead and then
things I'm looking at for the week
ahead. Do I think the rest of the week
with big tech and FOMC market can go
higher? Very possible. It all depends
on, you know, what the earnings are. Is
it already priced in? Are we pushing
because we're pricing it in early? Is it
going to be a sell the news event? I
don't know, folks. I don't know. All I
know is what the market's doing right
now
each day. That's all we can trade.
VIX wants to go 1586s.
I think it already it already did that.
It already retested 5m minutee flow
zones. Uh I see what you mean. You're
looking at that pivot from what 10 1010
this morning.
It's just trading. You got to understand
it's trading around the pivot from uh
yesterday at the moment and it's can't
get acceptance back through previous day
low. If it finds acceptance back through
previous day low for a squeeze back out
on the VIX, then maybe this market would
get weak. But we're not seeing that
right now. We're in a slow, grindy
market. You don't want to fade a slow,
grindy market.
I've heard other traders interested in
longs on MSTR. Let me have a look for
you, JD. MSTR.
Uh, is this the one with the massive
Bitcoin?
This is the one, right? My brain can't
work. This is the one which has a big
Bitcoin holding. Is that right?
Can't even do that pivot properly.
[clears throat]
Yeah. Okay, it is right. Let me do
I mean if they don't get liquidated
weak at the moment
midpoint in this block.
[snorts] It is interesting. It's holding
midpoint of that block. It's very
interesting.
152s.
Yeah. Um I'm not surprised they're
interested in it. It's if a hold of 152s
risking 102s.
Uh, and a reclaim of we go mid to mid.
Yeah, there's a trade here. A 152 to a
384 trade is possible.
It's possible, but it really depends on
BTC. And I'm not convinced
that this thing's out of the woods yet.
This has now turned resistance.
We've only done a single leg.
There has been big institutional buying,
but if we see weakness, step in here,
all right, we've built out a lot of
liquidity now there. If they can't do
this move, there's only one place we're
going, and that is a wash of this. And
that's what would worry me on MSTR is
that if this gets weak,
it's so pinned on uh
if this gets weak, this will do the
same. It'll come for these
into the 100
I don't love exposure to crypto. It's
just me personally, but uh I do have
some exposure, but like not on a I'd
rather trade like wait and and take I
bet when it's ready.
I would still love this into here.
Remember, this is the like 1,00 1,00
1,000 plus day cycle. There's the
pullback we need. We want up to 70% of a
pullback so far of the high we've seen
33. We went up to 70.
And let me check let me check if that's
measured to BTC correctly
up to 70. Oh my gosh, that would be
colossal. I can't see that happening.
Cannot see that happening.
Never know though. What would the
measured move be there?
Oh, it's [\h__\h] possible.
[laughter]
It's possible. I mean, that is an
average move on a sale, 70% which would
take you to the 161. Yeah, that's a
leave alone for me until it pro it's
going to have to reclaim. I'd rather buy
late on a reclaim than anything else.
For me personally,
Riley,
I L Y
that is [\h__\h] thin.
Is that gapping up off some news or is
that had earnings
that I mean there's no volume in this?
What is this?
It looks good.
Very thin though.
I was looking for this gap. Phil, you've
got to trade up to
me. Just clean this up. Make sure there
is a gap.
Yeah, it's look it's looking to trade
into this ledge at 1450s. I'll be
looking for that. I'll be watching
twelves and 1450. Where are you trading
right now? So, yeah, you want to watch
12elves as your next spot. Did it get
stuck there? Yeah, just shy of it. There
you go. So, I'll be watching twelves and
1450s. If you get acceptance over 12,
you're looking for 1450s. Over that,
you're looking for 21s.
But it's very thin. No volume in that in
that name.
and we're stuck. It's literally like
yesterday we we're just stuck. You see
one how important it is to like take
profit when you hit low hanging fruits.
So important.
I joined a ve a very really expensive
Discord back in September that I'm I'm
happy with and one of the trades from
there that I'm in as a call option for
300 on Oracle.
I'm very worried about this. Uh yeah,
you're you're not you're miles out. I
mean,
you're miles out the money.
you you're asking a lot. Uh it's not
going to happen. Uh well, hang on.
When's the expiry? You're on a leap.
18th to the 6th. You basically got until
mid June.
You got to do 65%.
I don't know, man. Uh, that doesn't look
good. I'm going to be honest with you.
Um, I'm interested in Oracle longs, but
yeah, I'm interested in this area here.
If we start to do sideways and we get
shorts get caught and earnings come out
good, I'm interested in a mean reversion
back to 230
and then if we get acceptance, great.
But, uh, yeah, I don't I don't think
you're going to hit that target, mate.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry if someone's got
you into that.
Okay. Starting to leave this gray box.
Sorry. I need to focus in here. You're
starting to potentially leave the gray
box. So, if you're interested in the
counter trend trade is now setting up.
All right. All the time is staying heavy
under here. There's a rotation. Um I
would be watching into sort of 74s and
then 62s
and then 45s. All right. So, if if you
want to play this short, I am not
playing this short because it's counter
trend. If you want to play this mean
reversion short, this was the trigger.
It was the gray box rejection. It is
here.
Not let me put this on for you. It's so
annoying. It is here. All right. To
here, right, that is your TP1. TP2 is
top of gray box. TP3 all the way down
here. This is possible. It is possible
we come down into this area. Definitely
possible. But like I said, this is the
hardest trade in the book. It's a
counter trend trade. It might well do it
for you. So if you're if you've been
waiting for that trade, it's now leaving
that volume for you. So TP1 about to hit
already into IB high, right? So TP1 is
IB high right here.
[snorts]
Remember, you're counter trend. So, you
need to be uh like more aggressive
with your take profit and more
aggressive with like managing the
positions as in like move the stop.
Don't be sitting in something hoping
because if it wants to stop here and go
all the way back up, it will cuz it's a
counter trend trade. We don't know how
far that pullback's going to go.
Uh, a UK. It's just the anchored volume
profile to the 9:30 open.
Took the trade and you're already out.
There you go.
ES single prints and C period.
Uh, I haven't got my TPO on on the ES.
Um,
I'm not going to put it on. Where is it?
Yeah.
All right. So, if they retest this and
stay heavy, there will be a rotation. If
they reclaim this, it will be a trap
like earlier. Remember, overall, you're
bullish. So, be careful with this. But
if they retest this and stay heavy, you
should then try and get down into this
next block down here. This is your TP2.
Okay? So, you basically hit TP1, which
was this purple bar, right? This is your
next one. You do not want a reclaim of
gray box. Gray gray box reclaim will be
squeezed back out. This is why I don't
take these trades. They're counter trend
trades. They're the hardest trade in the
book. Like I said, you got to be very
aggressive with your stop. [snorts] No.
No. I've I've said all day I do I'm not
playing counter trend in the breakout
market. I'm just showing you like what
is possible, but I'm always telling if
I'm if I'm going to take the trade, I'll
make that very clear. I've said the
whole time I'm not playing the counter
trend short.
How to place a trade and trade of a gold
micro. Please give me a quick t
tutorial. I don't trade in trade bait,
but you're going to need to trade MGC
and then
place a trade or buy or sell it,
whatever you're looking to do. But I
don't trade in trader.
So deep pullback flow zones holding IB
holding unfinished business higher. If
they reclaim this,
right, if they reclaim this, they will
use all this liquidity who just joined
in for this break to do this move here.
Remember, we talked about this being an
option if they can't do this.
This is your pivot which created this
high. This is the pullback. They've
rebid it. If they do this, they can
continue higher. Why I'm not fading it.
For me, there's no trade setup. Now, if
I was still in this long from down here
without getting knocked out and small
size, I'd be willing to just sit in this
and try and get all the way up into this
target here at 145s.
Nice, Stephen. Great work. Great work.
The volume node moved up. Um,
not really. Kind of same area. I guess
you could argue it's 96es.
Maybe a little bit here to be fair. Oh,
don't move that one. This one. Maybe a
bit more like this.
ES looks a bit dangerous here to me. VIX
has reclaimed previous day low. Might go
for a little squeeze out on the VIX. If
it does, ES might start dropping. Do we
have unison here with the market? I'll
give you read out on the MAG, by the
way. Tesla 0.06% up. Basically flat on
the day. Nvidia 1.66% up. Microsoft
2.18% up. Meta 0.41% down. Google 0.76%
up. Amazon 1.55% up. Apple 2.17% up.
Come on, Apple, get going. Let's have
some blowout earnings. I'm still
basically all my core positions still
net long in Apple. So hopefully we can
really get going.
Can't get going on my Netflix. Still
down about 7% but squad got a toe wet in
that and that's it.
I'm up on the rest. Apple's up over 20%.
AMD is up over 51% but I'm small size in
that now
unfortunately. Amazon is up 7.65%. Meta
I'm up 7.42%. Open Door I'm holding one
share just for shits and giggles up 189%
on that. Remember I sold most of that
500% up.
Almost [snorts] into lunch folks. We're
almost there. Market is starting to get
a little bit choppy here while it makes
up its decision of what next.
Can I give you a brief overview of how
prop concepts work across multiple firms
and accounts? Yeah, you just use Well,
assuming I would not do it unless you're
profitable, but if you're profitable,
you just use a trade copier. My personal
one I use is affordable indicators. All
right. And then you link them all
together. You take one trade and it
copies across them all. That that's how
you leverage your accounts together.
Hey Canary, how's it going?
Apple bouncing between the the 20 and
100. Let me have a look on the daily
APO.
Yeah, back to the 20day with the gap up.
It needs to break above uh sort of 61s
61 break um but 70 is the big level
right up into 70 50day there big node up
there on Apple but we are bouncing off
that lower Ballinger band so like even
you see how markets like big tech they
respect we respect Ballinger bands can't
trade outside it can't trade below it
back to mean trend down with 5day 5day
day low Ballinger band and almost got
down into the 200 day. No, too low. We
go up into 20-day. If we get acceptance
through this up to 50day and this high
volume node up here and by that point,
this will probably be down there and
then we'll have to do this for a bit and
then see if they open up for
acceleration or if they want to come
back and tag. I'm long from 220, I think
it is. So, I'm long from down
I think it was here or was it August? It
might be 202. I think it's 202s. So, I'm
long from down here, right? And I did
not sell. It's a long-term position. I'm
looking to hold that, hoping for one of
these. We'll see. I might have taken
like a couple
couple of uh profit takes up here, but
my core position is still long. Looking
for that.
Right, rejecting that gray box now.
So, this is your question for you
shorts. Are you going to get that move
down?
Yeah, there's a swing trading channel on
on Discord. I I notified two two things
I'm interested in this morning.
Yeah, if you go if you go to the Discord
right here. So, at the moment, I'm
looking at US and UU
and I've uh put in anything else that
I'm interested in, my core positions,
what I'm looking at. They're always in
there for everyone on Discord.
So, we did very well from that last
year. Our biggest winner was uh was that
um what was it called? One I just called
out open 500 plus% on that. We got last
year on commons not on options on
commons.
Short still valid? I mean
technically it's counter trend.
Technically yes. Like for me it's not a
trade I would take. Technically yes. You
haven't traded the other side of it. But
I would be very very very very very
concerned that we don't lift because
this is your swing low. This is swing
high. This is a pullback which is
holding. But technically if you are
adamant in trading this short all the
time you can reject that. You can be
looking for this move here. It's just
you're running out of time into launch
here. And remember, they've got targets
above. They have targets above. It's you
basically came to TP1. You basically
came to 74 and defended it. So, if we
keep defending the initial balance, then
we're potentially in trend higher,
aren't we? Right. If we keep defending
IB, we're in trend higher scenario. But
there is potential for a deeper
pullback. It's not something I would
play personally, but it's up to you guys
to manage your own positions.
[cough]
So I do Forex, but I'm also looking at
future prop firms. So I want to know
that in Forex there is pips. How can I
calculate pips and futures? Ticks,
they're in ticks. All right. So
depending on what you're trading will
depending how many ticks there are per
point and how many how much that's
worth. Yeah. So in NQ it's four ticks a
point.
Ballinger bands just completely normal
gibberish. There's there's no change on
them. They're standard Ballinger bands
which are two standard deviations away
from a 20-day.
That's all it is. Yeah, just standard
standard Ballinger band on Trading View.
Again, guys, go on my YouTube channel.
All of this is there for free. I I go
through all of this for free on YouTube.
You can have a look.
Yeah, CVD is showing more aggressive
sellers stepping in here for sure. It's
It's trying. We're failing to make Did
CVD make a new high when we made a new
high? No. So, there's passive selling up
here. CVD is telling us that there's
passive selling up here and that
aggressive sellers are trying to step in
here. At the moment, we've not got a
breakdown, though. We're going to need
see absorption versus here which is
here. So this is a very big highly
contested area as we know it's not like
I said it's not a trade I would look to
take. It's just something that might
happen. It might set up.
What does defending initial balance
mean? It means that they're unwilling to
trade under this purple line that they
keep trying to soak this purple line. So
if you get if you're short here, you
need to take profit into this partial
into this because you know it's a key
level. Then here, then here, and then if
you get under this, you've got all these
VWAPs, right? All these VWOPS
might be asking a lot for that. We'll
have to see if the market wants to give
back and take profit into lunch, which
you're now one minute away from.
You showed on YouTube that you can get
orderflow for free. Does it work with
Rhythmic Apex? Uh, no. Not with
Rhythmic. Not that I know of, unless
they offer it. Um, you will need to use
it with uh trade of eight setting.
How do I know where IB is? It's the
highest and the lowest point of the
first hour of trading in New York.
So, the high and low 9:30 to 10:30. So,
here's the short. It is starting to play
out. So again, TP1 will be this purple
line, then the top of the gray box.
So you're coming into purple line here.
So TP1 is here, here or hereabouts, and
underneath that gray box.
So this is second trade starting to
potentially play out, but you must
respect this level here.
I just delete that. There's your TP1.
All right. And your TP2 is here.
Is this developing profile as well? Yes,
it is. So blue line and gray box very
very key. This is TP2. I would not have
expectations below that. If you get very
lucky, you will come down. We have a low
volume node down here. If you got very
very very lucky today, you would get
this move here. But I think it's more
likely that they just try and trap
and keep you locked in in between here
and here. All right. And the rotation
might happen here for the afternoon. You
can see volume being built out.
So TP2 is here. You've basically hit
TP1. I'm going to consider that you've
hit it because you're only a point away.
I'll try and stick with you for the next
minute or two. I do have to walk my dog,
but just in case you get it.
VIX starting to go through that pivot
now. So trading back towards the 16s
now. Like we talked about once VIX
reclaims previous day low there's a
chance for more weakness. If we to think
about VIX we used it as the reclaim.
Once VIX reclaimed the green line there
you go reclaim a green line squeezes up.
We see weakness come back into the
market.
So purple line still holding for now
folks.
All right folks that's me done out of
here for the day. Great session. Just
one and done for me today. Shame it
knocked out my runners. I would have
loved to have held for a bit more.
Um, congratulations those who took any
of those trades with me today.
These were the trades that I gave you.
Right. So, two hit. This one's pretty
much hit TP1. If you have wanted to take
it, this is my least favorite trade of
the day. I do not love counter trends.
They're the hardest trade in the book.
But there you go. It is there. Uh, I
would be very cautious now for the
rotation. the rotation between sort of
26,092
and 26,62 or 26,046es.
So I would imagine
we might fill in some of this and do a
bit of a dance here. All right, weakness
can come if we start losing this. All
right, there can be a fail breakout and
a claim back inside. But if we lose
this, you will see weakness come in the
market. I am somewhat skeptical. I think
you might find that you spend most the
rest of the day in here unless they get
very very bullish and go for these stops
above. These are the the areas above. So
if you're aiming for higher if you're
still holding your TP should be sort of
117 to 124,
130 to 134 and then this high of 146,
right? TP1 now hit on this downside move
and uh I'm going to go and walk my dog.
Those in Discord, I will be back later.
Congratulations everyone. Thanks for
joining. I really appreciate it. Um,
love trading with you guys here. It's so
much fun. Makes it so much better than
trading by myself. Um, if you want to
support the channel, because I do this
completely for free, use my code, okay?
Code FCT for all your prop firms. Um,
90% sale on Apex right now. Or use code
flowzone if you're trading with
TakeProfit Trader. That money just goes
back into the channel helping me produce
free educational content for you, etc.,
etc. If you want to do the courses,
there's no pressure, but if you want to,
the links are all down below. I will see
you. Should be on stream tomorrow
morning. And the reason I say that, I
have got some personal stuff going on,
but I should be on stream tomorrow
morning. I will not be trading uh FOMC.
So, let's see if we get a setup. Peace
and love those in Discord. I'll see you
in the afternoon. Take care and use hard
stops, right? Use hard stops. Take care.