Let's move this round a little bit.
There we go. Morning folks. Morning.
Morning. Morning. How we all doing? Did
you all have a good weekend? I hope so.
I hope you got off the charts. I'm sure
lots of you are waking up to snow or at
least uh frozen roads. Those of you on
the East Coast, I hope you're all okay.
big big storm over there. All right, as
always, we're going to start off in the
daily charts, work our way down all the
way until we get to the one minute. We
will look at NQ ES the ETFs. I'll even
have a little look at the metals today
because they are parabolic and moving
and we'll go from there. But before we
do anything else, make sure you've gone
through your morning prep. All right,
are you fit and able to trade? Have you
done your visualization or your
meditation? Whatever it is you need to
do to get into the zone. All right. If
you're not feeling emotionally or
physically able to trade, don't trade.
Do not be forcing yourself on the
charts. Okay. Let me have a sip of this
and let's get into it. All right. Daily
from the daily. What do we have here?
All right. We are already
having a big drive out. You can see the
Sunday opened up a weaker. Here's our
close Friday. Here's the Sunday's open.
There's the dip. Guess what? has been
bid back up again. All right, coming in
all the way back for this gap fill based
on the daily and the weekly chart. All
right, there's your Sunday open. There's
the weakness and we're already back to
exactly where we closed. So, nothing's
changed. This is very much like I talked
about in the newsletter. Remember the
newsletter? We also said nothing's
changed to here because this is Friday's
close last week. This is Friday's close
this week. This is where we're at. All
right, we're not seeing change in this
market. What we are seeing is some
sentiment maybe getting ready to
position themselves for the big week
ahead. Uh hopefully you all read the
newsletter but volatility will come
Wednesday, Thursday, Friday this week
and FOMC into like some big data prints
and of course MAG 7 earnings. All right,
so we are in rotation right now. I'd say
most of that rotation is happening from
550 to 750 and we can have a look at
that on the hourly charts. Just remember
all your EMAs are all here. 50-day,
5day, 20-day, we're stuck between them
until we find acceptance above and above
for a giant squeeze. You have to be
careful of getting caught each side of
this range. Do not get overly bullish
without the ability to hold and go. All
right. Every time we've come up here, we
haven't been able to hold and go. So,
just be aware of that. Hourly.
Make sure you guys can see all of this.
I'll pull this down for you. There we
go. Right. hourlys here is last week's
range if you want to make a note of
this. All right, so previous week low
just just under the 300s
down here you can see there was a shelf
here built out into sort of 420s which
we held on that Sunday flush and
reclaimed previous week high up into
that sort of 820s 825ish. All right,
that's your value area. All right,
that's the rotation from last week. Here
is the shelf and guess what? We're
trading just above point of control
right now into the edge of the next
shelf. If we find acceptance over this
this morning over 7:30, over 750
potential for a drive up to come and
retest these sort of 825s. All right, so
that was the rotation. This guy here is
going to be important. You can see
overnight he's already become important.
This is where most of the range has been
created last week. All right. No
acceptance above, no acceptance below.
This is your chopfest. 750 to 5 sort of
520, 550. Just call it 750 to 550. All
right. 200 point range of choppiness.
All right. Acceptance above. Maybe we
come and take this out. Acceptance
below, maybe we come down to here. In
here, chop. All right. In there, chop.
So, just take it easy this morning. If
we're in there, if we go and have a look
at what happened overnight, this is
overnight's value. I just put this on
because the range was pretty big, right?
You can see that we cannot find
acceptance underneath this this big
pivot into sort of 550 600, right?
Reclaimed Asia goes sideways. Little
expansion. London flushes down, swipes
everyone out, reclaims back up to the
upside. Here are the pivots, right? 750,
550, and there is a node developing here
into 650. So, you've basically got 100
points and 100 points. That's it. All
right, that's pretty much it until we
find acceptance. So, what are we looking
for? Well, if we're going to find
acceptance above 750 and we can base and
hold, there's potential to come back up
and test last week's weekly range and
daily range up towards the 850s. If this
is a little look above and fail, you
want to be very careful about that
rotating. Remember, this is your
chopfest. All right, that is your
chopfest in here. If we find acceptance
below 550 underneath the fire day, maybe
we come back and retest four and maybe
even threes. All right, but again just
like the top side, you need to be
careful of a look below and fail and
reclaim because this is what we are
likely to see on edges until it proves
otherwise. Remember, most the move I
would imagine unless they position early
into tech this week expecting earnings
to be good, most the move will come
Wednesday, Thursday, Friday.
Okay.
You can see here in the one minute chart
again this is just a GlobeEx value no
acceptance above so far no acceptance
below trading inside GlobeEx. Question
is right now can we do this or this? All
right moving through to ES then
same kind of story. You can see this is
the big trigger. This is why we've got a
uh notification up here. I think that is
gap fill. Is it? Yes. Still haven't
quite filled that gap. So ES might want
to be efficient and try and get up to
975. So that's obviously what it's
trying right now. We filled this old
imbalance down here which we swept into
from Wednesday overnight. There's the
flush. Run out all the buyers and bid
back up. And this is the target up here
into 75 right now. So that's what ES is
trying to do. Same kind of story. Can it
base over 40s to get to 75 is the big
question. If we look at the ETFs, they
should be nicely in line. So spy, same
kind of thing. Trying to get this is the
equivalent of 975 on the ES, right? It's
trying to get to gap fill up here into
sort of 92s. Let's call it again. This
is death chop, isn't it? Look at this.
How many sessions have we been here?
Thursday, Friday, Monday. All right,
there's your death chop. All right, be
careful, folks. Zoom out. Make sure you
understand where you are. Q's, same kind
of thing. Death chop, right? No
acceptance above so far. No acceptance
below here. Definitely none below here.
There's your death chop. There's your
death chop. Can it base and go? Big
question mark.
All right, I'm going to have a very
quick look at metals because I know some
of you, I'm sure, will be trading these.
I'm not trading these. We are parabolic.
All right, there's no way of talking
about it. This is a parabolic squeeze
move. Right. I would expect some mean
reversion at some point. It really
depends. Macro says we can keep going
higher but I mean it's becoming starting
to become a little bit unreasonable at
this point and we are probably there or
thereabouts. So I think we will go
higher essentially uh longterm but it is
due a mean reversion. This is a colossal
move right if we think from this
breakout right here
that is absolutely ginormous over 100%
since October alone. All right. said
probably due in mean reversion. Same on
gold. You don't want to be the first one
to it, but it will come. You know, if
retails retail's chasing all of this.
All right, we are past three sigas. It
will come. It will definitely come. It's
just a question of when. Don't get
caught the wrong side of it if you're
desperate for that trade. I'm certainly
not. Dixie, all right, continues to be
sold off like we talked about. All
right, so this is why we're seeing the
rotation out of the dollar into metals.
out of the dollar into metals mainly
being driven by the Asian markets. It's
been going on for two years now, but
it's starting to get very, very
aggressive.
And the VIX, all right, VIX driving back
up to some key levels this morning,
right on the daily, you can see this.
It's the same channel we've had on since
early or mid December. Still in this
channel, we can't really find acceptance
above. If we move down the time frames,
right, you can see that we are trying to
find a bid above 1650s and we have some
resistance up here that we created on
Wednesday which we just had a little
push into right here coming back down
potentially for gap fill. Does it rebid
back up off trend? We don't know. We're
going to have to see. Again, most the
volatility I would imagine will come
later in the week. Right, let's go
through the mag.
Good gap up there for Apple. That is a
strong gap. Where are my flow zones?
Hello. Can we have these on, please?
There we go. And you?
Okay, so nice gap up on Apple
about three B three buck gap up. Uh
question is can it go over this high
from Wednesday? So if we can find
acceptance over this high, it's got a
gap fill up here. And this is remember
where the trap volume is that we've been
talking about, you know, all this trap
volume on buyers. So it's got to get
back through that to be if we start
getting acceptance through that on
Apple, then you know, there is a chance,
right, that they're coming back in from
the bid. So I wouldn't be surprised to
see this before earnings to see us into
there and then it make its decision of
what it wants to do. But strong gap up
off the lows on Apple. Double bottom
there and we'll see if it can get going.
Same thing on Amazon. Nice drive up here
into Friday last week, right? Holding
its gains so far. Can we get a breakout
over sort of 40s? Yeah, 40s 41s for
acceptance into that old range. So, a
bit like Apple, but it's uh about a
session or two ahead right now. Google
had a had a big end of week, but we're a
little bit weaker today. All right. So,
pivots down here on Google. You can see
down here, not that first one, down here
on Google. Can it find acceptance over
here? All right. So, is this failure to
break lower and a breakout? Time will
tell,
but not the strongest today so far.
Meta, beautiful. Remember, still long
meta. We're looking pretty good here,
right? We've been long meta since down
here. I bought down here, held on that
pullback. So, we're looking good from
the 80s. We're almost uh almost 100
bucks up now on that swing, which is
pretty good. So, let's see if we can get
a gap fill up into 750s for earnings,
but we will see. Coming into a pretty
critical level right now on Meta. That's
a big old squeeze out. I would not be
surprised if they need to retest down
here. All right, we tried to do that
move pre-market Friday. Haven't done it.
It's very possible they come for a back
check of that, but so far looking good.
Microsoft that is off to the races on
Friday as well. Well, this one's got
room. This one's got room. All right,
he's trying to find a bid out of here.
All right, remember that's the old
flush. There is a old gap down here from
that gap up, but it's got room to run.
If they're going to bid on earnings,
it's a big if, but if they are, you
know, that's like a 50% pullback. It's
possible. It's catching my eye for a
potential swing. We're just going to
have to see how we go. I'd like a
pullback to really start to hold for me
to get into that.
Nvidia, same story. It's still got gap
filled down here to 84s after that gap
up on Friday. Uh a little bit weaker
today. There's previous day close,
right? Currently trading under it. Does
it get restuck into that and VW up or
that sell down for the gap? We'll wait
and see on chips. Tesla
um that's had relative strength for the
last few weeks. We just zoom out or the
last week I should say. Starting to bid
off those lows from the midpoint last
Wednesday
and starting to reclaim key levels.
Here's our dance. So, if it can hold the
upper edge of this and find acceptance
over 55s, then this back to the races
again. Everyone's looking for earnings
this week. Let's have a look at some of
the broader chip names. Oracle trying to
find a bid here. Looking a little bit
better here. This has had a lot of
weakness. It's still got a little bit
more to go. I'm still watching this sort
of 65 area to see if we dip down into
here and we catch sellers off guard for
that ripper. Uh Netflix starting to try
and base out a bit. I am long Netflix
remember just a small piece just like
for a starter position swing long on
that undercut willing to add down here
but we will see we'll see at the moment
doesn't look too great uh AMD still
going still looks good for this breakout
very very strong
might need one more pullback before we
go but we're at alltime highs right now
so let's see a break of uh well there
already yeah looks good for a breakout
to be honest that last pullback held
very very nicely so strength in the chip
names. We just have to see if that uh
actually continues into this week into
earnings or if it was just early
positioning for them. That pretty much
covers most of it, folks. That covers
most of it.
Let's get back into the ENQ. Make sure
these levels are lining up premarket.
This guy here 50s. All right. So,
really, I'm watching 650s, 750s, 550s.
It's kind of not too bad today to think
about that. 650s, 600, 550s down here,
and these 750s here for this breakout.
Let's see if we base above anything.
Don't be pushing your your uh week too
aggressively. All right, it's nice and
early. Nice and early in the week.
Liquidity will be built and we will use
it and uh we will see how we go as we
get into these earnings. Big big big
week ahead, right? Don't go blowing
yourself out before we even got to the
key data points.
All right, morning, morning, morning,
everyone. Do me a favor. Smash that like
button nice and early for me. I want to
give away some stuff as always. So, I'm
sure we've got lots of you in here
watching. Please smash that like button
nice and early.
bias of the day. Like I've just
literally gone over everything
in a range. In a range until it proves
otherwise. It's absolutely incredible.
Absolutely incredible.
And just spend 20 minutes going over
where we're at in the market and that we
need to find acceptance.
people so willing. Just tell me if I can
go long and I'll press it.
We're very neutral right now. We're
opening up right where we closed on
Friday and last week. All right, we're
neutral. We might want might want a bit
more upside, but we're definitely at the
open. We're literally opening up right
where we closed Friday. All right,
nothing's changed.
Right, let's see. It's possible if we
find acceptance over this red box, they
come for the squeeze up here. I just
want to see how we open what the mag
looks like. So, coming up here in five
seconds, folks.
See how we go.
Okay, mixed bag in the mag on the open.
Tesla 1% down. Nvidia 0.07%
down. Everything else green other than
Google is pretty much flat trying to go
red to green. So MAG looks okay. The
weak one there is Tesla.
Strength in the RTY again today on the
open third of percent up. So sweeping
out this liquidity. This was the failed
breakout level we talked about. It's
possible if they come back down they're
going to look to hold some of these kind
of areas. Then we see how we go after
that. Let me get volume on here nice and
early before I forget.
Where are you? Right here.
Just one minute. See?
Okay. So, the same level 750s
been the same level
and see if we hold previous week point
of control, previous day value area low
for a drive back up. And if not, we've
got this pivot at 650. And if they lose
650, we'll probably go 550.
So, just waiting to see. So far they're
trying to find a bid here. ES is trying
to go.
What's this level on? ES is this
previous week high
week. Previous day. Previous day high
coming up. Previous week high above that
gap feel still there. It's still bidding
on ES. So let's see if the market is
willing to get going here this morning
through this red box. If we can base
over this, I'll consider a long. If we
can base, not if we just drive. If we
base over this, I'll consider this move
here. If we keep failing here, if
there's a look above and fail again,
this move here will be the first
rotation. If they bid this back up, back
up. If they lose this, 650. So, watching
here for a trigger long on this squeeze.
Here we go. Some guys coming in at the
high of day here. Some buyers. So, in
this to see if we can trigger through or
not. And going to need to hold this dip
onto 750s, which they're trying to hold
so far. ES taking out previous day. So
just a little scalp there for me to
start the day
and can ES get up to what's that is that
previous week above. So next stop for ES
would be 69 and then there's 75s for the
gap fill.
So buyers keep coming in here at the
highs. Be careful. Yes, taking the
liquidity already. We're trying to see
if we can turn this now into a blue box
for acceptance higher. This is the
question at the moment. The moment is
looking okay. There are some sellers
caught with these lows, but they keep
buying the 57s and 60s here without a
drive higher. So, just be careful. I'm
trying to see if we can find acceptance.
Here we go. Lovely. Right, let's trade
through this then. Be careful because
it's the start of the day. I'm not
willing to hold too much. I'm just
scalping my way through this at the
early point of the day, seeing if we can
get up into these 800s. That'd be lovely
if we could.
down to these 750s again. They've got to
keep absorbing these 750s for me to
hold. I won't hold underneath. Certainly
won't be holding under 740s.
Might lose my runners here. His 50s, his
40s. No. Out.
Out on the runners.
So, locking in just a couple hundred
bucks there, which is fine. Back to this
view up. Remember, if we lose this, we
can come. This can be a failed look
above. Look above and fail. And if they
lose this, they can rotate all the way
back down to here. Remember, we're at
the top of the range. We're just trying
to see if they want to hold that as a
support system. Might just knock me out
to go again. Certainly looks that way at
the moment.
Yep.
Ah, it's like last week on repeat.
Last week on repeat.
All right. Can they find acceptance
higher here? The next target is 800 if
they can go.
Here we go. Lots of buyers keep getting
caught up here into 770s.
They get through here. We should go
800s. There's 780 on the book and then
800s. Here we go.
want to add and then want to hold in
this low ball mode. But there we go.
Wicked out into that 800's next stop.
There they go. So, here come the 80s
through here. We have a little old
imbalance here. There's a big seller
trying to protect these 80s through
here. We should go 800s. Watch ES into
previous week high. All right. Be
careful of a fail breakout here.
Yes, almost there.
And then you got gap fill above on ES
into those 975s.
So, it's got room on ES previous week
high coming up on ES. Just be careful.
And then you've got gap fill above into
975s.
Looks really good here, folks. Those of
you who managed to hold this long,
that's a really nice move. I got wicked
out of the 40s. So, made some money,
wicked out, and then it went again. I
should have given it more room. But
there we go. That's what happens when
it's the opening drive. All right, 20
more points. Make sure you're paying
yourself into these 80s, but you should
get higher here.
Tes are still very weak. Rest of the
market, but it's okay.
There we go. Coming for that previous
day value very high. if you get through
these. So 800s, then 830 and then 845s.
Oh, your targets. I'm out of this folks.
I got knocked out of it. But if you are
guys are long, that's where you're
looking for
the whip. My my whip was an entry. Yeah,
it was. I mean, I was already long and I
was already taking some, but I didn't
like that we came through this shelf.
All right. So, but previous day point of
control did hold. It's just it is what
it is. It is what it is.
If we'd held that, maybe I could have
given it a couple more points, but it's
fine. All right. Big seller just came in
here. 265 lot. He's now stuck underneath
us at 83s and we are using his pain now
to go higher. Here we go. So, point of
control moved up because that big seller
came in there. We absorbed it. Here you
go. Here's your 800s coming up. So pay
yourself into this and then a squeeze
above into 830s and 845s.
Nice work team. ES has already almost
completed that gap fill into 75s we
talked about. So everything we wanted to
see this morning. We talked about this
red box becoming blue. That's what we've
seen. And there's your drive out. And
you might get almost 100 points here.
You certainly got 50 plus to start the
day.
into that psychological level.
Right. same level as your overunder down
here.
They just got a little bit stuck into
previous days uh value area high. So,
people front running that like we talked
about. This is why I said make sure you
pay yourself into that.
SPY still going. Still got gap fill. SPY
still got gap fill potential. It's
trying to get there. Remember that big
seller came in at 82. It's right here.
This huge line that's mainly a seller
and he's being absorbed right now. So,
they've got one more squeeze up in them
here. Seeing if we can get a bit through
95s and through the 800s. That's where
it really get going.
Very close there on the ES gap filling
to 75. Very, very, very, very close.
You're a couple points away. You're
almost there. Which means I think we
will lift this. I think we will lift
this and squeeze through up into this
soon. And you must take profit on that
move.
Spy into those 92s. ES into 90 into 75s.
That's the level. The spy into 92s. ES
into 75. There must be a level here at
92s. We've got right stuck into it.
SPY's actually crossed that gap and uh
ES is uh lagging behind. So, slight
divergence between the ETFs and the
futures here.
VIX coming into that gap as well. So
almost closed that gap on VIX which
basically down into 16. It's just above
16.68 is the gap built on ES.
Still got room here. See if they rebid
ES into a previous week or previous day
high. Still got room for higher if they
can. If they can keep going,
starting to get a little bit stuck here
though. You don't want them to lose
these uh this big level here where that
big seller came in because there'd be a
flush all the way back down to 55s.
Right. We haven't really retested this
since we broke out. We built liquidity,
but if they lose this, they can retest
this. So, I'd be very careful here. Make
sure you've locked something in.
Remember, we're long from here to here.
Hopefully, they rebuild this to go for
you. But do not let yourself get flushed
out and give the whole move back. That's
all I'm saying here.
Don't let yourself get completely
flushed out and get the whole thing
back.
Alex on the spy chart is like a 30
minute chart. Is it bull flag? 30
minute.
Yeah, potentially. Potentially. It's You
just got to watch that previous week. Uh
where's that close from? From the
previous previous week from Friday the
16th. All right. You got to watch that
close at sort of 9164s.
We've traded through it. If we find
acceptance through that on SPY and we
base there, right? If we can base at 92s
and above, then there's arguments to
move to 95s, 96s on the spy, right?
That's what we're trying to do.
Okay, so they just flushed caught those
sellers underneath that lot. We should
squeeze up now. Should have the juice to
keep going. Here we go. Here's your
targets, folks. Nice. I'm in this now.
Let me move my stop up. You mother
clucker.
Let me move my stop up. Can you please
let me move my stop up? There we go. So,
through the 800s, can we get to 30s?
Really nice. So, through the 800s, can
we get up to here into 30s? So your next
TP is 32 and then 45s and then if we get
really lucky we get into this block all
the way up here. But really nice to
start the week. Didn't think we'd get
this to start the week but very very
happy with it. So you just got TPS left
now. 33s 45s
and then up into this
block here which takes us back to the
point of control from the week starting
Jan 12th. ES now filled that gap as well
folks. Right. ES has done its job into
75s that we talked about. So, we have an
efficient market here, which is great
and we might be done with this once we
hit targets.
So, they use this shelf here
to trap these shorts and we come
straight back down. They're red dipping
into this. I'm not adding anymore. Now,
if we get here, here, and here, great.
But otherwise, not going to add. So long
after that dip and rip. All right,
selling some into these pushes. If we
get up here, fantastic. If we get under
here, I'm out cuz that will be a
rotation.
I should also note
10:30 we have a manufacturing index, not
red boulder news, but just be aware of
it at 10:30.
Nice folks. Yeah, great start today. W's
in chat if you caught any of that with
me. Holding the flow zones nicely. Can
you explain my indicators? On the right
hand side is anchored volume and this
right here are my flow zones. They're
based on rolling Fibonacci.
I got rewap on here twice. There you go.
Lots of you catching it. Nice. Richard
getting it. Dean getting it.
Antler up getting it. Ray, Ray, Jean,
Matt,
Telmos,
lots of you getting it. Love to see it.
Great work, guys. Great work.
Okay, back down into this P. Again,
it's very possible if they trade under
this, there's very possible a rotation
back down to uh to 750 is where we broke
out from. So, make sure you're paying
yourself. I've locked in my money. I'm
good. And uh I don't need to force
anything else for the day now, right?
So, we've got the trade that we want. If
it keeps going higher, great. If not, we
get stopped out. We're going to have to
have two goes a day, unfortunately. So I
was long here partial stop out and then
long after we reclaimed partial and then
we see right break even right now on the
runner and let's see if we can get up
into here.
So far so good. Starting to try and base
above previous days value area higher.
Remember if we get get acceptance above
previous day above previous week means
we are going to try and move value
higher. Need to be very careful of this
kind of move here though. All right.
Anywhere around here.
Coming to the extremes of last week.
Pilots bought both trainings on Friday.
How do I join Discord to make trading
view indicator request? Um, at the end
of uh the 20hour course, if you just
scroll down to the bottom of it, there's
a module on Discord and you just do what
it says in that module. just shoot me an
email based on what it says and I I'll
add you.
Okay, so opening range now set up here
as well. You're almost there, folks.
33s.
We're almost there. Looking for these
sort of 30s. Don't be a dick for a tick.
And then through that, we're looking for
45s.
Tesla very weak. Rest of the market
looks good. Amazon half% down. Apple
having a day here, which is great for me
because I never really sold much of
that. So, I'm still holding that long.
Let's have a quick look at my swing
account. Where are you swinging account?
I lost you.
Here we go, folks. So, tagging that next
TP and last stop all the way up here at
previous week high. Looking good here.
So, my Meta Swing now 7% up. Uh Amazon
6% up. AMD, I've still got a little bit
left of that, 53% up and Apple, 17% up.
So, starting to climb back up on Apple.
My Netflix swing is down 5.85, but I've
got like no size in that whatsoever.
It's just a feeler, so I keep an eye on
it. All right, so TP2, TP3, and then
anything into here would be amazing.
Remember, if we start getting above
this, all right, if we start building
above this, a big old squeeze is
possible. We're coming into the edge of
range here. All right, we're coming into
the edge. We know a massive massive
massive level that we were trying to
trade into last week is into these 890s,
isn't it? This is the old naked point of
control from the week dating back to
Monday the 12th. So the weekly point of
control is right in here. This is the
same target as we had on Friday. Anyone
that traded with me Friday, we were long
trying to get into this block up here.
Just be aware of that. We are coming
into the edge of that block. Um it has
kind of started now. We have like 850
and then really we starting to really
thicken up into this red block.
You sent the email yesterday. Can you
check that?
I'll check my spam.
Oh, it's gone spam. I see you. I'm
really sorry. I just checked my spam.
Glad you just told me that. That's
annoying when it puts it in spam. I'm
going to email you right now, my friend.
Going to be a very short email. I'm not
being rude. It's just cuz I'm trading.
There's Discord for you there. Uh
Connell
must check my spam. I've got to remember
to do that.
Okay, so ES hit targets. We have uh come
into most targets. The only thing left
is up here now.
And then that naked point of control
into 890s, but most targets hit here.
You should have paid yourself if you got
this long from down here. All right, you
made about 100 points here, didn't you?
If you managed to hold somewhat pissed
off that got knocked out, but there
there's your 100 point banger to start
the week. There you go. Right.
Fantastic.
We just did just hit all targets. VIX
has now closed its gap like we talked
about as well. So, we've got a nice
efficient hit market here to start the
day on a Monday. The only thing left
really is that previous week high and uh
previous
uh naked PC.
It's the only thing left. So if I take
you onto the higher time frame chart,
where are we? Right, this is the only
thing left to come and tag. Same move we
tried on Friday. If you remember Friday,
we were long from here for this. Today
we were long from here for this. All
right, if we get acceptance over that,
we have a resqueeze. But here is a big
block. This is our it's naked. It's our
first time visiting it. We don't expect
to just fly through it.
Okay, so really nice trade. I think this
is the first one that we put in Discord
this morning as well. Was this the first
thing?
Try and remember. Yes. So, we're almost
there.
All right. Basing above through the 800s
into this level here, this naked point
of control. All right. So, push, pull
back, go. It's exactly what we've done
this morning.
So if we start losing previous days
value area highs, potential for a retest
down here into 80s and if we lose that
potential for a wash down into 750
still. So you should be small size now
managing your position.
Done for the day. Yeah, I mean I might
well be the same to be honest. If we if
we fail up here in previous week's value
area high, right, then it's possible to
rotate down, isn't it? So if we start
losing previous day and point of
control, you got to remember remember
that previous days value area low. So
we've if we lose this and lose this then
this is possible. These are the the
downside moves, right? We're bullish
though trying to get into here. But if
they start doing a rotation, if they do
a full weekly rotation, which I don't
think they will, it would be all the way
down here.
So far, we're bullish. It's got targets
above it's trying to get to. It's just
we don't want to be buying in premium of
last week, do we? We don't want to be
buying previous week value area high in
front of it.
Got super late. Was planning to get in
at 7:45. Got a 785.
Only holding two MRS for that naked
point control. Yeah, same exactly the
same trade as we looked at Friday,
wasn't it, bud?
Let's see if they can do it. See if
they've got the juice.
They can afford to pull back into 750s
though. Looking at that sort of 15
minute and hourly. They can afford to
pull back into 750s. That's the only
thing. So it just depends if they can
resqueeze above previous day value area
high and previous week for that squeeze
up. Otherwise if they need to rebid, all
right, the only thing I'd be careful of
is if they need to rebid, which is where
you're long from, they'll come back for
here and then rebid it.
And under here we get weak. But I would
imagine bulls will want to either do
this or you know it might be like this
today. And this is the target.
Yeah. The end of the course. Green
otter. Scroll. Scroll down towards the
end of the course. Exactly that.
All right, folks.
I didn't think we'd have it out the gate
today. I'll be honest with you. I
thought that maybe they'd uh flush it
down and retest this before they bid
back up after this sort of grind up.
Thought maybe we'd flush down and rebid.
A strong market to do what it's doing.
Still holding flow zones, everything
bullish right now, but we are into the
top of previous week's value. All right.
So, this is your resistance, resistance,
and resistance up here. So, we're long
from here or long from here, selling
into these pushes. If it can't do this,
you need to be really careful. The way
they're setting this up is a little bit
awkward building a shelf here. think
they need to complete this, but if they
lose it, just don't hold on to it. All
right, you do not want to get caught in
a flush that back down to 750. So, as
long as they keep bidding this and
potentially this, as long as you sell on
the pushes into this, you can always
hold a runner in case we go mental
today, but I don't think we're uh likely
to push through 900, but you just don't
know if they turn the uh balgo on to
position themselves long back into tech
for the earnings early. It's possible.
failing value area high again there.
They can't get through it previous week.
They are trying.
Where's that top ballinger band on the
daily? 2695
basically 26100 which is our big big
pivot to go alltime squeeze
alltime high squeeze. Sorry, I've got
you on the wrong thing, haven't I? My
bad. There we go, folks.
Here we go. All right, so let's see if
we hit final targets here. So, watching
845s
and then 890s. 845s and 890s,
the final targets here.
Can we get 845s and 890s? That's what
we're looking for if they're willing to
hold it.
back to previous week value area high.
Do they rebid this to go 845s, 890s?
They don't rebid this. Then we're going
to go back to previous day value area
high. Sorry, from previous week to
previous day. There is a little shelf
being developed at 820s at the moment,
which I'm watching carefully. So sellers
currently are stuck under 8:16s on the
day. So we might come and test this
shelf. You need them to rebid the shelf
if we're going to drive higher.
Otherwise, don't really like it. So,
here's the 820 test.
We need to rebid this shelf really
otherwise I think we get a little bit
risky here holding too much longer
because we've just taken out previous
week a value area high. Only thing left
is previous week high. They're trying to
hold these 820s
literally like we just talked about. Can
they find acceptance now back above
previous week value area high? So,
watching this shelf to see if they find
acceptance back above here for a
squeeze.
Be careful. Just managing my position
here. Do not want to get caught in a
horrible flash. I know we're at the top
side of the previous week range right
now. I think we've still got targets
above. We can go for nice hold of that
shelf. So, still holding this. Can we
get acceptance higher here?
Lovely. Come on. Let's go for that
previous week high and then squeeze
above 845 to 890s. It would be so nice
if we just do it. We definitely have a
buyer stuck at 840 right now. Actually,
technically 839
developing holding this. This here is
starting to become pretty key. We can
draw this in this point of control. This
level here, they've got to hold this
level here.
the newsletter.
Oh,
I hope they don't start looking at it
soon. Okay, here we go. Come on, market.
We've just got one player who's stuck at
39. If we can get through him, there's
an old imbalance here. If we can get
through him, then we should get that 45s
and then 890s if we get lucky.
Come on.
Red line, next target, and then up here
into 890s. I can put a horizontal line
on so we can see exactly where that PC
is right here. Right. This is the old
naked PC.
Take care, mate. Have a good one.
Here we go. Come on, baby. Come on,
baby.
Give it. Give it. Give it. Give it. Give
it. Give it. Give it. Give it. Previous
week high. Let's go, baby. All right. 89
890 is next target. Let's go.
Let's go.
Is there anyone up at 890? Let me see.
870. Yes. Look at this. All right. On
bookmap. Big seller up at 900. That's
what I want to see. Nice. Hopefully they
start adding liquidity up there. So 55's
now we're pushing through 55. 72 is on
the book. Once we get through there, we
should get up into the seller at 900.
Just make sure you're moving your stop
up and managing your position. Right,
this is grinding now trying to squeeze
out. All right, just make sure you're
paying yourself in this. Right, what you
don't want is this. It's very, very
possible. So just be very careful.
manage your position. And most of you
along from this blue box, I got knocked
out, so I had to join a little bit
later.
So now it shouldn't come back down into
the previous range. Um, it's a bit
early. We've only just broken through
it, right? We can still look we can
still look above. Remember previous week
value here. We can look above and get
stuck here and come right back down.
This is still the previous day range is
here. All right. That's previous day and
previous week is
here.
Right. All we've done is poke through so
far. Right. I don't think we haven't
like based out yet, have we? We've just
poked through. We haven't based out. We
haven't dropped, reclaimed, and gone.
So, we're long for the first move, but I
think it' be it's Monday morning. It's
far too early to say we're not going to
come into the previous week's range.
It's far too early to say that. It's
only a Monday morning. We got a whole
week ahead.
This is definitely the target now.
My streaming every day or certain days.
Found your channel today. Yeah, I stream
every day, mate. Monday to Friday, 9:15
Eastern time all the way until lunch.
Right. So, here comes the retest of
these sort of 820s where we built out
this shelf. Be careful if they start
losing 820s and 800s. Certainly a
rotation down to 780s and very very
possible all the way down to 750s. We
still this is a squeeze up. We have not
retested this. We are still bullish. I'm
not telling you to be bearish. Right?
You are still bullish. I'm just letting
you know that if we start to lose these
areas here on a retest, this rotation
here can happen. Right? Until that
happens, we're bullish to try and get
into here. But just be careful because
we're the top side of range. Right? We
are in deep in last week's premium.
Deep in last week's premium.
Better not make this move up easy. I
think it's not doing too bad so far. I
think it's been pretty good. Just one
little uh trap which knocked me out
here. But still made money on it. It's
just a shame I was positioned really
nicely for that. Shame that wicked under
that little low volume node here. They
defended it.
I would have had like best price. I
would be up 100 100 uh points here
instead of having to enter on was it
this reclaim here.
Just watch in case you do not want to
get caught in this flush. ES possibly
going to come back down to the New York
VW up here. So this is what I was
talking about. Do not let it come and
rinse you completely out of it. You must
pay yourself.
We hit most targets. Only thing left is
the naked PC. We've hit most the targets
and we've got that new 10:00 candle. So,
new hour, new 4hour candle, right? That
last hourly candle was pretty big,
right? From the 700s to the 850s. It
might be that they want to re repric and
rebalance this down into 750.
that just
eight or nine level.
Still holding in front of this blue box.
Still bullish. Still trying to get up
into this.
Wouldn't mind a little trap under here.
We're still holding well on a five
minute. Amazon back under its VWAP.
Google into like a towards a pivot. It's
got a previous day high another three
points or $3 higher. It can get going.
Meta just stuck right now. Previous days
high after trading through it. Microsoft
just doing the rotation getting stuck in
front of previous day high and the
20-day moving average. Nvidia big drive
up this morning selling back off coming
back down. It's under previous day
close. It's coming back down maybe for a
retest of VWAP and previous day low.
Tesla is completely stuck between the
20-day and 5day which are in a very
tight range here. So it's sold this
morning through the 20-day right back
down to the 5day founder bid. Oracle
drive up through previous day high
coming back down to back test it right
now. Let's have a look at some broader
names. Netflix
sold off this morning trying to find a
bid on its higher time frame. Algo AVGO
pushed up to 5day sold off into 5day
coming back down to previous day high
kind of in no man's land. And the VIX
VIX is uh finding a bid on that gap fill
that we talked about.
That gap bits definitely found a bid on
to here
in that blue box finding a bid. Yellow
lines gap fill remember. So sold off
into gap fill. Finding a bid there so
far. Do they bottom out here and start
to drive? If they do, we're going to see
some weakness come into the market.
If they can sell through the gap, then
we might get that resqueeze.
What's up, Tyson?
They still got a target up here. It's
just where they need to flush it first
before rebid.
We will see. What's up, Gary?
We will see if we hit final targets
here.
So, we've got almost 800 of you watching
and only 250 likes. Come on, folks.
Doesn't cost you anything. Smash that
like button. Most of you 100 points up
right now. Let's get it up to over 500
likes and we'll do a giveaway on stream
as well.
Is the VIX a tradeable asset? Yes, it
is. Absolutely.
It's very tradable. You see, most
people, smart people, when we see drives
over 20s and above,
they will just sell the sell the VIX
longterm because they know it'll come
back into the teens.
They use it as a hedge most of the time.
Now sell. There's no reason to sell
right now.
Zero reason to sell,
right? We're getting stuck at this edge,
but like you've got no confirmation.
We're not under any key levels yet. I
mean, look, you you do you. But for me,
all right, yes, we might come down here,
but I'm more interested in selling if we
start losing volume. At the moment,
we're building volume.
above the key level, above previous day
value area high, above or at previous
week value area height with a clear
target up here. Right? The short for me
would have to be here on a rejection,
right? I'd have to know that we're
starting to reject this. We're not we're
not doing that right now. So, there's no
short for me. I'm not going to scout
this short side. Yes, we're at premium.
Yes, it might come down to here, but for
a bigger uh fade move, I'd have to see
it really let go of volume. And I'm not
seeing that right now. I'm seeing quite
the opposite.
Uh the orb is 15 minutes. This this
white line is 15minute orb that's set,
but you can change it with the indicator
to whatever you want.
Yeah, agree, Peter. Just sideways
building out this volume at the moment.
It's all we're doing. Building out the
volume. It wants to move higher. It's
just whether it needs to trap first
before we do it.
Very, very possible we come and retest
some of this before we do it. It's very
possible they do something down into
this low volume node like very very
possible we do some sort of dunk into
here, save it, reclaim and then finish
the move. Same move we were looking for
Friday. Even this will be the same as
what we were looking for Friday and it
it didn't happen Friday. We sold on our
push if we remember those who traded
with me Friday was exactly the same
move. Here was the move Friday. We
caught it
I think it was here, wasn't it? here and
an add and we sold into this and then I
was saying I would like to see it do
something like this to complete the move
or this and all we did was go sideways
Friday sell back off into range so we're
exactly the same level if we look at
where we're trying to trade into exactly
the same level this is identical to
Friday it's just can we base above come
up to here can we do the move I was
looking for Friday which we never
completed is the question right now or
are they just going to trade the edge
and go back into the dance hopefully not
it would be Nice if we moved out of
range.
But yes, maybe coming back down for
VWAP, which is at 72s, the New York
VWAP.
SPY can afford a previous day high ret
back into sort of 90s 91s
and we can afford to come back down into
these 800s. It can afford to come down
to 780. You can see the shelf here where
that seller got trapped if it really
wants to. This blue box here may very
well be defended.
We will see. I'm willing to play a trap
to get long if it's willing to do it.
There's the flush right back down. So
this just like Friday watching this into
previous day value area high and VWAP
and the big big pivot here is 780. So
that's where that seller came in. So
they're rebidding previous day value
area high for now. They are stacking
underneath. It might very well lose this
bid and come for a flush and then we'll
see if they want to trap or not into
this low volume node which we literally
just talked about. So we will see. Time
will tell what they want to do. Here's
previous day value very high.
So far bidding in front of that
stacked up under 800 so far. Seller
coming in here at 15. So far he's got
himself a little bit caught offside.
We still got more to fill into 800s and
95s, but we'll see.
I'm interested in the trap if they can
allow it
somewhere down here and then a reclaim.
Big buyer coming in here. They're trying
to resell 40s right now. So, here's the
potential trap if they can squeeze back
over previous week value area high. But
this where they're going to try and sell
30s and 40s right now. It's where they
resold the first breakdown.
I really want to see this flush under
800 before a reclaim would be the most
ideal scenario here.
I'd say as long as they protect uh 90s
to 82s the buyers then they will remain
in control and this will be a pullback
which can still be ripped higher and if
they start losing all this certainly if
they lose this the move back down to
750s is possible. We haven't rechecked
that since we bid off it. So so we break
out we haven't actually rechecked it.
It's possible they go for the recheck,
but if buyers want to really hold
momentum, they're going to want to bid
somewhere in here, all right, for a kind
of trap play like this to move back up.
If they lose this, the rotation to 50s
is possible. That can still be a higher
time frame buy, but if they lose that,
then it's a failed look above again,
just like Friday. So, we will see into
these areas of interest. Now, I'm just
going to watch the tape. I'm put that.
What's going on here?
previous day value area high. Yes.
Trying to bid off New York VWAP.
We can't get under previous day value
high yet. Still bidding off that VW up
and previous day value area high.
Sellers came in here under 17s.
Here
comes the squeeze back up. All right,
let's see and get what we want here.
Yep, let's go then. See if we can get
back through previous week.
Nice. All right, VPO now at 40s. Squeeze
through that and we're going to go back
for the highs. So, we can complete this
move up here if we can force this bid
through. Now, we've trapped enough
sellers there underneath the 17s just
like we talked about. The trap can be
under here if they're going to complete
this move. This is what we talked about.
Build this liquidity. I wouldn't have
minded a flush into here, I said, which
is what we had. We've reclaimed this. If
we reclaim this and hold, this is what
they will try and do. All planned out
beforehand for you. This is exactly how
we build and use liquidity.
Here we go.
Let's go. Let's go, baby.
seller at 40s. We just want to see us
run through 40s here aggressively and
then we should lift 55s and go. There is
this passive seller here at 40s. He's
actually they're front selling in front
of they're selling in front of him at
the moment. Come on. There's a bid at
20. I'd like to see this bid at 20 step
up to 30. Don't really want them to drop
that down to 20. I'd like to see this
bit just to step up and force us through
40s and 45s. ES going for high day break
as well.
Vicks flushing underneath PDC. So, we're
in sync here. We look good. Just want to
see a bid step up and take these 40
players out. And then we should see Here
we go. Let's [\h__\h] go.
Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you.
Come on, force it. ES new high day.
I need them to step on the tape
aggressively now. Let's go. Start
lifting these offers. Come on. Start
lifting these offers. Don't want to get
stuck here again. Do not want to get
stuck here. They've got to bid this now.
Otherwise, I'm out. If they I don't want
to get caught back down into here. I
want them to bid this here and force
this up. We've got the liquidity looking
left to run. Just want to be careful
because ES has already done this move.
Okay. So, I want to see a rebid here to
hold this. All right. Long on the
reclaim when I said sellers got stuck
underneath 17s. Sellers got stuck under
17s. Long on the reclaim. Partial into
here. Want to see this build out and
squeeze for that naked PC. Just want to
be careful because ES has already done
the move. Come on. Come on. Come on. NQ
bid. Step on the tape, please. Don't
like this guy fanning around at 25. This
is just like last week. when they need
to step up. They're not stepping up.
I'm going to cut this on the runner. Out
on runner. Might be too early, but I
just don't want to get caught in
something nasty when we're in premium.
But either way, made some nice smile.
You [\h__\h]
Soon as I said that, the 25 bid stepped
into 30 as soon as I cut it. Oh, you got
to laugh, Alex. Your timing's so [\h__\h] at
the moment, mate. Your timing's so [\h__\h]
Your timing's so [\h__\h] This will go now.
Naked P. This will [\h__\h] rip.
This is like every day at the moment. To
the tick. It's knocking me to the tick.
Oh, it's funny. It's funny.
I'd be looking for 900s now. Basically
890 900s. I'm out of this now. It's just
[\h__\h] done me again. But I think
you'll get 890s 900s now.
Oh, folks.
Oh, yeah. I mean, it's fine. Like, I
made money. It's just annoying.
Here you go, folks. It's doing exactly
what exactly what I wanted. I'm not
patient enough. Not patient enough. Not
giving it enough room. All right.
Remember, stops are at high day. Once
you poke through here, we should come
ripping up into here. Now, this is
exactly what we did. You can rewind when
when we were here. We talked about this
move down into here, setting the trap.
Sellers got cut caught under 17s in
here, and we're ripping. All right. I
can probably show you it here. If we go
to a one minute,
right, sellers got caught under 17s
right here.
All right, sellers got caught here
and especially here. And once we
reclaimed that, I should have just moved
my stop into this imbalance.
Anyway, here we go, folks. You're almost
there. 8.90 is your stop is your stop is
your target now.
It feels personal. Yeah, it does. It
does. To be honest, it's just poor
trading for me if I'm honest. I probably
just should have given that a bit more
room. Uh I just didn't want to get
caught cuz they failed there three
times. I wanted them to hold value here
uh for that rotation. I didn't want to
get caught if they flushed back down
here in a horrible stop run. But um
anyway, whatever. It's fine. Hopefully
you guys are all in it. As long as you
guys make money, that's all that
matters.
So 890s is is the target for you guys.
All right, 890s. 890 is 900. We've got
liquidity up there. There was a guy at
900. Let's have a look if he's still
there. He is still there. 100 lot just
sat there all day. In fact, he's added
some size on in the last minute. So you
can look for that this move. Red box is
the start of where we thicken up.
Remember this dates back. This is the
naked point of control dating back to
the week of Monday the 12th of Jan. All
right, we're trying to trade into that.
We've never tagged it before. Right into
the red line will be that weekly PC.
This is where we're trying to get, but
it get we get thick into this red box,
but I think you will get it. You must
take some profit into this, right?
Either at the edge or really ideally
into this and then I think you get it.
What a beautiful, beautiful trade.
Lovely. And we've now got a seller who's
just got himself stuck at 57s as well.
Here you go, folks. What a trade. All
right. Hopefully that makes sense to you
all. Especially those of you who are new
here. You might be thinking, "How did he
see that? How did he know it was going
to happen? It's just too many years of
experience, too many gray hairs
understanding how we build liquidity."
The longer you're here, the easier it's
going to get for you to understand what
I'm looking for and why why I said I
wouldn't be short unless we lose all of
this on a retest. All right. Some of you
were looking for shorts. Did we ever do
this move here? All right. Did we ever
fail underneath, turn this into red, and
fade? No, we didn't. We faked it and did
this. We used this liquidity. Here's
your target, folks. And you can hold
runners above here. Congratulations.
Fantastic trade. This is your lowhanging
fruit for the day gone. All right, this
is the lowhanging fruit. Your trades
from here on out get much, much harder
to take, right? Because you're just
tagging into low hanging fruit now.
No worries, Stephen. Yeah,
congratulations. Thanks, everyone new
that's joining, welcome.
All right, if you're new joining here,
what I what I try and do that separates
me from the other traders you might see
in YouTube is I try and educate you as I
go. All right, I try and make you
understand what I'm looking for and why
rather than just saying I'm long here
because it's a flag or some [\h__\h]
like that. All right, not that flags
don't work. They do, but you got to
understand premise of why, right? what
we're trying to do.
Here we go. Beautiful, beautiful,
beautiful moves.
So, there you go. Getting stuck right
into that level, aren't we? Right into
the naked point of control. So, you
should have taken some profit into this
red line. There's a reason there's a red
line there. It's not just random on the
chart. All right? It is a very, very
thick area. And if we lift through this
red box now, I will tell you if we lift
through this and we base above, then we
can look for these targets here. I'll
thicken this up a little bit and make
sure we've got it
right. Where are all the stops? These
are the next lot of stops up into here
into this gray box. So, if we lift
through this, it very well might be that
you get 950 today. If you get over 950,
well, we can't rule out 26,5.
But, you know, we will see, won't we,
folks?
No short from here. No. Why? Why? Why?
Why? I've got to drill you guys on that.
Why? Why short? No shorts. Why are you
trying to get short? What is there in
this market is telling you to get short
right now? Nothing. Okay, you're into an
area of interest. But you know what is
short about this? What is short about
this on an hour? Look, look on an hourly
chart. What is short about that?
Breaking out of this range, right? Maybe
maybe it pulls back into here. But why
are you trying to time that? Why are you
trying to frontr run it? Have you left
any volume? No. Don't guess. Look, the
trend up, lower time frame up, higher
time frame up. We're in a buy since
pre-market. All right, don't be trying
to guess tops. It's the easiest way to
get yourself caught. All right, do not
be doing that. Trying to help you here.
This is talking from a guy who had that
habit. All right, I'm trying to drill
that habit out of you. That's exactly
how I uh used to lose all my money. All
right, trying to guess the tops. Don't
guess the tops. If we're in a bullish
momentum, just wait for the pullback.
much much better to play the higher time
frame narrative.
How do you join Discord? Uh you have to
do the 20our course. All right. I have a
20our course on demand. It comes with a
version of the flow zones and Discord.
It's uh it should be $6.99, but I don't
know if he's adjusted it yet, but it's
probably $649 right now if not
onetime fee.
Nice, Larry. Good work.
Can you go over your daily value area
settings? They're just normal settings.
Um, just 70% of previous days volume,
but I'm always looking at the New York
session, right? Don't really care about
overnight.
Can I summarize that into rule? Yeah.
Don't guess tops, don't guess bottoms.
The main thing where people go wrong,
right, is they they they they see an
area of interest here, right? And may
maybe this pulls back to here and maybe
it does that. But why play this move
here if the main time frame wants to do
this move here, right? So
if you lose this, then maybe you can
think about short. If we're going to
lose all of this, then then you can
think about the rotation. But why bother
up here? You will become liquidity.
Think about how many people saying, "Oh,
this has gone too far. This has to come
down." What what if it doesn't come
down? What if everyone gets short here
and they all put their stop at higher
day? What then happens when they mark it
out? Where's the structure here? What
here is telling you to go short? Unless
we build out volume here and we leave
volume and even that it would just be a
counter trend down. So, you'd be trading
from 76s to maybe 50. So, it's just not
worth it. It's not worth it, folks.
Do I have a discount code for the
course? Uh, not right now.
No worries, Ray Ray.
Yeah, every everything this everything's
covered in that course. 20 hours. It's
it's quite efficient. It's a lot to go
through. Right. So, back to flow zones.
Like I said, it might be that they come
back and back test some of this. Now,
we can have a look at that high day.
What was left at hive day?
Not much of an auction up there. Uh, and
you can see this imbalance starting to
be bid on again. So, I'm not convinced
high day is in yet, but we will see.
What are my thoughts on overnight
inventory? Have you heard of that? Have
I heard of overnight inventory? Yeah,
it's just GlobeEx. I mean, we're gapping
up over GlobeEx, right? So, here's your
GlobeEx. Here's your overnight
inventory,
right?
Fail break into key level. Reclaimed,
held, GlobeEx low, grind, held, break
out of GlobeEx up to top side of weekly
inventories. Inventory is net long.
Look, net long, net long, net long, net
long. Anyone who was short overnight was
short from 740s. Remember 750s if you
were here pre-market 750s to 550s was
the rotation above that and a hold is
bullish. All right. Look above and a
fail is bearish for rotation. Look below
550s and a fail is bullish rotation.
Look below 550s and rejection is bearish
rotation. All right, there's your box.
There's bullish. There's bearish. That's
your dead man zone. That's where you get
chopped up.
Do I use midnight open for volume
profile? Uh for trading London. If I was
trading London, I'd use the London open.
Or you can if you want to look at the
session before you use use Asia. I was
trading London though, I'd be looking at
the developing profile during London.
I don't know who Jay Fronman is. Sorry,
Tono. No idea.
Yeah, I trade here every day. Monday to
Friday.
Best long entry. Well, they've got a
whole dips into here, right? But
remember, we're premium now. So, you
want to see them defend previous week
and previous day value. Same thing here.
We defended previous day. You'd want to
see them defend previous week. Remember,
lowhanging fruit has just been taken.
What was our target today? Ding ding
ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding
ding. All right, low hanging fruit's
gone.
Market can do what it wants now. We've
like for me, I've hit my target today.
This was the target. This was the same
thing we were looking for from Friday.
Look how accurate that target was.
Look how accurate that target was. That
red line. All right, we traded through
it by what, a tick or two. Doesn't mean
we can't go higher, but for me, target's
gone. If they want to rebid this, fine.
I can hold the runner on a rebid if it
keeps going. But I also have to be open
to the fact that if this was the drive,
right? I know some of you be saying the
short's working. The short is back down
into here. All right, I wouldn't trade
this. It's counter trend. We they can
still bid this up, right? But if you let
go of this, there is your safer
rotation. If we trap bulls over this,
this is your safer rotation back down
into the edge. If they let go of 750,
there's a trade back down into 700s,
then 650, then 550, and we get much more
bearish under 550. All right, so
remember 750 to 550 is a rotation. What
that means is everything over 750 is
technically bullish. All right, so you
can do this whole move back down. All
right, but that would be counter trend
because technically they can rebid that
up. That means you can take a counter
trend short under 800s 2750 if they trap
buyers. I wouldn't be short before that.
There's your pivot pivot to here. All
right, this is a pullback. It can hold.
If they lose this, there's a short here.
If they lose 750, then you can trade. If
you really want to trade inside the
range, you can trade 750 to 550. I'm
going to avoid this week as much as
possible 550 to 7450. I really don't
want to trade in here. So, I would like
bulls to be above this and I'd like
bears to be below this. I will trade
failed breakouts back inside and I will
trade
failed breakouts back down, but I will
not enter inside that range or do my
best not to.
If that doesn't make sense to you, um
I've probably got some stuff for free on
YouTube on um higher time frame, lower
time frame. All right, let's pass Apex
Eval with that move. Nice.
Congratulations. Full forward out 100
points in that move. Great call as
always, Alex. Nice work, mate. Nice
work. Yeah, you were long from 85s,
weren't you? Wanted 45s and got in late
and joined at 85. That's nice move. Same
as me. I was I was actually long from
45s, knocked out, rejoined 85s basically
for that move out and job done.
Done for the day. Thank you so much. I'm
green 320 on each pa. Have a wonderful
day. And you? And you. Pretty tidy
market today.
Shoulders held. Gave good clean moves
off the edges. Have a great day. And
you, Rob, nice work. Looking short here
would be high risk, lowreward.
Uh, it'd be a high risk, high reward if
it worked. I mean, it's probably only
low reward, but like, you know, if you
were short here and you got lucky, you'd
get down into this. If you got really
lucky, you'd get down lower. But there's
nothing to say it's going to do that for
me. Look at this. This here is what's
key, right? This is what's key now for
the day, right? Do we trade underneath
that or do we hold that and go again?
What levels do I have past 26k?
Let's have a look
this chart right here, guys. All right.
So this move here will be sort of into 9
stops at 930 to 960. The edge of it is
actually at 26,000
and let's just call it 20. And then
stops here, let's just move this up are
into 26,045.
And then we have a ton of stops above
here into 100. So if we think about this
move here, all right, if we just pull
this back, right, this is where if we
talk about a range, a bigger range, all
right, a bigger range,
the big range in this market right now
is here.
All right. If we think about from
November, right, November, bottom side
of the range, top side of the range,
bottom side of the range, mean reversion
underneath the range, look below and
fail, reclaim the range, held the dip,
top side of the range, top, top, top,
fail, mean reversion, bottom side of the
range, mean reversion, mean reversion,
mean reversion, top side of the range,
bottom side of the range, mean
reversion. Right? Does that make sense
to you? Here's your middle. Right? Look
how much we're trading around this core
of the middle. Right? We can't get under
and we can't get over. So over 26,000.
What we looking for? Basically 120s,
150s. If they do this, I can tell you
massive all-time highs are likely to
happen unless they do a very quick look
and a huge flush. But if they base over
all these stops, think about all these
stops from November, November, December,
December, January, January, January. If
they do this, think about how much
liquidity is in here. All right, how
much liquidity is in here? We will
absolutely rip faces. All right, the
same thing. If they look above and then
they fail under here, they will
absolutely tank this probably back down
towards the 200 day moving average. All
right, because we have so much liquidity
being built in a sideways market, right?
Even if you think about the beginning of
the day when we talked about um on the
daily chart,
we go back to the daily chart,
right? Look how tight we are getting.
You can see the edge of this range.
Basically got it drawn out. Blue box,
red box. Look at the Ballingers. They're
getting so tight. When we're healthy,
Ballingers are nice and wide. Now the
Ballingers are very tight. 20-day,
50-day, 5day, everything's tight here.
All right, so we're trading away from
the mean towards the top side. If we
find acceptance here, all right, and the
bulls trend up and the SMA support, then
we can go back to all-time highs, right?
If they reject this again and we go back
into that range trade, if they get under
here, this is the flush where we can
maybe get towards this 200, which by the
time we do that, if we do it, it's
probably going to be very close to this
wick. All right. So, this is often a
higher time frame trigger long. We have
not hit that since here.
May 23rd. All right. June, July, August,
September, October, November, December,
January. It's already been 8 months. I
can't see it happening right now in the
next few days. So, it's probably going
to be 9 or 10 months before we even get
anywhere close. But, we are building out
huge amount of liquidity up here for
months and months and months and months.
It's really important you understand
what the market's trying to do.
Okay. So,
market rejecting this. So, I'd be
watching this right now.
Right. This is
where buyers are potentially stuck. Let
me have a look at my uh
actually dig into this.
Not too much to be. Buyers are stuck
over 80, but lots of sellers are caught
up there at 75. We are still absorbing.
Like I said, I would not really feel
comfortable about short unless we get
under all of this. All right, for me,
this is bullish volume being built out
and the narrative is to still to go
higher. I'm out of this position, right?
I sold into that. Once I saw that fail,
I sold into that. Low hanging fruits
have hit, but I would still be bullish
in this market. There's no reason to
trade lower right now. All right, zoom
out. No reason to trade lower. Like I
said, you when one of you asked about
the short, I said I wouldn't do it. It
might come to here to here, but they
will probably rebid it. Well, what have
we seen? A rebid. Why? volume. All
right. Volume. All right. So, think
about if you're going to draw this out.
Is there any breaker structure here? Is
there any change of character? No. So,
what we assuming higher prices? We're
assuming higher prices.
The only key level now is this little
shelf right here. This is sentiment
right now for if there's a resqueeze,
which they're going to try and do. Okay.
So hopefully those of you who are
looking short, hopefully I've kept you
out of it.
Hey Alex, still working my way through
the course. Question for you. That may
be your answer as you finish up, but do
you have any volume minimums that you
look at to keep an eye out for the
market? No. Uh, not really. But what I'm
looking for is outliers, right? So what
I'm always looking for is outliers. I
don't really care about the the the
small intricate volumes, but like if I'm
looking for someone stuck, I'm looking
for them to be stuck as an outlier. So
like on the delta,
right, I'd be looking for them to be
stuck here. So if we zoom up right now,
there's nothing like huge out of place,
but maybe if we go downside, we might
see some players of bigger size that are
stuck. So we can see buyers stepped in
here. Here we go. So sellers are stuck
here from 57. So I know 57s and 56s is a
big level where sellers got stuck,
right? So, I'm looking for outliers the
wrong side of the tape. And you can
either use the DOM to do that or you can
use footprint or you can use bookmap,
whatever you're comfortable with. I'm
I'm looking for bigger lot sizes
outliers because that's when we're going
to get a move, right? You're going to
need lots of people stuck.
What time frame do I lose to trade?
Well, I execute on an M1, but I'm
looking at hourlies and five minutes
most of the time.
What about the non-favorable news of US
dollar? Yeah, well, that's why we're
getting that the rotation constantly
into gold and silver. Been talking about
that for well, probably about a year now
to be quite honest. Probably about a
year now.
What are the blue boxes? Uh, potential
demand areas, right? So, red boxes
potential supply areas, blue boxes
potential demand areas. Gray box is just
little volume shelves that are drawn.
Yeah, initial balance now set. You're
quite right. Purple line on the top of
your screen and bottom screen is your IB
for the day now.
Still looking bullish. Yeah, absolutely
still looking bullish.
Oh, duo. Uh, I can show you the trades
today. Um, so I was long here. Let me
draw them on the screen for you.
So was long here, sold here, and then
knocked out break even on the runner and
then re-entered on this reclaim
with target up here
and added a piece into that.
And it was over 17. So I joined reclaims
to like 20s. Well, here I'm now flat.
Those were the plays today.
One minute. Someone just asked again the
time frame. This is a one minute chart.
But just because I'm executing on one
minute doesn't mean the thesis comes
from one minute. All right? The thesis
doesn't come from one minute. This is
comes from higher time frame and then we
join based on what I'm seeing on lower
time frame
is that special volume profile. This
just anchored to the 930. It's just
completely free tool on uh trading view
right here.
Uh anchored volume profile. That's all
it is. anchored to a 930 print
trader doc. I have never seen anyone
explain the market structure with such
fluidity. You paint a very clear picture
logical view of the market. Thanks for
the good work of opening eyes for
traders. Oh, you're welcome, ma'am. I'm
glad it helps.
How much I make off that? And well into
four figures. Well into four figures.
You talk about runners. So, how many
contracts would you recommend someone
new to your system? Rick, I don't that
is dependent on right a few things. What
size account you're trading, what you're
willing to risk on each trade, all
those. If you're trading like a prop
firm and a 50k account, you only need to
start with two or three micros, right?
two or three micros like
sell one on the push knock out two or
three micros
sell one on the push hold the runner
sell one on an extension sell the the
top add in here sell the top like sell
half into this break and the rest into
here right you won't need more than that
if you get two or three micros to go 100
plus points for you that's 600 points on
a 50k account you do not need more than
that not in this market when we're
getting 100 plus points point moves
numerous times a day and if you go up in
account size or you start to get above
your buffer then you can start moving to
five to six to 7 to 1 minute mini etc
etc.
Biggest problem traders do is they
oversize too early.
Can I explain how I get buyers or
sellers stuck on the dom? Yeah, I use
delta. So I use volume profile delta on
the dom. So back down. So we failed to
get above this green, the gray box,
right? So this was the target. They
needed to get back above this. This is
why we put it in. This is where buyers
were stuck. All right, we didn't find
acceptance above for the resqueeze.
And we still have the ability buyers can
still try and keep bidding this, but
this is a failed breakout. Now, this is
your first attempt to move higher that's
failed. It might be that we do this for
a while. If we do this for long enough,
all right, and we let go, then we can
use that volume to go lower. right now
and technically it's still for me it's
still bullish cuz your pivot is from
here to here. This is internal range
being being built out. If we start
losing this it gets more interesting.
If you're a scalper maybe is an argument
to take this to here but for me no I try
and avoid stuff like that.
How many props? Fiff prop firms I trade
with at the moment. What do I use? Just
this one here on um bookmap.
I have a funded TPT 50k account. Should
I just use only one contract? You can
use like two two or three micros. Micros
though, not minis.
Just start with micros. You don't need
minis to start with and get above the
buffer. Build some like room.
ES back into its VWAP now. VIX trying to
reclaim its PDC. I'm just going to get a
refill on my drink here, folks, because
we've already been here for what almost
probably over two hours now. 800 of you
live. Smash that like button. Let's get
this over 500. We're going to give away
some Apex accounts and maybe some
courses as well. Be right back.
Okay, so they're still rebidding this.
Same thing. Structure still bullish.
Still re rebidding it. The squeeze will
probably happen over 880s, but they're
still trying to rebid this.
Right. This is potentially can build out
liquidity here which can still be
bullish for this move here. Until we're
underneath this, there's no short in my
mind. All right, made that as clear as
possible today. Very, very bullish in
structure right now.
Yes. 10 micros is one minute. Correct.
Correct. Correct. Correct. Correct.
Correct.
Hi Alex, the bar graph at the bottom of
your screen which is helpful for
beginner traders. If so, what indicators
would it fall under on top set the uh
this is volume. So there's two, right?
So this is delta.
All right. And this is volume. All
right. So the bottom one I don't that
would just be some type of volume
profile volume uh indicator on top step.
I don't know if they have delta. You I
don't trade with them. You you'd have to
check, but this is Delta, right?
What do I use? I think you just asked
that a minute ago. I use the one right
above me on bookmap. Right. So, the
ladder you see on the top right hand
side of my screen, that's the DOM that I
use.
Alex, would you please trade GC live
with us sometimes or record an overnight
session? It would be much appreciated.
It moves about $50 on an average day,
which is about 5K on one minute. Yeah, I
just don't trade it. So, I mean it it's
all the same principles, right? The the
principles will be exactly the same if
we go over to GC.
So, I would I would trade it exactly the
same way.
There's your 9:30 open,
right? So, that's your dance right now.
I'd be going from higher time frame. You
can see a clear pivot here. So this is
the low that made this high. All right,
we're trading inside GlobeEx. I'd be
very careful about building an overnight
range. If you start to lose this is
where it gets more interesting. And
right now inside the New York session,
you have a look below and fail of value,
right? And they're trying to bid back up
to the midpoint right here, right? And
they find acceptance of it, they come to
the top side. And if we find acceptance
over that, then they'll come to the top
side of GlobeEx because they have lots
of stops to run. All right? is is
exactly the same principles. You don't
need me. You don't need me. You just
trade it the same way. The markets move
the same way. No market moves a
different way. We all move the same way,
right? We bid up the same way. We sell
off the same way. The only difference is
the personality of the market. Why?
Because that depends who's interested in
the market. So ENQ volatile, likes to
run stops, especially Alex's stops,
right? Likes to overextend through some
levels a bit more. ES most this thickest
traded market in the world. So probably
respects levels a bit more. So if
there's a shelf, it's probably going to
bid off that shelf. It's probably not
going to swipe through the shelf and
reclaim the same way as NQ does, right?
I passed four funded accounts and still
only trade two micros. Sometimes I scale
out three micros, but that's max. It's
all you need. Honestly, it's all you
need. That that's your biggest friend.
If you move to minis and you got to do
it a when you're a very good trader and
very confident or b when you've built
the buffer. If you move to minis too
early, you are a prop firm's best friend
because you are likely to get get caught
in something.
I would actually love to trade the
cattle market.
The one I was looking at last year was
uh is it caca?
The cow.
Am I spelling it wrong?
I can't see it. Why am I being stupid?
There we go.
This last year because we got that
overextension.
Look at this.
Back down it comes. All right. This is
what I was looking at last year. It's
when we had like no chocolate in the
world.
Big old ripper.
So [\h__\h] dumb.
So dumb.
All right, back to that gray box.
Edge of value on the day. If you get a
squeeze through this, the things I'd be
considering now is still bullish, but
you're coming into premium. So like if
you rebid this, you want to be selling
some into this and then holding runners
here. here. You want to see a base and
hold above it for expansion. If you're
going to get that IB rotation, then
you're going to see that failed break
and then come back inside. And if you're
going to play the IB trade specifically,
then you'd be looking for that trade
back towards VWAP. But uh just be
cautious on that today. The way we've
built out very very thick underneath.
Yeah. Don't This is what I was saying to
you, Sean. Honestly, my friend, it's the
easiest way to lose money. Right. This
trade here is the hardest trade in the
book. Right. I know like that trade
there is the hardest trade in the book,
right? Why? Because it's not the
protrend. So if we think about
if your higher time frame, if your
daily, let's say the daily is doing this
and then the hourly we're doing this,
right? Then your one minute is doing
this.
Yeah.
Right. Daily hourly M1. What you just
tried to catch is this move here. Right.
You tried to catch this this part of
this when the easier move to get is that
is that is that is this. Is that Does
that make sense? Oh, don't do that. Oh,
I need this back in there. Please
move that along.
All right. So, you want to be pro trend
as much as possible.
As much as possible, you want to be
protrend. It makes your life way easier.
It would be much more forgiving for you
as well, right? I mean, way more
forgiving for you. If you're wrong
protrend, right? If you're long
protrend, if your narrative is that
we're moving higher on a daily and an
hourly for etc., If you're wrong, you
might get wicked out by a tiny bit and
then keeps going, keeps going. But if
you're wrong, counter trend. Oh my god,
look how wrong you are. Right? Why are
we moving higher? Think about all the
shorts that came in. Oh, we're short.
Blown up. Short again. Blown up. Short
again. Blown up. Short again. Blown up.
Short again. Oh, we're right. We're
right. We're right. Oh, [\h__\h] We're not
wrong. Short again. Yes, we're winning.
We're Oh, [\h__\h] We're wrong. Right. Look
how many times they lose. How many times
did buyers lose?
They didn't. This pivot created this
high. It's why I said I wouldn't be
short. But like maybe if you got long
here, you got wicked out and you got
back in. I don't know. But that makes
sense. Hopefully that makes sense to
you.
Do you show in your order flow course
how to set up everything? I do. Yes.
Yes. So it's identical. I do. And if you
want this setup here for Trading View,
there's a video for free on my YouTube.
You don't even need to do the course,
right? I literally go over it in Trading
View. I think I posted that last
weekend. Not the weekend just gone, the
one before. So, you can I don't tell you
how to use it. I tell you how to use it
in the course, but I do show you how to
set it up for free.
I'm short. 25526.
Should I just take my loss? Uh you're so
you're swinging short from down here.
I mean, yeah, you're you're out of
position.
You're out position cuz we're haven't
we're not underneath the 550s. You're
you're really out of position.
I wouldn't be holding that. But I mean,
I don't know what your strategy is, so I
don't want to tell you what to do. But
right now, we're we're trading the other
side of the range. If we start the base
today above here, you're going to be in
big trouble, I think.
I'm up $489 from this pump. Let's go.
What is the easiest setup? Yeah,
protrend. The easiest setup. What you're
seeing right now, prot.
Yeah, bookmark setup also in the course.
Every bookmap, volume profiles, delta,
um footprint charts, everything is in
the orderflow course. Absolutely.
Do I show how to set up Apex account
somewhere? Um, I don't know. Sure, I do.
It's pretty self-explanatory. buy
account. They give you your trading the
uh trade of eight login if you use trade
of eight. Log into trade of eight
approve it all and then log into your
system whether you're using Ninja or
whatever you're doing and that's it.
It's pretty straightforward.
What price is a huge seller defending?
Well, the biggest lot right now on the
book is 900. There's 113 lot defending
at 9 900. But there's liquidity above
him. Let's zoom out. We've got liquidity
all the way up into 930 right now. In
fact, we've got liquidity up at 950.
Yeah, 950 is the highest liquidity of
the day with anything reasonable. There
is a little bit at 26,000 to be fair,
but yeah, 900's currently being
defended.
I would say you're probably going to
trade through it.
So now see this last dip, the IB, which
is also the old naked point of control.
It is starting to hold, right? So if
they keep rebidding this, they're trying
to try trade to this set of stops here
and then we have more stops up here. All
right? So if they can hold this, they'll
trade to here. If they let go of this,
this would be the failed look above the
IB. I'd be cons you'd con consider it
sub 77. If you really wanted to try and
trade that IB trade, it's a riskier
trade today because we're moving value
higher. But
if you're absolutely adamant on it, I
would say you've got to get closes
underneath 77. But look how look at the
structure, the way we've built out
structure. All right, there's lots of
nodes here which they can use to bid
off. That's the only thing. But if we
let go of this, there is an argument for
this. Again, it's counter trend, but
it's based on a very specific trade, a
look above and fail of the IB for a
trade back down to VWAP. I'm not
convinced we do it today, but it's
possible right now. Until you get under
this gray box, you couldn't even think
about it. And even then, would be my
least favorite trade today, I'd say.
even if it works out.
I think you can use any of those prop
firms now for order flow. I think
they're all approved with trade of eight
that it's again it's on my YouTube uh
Enrique there's a free video how to get
free order flow. It's on my YouTube.
you where where you getting your data
from on your trading view for that? I
haven't got that. That's crazy.
That's crazy, man. That drop you're
talking about.
Lowhanging fruit you can catch mainly in
the first hour. Not necessarily. Not
necessarily. No, it's it just happened
that today we got that. Sometimes we
don't go for low hanging fruit. This was
the same targets we had Friday. We never
got there. It was the last target for
Friday. If anyone traded with me for
Friday, we were holding for this move.
We never got there. Right? So, it
doesn't always happen. It just today
they went for it. Right. Today, they
went for it.
Any opinion on Quant tower or ATAS for
order flow? If I have bookmap, do I need
anything else for orderflow like smart
tape and ATS? I don't use ATAS. They've
actually emailed me quite a few times
asking me to um
like become a teacher on it and stuff,
but I don't use it. I'm I partner with
Ninja Trade. That's that's who I that's
who I work with. It's who I like using.
So I I don't want to comment on that. Z
I've heard very very good things. I know
Quantau is very good especially for um
like its profile levels and and tape
reading levels on the right hand side.
It's really really nice.
What's the best volume profile indicator
to use on Trading View that's similar to
yours? Uh, this is a Trading View
indicator, anchored volume profile,
right? It's free. Completely free. All
right, back to these key levels, right?
If you start to lose this, all right, if
they stay heavy versus this and this,
all right, there's an argument for this
trade here. Again, I'm not going to take
it because it's counter trend. So, I
know it's an IB trade, but I think it's
very, very risky today based on what
they've done here, here, this, it's
this,
but the trade back to here is possible,
but I'd be very, very cautious. It would
have to, you'd have to see this with a
clear rejection. I'm very unconvinced of
that trade today. Um,
sellers just got caught there again.
Look at these sellers at the low. This
candle just caught there again. And
there you go. They're getting squeezed
out.
Nothing in this tape telling me to sell
it right now.
motive wave the same. I I don't use I
don't use it, guys. Like, it's not cuz
it's bad or anything like that. I just
can't comment. I have never used it, so
I don't want to comment about it. I've
heard good good things, but I can't
comment.
Tyson, 600 times 4 PA today. I'm going
to call it a day. Hey mate, look at you
on a roller. On a roller.
Was I 100% sure my first trade from open
I was told I should wait till first
15minute candle and go from there. Um I
mean I was fairly convinced we're going
to go move up but I got wicked out of it
either way. Right. But this but after
that I was very I was I was very very
sure. I don't wait 15 minutes. If the
trade's there I take the trade. Right.
If you're new, it's fine to wait 15
minutes. Like firstif first first five
15 minutes can be very volatile, but
sometimes there's a trade at the open
there to be had. Not always. You'll see
sometimes I wait hours to trade.
I did have a nice short and naked Vpo on
ES today. Was lucky. Got 10 handles.
Nice work, SP. As long as you're being
sticking to your rules, whatever those
are, it's all that matters. Remember, I
guys, anything I'm teaching you or I'm
talking about here is how I trade. I
want to make it really clear. It is not
gospel. All right? If you find edge in
the market in any single way that you
trade, stick to your edge in the market.
This is how I trade. This is how I like
to execute. This is what makes sense to
me. This is what makes me money. This is
what keeps me safe. But there's lots of
different ways to trade. If you found
Edge, great. If there's another
mentor or whatever that you like to use,
fantastic. Like, as long as you guys
make money, it's literally all that
matters.
Uh, DCT, cuz I can't draw in Ninja
Trader. I can't like draw and switch
between accounts, right, and look at the
SPY and look at the hourly quickly and
look at the VIX and look at QQQ. That's
the only reason
like I can't even do this. I can't even
do this like on Ninja, right? Can't move
it around the same way. I can't draw
like this. I can't show you what I'm
looking at. I can't teach you. That's
all it is.
So, I just execute on there. That's that
that's all it is, my friend.
Um those in Discord will tell you I will
post. I I still do the same on Discord
when I'm drawing out. like when I'm
drawing out, I'm drawing it on here cuz
it's it's just way easier for me to draw
on. But if I'm taking actual trades, I
don't know how far I'd have to go up the
last time we took a trade together in
here last week somewhere. But if I'm
taking executions, I will show the
execution in Discord on on Ninja Trader,
but I will always do the teaching on
Trading View. Always, always, always,
always it'll be on Trading View. See all
of these trading views and then we get
into some Ninja Traders. some of the
other guys even the same for bookmap
everyone we will always draw it out
where we can see it see still all in
discord in in uh trading view
and it shows how long since it's been an
afternoon trade. It's been a while
and it's been a really long time by the
looks of it.
really long.
And there was one there maybe.
Yeah, that's the only reason
As mentioned earlier, I can't see an
edge in bookmap over footprint. And then
that's good for you. SPT,
I like it cuz I like seeing where the
liquidity above is and below and I like
seeing who's spoofing. So that is edge
that you already don't get in footprint,
right? You don't have any historical
data on people who haven't filled their
orders. So if there's someone spoofing
or moving around or jostling, you won't
you won't see him unless you're very
very good at reading the bid and ask it
moves up and down and people pull.
Are my homies with Dom? Yeah, I am.
good friends with Dom. Why is that?
What does delta divergence usually
signify? Uh it's all about who's in
control of the market. So we can see if
we have any divergence today in the
market
pretty much in line. Um but we actually
had passive buyers today. So if we go to
just a five minute.
All right, if this is delta, all right,
so we got aggressive buyers stepping in
and aggressive take moving higher. All
right, price moves higher. We see a
pullback here in Delta. So we see some
aggressive sellers stepping in. We see
aggressive uh pullback and then we see
buyers step in. We only just about take
out that high on Delta, which means
there's a passive buyer here pushing
bids up. All right, which shows even
more strength if anything. We go
sideways from here. There's a little
pullback and we're pretty much in line.
We're making higher highs and higher
low. What you'd be looking for is
something like if if we were going to
put a high in, right? If we were going
to put a high in, what you'd want to see
is delta start to move down, all right,
and start to get stuck and buyers not
able to move it higher. Or you'd want
like to know that there's a passive
seller holding price here non-stop. So,
someone just unloading passively. So,
Delta can't move higher, which we might
get soon actually in fairness.
So, you're looking to see where the
passive sellers are, passive buyers are,
who's the aggressive into this gray box
again here, folks. This is your like
overunder. So, like I said, potentially,
it's not a trade I'm going to take, but
potentially if they lose this, there is
a trade down here, but you need to be
very aware of this down here today.
This would be the IB debt IB trade. Look
above and fail. If they stay heavy under
here, you would need this to stay heavy
to flip to sells and then you might get
that. It's not a trade I'm taking. I
want to make that clear. But for those
of you who like the IB trade, that is
potential.
Am I done today? Yeah, probably because
we hit low hanging fruit. I'm not really
looking for the counter trend trade back
down.
guy at 900 looks spoofy. No, not for me.
He's not left the tape all day. He's
been on there all day. We're going to
come and tap into him. In fact, he's got
thicker. He's He's literally never left
the tape once today. He doesn't look
spoofy to me. We We'll see.
He's been there with a 100 lot all day.
Oh, don't move that, Alex. So, if we get
through the next target is sort of these
907s and then we come into a bunch of
stops here. is great. It's gray box
which are stops from
the 15th of Jan. All right, 15th of Jan.
All right, so those are the stops. And
if we get through those, then we have
room, right? If we get through these
stops,
then we have room up into here. That's a
big ask, but you never know. They turn
the booster jets on. You just don't
know.
So, they're still looking for this move
to 900 if they can. He's still on the
tape. You can see him above this red
block. And I can show you like he has
literally not moved all day, right? If
we zoom out here, he's been on here
since the start of the session. Look, he
came on the tape here.
What time was this? Right at the open.
93031.
9:32. He's been on on the tape since
9:32. Looking to get filled 100 lot up
here in 900. It's not a huge amount of
size to be honest. 100 lot. It's not
like we're seeing a thousand lot, which
we do see sometimes.
You can see they're trying to hold these
bids here for that squeeze up into him.
Alex, I like to see you back to the man
you were a month ago. I'm back. Thanks,
Raph.
uh f like not necessarily individual
bars but like on on like five minutes as
we start to build like we're still
seeing aggressive buyers step like so
right now delta is aggressively trying
to move higher and we're unable to do it
which means there is passive selling
there is 100% right right now passive
selling here because we are trying to
move higher delta is pushing higher and
we're not able to so that is a sign that
someone is unloading here right so it's
very possible we we fade under this but
this this is what makes it hard the way
we've built out structure. Look at this
node. Look at this PC. Like I keep
saying, if we lose these levels,
then there might be a trade down. But
again, it's counter trend. It's not the
best trade in the book. All we're seeing
right now is there is a seller here. We
know he's up towards 900.
But if you look at Delta, it was uh
creeping higher and higher and higher
without price moving higher.
Hey, Alex. After using Bookmap for a
while now, what's it missing that would
make it better?
Um,
I think the DOM could be a little
better.
Um,
I don't know. I don't use any of the
add-ons because I don't think I I need
them.
Um, I'm sure like lots of the add-ons
can be useful, but I I quite like it.
It's it's it's easy enough as it is. I
don't think I have any major criticisms
of it or anything like that.
Maybe like a
maybe the way it looks, to be honest,
could be a bit better. Just like the
actual detail of how it looks, like even
the the the profiles and stuff, it's a
bit like pixy and janky. Maybe that
could be smoothened out a bit.
The candles are closing funny as this
usual. What do you mean they're closing
funny? I don't think it's just normal
and sideways.
How would I characterize spoofers
that they literally have to leave the
tape, right? So, see this this guy above
us? If you just see this solid red line,
he's been there since the open, right?
He's never left. Now, if we trade up
towards him and he pulls his order and
he moves it higher, let's say he moves
from 900 to 20 to 30 to 50 to right,
then he's a spoofer. What does that
mean? If he's lifting, right, then he's
a buyer looking to sell higher. Or he's
a buyer attracting price. Come and get
me. Come and get me. Come and get me.
Come and get me. Come and get me. Come
and get me. Right? That's a spoofer. A
spoofer is someone coming on the tape,
off the tape, on the tape, off the tape,
on the tape, off the tape, trying to
move price around. If he's just there
and not moving, there's nothing in this
right now to say he's he's anything but
a legit seller. He's never left the
tape, not once.
There you go. Literally just what Adam
said. Yeah. Ridiculous size coming on
the opposite side of the movement and
then moving it around to catch eyes.
Exactly.
Do you see passive buyers and sellers?
If if you do see a big move coming, do
Hey, Alex, do you see passive buyers and
sellers? If so, so do you see a big move
coming?
I'm not sure what you mean. As in right
now, I mean, there's a passive seller at
900. If we trade through him, maybe
there's a squeeze out, but maybe that's
the top of the auction for the day. Um,
all we see right now is a huge amount of
liquidity being built.
We're getting stuck right here.
This is your build out.
Their target is to come and take the 900
out and maybe lift. And if they get
lucky, they come into all these stops up
here, right? If there's a passive seller
slams 900 and above. I can only see
really a guy at 900 right now. There are
guys above him, but if they chase the
market down and they sell under here on
a retest, then we'll get the rotation.
There's nothing else to look at right
now. that that that's all there is right
now. ES stuck between its new. So ES by
the way has done the IB trade. All
right, that's another thing we should
mention. ES has done the IB trade. IB
high
2 VW.
IB high 2 V. It's done the trade right
now. It's in the middle of the two. It's
already completed it.
Sorry guys, I'm trying to read all your
questions here.
Um,
I just joined when the delta moves but
the price not really as you mentioned.
What is it meaning? All right, so if
you've got positive delta, right, if
you've got big positive delta but price
isn't moving higher, it means you got a
passive seller. means you got someone
just unloading on the limit, right? Just
unloading, unloading, unloading, which
which is when you can get buyers stuck
because you got big aggressive buyers,
delta moving higher, but price can't
move higher, right? It means you got a
passive seller. So if you then come
under that neath that price of delta
point where those guys come in, we get
weak, right? Which is probably going to
be here. All right? All right. So, if
we've got big aggressive buyers keep
stepping in here, if they don't get
their way and we get stuck under here,
then their stop run can open up this
move. All right. This is what I keep
talking about. If we come under here and
we reject it, this can open up because
if we have big positive delta above
this, they will get caught. So, we can
have a look at that
right here.
And you have positive delta above 85s
right now. All right. So, we're coming
into this sort of key level. If we start
to lose this, the last time buyers came
in were 60s and then 40s. So, we might
very well drop down into 60s and 40s
here. If we start to lose this gray box,
right? If we lose this gray box, 60s.
Look at the profile. 60s
and 40s, right? So, if these become
trapped buyers, we might well get this
flush to here and here.
And they will have to reject this. They
have to reject this to get that. If they
reclaim that, this is a look below,
fail, and a rotation back up again.
Right? So, these will be the trades that
you can look for. You're adamant on
short. It must reject this here, and
you'd be looking for this node and this
node.
Like I said, buyers currently are caught
above 85, definitely above 91, but they
have been uh stepping in at 60 today. So
that's where they're trying to hold.
They're trying to hold 60 here.
So this will need to reject now for
sellers to take control or at least to
fade down to to 60, which is what
they're trying to do. They're trying to
aggressively step in here. If they fail
to do it, there will be a squeeze. If
they reclaim this gray box, there'll be
a squeeze out to higher day. That's the
two sides of the tape. So if sellers can
step in here, you get this. If they
reclaim, then there'll probably squeeze
out.
There you go. There's a reclaim. So, if
they base above this, there will
probably be a high day squeeze out. Now,
that's the battle. That's literally how
they battle over an area. That's why
today I've said I'm not going to trade
the short because there's just not for
me. There's not enough edge in the short
today. Doesn't mean it doesn't do it,
but it just means like is it a favorable
short? Is it where I think it has to
happen? No, not really. doesn't have to
happen today. It can happen, but the way
we've built structure out, you know, am
I going to am I going to like I probably
would have just got stopped out here
again. Maybe now they're going to do it
down to 60 and then I've got to argue
with myself. Am I really looking for 10
points and hoping I get 30 points when
I've had 100 100? Not really. Right. So
maybe they do this. Maybe you get lucky
and come to here. It just fail IB. It's
kind of nasty. This is like NQ. This is
how it did me at the lower day. Pop
through it and then fades away. So your
TP if you are in this short and you
really want to take this short your 40
is here. There you go. And then then 60
here. Sorry. And then 40s. Right. These
are your targets. So TP1 is about to be
hit. TP2 is down into this block here.
And did we reject those sellers? Get all
my screens up. Remember we just talked
about where these sellers were, where
these buyers were. Or give me that Ninja
Trader screen back.
No, don't say that's just left. I need
it back. There we go. All right. So,
that pop up. Where were the buyers
caught? We talked about them caught
above 86s, 85s, and 90s. So, we rejected
that into this imbalance here of 60. See
the how they're bidding at 60 where the
buyers came in earlier. We're rebidding
60. This is why I'm saying you're going
to take the shorts, you've got to be
taking partials into each one of these.
You do not know if it's going to fade.
So you have to respect it because
overall structure is still bullish,
right? That's your range right now. This
swing low to this swing high. This can
still be protected if they want. If you
get lucky, you will get this.
Working hard to try and teach you guys
today.
No, definitely isn't nothing for free.
Uh, jockey.
Spoofing is illegal. It is, but you've
got to prove that they're spoofing. And
it's quite hard to do. They might just
be like, "Well, I wanted that price and
then it came up and I didn't want that
price." And you know, yeah, Luna's
great. She's doing great. Thanks, mate.
She's currently asleep in my bed. All
right. So, maybe you guys will get your
40s now. So I'd be watching into sort of
45 all the way down to 33s. I would be
taking at least 80% off into here. All
right? Because you are not expecting
price to move under here today. If you
get under there, you'd be very very
happy. So you've hit TP1. This is TP2.
Buyers became trapped up here. Failed to
break higher. It whipped you out
probably the first time and then dropped
down because it's NQ and it's a little
[\h__\h] that way. And now you have to see
what's what.
Uh, it's called City Footprint. It's a
paid indicator.
No worries, guys. Doing my best here.
How does one participate in the
giveaways? Uh, I'll I'll tell you. We
We'll do it in the next 20 minutes or
so.
Yeah, it's it's like I said, it's
definitely possible, right? Think about
the structure. Ignore all ignore all
everything else. Think about the
structure.
Main structure.
That's your main structure, right? Until
we break below this, we are still
technically bullish. Okay, this is why
I'm ignoring this trade. It's exactly
why I'm ignoring this trade. If we were
pro if we were protrend down, right, I'd
be much willing to hit that trade
because the if we did a magnet, it would
be much more likely, right, to come down
here if the protrend was lower. Right
now, the pro trend is not lower. All
right, look, we're bidding above
previous week value area high. We're
bidding above previous day value area
high. We're not even in a rotation. The
rotation was in here, right? We're above
the rotation, right? We're above the
rotation. The protrend is higher. This
is why I was saying like you have to
take partials counter trend. Remember
this morning we I went over that example
of drawing what a pro trend on a daily
is right daily
hourly
1 minute.
Right? What you just took is this.
Right? If you took that short what you
took is this. But the easier move is
higher. Remember we went over that a
couple hours ago or an hour ago or so.
All right, so there you go. Didn't even
get to that 40s, did it? Held in the low
volume node. Didn't even get down here.
Held it and reclaimed and reclaimed the
squeeze. So maybe that can explain to
you the trade, why it's set up, but also
why I didn't take it, why I was
unwilling to take it today.
Fundamentally, there's no reason for NQ
to go up. Um, I actually disagree with
that.
I actually strongly disagree with that.
I wish I didn't disagree with it, CC. I
really wish I didn't disagree with it
because I want the market to do a
gigantic pullback.
Um, but what you might see is a bunch of
liquidity coming into ENQ um, based on
what's going on in Asia, especially as
they position into this week. Hopefully
that doesn't happen. Hopefully we get a
giant sell-off. I would much rather that
happens, but uh, yeah, it's very, very,
very, very, very possible um, with
what's going on in Japan that you see
more liquidity coming to the market. I
would also just watch out for some of
Trump's comments. I mean, if his cronies
based on what he said in Davos last
week, it's not too dissimilar to what he
said in April last year when he said buy
the market. He's talking about the
market doubling at the moment. Like, I
don't want to believe his [\h__\h] but
you you just [\h__\h] wonder. We've been
going sideways for a while. I would much
rather see this market pull back. I'm
with you, CC. I know what I'd like to
see, but at the moment, we're not seeing
it. We are just not seeing it.
the New York VM map. Where is that in
Trading View? It It is not in Trading
View. You can just do an anchor view up
to the New York Open. This is an
indicator made by uh someone in our
Discord. So, if you're in Discord, you
can get it for free. It's not mine, so I
can't give it out.
Mr. Biggest Nobody, my first time here.
Good to listen to you explain. Oh, thank
you for joining.
Santa rally moved to Chinese New Year.
That's hilarious. What is it? Is it year
of the horse? Is that right?
I don't know if Iran will cause a drop
to be honest.
War very very rarely is bad for the
market.
Um
the the mark what I'd say look new
highs.
All I can say is this market uh is very
very very strong and when it should be,
you know, letting go, it isn't. And all
we can do is this sell is still up here.
By the way, folks, you just had a
192 lot try and buy through him and he's
still there absorbing the tape. So just
be aware of that. So now you have major
divergence. You have delta now negative
and us at alltime highs. Alltime highs,
high of day, sorry. All right. So, you
have divergence here in the tape, which
means you've got someone trying to step
up.
It's a one minute SPT. This is just a
one minute here.
They renamed the year of of Trump. He
owns everything now, even the calendar.
It's my calendar.
China. No more China. Trump calendar.
They said it was the year of the horse.
It's not. It's the year of the bull.
We're bullish.
All right. So, next target. Still got to
get through these 900s. He's still here.
This seller is legit, guys. He's still
here. And uh and then once you get
through that, you're looking at 9007s.
And then there's a ton of stops up here
into 950s. All right. So, that that 100
lot just got filled. He was not a
spoofer like I said. So 261 lot buy side
just come in here and filled him into
900. So you have buyers coming in here
trying to aggressively push this market
higher now and their next level to get
into is 25s and after 25s they're
looking for 55s.
This is why I was saying I personally
wouldn't be bearish today. We called
this trade down here but I gave you the
good reason I wouldn't take it. Even
look at the flow zones. Deep pullback
absorbed it. All right. the rolling fibs
absorbing.
Why am I so good at that? Just probably
watch Shane list too much to be honest.
Fake news. Fake news. Fake news. Did
anyone watch the uh Oh, look at this.
All right. Stops now. Popped. Squeezes
on.
Oh,
I would have actually bid if we come
down into here again. I would have rebid
it. Uh, so next level 25s now. So like
if you any of you are still in this,
like this is your level to take TP. 97's
top of the red box. And the next level
you're looking at is 925 and 955. Really
nice day.
Have I watched Tires? Yeah, I love
Tires. Love all those guys.
Love all those guys. You're in it. Nice.
DT.
Trap sellers down there. Yeah. Let's
have a look. Where's my mouse?
Come on.
Yeah. So, trap sellers came in here as
we started to break underneath this low.
Look at the amount of selling that came
in
right under 67 down into 50. All these
sellers got absorbed instantly and now
they're out the money. So, they are
causing this squeeze up and we now have
a new pivot here. But definitely at
these highs, you have some buyers. Look
at these uh 900s and above. So, you're
going to need to see this keep
auctioning up and then pull back and
rehold the dips because we can see here
strong buying came in with moving point
of control higher. I'd say as long as
they're holding over 96s or somewhere
over there, we should see continuation
for a squeeze.
But you know, you don't want to be
buying at high day. Don't be adding a
new position here. You've got targets
above to add into to sell into. Got Alex
try and talk properly. So this level
here like we keep talking about 925 and
then 950.
And then if you get very lucky today,
you'll get sort of 26,015.
Nice, Dean. Great work.
How can you join Discord? Uh, it's for
members only. All right. It's not a paid
Discord, but you do have to do the
course. We talk about that uh quite a
lot. Um, it's not because I'm trying to
gatekeep. It's actually so that the
Discord works well for everyone trading
the same way. All right. So, if you go
to flzontrader.com
and it's just a onetime fee to do the
course. You want to go to this trading
course here. It should be they should
have put prices up. If they haven't,
they still haven't put it up. So 649
onetime fee. All right. It's a 20hour on
demand course and you get a version of
the flow zones and discord for life. All
right. So
it's just so that everyone in Discord
then knows what they're looking at. All
right. Everyone's trading the same way
because from experience I've been in
lots of Discords over the years when
they start to go wrong and fail. It's
when they're either free or they're
gatekeeped at monthly fee and everyone's
trading in different direction. Here you
go. So starting to lift now. 26 is now
they are adding liquidity above now into
the 30s. So squeeze will be here all the
way up to 30s at the moment and then
through there 950s. All right. And then
we've got a big pivot here into 950s. We
get over 950s, my expectation would be
26,000 on the day. Right? If we can get
over 950s, then my expectation would be
26,000.
There are a few more bonus. What are
these in in your courses? What do you
mean, Alli?
I'm not really sure what you mean there,
my friend. Let me know what you mean.
I'll try and answer any questions. Yeah,
don't chase FC SFC
GC tanking. It's still up 1.83%. Let me
have a look.
It's just in a range till it lets go of
all of this. It's just in a range. It's
a It's a decent pullback on the day,
don't get me wrong, but like higher time
frame, right? Some profit taking maybe
it's got a long way to to call it a
tank. It's got to get under all this
liquidity really for there to be a a
bigger move.
So, into that gray box. So, you hit TP2.
So, TP1, TP2, TP3 up here. And if you
get really lucky, uh, your previous week
value area high, no, not previous week,
the week before will be 26,020ish.
You should, you should be locking in no
matter what.
Which prop firms do you trade with or
live and do you copy trade? Yeah, I I
did a video on this a couple weeks ago.
Um, top five prop firms to trade with
are Apex, uh, Funded Next, Lucid,
Tradeify, Take Profit Trader. Those are
the five that I trade with. And do I
trade my own money as well? Yeah, but
mainly uh, swing positions, right? Swing
positions for my own money.
Just took another I can just show you
here. Just took another literally just
came in. It's another payout request
from TPT.
just gone through now. Fantastic.
So the question is now, do they pull
back and hold or are they done with it?
Are they done with it? It would still be
the same levels for the remainder of the
day, right? Until they let go of all
this node, there's just no reason to get
short. And really, the biggest short
will come when we let go of all of this.
And we might not.
All right, 25 minutes left and then
we're going to do uh giveaways and all
that good stuff.
Is that email gone?
Is there a website in your website?
There are a few bonus courses and
indicators with extra charge. Yeah. So,
like if you want the pro indicator, it's
an extra charge. or if you want to
upgrade to the um
uh volume and orderflow course, you get
like $100 off off that if you do it like
all in one go. That's just up to you.
You don't have to do it.
So, from overnight low to 26k, 700 point
day. Yeah, there you go. CC. Crazy, but
it's very possible. I mean, look, we're
only 64% up on the day, right? Because
you got to remember the the gap fill was
here, right? This yellow line is last
week's close, right? This yellow line,
right? So everything that happened
overnight,
I don't know if you you on the on the
weekly newsletter, but this was the big
level. All right, they reclaimed. All
right, look at below and fail. They
held, they came down, they held again.
That's 550 showing strong. They fill the
gap. All right, now we're flat on the
day and now we're bullish. All right, so
all that happened was anyone who was net
short got smoked.
Most people would have been net long
down there, though. There was no reason
to be net short down there.
Remember 550 to 750 was the rotation.
Take care. Take care FSC. I hope you had
a good day.
Stop loss hit with profit. Nice work,
DCT.
Flow zone pro system indicator for Ninja
Trader and bonus offer. This is required
or only learn trade the markets for
beginning to rot is more than enough.
I'm not I'm really sorry. I'm not really
sure what you're saying. If you need the
indicator for Ninja Trader, then yeah,
you'll need to upgrade. But if you don't
need it, don't upgrade. Don't not like
it all depends what you're looking to
learn and what you trade on.
Oh, sorry, Jake. Yeah, still haven't
done that. I'm really sorry. We'll do.
We'll do. I'll put it on my list to do.
Low volume node. What does it represent?
Uh where no volume's really been traded.
Where we've traded through aggressively
very quickly. Where there has not been
price acceptance. But
this is price acceptance down here. This
was an area fair value because we traded
there for a while. Then they deemed it
was too cheap. We moved aggressively
away from it. We had an area fair value
deem here. And then they deemed for a
moment it was too expensive. So we
traded aggressively below it. Here's the
low volume. Here's the high volume. Then
they went, "No, no, no, no. We've
already said that this is too cheap. Go
back up." Okay, go back up. Trade
sideways. Now we're searching for higher
prices. Now it's in an auction looking
to see are we going to find fair value
here. Right? If we don't then if we
can't find fair value then we'll come
back down and look for fair value again.
We know there are stops up here at the
top of the gray box as their next target
and then over that 26,000.
Hunter Porsche, thank you for your
analysis. You are insane. Hopefully you
mean insane in a good way.
So, when am I going to short? Well,
right now,
I can't see a short developing today.
There might be a counter short down a
little bit, but until we let go of all
this volume, until there is a reason for
this market to let go of this and this,
all right, until there's a failure,
right, underneath all of this, then
there's a rotation back down. But right
now, the only short would be a counter
trend pullback, right? That's all we're
going to that's all that today might
offer. If it offers a short, it's
probably going to be a counter trend
pullback. If you get really lucky, it
comes down there for a continuation. But
this is the pivot. We are bullish over
750 right now.
We are bullish over 750 right now.
uh the other day Dave, if you need it
now, my friend, just scroll towards the
end of the course and there's a module
that talks about Discord and then you
just do what it says in that module and
I can add you straight away.
No, I don't think many people use wealth
charts here. Simpleton simpleton Jeep,
sorry.
$2 away from passing TPT. Just take your
time. Don't force a trade. Don't worry
about the money. Focus on the setup.
But we did get a good IB breakout trade.
I didn't take it. What should I have
been looking for to possibly take it
next time? Just that mini flag
once we reclaimed. I mean, it's not
ideal because we are so close to to uh
TPS here, right? Because you've set up
the IB here. All right. And your target
is one, two, three. It's not ideal. I'm
going to be honest with you. What would
a better IB have been? Well, if we
hadn't taken low for hanging through,
let's say IB was here,
right?
That would have been a good IB trade
because you got room. I would say the IB
trade today, although bullish, right?
This is the same thing, right? Look, I
want you to see these traps that we talk
about.
Liquidity
trap liquidity inverse head and shoulder
two-leg liquidity trap liquidity. That's
your t your long trigger. But you
haven't got much room which is the
problem now. You're buying premium to
sell premium. What you want to do is buy
discount to sell premium.
And really really we were buying
previous days fair value actually and
then we actually bought premium but now
we're deep in premium.
No, they're not really order blocks.
They're
they're where stops have been placed.
They're they're high volume nodes. I
mean, you could call them that, I guess.
How is the gray box level determined
based on volume?
Alex, I heard a guy recently made 900ks
in two days on TPT over 550k accounts
and managed to cash it out with no
problems.
What do you think's the ideal scenario
and contract number would be needed? I
don't think you can do that unless he's
on a live they would they would they
will cash you out at um 10k each account
and maybe if they moved him to live they
they would have done it. If he was on a
live then yeah for sure he could have
done it.
Uh what do you think the ideal scenario
and contract number would be needed?
Well they would have had to be well
above their buffer and scaled in to a
trend day. So if if they were, you know,
today wouldn't have been bad if they
were trading GlobeEx.
So if they did bought this, for example,
and then rebid this and then rebid this
and they have a core position down here
with some big size. So they're 500 and
they're 400 points higher, right? With
some big size. That will do it. And if
we keep going, that'll do it even more.
But I mean, just don't worry about it.
Just focus on your setup. Don't worry
about all of that.
Okay. So, gray box getting tagged.
Here's your shelf here. Again, buyers
will now want to defend this into here.
Right? This is your sentiment for the
day. Buyers must defend this. If they
start failing to defend that, then maybe
there's a rotation, but I'll again be
somewhat cautious today. I'm definitely
done for the day. 15 minutes left. I
want to do some giveaways. How we doing
for the likes? Or you can do some
giveaways.
Yeah, exactly. Trader Rick, just like
Woff, same same kind of thing, right?
My plan is to show up every day with
you. Maybe I can win a volume course
with Discord. Oh, we don't give away
those courses. This is only like the
introduction courses.
Sorry, too too invaluable those.
Uh yeah, it's very possible he was a
swing. He could have been a swing long
buyer. The guy selling 900. Yeah, very
very possible. Very possible.
Overall market not in sync. Um, you've
probably just got a sector like a little
bit weaker. Let's have a look.
Uh, energy. So, energy today is a bit
weaker. All right. So, you got Exxon,
COP, VLOO,
um,
FNG, KMI, MPC, all down on the day. So,
that's the sector showing weakness. Um,
nothing really out. Some of the semis
are down a little bit. Nvidia a little
bit red. MU, AMD, INTC all red, but
they're being outpriced by the size of
Apple, Google, Meta, Oracle, and
Microsoft moves. All of those bigger.
Um, and Tesla also red. But yeah, the
breadth I guess industrials are down a
little bit. Farm down a bit. A little
bit.
Yeah, that's that's why finance is
looking good, which is holding uh ES
kind of steady. here. Finance starts
rotating red with energy. Healthcare's
uh green as well. Looking okay. Not big
green, but it is green.
Okay. So, back down into the shelf we
just talked about. Remember, this is the
level. Now, buyers will need to defend
to maintain structure for price to move
higher. This is now your swing point.
This low
created this high. This is the structure
buyers want to defend. they fail to
defend this structure then there's again
a rotation. I will be ignoring rotations
today.
New York VW how to set up um still
bidding off that gray box. If you don't
have an indicator the best way is just
to come I'll show you where's my anchor.
Is it here?
anchored view up. See this setting here?
Anchored VW up. Right. You'd want to set
anchored view up. And you go to the 9:30
print.
Your opening candle of the day. Click on
this. Go to the 9:30. Click on that.
There you go. There's your anchor.
That's your 9:30 print. Right. Your New
York VW. So, you can just do an anchored
VWAP off it.
And again, there's a free video on my
YouTube all about anchored VWs, how to
use them.
Is this a bull flag? ES. Uh, it doesn't
look like it to me. It looks like a bit
more like a wedge. You're making higher
highs and you're making you're making
higher lows and you're making lower
highs right now on ES. It's It's
struggling a little bit here to get that
breakout.
Wales. Does it refer to a big category?
No, just big just big participants in
the market, right? Just big
participants.
on ES. Yes, you've got a naked PC. You
got this PC higher on ES which we keep
failing at. I know what you're talking
about. Yeah, it can be. It's I mean it's
obviously it's fair value. So, if we're
trading up into fair value and they
can't get through it and they start
rejecting it, then we can trade lower
again. And this gray box here is
absolutely key for your sentiment for
the remainder of the day.
Right, I'm going to set up a giveaway
here for you guys who have stayed with
me all the way through.
Right, when we set any of these
giveaways up, please don't spam it. You
will get automatically banned and won't
be entered in the giveaway if you spam
it. So, just only need to press it once.
Okay.
Is anchored view up n on ninja trader
for free? Uh yes, I think so. Okay. Just
type FZT once.
Just type FCT once and we'll do a
giveaway.
And while you guys do that, I'm going to
use the bathroom and then I'll be right
back. and we'll give you guys an Apex
All
right, guys. Give you 30 more seconds
and we'll pull this winner.
Guys, you just get those of you entering
more than once. You don't get entered
more than once. It pulls you out. I did
warn you. Okay, I'm going to pull this
winner in five, four, three, two, and
one.
David Phillips 4186.
Congratulations. Free Apex count on the
way to you. just let me know you're here
and I'll tell you how to uh how I can
give it to you.
Nice. All right. Okay, David, all you
have to do me info@flowzonerader.com.
Send me a screenshot of you logged into
your YouTube just so I know it's you and
I will sort you out with a free Apex
account, any size that you want. It's
anywhere from 25K to 300K,
right? So, info@flowzonerader.com.
Okay, we'll do one more giveaway. Hang
on, we're going to do something
different. I'm going to give away an an
introduction course. So, this is good
for people who've never traded before.
All right, this course is only worth
$99. If you've never traded before, if
you don't understand anything in the
market, it's a good course to get you
started off on. All right, so just type
course once in chat. You can always give
it to a friend or family member as well.
A very very beginner course, very very
entry level.
Give you guys a couple minutes to do
that. As you can see, we're still
holding the gray box. You see why
there's no shorts for me? We're still
holding the edge of this node, right?
Every single dip today so far is being
absorbed. Until that changes, for me,
there's probably no edge short side. If
that changes and the sentiment changes,
then maybe there's a bit of edge.
And you've got what about 8 minutes left
to get into
Okay, you guys. 30 more seconds.
Alex, do you like the break and retest
of the naked PC? Um, we've kind of
already Oh, you mean to the downside or
the upside?
Yeah. I mean, look, this the only thing
that would per my interest and I don't
think I'm going to trade it would be
this, which is the old naked PC would be
to trade under it, get stuck in this
kind of node here and rotate down. But
even then, you're going to have to
respect everything we've built out.
We're very, very, very bullish for the
day. All right, this is just like a
straight grind. All right, trying to
come higher. All right, if they let go
of this, maybe there's a pull back into
it. Again, this is still counter trend.
We are not pro 10 short until we get
underneath all of this, right? Really,
and even on the weekly, it's got to let
go of 300, but maybe under 700, there's
a 550 rotation. Under 550, there's a 200
rotation. But really, anything here can
still be a pullback. So, if you're going
to take the short today, you're going to
have to be very, very careful.
All right, I'm going to pull this winner
in five, four, three, two, one.
Patel S2MS, are you here? Patel,
you meant bullish. Same story. Yeah, I
mean, if you hold it, yes, it's an IB
hold, but again, just remember you're
buying deep uh deep in into premium.
Remember, we opened up today at 739.
You're now trading 900s. Can it go
higher? Yeah. You just got to ask
yourself, do you want to be buying sort
of 8 880s 900 for expansion higher when
we've hit low hanging fruit? Okay,
Patel, same same story as we had for
David Phillips. All right, all I need
you to do is email me, please.
Info@flowzonerader.com.
Send me a screenshot of you logged in.
I've uh made a note of your name and I
will sort you out with an introduction
course. All right.
and get you all set up so you're ready.
F1 testing starts today.
Has uh have they announced who's they
might have announced it and I missed it.
Who's going to be a race engineer for um
Lewis? Have they said?
I know they got rid of the old
knob.
I am tempted to go to Melbourne in
March. Very tempted. A friend of mine's
going. It is tempting.
You haven't heard? Yeah.
Might win a race this season. Yeah. If
they can get their act together.
was a joke, wasn't it, last year? Geez,
what a joke.
What a joke. A bit like Arsenal and Rams
at the weekend. I couldn't have had
worse Sunday if I tried. I [\h__\h] knew
Arsenal would do that. And I knew
because we got the same owners at the
Rams. The moment that happened, the Rams
would blow it. And great. What a [\h__\h]
weekend for me.
Uh
oh, Cedric's going to do it.
Is that right?
No. Is that right?
It's a target. Has it been confirmed?
Hampton's. I'm going to look now. Could
be not confirmed yet. Be good if they if
they grabbed him.
Yeah, I know. Going Super Bowl. I know.
All right. All right, mate.
Stafford doesn't blow. I mean, I think
there was
there's some like really poor plays all
over the field, but No, I'm in LA. Los
Angeles.
Yeah, he's had a great season.
I think he was let I think he was let
down. Some weird play calls as well.
That's That's comment of the day. As a
Niners fan, I wanted both teams to lose.
Comment of the day. Oh, I love that.
Oh, it's funny. That is funny. Made me
giggle.
All right team, that's it. We are
basically into lunch here.
Nothing really moving now. Um, like I
said, I'm done, guys. We hit low hanging
fruit for me. Can it drift higher? Yeah.
Can we do a pullback trade? Yeah, we can
pull back under here. But I think I'm
I'm done for the day. But if I was you,
what I'd be looking for, um, you're
either managing your long position.
All right. So, if they can if they
continue to hold this gray box, we can
get rid of this now because we've traded
through it. There we go. If they
continue to hold this gray box, right,
then you're looking for extension up
into here. But, you know, I'm not going
to buy that cuz we're buying, remember,
we were buying today here, here, and
here. I don't really want to buy this
for this. We bought this for this, and
we bought this for this, and we bought
this for this. We don't really want to
buy up here. But if you are adamant on
adding to your position or or looking
for a new trade, then that is what you
can look for. If we lose this gray box,
right? If we lose
under here and we stay heavy, there is
potentially a rotation into VWAP into
this node here and previous week value
area high. They might very well rebid
off that again. If they don't rebid off
that, you're looking for next target
down current day and previous day value
area high. If they lose that then all
the way down into here. I would very
much doubt we see that. I would imagine
they will either bid this or bid this.
Um I can't really imagine them coming to
800s but is NQ maybe. I would love to be
a buy down here later in the week now.
750s again. That would be fantastic.
At the moment it's just a continuation
of the same play upside.
Oh I know. Uh, as soon as we fumbled the
punt return, I knew I I was the same,
man. He dropped it twice. Like,
Alec, I'm I need to stop. I just don't
get it. Like, having played rugby, I'm
just like, what are you How can you drop
that ball like that? Absolute douche.
First timer. Excellent work. Thank you.
You're You're welcome. Thank you for
joining. Appreciate you joining and and
following. We'll be back next year.
Yeah, we will. We will. Rams will be
back.
It was my first time and I'm super
amazed by what by what I see in here.
Planning to buy the course. Oh, thanks
for joining. Yeah, everyone that's new
here, thanks for joining. All the all
the regs, thank you as well. Love
trading with you guys. It's keeping me
going at the moment. As you know, I've
got going through some pretty tough
stuff right now and I genuinely love
trading with you guys. It's so much fun.
Makes it super enjoyable.
Do I ever trade ES? Very rarely
nowadays.
It does respect volume really well, but
I've just got so used to NQ.
What tea do I drink? Uh, at the moment
it's a Yorkshire. It's very English
Yorkshire tea. Okay. All right,
everyone. About to take out the high as
well. So, still looks good. Vick's
lowered debt as well. Uh, so you still
look good for now. All right. Peace and
love, everyone. Um, thanks for joining.
As ever, all the links are down below.
If you're interested in doing the course
or any of the courses, all the links are
down below. I would always say study
everything on my YouTube for free first
before you go and commit to spending any
money. Make sure you like how I teach.
And uh, if you do, then the links are
down below. As always, if you use code
FCT for your prop firms, it does help
me. I do make commission on that. It
goes straight back into providing things
like this completely for free where you
get 100 point winners. All right. So,
code FCT for all the prop firms other
than take profit trader. That's code
flow zone. I will see you tomorrow
morning, 9:15 Eastern time. Everyone in
Discord, I'll be back in about an hour.
I'm going to walk Luna and then I'll be
back. Peace and love. Be kind to each
other and use hard stops. All right,
take care.