There we go.
Morning everyone. How's it going? How's
it going? Hopefully you had a good uh
GlobeEx session or a good pre-market
session. Market is moving, but we are
inside previous days range. So, as
always, we're going to start on the
dailies here. Let's just zoom in a
minute. This key level up here, we still
cannot find acceptance over 700. You can
see on a daily every push over has
failed. All right. And we're trading
back inside what? Inside previous day.
All right. So, we have an inside bar to
start the session. All right. That's the
first thing we're thinking about. Inside
bar, which means what? We're probably
going to build liquidity, which means
[snorts] on an inside bar, we're aware
of the previous day high and lows. All
right. And we're either looking for a
breakout and continuation or we're
looking for a failed breakout and return
inside. Failed breakout and return
inside. So, that's the first thing.
We're inside a range. Second thing to
note is this gap. We didn't quite uh
take out these uh and fill this sort of
imbalance yesterday. We talked about it
many many many times in the New York
session. All right. And we're also stuck
between the 20-day and [snorts] the 5day
50-day also in here. So, we're rotating
between this. This is a very common
liquidity building phase of a market
between a 5day and a 20-day while it
makes its mind up. This can change to
blue. We don't need this like this now.
Right. And you can see we're trying we
are trying to hold the edge of balance
here which is moving as I zoom out zoom
out a bit more. We're trying to hold
this edge of balance and we keep getting
stuck in this node towards the sort of
690700s.
Right? It's a big problem area for the
market. Let's move down into the hourlys
and see what we get. Here we go.
Get rid of this little guy. Okay.
Developing week profile. You can see
we're trying, we are attempting to find,
let's make this a bit bigger for you
guys. We are attempting to hold above it
right now. This is the developing week
profile. You can see from yesterday and
current day, well, really from Wednesday
all the way into now, we've built out a
huge amount of liquidity up here. You
can see we're very actually thin on the
developing week in here. All right? So,
we don't really get thick until 416s
again. So, there is a case. All right.
There's an argument that if we start
breaking below this edge, let's [snorts]
call it 550s. All right. If we start
breaking below and failing that 550s,
there is an argument for the rotation
down towards 420s and 330s. I can see
that happening. We are thin in here like
we talked about. All right. At the
moment, every pull back into there is
being bid up and being bid up, but we're
back to this same area. You can see
we've had three drives now. One, two,
three. We're starting to see potential
backside into this key level here, 636s.
All right, so that's kind of the trigger
right now. We're watching 636es. Do
[clears throat] we reclaim and say
strong or are we looking for this fade
and the let go of sort of 550s for that
deeper rotation back down in towards the
sort of 340s, 350. So there is a move
there. There's a 200 point move there if
the market is willing to let go. But
what's going to be key is previous day.
So if we zoom up right now
and this should be previous day. Yes.
All right. Here's our rotation yesterday
and overnight. All right. Yesterday
failed to take out the highs,
failed to take out the lows. We drive
back up overnight. Failed to take out
the highs. We failed during London.
Failed to take out the lows. You can see
this how much we're boxed in here. And
we're coming back down for this double
bottom. All right. So this is our box.
All right. This is your rotational box.
So outside of this box, you're either
looking for breakouts or fail breakouts.
Breakouts or fail breakouts. Breakouts
or fail breakouts. In this box, this is
all you're expecting. All right. This is
liquidity building phase of the market.
All right. It was the same actually the
day before. Most of the liquidity was
built in here. All right. So those are
our big trigger points. Those are what
we have to watch right now. In fact, I'm
going to be somewhat cautious calling
this demand. Let's just
make this a gray area more.
All right. And really a letting go of
this guy here
will be what's important. All right.
Moving into lower time frame.
So you can see these same levels playing
out. So if we start losing blue
definitely uh if we start losing this
there is an argument for this drive down
into here. If we lose that there's an
argument for drive down into is it here?
No into this block here 300s. All right.
So if we start losing this target will
be this runners will be all the way down
here. If we do a fail breakout it will
look something like this. And we'll
target back the other side. Currently
previous day value area low previous day
value area high. previous week value low
and current week developing here as
well. So this this is huge on multiple
time frames on on weekly and and
previous day levels.
Okay. So in a rotational market don't
think beyond that right now. See money
take money until it proves otherwise
till we get out of the rotation.
Let's have a look what we're doing on
ES. Probably very much the same. Yeah,
you can see this pivot high that I put
in. Closed that gap. Well, almost closed
the gap. didn't quite get there. All
right, it's still yet to do this gap
fill. You can see yes, gap fill got an
alert still up there. We are starting to
hold a node here into sort of 30s,
right? Low volume node below. If we
start losing 30s, there's a case for a
drive all the way back down. But, you
know, you can see we've got lots of
nodes here on the way down. It's pretty
ugly because we built lots of liquidity
for this move and really the collapse
will need to come outside of this. We
have had relative strength on the daily
on the ES. Let's have a quick look at
the ETFs. We'll start with the spies.
We're looking at ES. Same kind of thing.
So, pivot is all the way down here. All
right. For the fill. So, buyers probably
hanging out right now around 85 and 84s,
waiting to see if they can find this
kind of move, especially if we don't
complete the gap fill. They might be
waiting for this. If we collapse 84s,
then there is the question of is this a
multi-le pullback which is just being
sold into into this balance for that
rotation back down. Obviously, we'll get
clean break of structure underneath
here. Very unlikely to come today, but
we can talk about that in the newsletter
for next week. Q's, same story. All
right, we actually filled the gap on the
Q's right here. All right, tech filled
the gap. Finding sellers here. This has
been the same story for weeks now.
Remember, this is a four or five week
balance range. Every time we're coming
up there, we can't seem to get back
through it, and we definitely can't seem
to get upside. So, do we come back down
to these 15s, right, this pivot in here
and find a bid? I don't know.
Potentially, potentially we sell through
it, but we're we're dancing between two
balance ranges. Dixie still falling down
like we talked about it would. VIX is at
an interesting level. All right, we're
still in this like huge channel. We
broke out. We've come back underneath
it. We're in these sort of two bid
zones. If I zoom out here, you'll see
how much congestion we've had in these
zones. So, if VIX can start holding a
bid and certainly it's going to need to
get over 1644s,
then we're looking for a drive up into
1740s and it's from that point that the
market might see weakness. If we if we
keep like rolling over here on the VIX
and coming down into the low teens,
you're probably more likely to see a
slow grind back upside.
All right, the MAG
still ugly. It's still ugly. All right,
inside a two-day balance range right
now. So, this is the low of week,
Tuesday. Anyone who's done the course
will see low week Tuesday. You'll know
what you're looking for there.
Wednesday, we push back up. We set a pin
high. Thursday, we tried in we trade
inside Wednesday. Friday, we're opening
up inside Thursday and definitely inside
of Wednesday. So again, we're building
balance right now in Apple.
No real edge.
Amazon.
It's not so bad, but still stuck into
this pivot. Still cannot find acceptance
back through there. If Amazon gets back
in here, then you know what we've got,
right? If Amazon's able to get back in
there, then it's got a shot until that
point. Supply holding up.
Google, this was strong a couple days
ago and opening up inside inside bar
here, right? Versus this pivot high on
Tuesday. So, as long as Google holds 28,
they can try and force this rotation.
Lose 28 and this is going to start
looking pretty bad, right? So, that's
the pivot. Uh, Meta
massive drive yesterday. That's There we
go. That's the relief. We've been
talking about this for weeks and weeks
and weeks. This constant selloff. Once
they find the bid over here, it's going
to see a squeeze. We're back into the
balance. Here's the balance, right?
We're back into it. So, does it hold the
balance and try and come up to the
upside or is it just a poke inside
rejection? If it rejects 640, 641s, then
you're probably going to see 626s again
very, very quickly because this is a
squeeze up. It can definitely come back
down before deciding what it does next.
Microsoft
inside previous day as well. Same kind
of story. It's trying to get back inside
this balance. All right, it needs to
hold this pivot build liquidity to go
higher. Losing this will just be a
continuation sell back down to this
pivot 44s and then 38s. Nvidia should
have strength this morning from what I
saw. Yes. All right. Completed gap fill.
It's got a shot. It's got a shot. Uh we
will have to see but it's got a shot
here if it can base sideways. It
actually just needs a sideways day of
190. It can afford to come down to 85
that five point range. It needs to build
up liquidity there. If it does that and
it is able to base, then it's got that
shot for upside coming into earnings.
Um, it's had strength today. Um, it was
based on what's it called? The H20
chips. Some news coming that uh should
be able to order them soon in China. Uh,
Tesla
opening up flat as well again just to
the top side of supply. No follow
through yet. So, looking for that sort
of 54 55 break to really start to get
going back up to the 70s again. broader
market or a mag as a whole. You can see
this is equally weighted mag as a whole.
That's the chance they need to build
here for that shot. Failure here gave a
rotation back down.
Okay, let's just have a couple looks at
some broader names. Oracle still getting
hammered into Netflix starting to find a
bid. Starting to try and find a bid. All
right. I'm still interested if it comes
down here and scooping some more, but I
think longterm this would be all right.
But if if they want to give a weak flush
and trap, then I'm here for it.
Absolutely here for it. AMD that has
been mega strong continues to be strong.
What a pump on AMD. Incredible. All
right, that break of 33s, we've got to
be getting up towards those highs. We
are. So, you'll be looking for an
all-time high break soon. If not this
week, next week on AMD support structure
all the way down at 30s. I'm still long,
but I'm only 20% long. I sold most of it
into this push uh into Q4.
And that be that, folks. All right, that
be that. We can think about um some of
the news coming today as well.
Get rid of this guy.
It's bigger. There we go. Let's have a
look at what news we've got coming.
Friday. Friday. Friday. Friday. All
right. Consumer sentiment 10:00
and we've got PMI
9:45. All right. So, PMI 9:45, consumer
sentiment 10:00. So, two news drivers
this morning coming out. 9:45 10:00. Be
aware of those, especially if you're
trading on prop firms, which don't allow
it. You want to be aware of them. Uh, do
me a favor, folks. Smash that like
button nice and early. Over 500 of you
here. We'll probably get up to 7 or 800
again today. I want to hit those uh 400
450 likes and we can give away some fun
stuff on a Friday.
All right, we'll give away some fun
stuff as we get on through the day.
Yeah, you might well be right, Zar.
Yeah, we're in we're inside bar. We're
inside uh value. we are likely to see
rotation. So, we've got to look for, you
know, fail breakouts and edges or
breakouts if there's continuation
momentum if we stay heavy one side or we
stay [snorts]
uh aggressive the other side. But I am
very much like you. I don't like trading
inside rotation very much unless we do a
big failure and we clean it all up one
side. That's when it gets more fun. What
we didn't do yesterday, right? So, if
today wants to be nice, right, then we
want to see it clean some of this up,
right? We want to see it come down here.
And if we reclaimed this, then I'd be
long. From here to here, there's a
chance to be short. The continuation
runner is all the way down into here if
they let it go. So, but uh yeah, we're
just going to have to be careful. Gap
fill obviously is up here, which we've
already come into, but we haven't done
it in the New York session yet. So, it
might be a morning drive up into that
and then see how we act in previous day
point control, yada yada yada yada. You
get the point.
Rotation very much possible.
All right, ladies and gents, just over a
minute left here. We're coming up.
Don't be giving your week back on a
Friday, please. We've had a pretty good
week here. Some of you would have
caught, you know, 200 plus points with
me yesterday. Maybe even more if you
caught the trades I took and the 200
point banger. The day before, I think we
had 100 pointer or I think it might have
been 200 pointer again. And uh Tuesday
was pretty good as well. So, we've had a
good week. So, don't be forcing it and
giving it back. We're in an inside bar.
We're inside value. We're in a little
bit of no man's land. Um, just be smart.
All right.
Be smart. Thanks. Thanks for joining,
Brian. Looking forward to working with
you. Looking forward to working with
you.
All right.
All right. Into previous value.
Is that right?
Well, this is way off, but we will see.
I've got previous day value low here on
Ninja.
So, let's see if they're going to do
this morning drive up for the gap fill
and previous day point of control. Mag,
a bit of a mixed bag. Everything green
other than Apple. Apple almost 1% down
right now. Right, Apple almost 1% down.
[snorts]
Tesla has just gone green to red.
they can catch a bit of a bid here this
morning or not. And what they want to
do, their target will be gap fill. If
they're going to do a squeeze up here,
they'll be looking for gap fill here and
then previous day point of control. I'm
going to reme-measure this out because I
don't like that. That looked wrong
versus ninja
30.
Yeah, this is definitely wrong. This
needs here. There we go.
[snorts]
Okay, so inside previous days value now
these on nice and early
and let's see.
Nice and patient today, folks.
Nice and patient.
finding bids off the same area as
yesterday. Gap fill is up here into 58.
That's where they're trying to get right
now. And if they get through the gap
fill uh up into previous day point of
control, that was the most traded level
yesterday. And once we get there, we
will see what the market wants to do. We
are just in a balanced range right now.
You can see it. We're rotating between
current week's value and previous week's
value. And we're rotating inside
previous days value. [snorts] Big buyer
stepping in here at the 50s. They're
trying to force this squeeze up. So,
that successfully look like they're
going to be able to close the gap here.
ES trying to join in, but it needs to
get through its 24-hour view up. So,
triggers off this long here this morning
all the way up. I'm not in this, but
it's paying very, very nicely.
And if you are in this, you want to be
paying yourself into this gap fill.
Goo, Tessagon red, Apple red. Right. So
it is a mixed bag here. Apple 1% down.
Amazon 0.85% up. Google 0.11% down. Meta
half a% up. Microsoft half a% up.
Invidia the big winner 2.21% up. Tesla
now 1% down. That went straight into a
sell here this morning. So giving back
its gap and some
as we trade back down to previous days
value area low. Not quite filling the
gap there which is kind of nasty to be
honest. And also reme remember down here
we still have an unfinished auction from
yesterday. So very very very dangerous
market as we chop around. There we go.
All the way back down it comes.
[snorts]
Goo starting to go red here or at least
flat.
I just have to be very patient today.
[snorts]
It's annoying again. We've left this
liquidity not quite filling the gap that
always uh find frustrating, but pushes
are still failing. We're now back
outside of previous days value lows.
There is a chance for a rotation down
into here, but like we've seen the last
two days, they keep scooping it and not
cleaning anything up. So, it's somewhat
risky and dangerous. Google now gone
back red to green. Tesla trying to find
a bid. So, need to just let this settle
down here. Remember, we've got news 9:45
and 10:00.
And this just feels like the rest of the
week. They don't really know what they
want to do with it. I think they're just
trying to hold enough to get into
earnings without too much damage and
then make the decision.
Rejection in front of the gap fill on
spy as well.
Trading between the 20-day and the 5day
on spy. Right. 20-day currently 88.84
5day 87.16
also inside everything.
Be nice if they came and cleaned
everything out downside, but I wouldn't
trust it to do it.
Big rejection of VWAP on SPY. Big big
rejection of VWAP. Not cleaned out the
lows either. So, very much like
yesterday. Not cleaned out highs, not
cleaned out lows.
Let's see. If they reject uh previous
day value and New York open and this
shelf here, there's a chance for a
rotation here. They've built a shelf. If
they get through the shelf, then they
probably squeeze straight back to 20s.
So, they've got the chance for the
rotation to come and clean out the low.
It really depends what they want to do
with it. I'm not convinced of anything
right now
into this low where they some sellers
keep getting stuck at 87s here.
If they trade through 87s, then there's
chance for them to trade down to 57s.
It's possible. Here's the 87s again. And
then if they get through that, there's a
chance to go back down to 540s, that
GlobeEx level, and then we can get weak.
So, it's building out liquidity in this
shelf here. Here's the 87s again. It's
where sellers keep trying to trade
through. Unsuccessful so far. They're
trying again. They've come in with size
this time. They're trying to force it
lower. It's now point of control.
They've traded it so much.
Is there any follow through? No, still
no follow through. So, they can't get
through those 87s. Just a wick and
that's it. Point of control now for me
is shifted down there.
They're going to have another go into
these 80s. They're stacking now. 75, 70,
65, 55s, and there's a seller up at 620.
This is awful, awful, awful action to
start the day again. Nothing we can do
with this, folks.
We go back to the New York Open, back to
previous day value again. Tesla trying
to find a bid.
I mean, what can you do with this? Uh,
beyond me.
ES into its New York open as well. Q's
trying to squeeze now into point of
control.
They just need to clean one side out
like just do something and take
liquidity from one side. Please market
please. This is day two or three of not
cleaning each side out. Otherwise, we
can't do anything especially on a
Friday. All right. rejection up at those
previous day value area low. Can they
clean out the other the lower side now?
Can they get acceptance under 87s?
If we start breaking down, I'll join it,
but not before.
Here's the 87s. Can they get under
current value and start to snap? Looking
to see if we can find acceptance lower,
which we're starting to look for. Yes.
Okay, here we go. Beautiful. Lovely.
Fantastic. All right, in towards these
lows now. You can take a partial here if
you want or you can hold for 40s and
then all the way down underneath all of
this will be ideal if we can get very
very weak.
So this is demand here. If we can get
acceptance under here, we're looking to
trade under 40s and then down into this
block. And ultimately, if they really
want to get heavy, right, if we start
letting go of this uh current shelf,
which has developed at 560. All right,
if they let go of that, then we're
looking for a trade down into 470s and
ultimately 350s if they really want to
do it. But we're taking partials into
this blue box [snorts]
now. Need to see rejection of this next
try to come back in. Still watching the
mag. Tesla now starting to sell again.
Rest of the mag still holding on. Still
in a rotation. So, just scalping as we
go here.
The problem basically is
we can't find acceptance over this.
Sellers are trying to sell this. Buyers,
so you I can make you understand
are trying to bid this. All right? So
sellers are selling this. Buyers are
bidding this. This is the rotation. If
we find acceptance, we'll come down
here. If we can get back above this,
there's a chance to come up here and
finish this auction. Both sides of this
auction look messy.
Nice, Daryl. Yeah, you took that fade,
did you? Probably from value area low or
VW up or whatever into this level. I'm
waiting to see if we can get acceptance
lower here. It would be nice if we can.
Yes, looking like it's going to do it.
Yes, about to clean out that GlobeEx
level. Is NQ going to be kind and follow
through with it?
[snorts]
Is NQ going to be kind and follow
through with it for these runners? I'm
willing to try and get into certainly to
here and possibly down here if they
really let it go, but at the moment
they're still bidding on this shelf.
Once this shelf lets go, there is a
chance for a wash. We need to be very
careful about fail breakouts today.
remember talked about it at the
beginning of the day because we're in a
rotation.
Starting to see some weakness come in
here. It's just can they get follow
through under these lows? That is the
question. Is there follow through
underneath this blue box? And this is
current developing profile, the high.
So, if we fail that, we're going to go
into the current weekly profile, which
is when we can really start rotating,
but they've got to fail under the
moment. They keep absorbing on it.
Strong today. Nvidia starting to pull
back, but still holding green. Look at
that squeeze back up. They just very
much like the last few days, they cannot
let go of key levels. They can't even
clean them out. ES just cleaned out well
it cleaned out GlobeEx but it didn't
take out that 25 pivot.
It is messy. It's very very very messy.
Seriously, no follow through. All right,
runner's gone. That's that done all the
way back up to value area low.
This is why Alex hates trading rotations
because it's [\h__\h] to trade.
Uh, if you guys like it, maybe it's your
bread and butter. Some people love
rotational market.
All right, next node is up here into
26es. Squeeze will start to take place
over that. There's definitely buyers
stuck at 650 today. All right, buyers
got stuck up here at 650.
See that right up here. All right, 650.
Lots of buyers got stuck above here. So,
let's see how they act if and when they
get up there.
This is really ugly, though. If we just
look at this for the last few days. All
right, just all these stops. Everyone's
just in check. Every dips's like a
higher low being absorbed, being
absorbed, being absorbed, but then they
can't take out the highs. It's really,
really not a nice auction to play.
Here's the squeeze now. [laughter]
So, they're coming for those 50s now.
Trying to see if that they can let that
buyer out who's a big delta at 50. Big
big delta at 50.
Completely boxed in here.
Do they get the gap fill I guess is the
next question. Yes. Let that New York
open again.
More buyers caught up here so far above
30s. I don't trust anything I'm seeing
right now. We've done nothing really.
We've opened up, pushed, flushed,
reclaimed, and back to where we've
opened.
We haven't run anyone out.
VIX also trading at 16's flat right now.
There's previous day value area low
again and New York open. And if they
don't absorb this, we go all the way
back down to the lows in their
stupidity. If they absorb this, there's
a chance to take out 650 and close the
gap. But I don't think they know what
they want to do. I'm going to be honest
with you.
Yeah. News 9:45. So two 2 minutes till
news. 9:45 10:00.
We're just hanging around at BU for this
news.
Banging heads on brick walls.
Well, the good news is right that we've
created so much liquidity this week that
I would imagine if not next week, the
week after, we will have a big break out
of it one way or another. I do not think
we'll just keep going sideways around
these balance ranges for long. I think
the market will really struggle to do
that. Yes, rejecting New York open
still doesn't know what it wants to do.
Still hasn't cleaned up each side.
Not many bids on this market at the
moment.
Very gray on bookmap. What are you
doing?
20 seconds till news, folks.
There's the print. They tried to shove
it up. Still being passively sold into
into 30s and 40s. Here comes the
potential squeeze and sold into into the
40s again.
What are we doing?
No one knows. Clearly,
they're trying to get this squeeze up
here. They're just really struggling.
Lots of sellers up at 40s and 50s. They
can't even lift it up there right now.
This thing is just not moving.
They're trying.
They got to get through these highs to
clean out all these stops and then try
and get up to 700s if they're going to
do that.
Lots of selling up here. This is just uh
completely stuck on the book.
They're just stacked both sides.
If you look at the book right now,
there's bids 25 to 600 and there's
offers 40 to 60. It's literally just 20
points stacked each side. Right now,
we're just completely stacked. It's not
cleaning either out. No one knows right
now what they want to do with it. So,
I'm just like staying clear until
they're done and then we can hopefully
pick a direction at some point today
would be nice.
PMI 52.8 versus 52.7
estimate 53. I mean slightly cooler.
pretty much in line though.
Down we come then
into this edge probably at 90s. And if
they don't rebid this, then maybe we can
still clean out these lows if there's
actual follow through. But again, I'm
not really trusting anything yet.
So into these 80s again. Point of
control down here.
for me anyway on Ninja. They're trying
to sell through it and they're not
successfully able to do it yet.
If you're watching Bookmap right now,
you should see like there's so many
limit orders of small size just
following the market up and down.
We're not seeing like a one-sided tape.
And we haven't cleaned out these lows. I
mean, they should really have come and
tried to clean out the lows already.
Apple's continuing to sell now
approaching 1 and a.5% down. Rest of the
market holding on other than Tesla's 1%
down.
Uh we are 0.13% up as an equally
weighted mag. We've still not moved
outside of the orb. We're still just
inside of the orb. We've still not
cleaned up any liquidity yet. We still
don't know what we want to do.
All right, this mark ain't going
anywhere. Let me just get a tea and come
back and refill on this.
All right, there we go. Nice and quick.
So, still inside current day's value.
Can't get over previous days uh value
area low. Can't get below current week's
value area high. and just trapped. We're
literally trapped in no man's land.
Mag not in agreement either.
Yeah, just
be nice if it just comes to clean
something up today.
Trading around point of control right
now for me. Point of control is here.
Now it's shifted down.
No acceptance under it. Now we're
starting to see some bigger orders
starting to come onto the tape bid side
to be filled all the way down to 540s,
but
no, there's been no real selling to come
and clean anything out yet.
More news coming at 10:00, remember? And
then we're clean for the day. So maybe
after 10 we get some something a bit
cleaner.
ES trading near low of day right now. ES
looks like it wants to break down. NQ is
just holding up very very well.
Sellers right now are caught under 85.
So sellers need to get breaks under 85
and they are not getting it in this
market yet. So we have to be very
patient. Here's the squeeze because
those sellers are starting to get caught
under 85. They keep trying to get sell
underneath point of control. They're not
getting it. So we're reapproaching
previous day value area low. Come a bit
map. Catch up.
Still inside value. Still inside the
orb. Still no follow through. ES weaker
of the two.
Looking like it wants to break down.
I will join this if we start to see
weakness and follow through from sellers
until that point. No. Same with the
buyers. If we can if we reclaim and I
can see us starting to bid over here,
I'll be interested, but not until then.
Otherwise, there just there's just
nothing to do. It's just uh one of those
days.
Certainly not going to become liquidity
for them to go and run out of this
market.
Best way of putting it, we're boxed in.
There's no buyers at the highs with
enough strength and there's no sellers
towards the lows with enough strength.
So, we're just getting tighter and
tighter and tighter and tighter. Even on
a daily, you can see it. Here's the
squeeze all the way up because all those
sellers got stuck under 87. And now
we're back to value area high and point
of control up here. And can they
complete it to come and take out or at
least uh gap fill this? Probably not
because every time they've attempted it,
they've failed. But who knows? Tesla
suddenly found a bid out of nowhere.
Tesla found a bid out of nowhere there.
There you go. Back down to value area
low again. [laughter]
Well, this is fun. Not
[laughter]
ES rejecting VWAP. We're just very tight
here, folks.
Oh my god.
But they can't even clean liquidity out.
Like I can't explain to you
how bad this is in both directions if
they can't clean some very basic
liquidity out. I don't think we can do a
thing with it. Like
they should have the ability to squeeze
here, but they don't. Look, every time
they're coming up here, they're failing.
They can't even close the gap and they
can't get under here.
Why bother?
Maybe at 10:00. I don't know. Maybe.
Now we got everyone stacking 25 to 50s.
Now, no follow through from buyers. So,
now we're stuck here. No follow through
from buyers. Upside.
CVD has been very bullish today by the
way.
Val area high. They've got the chance to
squeeze to 50, but they got to get
through all these sellers up here.
Especially if ES gets back over the New
York open.
They want to get up into here is what
they're trying to do. They're just
failing right now. They want to get up
into here.
Not only are they failing, they are
failing miserably.
We are basically in a range right now
from 90
to 30.
Uh we're in a 40 point range.
We're in a 40 point range, folks, on
ENQ. That's what we're in right now.
They want to get up to 50. It's what
they're trying They are desperately
trying to do is get up to 50.
Yes. Just rejecting it New York open.
Yes. Has got to get over the New York
open and then it's got to get over it
up. And at the moment it's had one, two,
three attempts on fiveminute bars. Four
attempts on five minute bars to get over
it. It's not done it yet. Here's
the attempt to get up towards the 50s
that we talked about.
Yes, still can't get through this New
York open.
Do you want the QQQ's closed their gaps
on the ETFs? I've just seen that.
They're trying to get up towards these
high days and 50s.
More buyers getting stuck up there
again. No follow through on the push.
They're trying. Here they go. They're
really trying.
Here comes the 50s.
So was a buy stuck here. Once he gets
out, it should close the gap.
And I'll see what we do once we do that.
So gap fill yellow line. There we go.
Finally, they're closing that gap.
So the question is, is this the
objective just to close this gap or is
there follow through through it? All
right, that's the question at this
point. Was the objective just to close
this gap or is there follow through
through it?
So no cleaning up of the lows.
This is your gap fill. If we can get
over that into previous day point of
control will be their target and then it
just depends what the acceptance is.
See that yellow line how important it
was.
CVD on NQ is very very very bullish like
as in aggressive buyers and if we don't
move higher it means there's passive
selling here constantly
because for the amount of uh let me just
show you easier than me just saying it
all right CBD very aggressive buying are
we seeing very aggressive buyers step in
no we're seeing passive selling up here
because if we're doing something like
that you would expect the market to try
and do this means there's passive
sellers holding this market down right
right now.
Can we buy now? I mean, for me, it's I
don't want to play this right now, but
I've been very clear. I don't do not
like taking rotations, right? So,
technically speaking, you could have
bought from here to here. TP1, TP2, and
TP3. technically speaking, but you need
to be aware that if these sellers keep
stepping in here, that is possible
because we're in a rotation. Right? I
keep saying it. We are in a rotation.
Here is yesterday's rotation.
This is the current weekly rotational
high. This is current week value area
high, which we keep trying to bid off.
Their target would be point of control.
This is the most common value area from
yesterday. It's very possible from here
they sell. If they get through it, we
come up to previous day value area high
and previous week value area low. The
question at this point is, can they find
acceptance back up? Because if they
can't, we come back down again. Right?
We are in the middle of two balances.
We've said it for two days now. I went
over it pre-market. This is no man's
land. Between here and here is no man's
land, right? This is a liquidity build
between here and here once they while
they make up their minds.
There you go. Human craft. [laughter]
Sell every push, buy every dip. Yeah.
Well, especially while we're in ro. You
just want to play the edges like this.
It's amazing to me, right? This is this
is current week value area high. It's
amazing to me that we haven't washed any
of this. Like we didn't wash this. Like
everything's being protected, which is
incredible. But that's the story, right?
We're protecting this. Until we see
this, there's no follow through
until we see prints over this. There's
no follow through in here. We are
pinned.
Right. This is midpoint. Do they pin
this or do we find acceptance back up? I
don't know, guys. I don't know. No one
knows. Anyone that tells you they know
is lying.
Okay, squeezing up previous day point of
control here. This red line. All right,
this red box is uh key level now. That
might well have been their target. ES
about to close its gap as well.
And here comes the squeeze.
So, Apple the only one red. Now, here
comes a squeeze up into previous week's
value area low. Remember, this is where
we cannot find acceptance through right
now. Every time we come over here, we
keep selling, but we need there are
stops up here to clean up as well,
right? All the way to 740s. We talked
about it the last few days, right? We
kind of expected it to try and do it.
Um, and above that as well, actually
here, 750s. So, every time we come up
into those, we keep selling. But that's
ultimately what they're trying to get
through.
Big old squeeze up. Big old squeeze up.
He has now filled its gap. No closure
through it. Same on Spy.
>> [snorts]
>> Is that the same? Yeah, there abouts
[clears throat]
I mean, yeah. I mean, look, I just don't
love rotations, but they definitely pay.
Um, you don't need to hate them cuz I
hate them.
I like them when we clean a level up and
then we take and then we can go like I
feel much better about it then.
Okay. So, coming into previous week
value low, previous day value high.
Technically, we should probably kind of
take this out now. Um, you're very very
squeezy. Look from here. You're you're
almost 100 points up from this squeeze
trigger. All right, there's been no
significant pullback here. So don't be
chasing this long. All right, it's if it
goes without you, it goes without you.
What you don't want to do is be chasing
the market long in a squeeze and then
have to sit through 50 60 points of draw
down. This thing's starting to really
start to move now.
There's previous week value area low. So
this is the edge of the previous week's
balance and beyond that is a four-week
balance, isn't it? If we get through
previous week value low, I will say we
still have a naked point of control all
the way up towards 900 890s.
But I need to see us build out some
liquidity at this point, not just rocket
ship up.
Yeah, Vick's just Vick's just stuck. It
hasn't even closed its gap. It's very
odd.
I wait to see if there's a pullback
which is absorbed now or if we just give
this whole move back. But if there's a
pullback that's absorbed into previous
day point of control, otherwise into
640, I'd consider it. Or if we push
through and hold inside previous week's
value, I'd also consider it.
Certainly not buying up here.
Still squeezing. They've caught so many
shorts now. Still squeezing. Here's
previous day value area high now. Tagged
Gloveex and previous day high above.
It's just not going to provide me an
opportunity to get into it. This is just
like the last few days. Once it goes, it
goes.
So, we've completed full rotation from
previous day's value area low to
previous day's value area high. We only
have globeex and previous day high above
to aim for the 40s and 50s and above
that it can potentially go and break
out. And just be very careful if if you
are long in any of this.
Congratulations. I mean, I guess I guess
you could have taken the point of
control long. I don't love it, but we're
coming into the extremes here. You want
to be selling some into here and
potentially this is your target. All
right. potentially up towards a 900 is
the target, but this will be a congested
area here. We are in a straight squeeze.
You can see this for what the last 10
minutes. It's gone nothing but squeeze
up. No structure built. So, just be
careful.
What are you saying? Short if you see a
rejection up here. Not unless you build
out volume and leave it. Not unless you
build out volume and leave it.
Remember, we're now inside uh previous
week's value. We're still inside current
days value. You want to see if we build
out volume and leave it. Otherwise, I'm
assuming pullbacks be absorbed and they
try and keep squeezing.
They've got targets above previous day
high above and then those 890s we talked
about right
there previous day value area high check
again they're trying to get back above
previous day value area high ES just
absorbed on PDC
there is a case for a 900 here if we go
in trend day today but it's going to
have to get above uh 740s
test now going red. Sorry if I sent me
to yawn like that. All right, back down
to previous week close.
still absorbing here for now. Sellers
keep coming trying to come in around
700s. Not getting follow through yet.
They squeeze this one more time.
Yes is the answer. Big buyer trying to
step in here at 11s. Huge seller just
stepped in there. 200 lot. It's getting
feisty up here. It's getting very
feisty.
I don't think they're done with it, but
we'll see.
Still no significant pullback, though.
Remember,
we straight squeezed up. If they lose
volume here, 96 is we can fade very,
very fast. But
not convinced they're done with it yet.
We just have to sit and wait.
now holding previous week close here.
It's amazing. They bid bid bid bid bid
bid bid bid bid and then they just
disappear.
Like where are the bids gone? They're
now down at 75. It's It's actually quite
amazing to watch. It's really uh been an
interesting take the last few days.
[snorts]
Sellers will need it under 96s. They're
not seeing that right now. Buyers just
need to break over sort of 713s, 714s,
that previous day value area high.
Buyers will be looking for a break over
this to finish the rotation up into
previous day high and then squeeze
through it. Sellers are looking to leave
this volume here.
Another huge seller trying to step on
the tape here. market selling.
Remember, we lack structure on the way
up.
Definitely lack structure on this way
Buyers still trying to absorb here. I
don't like what I'm seeing on the tape.
This guy keeps [\h__\h] pulling. One,
two, three, four, five times. This buyer
keeps pulling. Someone's playing silly
buggers again.
Someone's playing silly buggers.
It bid 96. Bid 96. Bid 96. And then
pulled each time.
Watching these 15 sellers are stack 15s
to 20s here. Do we squeeze through now?
Stuck at the tens. Amazing. We're just
going to get stuck between previous week
and previous day. Come on. Come on,
Mark. Please don't do that. Please don't
get stuck between those two levels.
[\h__\h] market is so bad to trade for me
at the moment. It's been so bad. It
offers these huge opportunities, but if
you don't get it exactly where it wants,
it's just gone. And then it does this
nonsense. Oh god.
Four days of getting annoyed even though
making money.
Four days of me getting stressed out.
These buyers cannot get it over these
15s.
How do we go in such tight ranges after
these massive squeezes? Come on.
If you're going to go, just go. Stop
[\h__\h] about.
Insane.
What's this red 620 to 720 and then 20
point rotation?
[laughter]
Incredible.
Okay, watching here.
No follow through again.
Can't take out low hanging fruit. Can't
give Alex a trade.
If they sell this back down again after
two days of doing it,
well, I don't know what I'm going to
say, but it's just if you zoom out and
look at on an hourly, if you look at
from Wednesday 2:00 to now, it doesn't
look very nice. It really does not look
very nice.
We've been up here so much that we've
actually moved current week's value area
high up here now as well. That's how
much volume we've now created up here
without follow through.
I should be willing to play it short,
but I'm just not. I'm just not willing
to do it today.
I just feel like it's done it two days
in a row already at these levels. I'm
just not willing to do it. It might well
just flush without me, but I'm just not
willing to do it. Not when it's left
those levels above again.
It would be if I was going to play short
and I'm not going to play it, it would
be the same as yesterday, right? It
would be leaving this and rotation back
down towards here. This is exactly what
we've done the last two days, which is
why I'm very I don't like it because I'm
just like, but it's probably going to do
it. But
I don't like the market trading this
way. There you go. [\h__\h] It's such
[\h__\h] mate. It's such [\h__\h] what
they're doing here. [snorts]
I don't like it. I do not like it.
So, there's your TP1. If you took the
short, TP2 would be back all the way
down into value. Um, I just think it's
way too risky with how they're setting
this up in this in this range on an
hourly is what or on the daily, right? I
don't like what they've just done here.
They've just moved value up.
Value was here. Where was it? here on
the week and they've just moved up to
here and look how we're trapped in here.
I don't like this range. I do not like
this. Someone's got to get hurt. They
have not cleaned out either side. I just
think it's way too risky leaving this
like this and the lows like this, all
the stops each side. I don't want to be
the guy who comes and plays the same
trade three days in a row and gets like
skipped by, you know, 100, 200 points. I
just don't want to be that guy.
Mag also has no idea what it's doing
right now. So, here's the retest. If
they don't resell this, then the squeeze
is on where we just talked about leaving
this liquidity. This is my worry is
there's so many stops up here, which is
why I'm not playing it short side today.
Last two days, no, no worries. But this
is day three or four of all these stops
up at 40s and above. And you just think
if they come for it, oh my god, like
imagine three days of huge lots of
stops. Then I think we probably go 900.
And that is my concern why I'm not
playing short today because I don't like
their games of how they're setting it
up.
And they're going to go for the reclaim.
They might well do the squeeze now. I'm
more willing to actually play it higher
if they're going to break because
there's so many stops to aim for.
Need ES to get going though.
the battle up here. We get through the
teams. We're going here. We go in
towards the teens. Can they find
acceptance over previous day value area
high? That's all we're looking for at
the moment. Can they find acceptance
back over this
big seller earlier came in at where?
11s. So buyers need it back over 11s.
for previous day value do use ETH or RTH
regular trading hours 9:30 to 4:00 and
it's failed again
[\h__\h] are these lot doing
back to previous day point of control
again
absorb absorbed again.
They didn't even fill the guy down there
at 75. Still absorbed. Buyers came in at
85s now.
Oh my gosh, man.
I'm ready to go back to bed. I can't
trade this. If we can't do a move which
is not the same as last two days, I'm
not going to trade it. It's too
dangerous. There's too many stops
waiting to get run. It's way too
dangerous on a third day of doing it.
Wednesday, Thursday, Friday. Can't do
it. No way.
You think it's about to flush, Raph? I
think it's might do the opposite, which
is why I'm not willing to trade it. It's
going to do the for me. I think it's
going to do the opposite of the last two
days. If I'm wrong, I'm wrong and I'm
not in it, and that's okay. But, you
know, the last two days I played these
shorts back down to here. My my problem
is we've done this move once, twice,
three times. Think about all the resting
liquidity above. That worries me. That
worries me that they're luring people in
to look for the same move and that it
will go the other way, which is the only
reason why I'm like, I don't like the
psychology of this. Maybe I'm wrong and
they flush it, in which case all that I
miss is a trade, but I'm not going to
get hurt.
Maybe you're right, Raph.
Yes, much weaker though. Tell you that
much.
Well, that's the thing. Spearhead,
waiting for the manipulation. We
actually haven't had any for any of this
week, right? Since we've gone into
range, we have not swept or cleaned
anything up. That's half the problem,
right? That's kind of what I'm saying.
Like, we need to clean up one side and
we're not. The auctions do not look good
at the highs and lows. We talked about
it yesterday. The low of day had buyers
on. You don't want that. You want
sellers on it. We didn't take it out the
previous day. We haven't taken it out
today.
Can't really do much. Like
back to VWAP.
Wonder if ES comes all the way down to
35 and then rebids.
Oh, it's such a shame, man. [sighs]
You get up early and this is what you're
dealt with. It's such a shame. I find it
exhausting when they do this.
They can't get under this right now.
So thick here now on an hourly. It's so
thick.
I'm telling you, if a breakout comes, I
can see this at 8.90 today. That's what
I'm That's my worry. That's why I'm not
fading it. If a breakout comes, I can
see this at 8.90 today.
Here they go. They've just dipped it
again. All right. I'm interested. I'm
interested. Watching see if we can get
up to 30s now on GlobeEx and 40s for
previous day high and then through that
potentially 890s,
that naked PC.
So, they might well do that trap that I
just talked about.
We'll see.
This is where they need to get to.
Here we go. So, at least I was right.
Had a good feeling for the market.
They're not going to do the same thing
every [\h__\h] day. That's how they lure
you in.
Almost into GlobeEx
and value area high on the week. So, do
we find acceptance and expand through
that or not?
How are we not taking GlobeEx out
seriously?
Come on. I want to get [\h__\h] paid.
Come on.
Let's go. Come on.
Come on. Let's go. Now I want previous
day high in globe bets. Let's go. Let's
go. Let's go. One more push. One more
push. One more push. Trying not to take
a partial. Trying to be patient. Come
on. Let's go, [\h__\h]
I got your name today. I got your name
today. Market makers. Alex ain't stupid.
I know your [\h__\h] games. Okay, so
let's see if we go 900s.
Been around too long. I'm too [\h__\h]
old, man, for this [\h__\h] Let's go. Let's
go.
>> [applause]
>> No one you on YouTube's giving you that.
I'm telling you, no one will understand
why we're doing that. Most people would
been looking for that drop today. Three
days in a row, we're not doing the same
thing. If we go 890s now, I'm a happy
man. All right. So, pay myself in here.
If I get very, very, very, very lucky
today, we're going to come up for this
naked point of control.
[\h__\h] me. That took patience.
[\h__\h] just got personal. That's right,
JD. [\h__\h] just got personal. All right,
once we run these stops, I I want you
guys to understand this. All right, so
that when I'm not here, you understand
why I didn't want to play that today.
It's this. Okay, this is how they're
luring you, luring you in, right? We
fade away from value last week. We
create value. We push up. Fade. Fade,
fade, fade. Do we ever sweep? No, we
never sweep. Do we ever sweep these
lows? No. So, if we're coming this high,
what are we going to do? If we run one,
two, three, four lots of stops out,
where's this market going to go? All
right. Because these short sellers
become what? Market buyers. All right.
And then we can get a squeeze. So, we're
long to take that out because they are
hoping everyone shorts for the rotation
back down. But we've done that rotation.
one, two, three times already this week.
Wednesday, uh, sorry, Tuesday, no,
Thursday, Alex can't think. Thursday,
Thursday, Friday, we're running those
stops. All right,
don't fall for their games, guys. Do not
fall for their games. If they're setting
up the same thing over and over and over
and over and over again, all right, it's
it's to lure you in to make you think,
"Oh, I've seen this before." No, no, no,
no, no. Not when it's too many times in
a row.
Nice. You're long at 700. Nice guys.
Like guy, great work. Make sure you're
paying yourself. I paid myself most my
money. I'm going to lock in some good
money here no matter what. Uh I just
know the next lot of stops are the top
of this gray box or technically is
actually here. All right. So, we need to
run through this. Once we run through
this, there is squeeze potential up to
this naked point of control. But we're
paying ourselves no matter what. See how
this previous day point of control
mattered. They couldn't get back under
fair value flipped. All right, they
built this and then we're long, right?
Paying ourselves. And if we get a
trigger through here, we'll get up into
there and then this would be a great
Friday.
No, no one else would give you this educ
like lots lots of people know what I'm
talking about. Lots of people. But
they're not giving it to you for free on
YouTube. Right? This is not like, oh,
I'm the only person that knows this. Not
at all. Lots of people know this stuff,
but they're not giving it to you for
free on YouTube. I'm trying to teach you
while I trade. That's the difference.
When people like, when did you enter?
When do you I'm trying to teach you as I
trade. This is your next target, folks.
Once we get through top of gray box, you
can sell some above gray box. All right.
For the squeeze, I'd imagine we'll get a
squeeze trigger through 65s here. sell
some into that and then just hold like
10% in case we do like another 100 plus
points or it be uh yeah 100 plus points
just in case. [snorts]
Nice Scotty. I love it mate. Nice work
Scotty. You look good. Just be so on ES
you got 20day right your 20 days around
54 55 to 955. You've got plenty of room.
from GlobeEx 963, highs 969, and we've
got a squeeze trigger for gap fill is
all the way at 976 if it really really
got going.
All about the bass. It's funny, I
remixed that tune for Megan Trainer.
I've got a platinum disc at home for
that. It's funny that you say that. All
about that bass. [laughter]
back in the day. I wonder if it's still
up anywhere.
Oh, there it is.
many years ago.
Look at that. Many, many years ago.
Yeah, I got disc that somewhere
somewhere.
Somewhere in a cupboard at home.
Do we have a re-entry? Uh, well, you
want to be careful. We're We're squeezy,
right? So you'd want to see a basin hold
really here. It's trying to hold. It's
trying to now hold current weak value.
See this blue line moving up? That's
current weak value area high developing
profile. All right. So it's trying to
hold this to complete this. But the
re-entry could be down here. It could be
something like that. All right. They
might be even that they want to do
something dirty like this later in the
day.
But I wouldn't be buying up here now.
You'd almost be better off if if it
doesn't offer a pullback or a sweep and
a reclaim, you're almost better off
letting it base above this at that
point. Be very careful as we build out
volume.
What if it rejects here? What's the top
of the box? Top top of the box, mate. It
is the stops from Friday, right? 10:00
a.m. Friday the 16th. All right. If I
move you to 1H.
All right, these guys here. If we think
about how we faded this market last week
on Friday,
right? It's all these stops. So, anyone
who's swing short from here, this is
where they're swing short. Okay, so if
we pop through that, then we're going to
go back inside previous week's value.
And then the rotation next week would be
between here. If we do that,
we can go over that in the weekly
newsletter though.
[snorts]
Not only am I making money, I'm learning
too. No one does it like SCT. Thanks,
man. Appreciate it. What do you use as
confirmation for entry? Uh, order flow.
Order flow for me is what I use. So map
or here,
right? So at these lows,
anyone who's been with me the last few
weeks,
what do we see here, guys?
What are we seeing there? Anyone that's
been with me, anyone who's done the
course, you guys tell me. You guys are
smart. What are we seeing in these
candles at the lows?
There you go. Trapped. Yeah, sellers
stuck. Right. These are aggressive
sellers
stuck. Are we moving lower? No. What
does that mean? It means there's limit
buyers refreshing the bid here non-stop.
And once these sellers are stuck,
where's their stop?
What happens? They become market buyers,
right? So, these sellers become these
market buyers. Why? Because when you
stop out, they put their stops here.
They become a market order in the
market. We come up. We're still holding.
All right. We have some imbalances down
here. We can feel if it wants to pull
back and hold to go again. So when
someone asks, "What's my confirmation?"
My confirmation is, "Can I see sellers
stuck at a low?" This is a good auction,
right? We see sellers stuck at the low.
This gives us thesis to move higher.
That's what we're looking for. That's
not what we've seen, right, the last few
sessions at the lows, right? I don't
like this, right? Buyers at the lows
absorbing without a sweep. No, this is
not a healthy auction, right? So, when I
say I don't like the auction at the low
or the high, that's why what I want to
see is like, for example, if we drove
down under here this morning and we saw
delta and this was sellside delta and we
reclaimed, okay, then I'm long off the
bottom, right? Because I know sellers
played the breakout short and got stuck,
for example, right? So confirmation for
me comes from order flow, understanding
levels, understanding where I'm looking
to execute, where I think stops are, and
then it's about can I execute based on
who I know who not I think is trapped,
who I now know is trapped because it's
showing me
even in here, if I give you this five
minute chart, you can see this big
seller came in here and got himself
stuck. All right, into these 40s and
underneath these big sellers down here.
We had these huge lots here at 10:00 at
700. Then they try to sell underneath
previous day point of control. Once we
get through, if you're a big seller
here, right, we're talking about 300
lots here trapped between here. This is
why I was getting frustrated. I was
like, please don't dance between here
because it's going to be I can't do
anything. But once we run these stops,
we're only going one way. We are going
upside because that is where their pain
is. who will use their pain. [snorts]
What is delta? Delta is the difference
between aggressive buyers and sellers in
the market, right?
What is an aggressive buyer or
aggressive seller? Someone hitting the
market. So, if you're a market buyer,
right? If the I've got to do this the
right way around because it's reversed,
right? If the offer is here and the bids
are here and if you're a market buyer,
you're filling that offer. You're not
joining the bid. You're filling the
offer. That's someone that's being
aggressive. So, if we've got aggressive
sellers trying to sell, all right,
against the bid, right? They're selling
against the bid. If they come piling in
here and price doesn't move lower, it
means that someone is just bidding and
holding and holding and holding and we
call that absorption, right? Think about
a sponge. Someone's trying to sell.
There's a big sponge being like, I'm
going to take all your orders. We're
going to move up. Because remember the
market cannot move unless there's
aggressive participants. If you just
have like um offers here and bids here
between is what we call the spread. If
we just have that, it's never going to
move, is it? It's never ever going to
move, right? We always talk about the
Rolex. If I want to buy a road a Daytona
for $20,000 and the cheapest one on the
market is $30,000, then we got a $10,000
spread. Until I'm willing to buy it for
$30,000 or he's willing to sell it to me
for $20,000, the market doesn't move.
It's exactly the same in this scenario.
Joe, am I sec? No. So what I'm saying
is, let me get you on a higher time
frame. We have a what we call a naked
point of control on a weekly, right? So
this level here has not been retested
since we left it, right? Because this is
the old week. We have not retested this.
So if we break above these stops, it is
very probable that we will retest this
level, right? That's what the market's
trying to do. We're now starting to
break above these stops. So they're
going to try and get all the way up to
8.90ish. That's what they're going to
attempt to do today if they can. They
might not make it, but this is what they
want to do. [cough]
You think I IB trade is on the table? Is
it too bullish? Well,
it might be an IB. It just might not be
the IB reversal. It might be because
look where the IB is right on the gray
box. It might be the IB expansion. It
might be a trend day expansion. It
doesn't have to be the IB to VWAP.
Remember the other side of it is the IB
expansion. If we're in a trend day above
IB, we don't be short, do we? If we're
if we keep bidding above IB, we're not
going to get short because we're going
for expansion. If we get under here,
right? If we get under here,
that might be valid. But we're not under
there. We're in expansion mode and we're
long and strong.
Here we go. Here we go, folks. So, 800
psychological level. It would be nice if
uh ES can join in. The great thing is
here we're long in NQ, which has
relative strength. So if we look at the
broader markets, RTY down 1%, YM, this
is really good by the way. RTY down 1%,
YM down 0.59%, ES just above flat. We
are almost half% up. What does that
mean?
In November and December, we started a
rotation out of tech into small and
midcaps, right? Which is why RTY has
been at all-time highs. If we're seeing
strength come back into the tech market,
what does that mean? It means we're
rotating back into the mag, back into
big tech companies, which means ENQ is
going to have relative strength, which
is why we want to be long in this when
we're going to see that.
Can you trade my system without bookmap?
Yeah. Yeah. The beginner to advanced
course, guys, doesn't have any order
flow on it. It shows you like everything
I'm looking at without order flow. The
volume, profile, and order flow course
has all of that stuff on. So, I can see
some of you have just asked for it. Let
me
Everything is here, guys.
Everything's on that link. Just hit that
link.
[snorts]
Uh, I didn't use CVD for absorption. CVD
is is not showing absorption today. It's
actually showing very aggressive buyers
when we weren't moving higher. the
absorption I saw on order flow.
Yeah, MSFT uh 3% up softy.
So, just be aware sellers just came in
at 770.
770. That's where they're trying to sell
through back down to this node. Buyers,
all right, will want to hold 60. That's
where they held. Sellers need it under
70. If buyers keep absorbing above 70s,
we're going to keep squeezing. We know
the target where I want to get to. This
is where I want to get to if possible.
Thanks, Matt. Hope you're good.
Nice sniping candles. Yeah, looking
forward to working with you.
Why do I execute on Ninja Trader when I
could execute on Bookmap? Because I have
all my uh
copy traders. I have my order flow. I
have my flow zone system. Everything on
Ninja Trader. I like the ATM strategy.
Like literally everything I want is on
Ninja Trader.
Do I use fair value gaps? No, not
really. I mean, I I know what they are.
I can see them, but uh they are
imbalances, but they're not always
directly accurate. So, what you're
talking about is being in the imbalance.
Coming back to Friday at 9:00 a.m. A
pre-market imbalance is what you're
looking at. Coming back to Friday the
16th is what you're talking about.
Do I do discounts? Uh, I do, but we've
just did a huge sale for Christmas, so
there's um there's nothing due. Won't be
due for a while. And prices are actually
$699. I just haven't put it up. It was
supposed to go back. It was supposed to
go up in January 1st, but as some of you
will know, I've been going through a lot
of personal stuff at the moment. So
there 649. If I get time, I'll change it
this weekend.
What copy trader do I use? Affordable
indicators.
Indicators.
If we blast through previous week point
of control with an engulfing, you expect
sell off or even more of a fuel up. Um,
I mean, it would need to get through
920s.
If we get through 920s, you could say
there's validity for a move to 26,000.
I'm not technically bullish, right?
Until we're able, as in higher time
frame, until we're proved to me we can
base over 26 or 2600. If we start basing
over that, this market is going to
absolutely rip. It's going to do the
complete opposite of what everyone
expected, including myself. It means
there's no selloff. Just think about
this. Uh get you on a daily. Uh where
where are you guys?
All right,
we've undercut this.
Probably grabbed a lot of liquidity. Bid
back up. We've never been able to bid
over this. Remember, this is like the
old balance. The old balance. The old
balance. The old balance. All right,
this is where we're trying to trade in
towards this point of control as well.
Right, if we get up over here and base,
then the next target would be here. All
right. The big question is if they do
this, all right, and base above it, not
spike and fail. If they base above this,
we're going to have all these sellers
trapped in the market, which means
everyone from November will be trapped.
And if they base above that, this will
absolutely
rocket. It will rocket if we base above
this. All right? because everyone's
looking for, including me, thinking
we're going to eventually come back down
towards here, right? And maybe even
there's an argument for a retest back
down to here. So maybe a little dunk
underneath and a reclaim. If we don't do
that and everyone's positioned for the
fail, then we're going to keep going
higher, aren't we? So, you know, have to
be flexible in markets. This is why like
I can have thesis all I want, but the
moment my thesis is wrong, I have to be
willing to say what's in what's in front
of me.
or say play. I have to be willing to
play what's in front of me.
Why is ES left behind? Just broader
market. So if we look at Finn Viz, you
probably got some sectors not as strong
as tech. Remember tech's very strong
this morning.
Right? If we look at the broader market,
pull this in so you can guys can see it.
Oh, don't computer's just gone mad.
Uhoh.
Uhoh. I can't move it. Finn viz.
If I have to reset my computer, it's
going to be a problem.
It's just this one. There we go. God,
thank God for that. Okay, if we look at
broader market,
right, who's really green?
Microsoft, Nvidia, AMD, MU, Palanteer,
Amazon, Google, Meta, Netflix, right?
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight. Eight big stocks
green which have probably over 60%
weight in the ENQ. What's really red
which isn't in the ENQ? Financials. All
right, look at all these red, right? So,
that's dragging ES. What else is red?
Healthcare. Guess what? That's also in
ES. Okay. So this is why this is why you
need to understand when we have relative
strength. We're seeing rotation out of
these sectors out of healthcare. Well,
there's never really rotation into it.
Out of finances into some of these big
tech names, then we're going to be
stronger in NQ.
Where's my stop? Uh, I'm probably going
to move it up to just around this IB,
which might be silly, but I can always
re-enter. I just want to watch the order
flow as we come into. Well, I don't want
to get caught in.
Maybe I'll give it a little bit more
room because this is acceptable to do
this. We need to be careful of these two
nodes. If we lose these two nodes,
there's a bigger fade and I don't want
to be in it.
All right. How are we doing here for
likes, folks? There's 821
of you watching and 279
likes. And we are long and strong up
almost 100 points. And we're looking for
a target, another 100 points higher. And
you guys can't even hit a like button
for me to give you free Apex accounts.
Come on, folks. Come on, folks. Help me
out. Smash that like button for me.
Alex, do you use London and Asia high
and lows? Yeah, I do. But we didn't
sweep Well, we didn't sweep the lows
today. We didn't sweep London low. And I
don't think we did it yesterday either.
We didn't do it yesterday either, which
is why my bias was long because I feel
like we're going to we we're going to
run all of these guys out. And we're
starting to see that
today. I was really wrong on my
assumptions. I don't have edge in the
market.
I missed out on 200.
You mean I was wrong and you missed out
because of me? Well, I wasn't wrong. We
didn't sweep either side. I wasn't
wrong. I didn't like it. I waited for it
to hold and guess what? We're long. So,
you're waiting for signals. And I told
you what I'm looking for. When everyone
was talking about this collapsing, I
told you what I was looking for. I don't
know what crack you're smoking, mate.
Do I use ENT in the course? I've just
bought ENT and have a really hard time
with it. Yeah, uh I I teach on here. Um
but we go over some NT stuff and in the
Discord as well. There's also a free
video on my YouTube on setting up NT.
From which level did I trade it? Right
in here. Once once once I saw these guys
trapped right in here
long for this partial out early into
here bit more here and I'll just see if
we can get up here. We might not be able
to but hopefully we can. If ES can't get
going then we might end up cutting this
early.
Alex, do you use Ninja Trader for
execution and bookmat for the dominant
order flow? Yeah, Ninja Trader for
execution and for order flow. So I have
my footprint charts on there and then
bookmap as well. I just like like the
visual representation. I like to see the
tape. Sometimes like I might see like a
like a delta on the volume profile delta
on the the uh level two. Sometimes I
might see it stand out on um on the
footprint. So just any way that I that
gives me edge really anywhere where I
can see it.
There you go.
Yeah, I didn't have that quite nice. I
didn't have a bias any side until we
reclaimed a level and we've talked about
that in Discord as well and yesterday
numerous times. So quite right, Miguel.
Morning Bella.
What site was that for the stocks NQ and
ES? Uh, Finn. Fin.
Yeah, he must have been watching on the
stream. Average win rate around 68 to
73% between those two fluctuating.
But I will tell you one thing. A lot of
my winners, this is what one thing with
win rate. A lot of my winners might be
like one tick winners because I get
knocked out break even. You'll see me so
many times get knocked out break even.
But my winners, we normally get 50 100
point plus. Come on, baby. Let's go.
Let's go. Let's go. Let's go.
use 100 rows on AVP. Uh I I would advise
using either a thousand rows or two
ticks. I use two ticks currently.
[snorts]
Here we go. Here we go.
Here we go. Through the 800s. Let's keep
going. I want this naked point of
control. Let's keep going.
Where did I learn? Uh myself really.
Everything I learned from other mentors.
I'm going to be honest with you.
Everything I learned from other mentors
was terrible
and coupe will testify to that as well.
Other that's not fair. Other than the
guy guys that investors underground, but
they really focus on small caps
other than them, but I don't think
they're necessarily great teachers.
That's not like a disrespect. I think
they're really good traders. They're
really good or for me, they were really
good at making me understand levels.
What I struggled with is like the
pedagogy. I couldn't like necessarily
always absorb what was being said, but
maybe I was just too new. [snorts]
Anyone know if Apex Trader is legit?
Yeah, it is. And take regular payouts
from there.
What? Why should I show my trades when
I'm calling it out on here and I can
draw on here and I can't draw on Ninja
Trader and I can show you what I'm
looking at and I can teach you
everything and I have everything on here
for you and I can flick between the
charts. Why? Why do you need to see the
execution tab? It's weird.
Just so you can do exactly what I do.
Trying to teach you to fish, mate.
That's why
are most of not so entries looking for
someone to be trapped? I don't
understand what you mean there, Dylan.
All my entries are based on people being
trapped in a market. All the market only
moves based on people being trapped in
the market. You should understand that.
It's the only reason the market moves.
[snorts]
How do you validate a low volume node?
uh the reaction and what happens in that
low volume node. Really, you can't
always validate a trades. I would I
would say though that's one thing like
there is
I like to look for reactions. Sometimes
it costs me the ability to get in. For
example, if you were willing to long in
this low volume node and maybe add all
the way down into this high volume node
and risk the other side of this high
volume node, right? There is an there is
a case for this being support right down
all the way down to the bottom and for
this running up here. What I like to
look for is for this to come down into
here to see sellers get stuck to see
absorption and to move higher. That
might mean that I'm joining slightly
later. But what it means is I know or I
have more confidence that we're going to
go higher. So sometimes I don't get the
best price but I get the momentum.
Hopefully that makes sense.
So, like if if you were willing to just
buy this in this node all the way down
to here, it might be that we do this. I
would if I was going to buy that, I'd
need to see in here,
right? I'd need to see sellers
get stuck,
right? I need to see this to be red and
buyers absorbing and us to move price
higher. That's what I would need to see
for how I like to trade with momentum.
What sites for news, dates, and
calendar? Um, market watch and financial
juice probably the best places.
Sorry guys, trying to catch up with
everything you're saying here.
How quickly do I move my stock to break
even? If we're in a squeeze, then pretty
quickly because when we squeeze and we
latch structure, when we're like
grinding like this, you don't have to
worry about it so much.
So squeeze still going. We're still
looking for those. It might not do it in
one go, folks. All right, we are to a
pullback. Just be aware of that. So if
you don't want to sit through a
pullback, you can move your stop
tighter.
Where am I trading from? I have a
European accent. I'm from the UK, but I
live in Los Angeles.
Tyson, $650 on two PAS, 100 $1,400 on
two evals. Nice work, mate. Look at
that. Locking in those profits. Love it.
Love it, mate.
Carmine is very legit. Anthony said,
"Yeah, he trades I think he trades water
flow as well, right? I haven't seen his
stuff for years." [snorts]
He used to trade supply and demand, but
I remember seeing a video
not that long ago. Flash up and uh it
was an orderflow video.
No, they haven't. Apex don't do that
compliance stuff. That was like like two
years ago now. That stopped a long time
ago.
How many contracts do I trade? All
depends on the account size, Jake.
At the moment, I'm in my TPT. So, I've
just got one left. Trying to get all the
way up there. See if I can make like
another $200 on that one. I was
aggressive for the first part of the
move, but we're getting quite extended
here. If we think about
if we think about projected targets from
what we've done in New York,
right, we're at coming up to 300% move.
If we go from like some of these
pullbacks here,
same thing.
Even if we go from this flat top. Oh,
don't move that one. I need that one.
same thing. So, we're doing 300%. No
matter what pullback we're looking at,
we're doing 300% moves. So, if we're
lucky, they'll count this as one, but I
don't think we've built out enough
liquidity here. And then we'd almost be
getting there. But, we are probably due
a nasty little pullback soon because
look how extended this is. I can very,
very easily see this
collapsing a little bit before bidding
up later in the day. I don't think I'm
going to sit through that. In fact, I
might move my stop up here and just
protect everything. make sure I'm going
to lock on decent money no matter what.
Sorry guys, I'm trying to like the I'm
trying to see the chat and and help you
guys out.
Subscriber here from LA. Oh, you're up
early morning with me then. [snorts]
Am I watching 1 minute, 2 minute or 5
minute u volume print? Just one and
five. One and five.
You're absolutely frustrated to have
missed out on 200 points. Like
what you what are you going to do about
it? Like I made it pretty clear. So
it just is what it is. Let go.
Learn to trade by yourself. Listen to
the advice I give or don't or find
someone else. It doesn't makes no
difference to me. If you're frustrated
and you're sat here and you don't like
how I trade, go and go to someone else
or read some books. Like not forcing you
to be here. Like I'm My way is not the
only way to trade. [snorts]
Do I trail my stock generally or just
put break even and let your bias pay
out? Uh depends on the account, depends
on the size, depends on the confidence I
have of it going somewhere. Like we're
very The hard thing now is right, we're
almost here. We need another 60 points
higher. Have we pulled back?
Like let me get like very very simple,
right? Have we pulled back? No. The
pullback can easily be, you know, 70 80
points. I don't really want to give all
that back. Like if we start seeing
flushes in this market, I'll probably
get get out and then just like look to
rejoin if I think that the target is
still very viable.
If you wanted to go long, what would the
pullback level to look for? I'd be
watching this node here,
right? If you this node here around this
initial balance because this is the top
of the stops. Remember the gray box is
the top of the stops from a swing
perspective. If it pulls back into here
and does something like this, then it's
probably a chance to get long again. If
you start losing this though, you do not
want to be adding long because this
collapse back down here is possible. So,
this this area here becomes key for
sentiment all the time. We're above
that. Remember, we're above initial
balance. We talked about it. Someone
talked about the IB trade and I said,
well, we might be in the IB expansion
trade. Here you go. Absorption of IB
expansion move. Right. Even if we
measure out the IB today. Let's see
where the six um the measured move is.
Well, that's pretty good, isn't it? I
wonder if they did that on purpose. So,
the previous week naked point of control
is right at the 1618 of the initial
balance expansion.
Well, that gives me a lot of confidence
that's where we're going to try and go.
that can um that can actually work in
your favor, Tyson, because you're going
to trade eight more days now and you'll
build out more of a buffer. Sometimes it
works in your favor.
So, you got to think, why are we going
higher here? Well, the mag's all gone
green. Apple's gone green. And guess
who's making us go higher? The shorts
that tried here. the shorts that tried
here, the shorts that tried here, the
shorts that tried here, the shorts that
tried here, and every time we go higher,
they stop out. And we go and we go and
we go. Once we see exhaustion, you'll
see the pull back and attempt to go
higher again. We're almost there, folks.
We are almost there.
is this NQ or NQ1? That's the same
thing, right? NQ1 is the same as NQ. NQ1
is always going to be the current
contract. The current contract is NQ.
It's the same thing.
Yeah, I do use fibs. Yeah, absolutely.
Often I don't draw them on because I
can, you know, I can kind of visualize
where a 50% drawback or a 61% or a 33%
draw like pullback would be.
Rain life, I spent $7,000 on one teacher
a couple years ago
and for $699, it's a bargain. I've
learned so much just the past week
trading with you. That's awesome. I'm
sorry that you spent7,000 on someone and
it's it's ridiculous, isn't it? The the
garbage they teach for insane money.
What was the 860? I said no. 8.90 up
here. All right. It's a naked point of
control on a weekly and it's also a 168
expansion of the initial balance. So if
you do a fib of the initial balance,
you can see the 1618 is right into the
same level
literally to the tick pretty much. Yeah,
to the tick of the previous week point
of control. That is where they want to
go. We haven't pulled back. So just be
aware it might pull back like we are
squeezing and squeezing and squeezing
and squeezing. ES now into um
get your brain working GlobeEx. So I
think Foster's got a couple others along
ES worth taking some profit here.
Still holding five micros from 689.
689. Yeah, same point. You got more size
on than me. Nice work.
What is my A+ entry setup? I'd have to
draw it out for you, but it would be we
had it last week.
We had it. Was it last week on Friday?
last week
my plus my A+ entry I'm going to come up
here and draw it if higher time frame if
it was short right if it was a short
we'd have higher time frame have done
this right and we've left this trap
buyers up here and we've come down here
and it's a sell into that and then in
here lower time frame I'm looking for
something like this all right and that's
my A+ entry where we leave volume trap
buyers and we have a clear move down and
it would be the opposite
for the buys. Why has today and the last
few days not been an A+ buy? Well, it's
because we've not swept that liquidity.
We've not trapped enough shorts at the
lows. But you can see today they've just
turned the turn the booster on. We're
almost there, folks. We need 40 more
points. Let me just move this stop up
and I'm going to use the bathroom just
in case I get caught in a flush. I will
tell you now. Buyers stepped in at 813s,
824, and 836. So really sellers, you
don't want it under 8 814 8:15 as a
buyer, right? So I'm going to put my
stop up there to protect it into the 10,
maybe even higher here. Do I really want
to give 30 points back?
Maybe. All right, be right back.
All
right, here comes the pullback. I said
it's probably coming. It's been a big
extension.
So, you can always take your profits
here. You don't have to sit through this
draw down. It's a big squeeze. This can
completely collapse. This can completely
collapse all the way back down to here
if it wants.
>> [snorts]
>> Do I lock some in here?
Do I lock this runner in?
We're going to come down to these 10.
They're bidding these tens.
They're coming for these tens. All
right, I'm out of this. I'll reload. If
I want to reload, I'll reload. That was
a really, really, really good trade.
Give a little bit big bat off the top
like could have lots more in, but I'm
willing to rebid. All right, so our
target is up here.
If we drop that down deep enough, I will
rebid.
They're protecting tens.
And they might do one more little flush.
But this is the target.
A trap play would be something like
this. All right. To come back up. All
right. If they trap enough shorts in
here, otherwise all the way down here
sort of sideways. And they might do this
later in the afternoon.
Either way, what did I manage to get out
of that on the runner up?
130 odd points. Not bad.
Not bad.
Nice work everyone. Yeah, lovely work
everyone.
No, I swear just it required so much
patience today. We had to avoid it was
it was very I was getting very
frustrated when we were doing this
nonsense here because we weren't
sweeping anyone and we weren't
reclaiming a level. But you see like the
importance like even here I got pissed
off because I'm like this goes all the
way up. My fear was that we did
something stupid.
But fortunately, all right, fortunately
they played the game in here and that
gave us the entry. And that's the kind
of build if you look at that. Just a
basic two-leg flag, isn't it? So in
here, I'd be looking for an inverted
head and shoulders or something. Some
form of juicy trap. Now, if I was going
to reong, right? You'd want all the
shorts to pile in and something like
this. It might take time to develop.
Might be that they have to go sideways
into lunch and then do it later on in
the day. But I think this will get
tagged. I think it will get tagged.
We're still holding flow zones. I mean,
some of you can still be long. There's
nothing wrong with still being long.
[snorts]
Yeah, I felt the same. I felt the same.
Full forward. I felt the same. I was
like, do I just hold it? Like I know
it's going to go there, but the other
thing is like, do I really want to give
100 point back on a pullback? Like I get
caught in that kind of frame of mind.
900 up on the day. Can you sell? I mean,
I I wouldn't be selling. I wouldn't be a
seller in this market right now. It's
why it's we've got low hanging fruit up
here to hit. You've not left volume yet.
You've not created enough. I don't think
the high is even very good. I'll have a
look. It's not bad actually. It's not
too bad.
You can see absorption happening down
here. Point of control on this
fiveminute candle. How long have we got
left? One more minute on this fivem
minute candle. We've just flipped point
control up. Sellers right now stuck
here. We have an imbalance down here
into 800s. I think they they'll want to
do a dip and rip. It just depends how
long they uh need to take to do it.
I don't think this is done yet.
625 690. Thanks, mate. Uh all right. So
690 is where we're above it. It's
previous day high there for it to come
and hit on spy
65. Clear. Yeah, clearly a level on
cues. Clearly levels. But if we get
through that, we'll get positive gamma
squeeze up to 627, I'd say. And the same
on ES. Remember ES is trying to do the
gap fill. We tal we talked about this
yesterday on the spiders.
Right, we've got gap fill above. There
it is. All right, that's the gap fill.
We still haven't filled I move this out.
We still have not filled this gap. All
right, we filled this on the cues
yesterday. We have not filled this gap.
It's where the market wants to go. It's
trying to fill this gap if it can
pass 250 TPTs today. Nice work, order
flows. Nice work.
One of three today, but a good week.
That's all that matters. Don't judge
yourself on one day, right? judge it
over like a month and a year
trend day for longs. Yeah, absolutely.
We we are that we're above IB, right?
We're above IB. What else are we above?
Previous days value area high. What else
are we above? Current week's value area
high, right? We're in expansion mode
right now with a clear target.
This is the target,
right? from starting from the week of
the 12th,
we're trying to get into this node
and that's the point of control bang in
the middle of it. Right? So, we're
expansion over here, over here, trying
to get into here. It's what the market's
trying to do right now.
Right? We were rotation in here.
Rotation was in here. Now, we're in
expansion after that rotation. If we
came under here today, I know the person
got annoyed. We came under here. Guess
what? But we would have been expansion
underneath this rotation. It's how we
build liquidity. Like I can't say this
enough especially for you newer traders
or you guys that are getting frustrated
like if you don't understand that when
you are seeing this being done for
sessions and sessions on end. When we're
boxed in, we talked about it pre-market
today and yesterday and the day before.
When we're boxed in, this is a liquidity
build. When we break out, we will
squeeze. When we break down, we will
squeeze. This is a liquidity building
phase. If we come above here, we are
probably truly bullish in the market at
that point.
Okay.
Yeah. You're welcome everyone. You're
welcome.
These chips might start grabbing a bit
again.
Weaker video
weaker INTC
IBGO.
What about the broader names?
O fable corp today.
You're welcome, guys. 1.6,000 long
today. Nice.
Is it okay to buy? I wouldn't be buying
here. I wouldn't be buying here.
We were long out from down here, right?
We've just sold. There's a chance we
move higher, but uh
it's just you're deep into premium now.
Unfortunately,
I think momentum's still up. It would be
nice if it did a second leg down
and then did this, but it might be that
it just does this.
But you just got to know if you're
buying high to go high. It's very, very,
very risky.
No, I'm out of it. I'm out of it. I sold
I sold here. I don't want to sit through
the draw down or give like a 100 points
back if they feel like they need to do a
deeper drive into here. I didn't want to
give it back. So, it might be that it
continues to come up, but I'm happy with
what I made. So, I'm just going to take
that and be okay with it. What time do I
go live every day? 9:15 Eastern time.
Would you take a short for the pullback
or is it too much risk? I'm not going to
short counter trend trade it like
it is it possible it wants to do this?
It is, but we are above initial balance.
We're holding flow zones. We are in a
very bullish state right now. Like why
try and time that perfectly?
It's this is different now, okay, to the
last few days. Why is it different?
The last few days we had people to lean
on, right? So
come here.
We had lots of volume to lean on.
And Thursday,
we hadn't taken out the highs. We were
protecting the highs and we had volume
to lean on on a straight squeeze up.
Right? This was a straight squeeze up.
And here, oh, the same thing.
Straight squeeze up. You can see we
where we played these longs earlier in
the week. Straight squeeze up. And then
we faded this
right into key level. Lent on it. This
is different. Now we're above value.
We're running stops.
Doesn't mean it can't come lower, but
it's my bias for deeper prices is is not
really there today. now.
No, I don't trade fixed size. You can't
trade like I don't understand like you
can trade fixed size if you're a
beginner and you're trading like very
small lots. You can't trade fixed size
when you have to risk based on ATR and
swing points. [snorts]
Can I explain previous week point of
control? Yeah, it's just the value of
the previous week and it's the level
which was traded the most and it's never
been touched.
And I take a look at QQQ. It's going to
be exactly the same as this pretty much.
25s is the gamma level. If we get over
25s,
then 27s is where probably where we're
going to try and come. Um, you are if
you're short at 22, is that what you're
saying? You're short of this breakout.
This is the prop. This is what I'm
saying. This is exactly why I'm saying
why I said that the short here today
wouldn't work. One, two, three, four,
five. Probably go back. There's probably
more.
Yep.
Six, 7, eight. Lots of stops there,
right? Which is why we didn't want to be
short there today. You can't. If we
imagine that this is cell pressure and
this is a brick wall,
right? How many times if I keep banging
into that brick wall, eventually the
brick wall is going to break, which is
what happened today.
I'd say you'd look in trouble on those
puts.
Yeah, I consider ATR.
Alex, what data broker? I I pay for it
all, Rob. I pay for it all from bookmap.
Uh what's it called? Maybe I can find it
in here.
How can I find my global plus yearly
is what I haven't put that
right. How are we doing for likes? Can
we do some giveaways yet?
So, most of you probably already in this
long. Lots of you leaving because you've
made all your money, which is I mean
that's a good way to be on a Friday.
Yeah, the problem. So, the the problem
is uh what's your name? MJ MJ. MJ, the
problem is yes, you're right,
but how many times are we going to come
back up here? You're right in what
you're saying,
but it's like a four week range.
Okay. Okay, so let's think about it. We
left it here, traded back inside,
created balance, poked above, failed,
flushed, coming back into it. We We have
They haven't defended the bottom side of
this range. They tried early week. We're
through it. We're coming up to P. If we
hold above PC next week, then it means
there are no buyers uh who are no longer
stuck. They probably already stopped out
or they reaccumulated and everyone tried
to sell against them. So if we go
sideways here for a bit,
then we have the room to run these
stops.
All right?
Doesn't have to do it, but we have to be
willing to understand that that is now
very very possible. If we can close up
here and stay here next week, it has to
close up here and stay here next week.
Hey, can you help with a potential entry
level for a long? I like personally I I
would wouldn't really be looking for a
long until it came back down here and
trapped more participants in like down
here and like some sort of flush and
maybe a range and then build out and
then do this again. Otherwise, I'm
probably done for the day, guys. It's a
Friday. We've locked in 130 plus points.
I just drew that on the wrong screen,
didn't I?
Here.
I'd want it into here and I'd need to
see sellers get trapped.
No, Ninja's free, mate. Ninja's free.
Right, I'm going to get on to some of
these now.
Four more likes, folks, and we'll do a
giveaway.
What copper am I using? Affordable
indicators.
1,400 cross three evals will be funded
again next week. Nice, mate. Good work.
Good work. Good work. Good work.
What site for news calendar? Thin viz or
uh what's it called? market watch.
All right, let's do
Okay, guys. So, because I stream for
free on here, the way you can support
the channel is by using code FCT with
prop firms pretty much for all the all
the best prop firms. I have lots of
videos out on that right now. The only
one that you can use a different code
with is take profit trader. Use code
flow zone. But for everyone else, use
code FCT. And if you type FCT in chat
now, just type it once. Please don't
spam it or you won't be entered. You
will have the chance to win a free Apex
account right now. So, I'll give you
guys a minute or two to do that. Just
type it once in chat and we give give
one away.
It's coming down to that previous day
low as well. Interesting. That's kind of
stuck.
It's been another TPT request today. I
[\h__\h] love take profit trader. It's so
good
guys. One more minute.
Hopefully all you uh new lot today
learned something. It's the most
important thing
got to learn.
Okay.
Uh, if you want to look at gamma levels,
look at stuff like unusual whales and
stuff like that. They've probably got
some stuff on that.
Okay, pulling a winner here in five,
four, 3,
two, and one.
Well, I'm going to attempt to say your
name.
Alton Sebastian 5937.
Yeah. Flow zone for TPT. Alton Sebastian
5937. Are you here?
There you go. All right.
Congratulations. You've won a free Apex
account, any size that you want.
All you've got to do is email me
info@flonetrader.com.
Send me a screenshot of you logged into
your YouTube, okay? And uh just to prove
it's you and I will send you a code and
you can have any size Apex account you
want. Anywhere from 25K up to the 300K.
You can use a static account if you
want, whatever you want. All right, so
just email me info@flowzontrader.com.
You're welcome. You're welcome.
Okay. And we'll give away a 2hour
introduction course as well. So just
type course in. This is great for you
you lot who've never ever traded before.
All right, if you've traded before, it's
probably going to be a bit easy for you,
but it's a good place to start and it
you can always give it to a friend. Just
type it once in chat.
Thanks, Bradley.
I'm not looking for a short today. I'm
not looking for a short today. People
keep asking. I'm not looking for a short
today. We've got a clear target above
that it wants to go to. It's possible
that it leaves this. There is like
there's a counter trend short down to
here, right? But I would be of the
assumption we probably do this later in
the day. So, you just got to know if
you're going to play this counter trend
short, you've got like 50 points max,
right? As we leave this volume here,
max. They can stop short. All right,
they have a node here. I'd expect buyers
to step in somewhere around here and try
and absor absorb and go again. So maybe
you're in it here for this move down to
here. But you better be paying yourself.
You cannot assume that today collapses
like the other days. It's very possible
that they hold anywhere in here.
This is your second leg when we talk
about the two legs. One,
two. What I want to see down here is
someone get trapped. And then this.
Okay. Give you guys a couple more
seconds.
Hopefully, even me like telling you
this, if it if it plays out, even if it
doesn't play out, it's going to help you
understand it. The next time you come to
the screens, you'll see, oh, this is
what I'm looking for. This is where I
think price can go. I don't think it can
necessarily go further than that. So,
I'm going to take profit into that
level.
Okay, choosing a winner here. Five,
four, three, two, and one.
Chad W74.
Are you here, Chad?
you here, Chad? There you go.
Congratulations, Chad. So, an
introductory course. It's only two hours
long, but if you've never traded before,
you might find it useful. Otherwise, you
can always give it to a friend or a
family member. Nice little present.
Saved yourself 100 bucks. Um, same
thing. Email me info@flowzonerader.com.
Send me a screenshot of you logged into
your YouTube. I've made a note of your
name and I will sort you out with a free
course once you do that.
So you can see here, so those of you who
were just talking about the short and I
said you have to respect these nodes.
There you go. Right. So the short it's
just a counter trend trade into where
they were willing to bid off into here.
If they start to reclaim this, this can
be the squeeze back up. What I would
have been looking for is in here. There
you go. This is exactly what we talk
about. So into that demand level at the
lows of this auction on this one minute
chart, you have sellers caught. All
right? If buyers now can get back above
here, they've got a shot. All right? So
these are the things you look for here
to here. Buyers need to get back above
that. If they do that, they've got a
shot. These are the kind of like scalpy
trades you can look for.
You're welcome.
Lori, I'm I'm probably done for the day,
mate. I'm like I'm I'm happy with the
money I made. I'm done for the day.
Like, I don't need to keep pushing it on
a Friday. It's 30 minutes until lunch.
We've had a decent week. Um,
you know, I've missed some uh I don't
know if you were here early in the week,
but was it Wednesday? I think it was
Wednesday and
Tuesday. I think it was those two days.
I had two attempts
or three attempts on each of those days
of some very big fades and got knocked
out to the tick before they went without
me, which is a big trigger point for me
to be very careful about. Um, so like
sometimes you just have to be happy with
what you got.
There's not many not many jobs you can
do where you make comfortably into four
figures and still feel pissed off that
you've not made five or six. So, it just
is what it is.
Oh, Stephen, if you're here, I just see
your email. Let me get that sorted for
you now.
Tools.
that you set up.
Okay, it should work for you now,
Stephen. You're here.
Yeah, should work for you. Sorry, mate.
Only just see that now.
should be all good. Okay, into this gray
box. They refaded. Buyers couldn't
reclaim this level. So, there's no
squeeze points. They tried to bid here.
They failed to reclaim. We drift down.
This is the key point now. And if they
really let this go,
I'd find it somewhat surprising, but I
mean there is an argument to come back
down to previous day value high, but I'd
expect them to try and defend in front
of that.
But you're on a Friday coming into
lunch. So, this is why I'm kind of like
happy to just chill at this point.
ES might want to come back down to those
45s where it originally broke out from.
Seller just came in here at 70. So,
buyers will want to squeeze him out if
they can. Yeah. Just be careful, folks.
You're on a Friday. Like, you don't want
to go like ruining your day or your
week. You've worked really hard. Don't
give it all back.
Thanks Jay. Looking forward to working
with you then.
We did get the sale. Yeah, you got the
sale here. But you have to respect uh
structure as well. You've definitely got
the sell. We have been a straight
squeeze up, but we we must respect
structure as well
into the 50% pullback as well.
And you have to respect structure.
Everything matters, right? Everything
matters. This is momentum, but we just
came right into the IB.
Have you received my email? I don't I
don't know. You just emailed me.
Yes. I just see them. I'll do them as
soon as I get off stream. I I'll handle
all of that.
Is that footprint of Trading View? Yeah,
I will. I I did a video for it already
uh last weekend. How to set up footprint
on Trading View.
If I buy the indicator and later the
course is their discount on the course
as it's indicator included. The
indicator that comes in the course is
just like a simplified version of the
flow zones. The pro that you're seeing
on here with like uh GlobeEx and
Orb and uh some other key things is an
upgrade but you don't have to get it.
There is a version that you can trade
off that comes free with the course. So
you can see they've just dipped this IB.
It's interesting to play long here. I'm
going to be honest. Very interesting to
play long here. Watching how they act
into 800
to just scalp a bit up into this
imbalance.
That's why I saying this area here I
expect them to react into. Going to try
and stop myself trading. It's very I'm
very interested in rebidding this
because I think we've got unfinished
business. But it's probably better that
I just behave myself here.
Does it work on Trading View? What's
that, Chris? Sorry, I'm not sure what
you're talking about. Does what work on
Trading View?
So, I would still say this node up here.
Buyers buyers are going to try and
defend this and come up into here now,
right? Which is what we're seeing off
the IB off this level. Remember this is
where the stops were that we broke out
from on from last Friday. This is from
last week Friday top of the gray box
breakout pull back. This level here
becomes key. If they get through this
then we are still going for up here. All
right. This is what I was saying to you
the whole time.
Hopefully this is going to start making
sense. If sellers defend this all right
and they get under here then there's an
argument for lower but not until then.
This is a pullback. That will be a
squeeze.
This will be a resell.
Two options. Personally, I'd be more
bullish in this market right now with
how we're operating. Here we go. So, I
was very tempted to take this squeeze up
to this level. There you go. So, into
into this level. If you find acceptance
over here now and then go sideways for a
bit, you're probably going to get that
naked point control.
[laughter]
I know it's doing exactly as I said. I
know it is. I know it is. That's not
because I'm magic. It's because it
respects levels. When NQ's doing the
right thing, there was a moment this
week when it really pissed me off
because it wasn't respecting stuff. But
it respects levels, right? There's a
reason there's a purple line on my
chart, right? It's the initial balance.
There's a reason for the top of the gray
box. All right? It's because it's where
we popped the stops from last Friday.
Right. Right here. All right. There's a
reason for it. So, there's a reason for
this to be a pull back into it, isn't
it? And now there's a reason for it to
get back into this level. And if it
squeezes over here, think about
guess who would have come flying in.
Yes, there they are underneath the IB.
These silly, silly people. All right.
So, you had big selling here, here,
here, here. All right. And if we hold
now bids above that and certainly above
this, anywhere above this, this can now
continue higher. That's why I said I
wouldn't be selling it today unless it's
just like for a scalp down to this level
as a maximum point point that we could
go down to. [snorts]
Hopefully it makes sense to you, right?
Hopefully what I'm trying to teach you
for free is making sense. Hopefully it's
going in that brain of yours and next
time you'll be like, "Okay,
we are bullish. Why am I trying to
short?
Can I share my volume profile
parameters?" Yeah, it's just two ticks
right here. I have it on ticks per row.
You can have a number of rows. If you do
number of rows, have it on a th00and and
two ticks. That's all I change. That's
all I change. [snorts]
Nice, Stephen. Nice work, mate. Nice
work.
Yeah, I was very tempted to take it, but
I'm just like telling myself it's
Friday. I'm pretty tired. It's been a
really nice week. We've locked in four
figures. Going to pay myself another
four figures today. It's pretty much
every day this week on TPT and um yeah,
little resistance. Yeah, for sure. For
sure there is a little resistance here,
right? You can see this node, but my
anticipation would be that we're
probably going to get through it. We
might have to go sideways for a bit. It
might be that we do like this,
but my anticipation is we will probably
come up here today, right? So all all
day long once we start breaking out.
[snorts]
What are you seeing from last Friday?
Exactly. It It's just a high wick of a
candle. If you go back to last Friday
and you look at 10:00 a.m. All right.
That's where we started shorting last
Friday. So, think about anyone who was
short last Friday. Where would their
stop have been? It would have been
there, right? So, we had a group of
stops at 40s, 740s, and then we had a
group of stops basically at that sort of
65 level. Okay? Once we get through that
group of stops, we're assuming pullbacks
hold into that because anyone who is a
seller there then becomes a buyer,
right? So, they become a buyer again
here. And the anticipation is that we'd
probably come up into this naked point
control.
Thank you. Followed exactly what you
said for the pullback and reversal for
$1,000. There you go.
Need four figures daily living in LA. I
certainly do, mate. Certainly do.
Oh my god, I nuked two funded accounts
by a tick or two and it immediately came
all the way back. Sounds like you were
maybe overleveraged a bit there, my
friend.
Thanks for a profitable week. You're
welcome, Bart.
SVP look SVP settings. Just anchor to
9:30. All right, very simple. Anchor to
9:30 and use two ticks or a th00and
rows. That's all you got to do.
How do I mark my previous point control?
I I just measure out that whole week.
That's all I do.
Define naked by non- naked. Uh a naked
point of control is just an untested
level. Or if you were doing like
Malaysian SNR, you'd call it a fresh
level. This is a fresh level, right?
Because this is from last week. Since
last week in this week, have we ever
tested it?
No. Right? We gapped down. We never
tested it. Right? So, if this is fair
value from last week, we're trying to
test is this fair value. All right?
We're trying to get back up to last
week's fair value.
Uh, just send any email to
info@flowzonetrader.com.
I'll have a look at everything when I
get off.
How do we know those sellers haven't
taken profit and left the market
already? Whi which sellers? The one from
last Friday. I mean, you don't. They
probably did take some profit, but when
we're talking about institutional
selling, we're not talking about like
one or two lots, are we? We're talking
about thousands and thousands of
contracts.
Do I plan on taking any trades today?
I've already taken 130 point trade. I'm
I'm done. I've made my money.
Malaysian SNR. I'm Malaysian. Then then
you know Malaysian SNR or I assume you
know Malaysian SNR
because if you're from there it's very
it's very popular. Okay. So this is what
we just talked about this pullback.
Do they hold this little imbalance and
leave these guys here stuck? All right.
If they leave these guys stuck and they
hold this and they reclaim then upside
this gray box so far offering some
resistance but I would still anticipate
we will go through it. It might take a
while but I would anticipate that.
I don't have it measured out on ES.
Sorry mate. I'm not going to go through
all my charts and do it now.
How do we know they were higher time
frame traders? Well, you you don't know.
You just need to make the assumption
that institutional traders are not
trading for a tick,
right? And pivots will always be pivots.
That's why the market moves.
So, more absorption leaving these
sellers down here stuck. And again, the
longer it's here,
the more this becomes possible because
now you've got stops here, stops here,
people to test here. And we are above
initial balance. We are in bullish
momentum. We are in bullish momentum.
[laughter]
No more giveaways, guys. Well,
let's have a look.
Yeah, quite right, Anthony. 9:30 to
10:30 is initial balance. Yeah, the
first hour, the high and low of the
first hour of the New York session.
Correct.
>> [snorts]
[clears throat]
>> Initial balance should always be 1 hour.
All right. If if they're doing uh half
an hour, I'd just call that 30 minute
range or or 30 minute opening range.
Yeah. I wouldn't I wouldn't call it
initial balance. Initial balance, how
I've always been technically taught, is
the first hour.
Just replying to some of you guys who
won.
Okay, those who won just emoji back.
Uh yeah, Dean, I did uh do it on Ninja.
just haven't had a chance with
everything going on um to launch it, but
I I have I have got it on on Ninja as a
paid thing. I wanted to get it up. Uh
maybe I'll try and get it up this
weekend if I get some time. Yeah, I have
uh I have managed to do it. Yes, indeed.
I think uh
a couple people have it. [sighs]
Yeah, I haven't I I forgot to put the
the uh sale page up.
How far back do you have the anchored
volume profile just to to the morning
session? 9:30. Here's the squeeze,
folks. So, they're going to try and go
for it now. This is the target that we
talked about. So, if you did take this
long or you rebid this long, right, you
can trim some into this high and then
try and get all the way up into here,
right? So, this could be 100 points. If
you took it from here or here, you
should almost get 100 points up into
this final target.
This is what we've been talking about
all day long.
Do I ever trade the afternoon blocks? Uh
sometimes if there's a really good
setup, if I feel like the morning's been
selling up for an afternoon, so like if
we've gone sideways all morning long
without expansion, I'll consider the
afternoon is when I'm more likely to
trade the afternoon aggressively.
What about YM? I I don't watch YM.
Oh, I don't know. What did you put,
Dean? Sorry, that's not me. It's just
Nightbot. [cough]
Nightbot banning you. Is it? Have a
look.
Did trend friend Ninja ninja?
No worries, mate. Yeah, no worries. I
will get it up. I promise you. I think
we can go higher. Yeah. I mean, we've
been been saying it all all day, right?
All day.
the two leg to set the trap into here to
build the liquidity to use these stops
to get up into here. We literally talked
about it even when we're here. I was
telling you we probably needed two if
you rewind the stream to around 11:00
a.m. You would before any of this
happened would have seen me talk about
this exact setup.
Right? I talked about this exact setup
because this is how we get shorts
induced into the market so that we can
come up here. It's exactly how they do
it.
But worth going back like an hour so you
can see why why I said this is likely to
happen. Why? Because it's a giant
squeeze.
Giant squeeze,
right? 50% initial balance Friday 10:00
a.m. buy two-leg trap sellers create
liquidity. Use the liquidity to go here
if they can. This is their target. Not
guaranteed, but this is their target.
Same target we had from when we entered
long here, right? Same target.
Oh,
like an AI agent.
Right, I'm going to get a piece of fruit
and then come back. I'll be right back.
No juice.
We'll see into lunch. That's why I
running out of time.
I still got a shot of this. The hardest
thing is going to be coming into lunch.
They still got a shot at it. As long as
buyers protect this, they've got a shot.
The PC moving up there is not healthy
though above them.
Yeah, Willy, I do.
But it's been pretty much in line all
day today.
I move you over here.
Right. right here.
It's matched up pretty well this
morning. There was a lot of aggressive
buying happening when we were going
sideways, which had me very concerned
because it meant we have divergence and
passive selling here taking place, but
they managed to get the breakout and
force all those passive sellers to
become buyers. So, but I do look at it.
It's funny some some of you asking funny
questions like, do I use the dom?
What's above me?
definitely use a DOM.
Would I consider buyers on GLL at all
following the massive squeeze on metals?
Do you mean a a swing position?
It's almost that target.
It's almost there. It's got room.
It can It can afford a pull back and a
reload, but it's got room. Silver
probably going to go to uh the 100 or
it's already done it. Amazing.
I mean, this is a wild breakout from
base.
How many sigas? Hang on. Let me have a
look at this on
[\h__\h] me.
Yeah, it's running out of room. I mean,
it's hugging five. This is like a really
healthy trend
when we see this on the daily. 5day top
bowl, 5day top bowl, 5day top bowl, 5day
top bowl, 5day top bowl, 5day top bowl,
5day top bowl. I mean, it's going to be
due a pullback. You might see like a
blowoff top coming soon.
But it's running out of room.
Definitely running out of room. Probably
gold might have. Yeah, gold's way
extended through the [snorts] top
Ballinger on a daily. We move to weekly.
Has it got room? Through it on a weekly.
Let's check the weekly on silver.
Yeah, well over it. Yeah, these are
extended.
I wouldn't be buying these. No way. But
you would need you'd need to see
backside before you fade it,
right? So what you what would you need
on silver? You'd need a reason to be
able to fade it. You'd need volume trap.
Same [snorts] as we always talk about.
So probably it's more likely like the
first start is more likely to be under
here, right? So if you see a rejection
of like 98s, we come under 98 and you
see a rejection of 98s, then there's a
trade back down into this cluster. If
you start to see it then let go of 90s
then we can start attacking lower
prices. You got a huge amount of volume.
The real energy comes into market sub 85
86 right because you got this
consolidation here right? So, there's
probably a snapshot down into here to
the top of it. And then under that will
be more weakness.
All right, folks. I think I'm done. We
are done into lunch. Decent session.
Glad we took our profits when we did.
It's just chopping around now. Might do
this for a while. It might honestly
build out here for a while. They've just
had one go at trying to do it. They
failed. Still bullish and it can build
out liquidity here for a long long long
long long time. And then if it's ready
later on the day to have another go, it
can. If you start losing this look, VW,
everything's still coming up. You might
get a catch-up trade here and still have
that ability. Um, yeah, don't be giving
away your weekly profits on a Friday.
Do I cover bookmap in the course? Yeah,
in the um allining profile and orderflow
course. So on my website, right? So
everything's on the website we're
talking about, guys. I'll show you this
before we go. Just so you know what's
what's what and what's where.
Right, you head over to
flowzonerader.com
right here. Right, this is your 20our
course. This is everything included.
Right, 20 hours plus you get a version
of the flow zone indicator for trading
view plus you get access to the Discord
for life. All onetime fee currently
$649. It will be $699 hopefully by
Monday if I can get into it and get it
done. All right, volume order and order
flow course. following profile order
flow course cover everything in there
that that you need. This is like a
six-hour course. You don't get access to
the Discord with this course, but I go
through everything like footprint, bookm
CVD, divergence, what we're looking at,
track players in the market, volume
profile, everything is in there that you
that you need for like more advanced
stuff. I would say start with this
course here.
All right, start with this course here
so that you understand like key
principles of the market and then do
this course. You can buy them both
together. There's like a bump. You buy
them both together. Let's see what it
comes in at right now.
Um,
there you go. N 948 if you get them both
together. So, you get $100 off right
now.
Okay.
No worries, everyone. Yeah. Have a have
a Oh, did I just do that all on the
wrong thing for you?
Jeez, Alex, you absolute wally.
I'm going to try that again because some
of you are asking. Make sure you
understand.
Okay, there we go.
Right. flowzonerader.com
trading course. This is 20 hours on
demand. 20 hours plus a version of the
flow zone indicator plus the discord.
Okay, so lots in there. It's on demand.
The Discord is invaluable. You will only
get that from doing this course. It's so
that everyone trades the same way. If
you want to do the orderflow course
doesn't come with Discord, it's six
hours or over six hours and I cover all
the volume stuff, order flow, footprint,
bookm um CVD, divergences, everything
that you need to know for order flow is
in there. If you buy this one here and
you add on the volume and order flow,
you'll get $100 off. So, you get both
for 648 right now. All right, I will see
everyone else on Monday. Look out for
the newsletter. I will try and get it
done tonight. So, it'll be in your
inboxes tomorrow morning for all the uh
key levels that we're looking at next
week and all the key news. Don't forget
to sign up for that. It is completely
free. There are links down below for
everything I've talked about today,
including all the free stuff. If you're
brand new to the channel, don't just buy
the course. Go and do all the stuff on
my YouTube for free first. Make sure
that you understand as much as you can
for free and that you like how I trade.
I will see you back Monday. Remember,
there's a whole world out there that
doesn't involve charting. All right?
Make sure you go and enjoy some of it
because this is your job so that you can
go and do all the other fun stuff. Make
sure you're doing that fun stuff. I will
see you Monday morning, 9:15, bright and
early. Peace and love, everyone. Spend
time with your loved ones. Take care.