Morning everyone. Morning. Hope you're
doing good. Hope you had a good
afternoon session yesterday. Lots of
volatility yesterday.
uh caught the move up with me in the
morning, then the move back down. And
then maybe some of you positioned for
that move back up, which had happened
very quick off Trump's news.
What was the news? The news was that
they're coming to a deal with Greenland
and there's no longer going to be
tariffs. What a surprise. Just a one
huge massive bluff from him again. Okay,
so what do we have? Well, we filled the
gap on the daily, right? We're going to
start off in the daily as always. gap
filled on the daily. We can see that gap
was filled
right into here into just just under
700. All right. So, it's worth watching
that gap. If we're able to base above
that gap, we do have some levels to
drive for above. The one thing we need
to be very, very, very aware of, which
I've talked about numerous times, is we
have an old range up here. Week one,
week two, week three, week four. Okay,
this is where we failed to find
acceptance above it. We are still in
this like big old wedge right now. All
right, nothing's actually changed. We
had the chance to break down. All right,
and come and try and attack 900, but we
caught a bid down here in this blue box
like we talked about. Never was able to
break this and roll. So, we've gone back
to range, filled the gap. So, the
question now is, do we go back inside
this old box? Right? If we consider this
an old box, are we going to rotate back
inside here? All right. Or are we just
going to poke our head through and say,
"No, we don't want to go back in that
value and come back down." All right,
these are the two things that can happen
today is what we're thinking about
today. All right, so we need to be aware
of that. Let's have a look on the hourly
chart. Get some more details on this.
Okay, so you can see previous week's
value. Make sure this is big enough for
you guys to see. Let's move this up a
bit.
Okay, here's previous week value area
low. We're currently trading around it
right now. All right, so see this level
right here with this node right here.
And we're very, very thin on this drive
up leaving current week's value. All
right, so support really, really strong
support isn't down until sort of
25,440ish,
right? Previous day value area high,
previous day point of control, current
week value. This is really strong
support. This is an overnight. Make sure
this is overnight. Yeah, this is the
overnight squeeze into previous week's
value. If we hold bids here, right, and
we want to continue to squeeze, then
this right here is what it's a naked EC.
All right, so if we can rotate, this
will be target up towards the 900s. If
this is a poke inside and an absolute
failure, all right, if we fail this
node, which so far we're looking like
we're getting stuck around these two
nodes. If we fail here and fail to get
acceptance back into previous week
value, there is a trade back down to
here. You can see this pivot here. Let's
just move this out. There is a trade
back down inside this range possibly to
come and back test some of this. And
then we can see do buyers want to step
back in again or is this a complete
collapse again? So, a couple couple ways
to trade this. Um what don't I like? I
don't like trading in here. uh
unfortunately like I'd be willing to
place a buy here if we show a lot of
strength here and there's a squeeze up.
I'll think about it. But I want to be
very careful because we already know
what happens in here. Chop, chop, chop,
chop, and chop. Right? That's what
happens in this box. We talked about it
yesterday. Acceptance out of this box,
then we're probably looking for a big
old squeeze to alltime highs unless we
get a fail break and a sort of reversion
back down. At the moment it's starting
to look like this might be the failed
breakout side again twice like a woff
okay this might be the spring and now we
need to see do we find acceptance so
want to be careful for the rotation all
right this is not a day where I want to
be big big risk on if we move up to the
fiveminute chart we can just see how
we've got here right here was
the Trump news I think it was right here
2:00 yeah this is the Trump news huge
spike we managed to base above the old
pivot. All right, remember this was
resistance. This blue box was
resistance. It was red. It now becomes
support. All right, we find bids off it
into the close. Asia goes sideways. We
hold that pivot, that strong pivot 450
gets held. Uh, sorry. Yeah, Asia holds a
pivot. London drives back upside. We're
now at the 20-day on the mean reversion.
That's the other thing we need to talk
about. We're right back at the mean of
the Ballingers. So maybe if we uh just
talk about this a minute, we're right
back at the mean. If we think about
where the Ballingers are, right? Failed
to find acceptance underneath it. Top
Ballinger here, mean here. So 50% move
to here, 50% move to here, or 100% each
side, however you want to think about
that. All right, this is your range.
We've got room in the upside. We've
already covered the downside. So we're
right back to the mean.
Okay, going into the lower time frame
charts now.
Uh
this right here is a node. This gray box
is our gap. If you want to mark out any
of these levels, I'll leave them here
for you. But you can see this is the
strong support right now. Sort of five
520s down to 450s is a level of interest
for me. If they are willing to hold bids
down there or even if they're willing to
hold this previous week value and old
gap and then we're looking for that move
to 900. If we lose this, all right, if
we well, if we lose this, there's
probably a filter here. If we lose that,
there's another rotation down. We have
to be willing to play both sides at the
moment. It's just the market conditions
we're in. That's the market conditions
we're in. All right, let's have a look
at the ES and the ETFs, which are going
to look very, very similar.
Same story here on the ES. If we just
think about this pivot we talked about
the whole time, this kind of pivot level
here, right? Here's the Trump news.
Here's the pullback. We hold the pivot.
We hold it twice. We're now bullish and
they're trying to complete gap fill. Gap
fill for ES, by the way, is going to be
up into here. 976. So, it's not quite
there yet, but it's not far away. So,
yeah, we have to watch that. Let's set a
price alert there so that we know.
Um, why are you not doing that? Just do
it just shy. Then we can move it. Add
alert. There we go.
message ES gap fill
in case we start selling in the broader
markets once we get there.
Okay. Uh SPY, same kind of story. Let's
just check the gap. Yeah, same gap. Uh
if you're trading the ETFs, you're
looking at 9160s, 9170s for a full gap
fill. It is the same story here, folks.
Remember, we had a failed breakout on
the spiders of this all-time high move.
All right. Oh, I don't know what that
is. This failed breakout. We have the
same kind of thing here that we've been
talking about on the cues where we have
this box. All right. Most of the box is
sort of 930.
930. Sorry. 690. God, why can't I talk?
690. Yeah, 690. All right. Most of the
volume is trapped in there. So, do we
reject this and rotate that down or are
we going to hold and just do one of
these again and build out for a week or
two into earnings and then you know
what's coming after that if we're able
to do it. So, all to play for. Same
story on Q's
gap already filled up. We talked about
so ES is the one lagging. Same story
into this volume. Can we find
acceptance? How long did that last?
Dixie trading back downside. All right.
Taking uh pressure off the market. We
zoom out of here. All right, we need to
see is the Dixie now going to collapse
and break down or is it going to try and
reclaim this same range?
VIX got absolutely smoked. All right,
back down into this old pivot. So, we
can make this blue again. All right, so
that big spike up on VIX got sold into
these now turned to resistance levels
because we traded through them the other
way. You can see how I trade all the
levels become important all the time and
we are probably back into sort of some
form of trend here on VIX. So, we had
this channel. We had a channel breakout.
All right. And we're back into channel.
So, all the time VIX keeps fading under
these key levels. It's already filled
its gap pretty much. If we get down into
these, it just means the market's going
to continue to squeeze up.
All right. MAG, how we doing for time?
Not too bad. I got to get a bit of a
move on here. Apple finding a bid
yesterday, but again, you're going to
see the same story here, folks. All
right. Gap is all the way up here to
55s. We gapped down on Tuesday. We lost
we lost that bid through Tuesday. We
haven't even got back up there, but we
are inside previous day's range right
now. So, the question is, can we retest
this on Apple or is this a build out of
liquidity to remain weak? But a little
gap up here, but it's still inside
yesterday's range. Amazon,
same kind of story. You can see where
I've got the alerts above. That's the
old range. It's trying to reclaim.
Might well find a lot of resistance up
there.
Google, massive strength yesterday, all
day strength. Even off the Trump news,
more strength. We're already back into
that range on Google. All right, we're
already back into it.
Meta, same kind of story. Remember, I'm
still long meta. A nice hold of 600s
there, the whole number. And we just
have to see like can we get back into
these these blocks up here, sort of
640s, 645, 650s wants to come and trade
back into there. Remember that's same
story across all tech right now. These
are the trap participants, right? We are
coming in to test these levels. Do we
find a sell from there? Do we find
acceptance through as we come into
earnings in the next few weeks? It's the
same story across the board. Same on
Microsoft. Argue Microsoft's
considerably weaker. It's got a long way
to go to get up here, but maybe not 20
points. I guess it's achievable. But
that's where it's trying to go. Strong
strong break away from here. Mean
reversion back up. Do they resell it?
And then Nvidia. Remember, chips have
caught a name um caught a bounce here.
Nvidia coming up for this gap fill. We
can uh add this alert in here as well.
So, we're aware of it.
Right, that's the gap fill up into 86s
from that. What is that? Friday to
Tuesday gap. Yeah, same kind of story.
Tesla, same story. It came up to it
yesterday, rejected. It came up to
pre-market rejected, but it's still
holding high lows. So, can it find
acceptance back into that old range?
It's the same story across the board. We
can look at some uh broader names here.
Oracle got a long way to go, right? Got
a long long way to go to get back up.
It's inside this pivot, but really it
needs to get back into this range up
here to the 200. Nvidia offer earnings
still starting to climb back, right?
Still holding this long. I'm still feel
fairly comfortable in this. Right. We we
were in deep deep discount, which is why
I feel feel fairly comfortable and we've
just undercut that. So, anyone who is
looking at this with me, right, we were
in deep, deep discount and willing to
add back into the 70s, but we've just
traded a 40% discount. All right, off
the all-time highs. AMD, a rocket ship.
All right, you can look at this. It's
getting ready to go, right? This thing
is looking like it wants to break out
again. I'm kind of a little bit gutted.
I only got a little bit left of this. I
sold I'm sure it was into the 80s, so
this must be pre-market.
Maybe I'm just wrong. Must be wrong.
Okay, I'm sure they got into the 80s.
But anyway, AMD looking like a rocket
ship trying to retest these highs and
potentially break out.
So, tech strong, chip name strong. Um,
we do have news coming today as well
that you need to be aware of.
Zoomed in.
Uh let me just check this news. What
have we got today?
So yeah, 10:00
um
personal income delayed report. Uh
personal spending delayed report um PCE
index delayed report PC yearover-year
core PCE as well. And then PCE uh uh
core PC year over year. So lots of
prints coming at 10:00. Be aware of
that.
All righty. See what you guys are saying
quickly. Good morning, everyone. Do me a
favor. Smash that like button nice and
early so I don't have to talk about it
anymore. We need to get up well over 400
likes so we can do some giveaways
towards the end of the screen
screen. End of the stream.
What are my settings for volume profile?
Uh, for which volume profile? I just
anchor everything from 9:30. All right.
Um, I'm interested in the 9:30 to 4:00
prints.
Morning from Arizona. Nice. Very nice.
Morning. Morning. Morning, everyone.
I don't trade uh options for those uh
individual stocks. I always trade
commons unless I'm doing a LEAP.
Correct. Yeah. 1%. Uh yeah. How do you
mark out previous day point control
value high? Val. Correct. 9:30 to 4:00.
That's exactly what I do.
Yes. Good morning from LA. Hopefully,
it's nicer day today. It was a bit muggy
yesterday. I think it's supposed to
rain.
I think it is supposed to rain.
So, make sure you've gone through your
daily routine, whether that be
meditation or doing your daily charts.
Make sure you're fit and able to trade,
all that good stuff, right? and just
turn up and expect to be able to
execute. Well, you've got to go through
your morning routine, morning process.
And let's see what we get here.
[snorts]
Somerset, summeret, UK.
Nice to see people from all over the
world here. Fantastic morning from
Morocco. Lovely. [snorts]
I bet it's hot there right now. Okay, so
starting to get stuck in this little
node, but remember if we find acceptance
above here, anywhere around here, the
drive is going to attempt to come to
this naked weekly PC up towards the 900.
If we start losing value and we want to
sweep, right, we've got lots of stops
down here that we can look at, even
previous days high, even VWAP. And if we
start losing more, then all the way down
here is possible. I'm going to get rid
of this. Thought it already got rid of
that.
So, don't rush out the gate. All right.
No rushing out the gate.
>> [snorts]
>> All right, folks. Almost there. 10
seconds left. Let's see what we do here
this morning. Nice and patient here as
we open up inside previous week's value.
Good luck, everyone.
Just going to watch this order flow to
start the day. See if we uh want to
sweep or hold or what we're going to do.
All of the mag opening up comfortably
green. We know we're coming into some
resistance levels. We know SPY hasn't
quite filled that gap yet.
So into previous week close here.
Seeing some selling here on the tape. So
underneath current or previous week
value
there. It's possible move down to 53s if
they really want it. And below why is
the weekly developing profile way way
lower. Right. Here's lower time frame
algo tag.
So, previous day high is down here into
50s. VWAP is hanging out underneath.
We can move significantly lower if they
really want to, but I'd imagine they'll
look for a sweep in a bit, but we will
see.
I don't think they finished upside yet
is my feeling.
Okay, watching this New York open now as
well.
So into lower time frame algo. Finding a
bid there. So far they're still stacking
bids way down into 650 right now.
[snorts] Back inside value now. So
bidding off lower time frame algo.
There's the squeeze back up inside.
Previous week value. Can it find
acceptance back inside that or not?
Apparently not. There's lots of bids to
come and fill down to 650 still.
So they're bidding all the way down into
here right now. We've got stat bids on
the tape. Just limit orders waiting here
to get filled at the moment.
[snorts]
The 80s
it's holding up well.
What was that? Okay. Nvidia crossing. So
Nvidia's now filled that gap. That's
what that alert was.
Is that right? Let me have a look at
that. Yes, it is right. Okay. Yeah,
Nvidia now filling that gap. ES finding
a bid. We're coming down to fill all
these orders like I talked about.
Previous day high possible here, right?
We just rejected value. We're going to
come back down into here by the looks of
it or attempt to come back down into
here. Still no trade yet for me. I just
want to see if these bids hold. ES new
high of day. So we've got divergence
here. Remember ES is trying to get back
up towards 75 to fill its gap right now.
SPY is trying to get back up towards 95
to fill its gap. It is into some sort of
supply here. So interested to see if the
market catches a bid here to join up
with the ES or if we go into a divergent
sell. So I'm still watching 700 as a
potential trigger if we're going to
trade back over that and inside for some
strength.
We filled most that or most of those
orders. Still some orders down there.
Watching this now into 700s.
Make sure that lines up. Yeah. 699. We
go. It's still not through that value
yet.
Still rejecting so far. So no trigger.
still rejecting previous week value.
If we get very heavy here and start to
get underneath the week before
650. Yeah, if we trade start trading
under 650 aggressively, there is
potentially the move back down to these
sort of 500s and 480s. So that's the
other side of it. If they really start
getting aggressive under 650
Okay.
So, I'm just watching the hourly here
and see like where we've got stuck and
where we'd need to find acceptance. We
just went over this pre-market, right?
So, if it's going to find acceptance,
it's got to reclaim this to do this. If
it keeps rejecting this, this here is
the next level where they might want to
bid off. So, you have to be careful
here. Be willing to like watch this both
ways while they make up their minds.
Lots of selling coming down here and not
getting that flush yet.
They're still bidding at 650. Still
waiting to get filled. Have they moved
any lower? There's some at 635s. So into
VWAP we come then. So this is the 650.
This is where we expected it to go.
Previous day high and VWAP. The question
is do they bid here or we going to see a
bigger flush now all the way down into
these levels? Very very very possible
that they do that.
So all the selling started at 670. So
670 down to this level now is all sell
side. All right. It is all aggressive
selling.
QQQ coming into a pivot. So they have
got a chance to bid off here buyers if
they want. Where we are now. Did we just
sweep? Yes, we've swept. So a reclaim
now. They've got a chance. If they stay
heavy versus 650, then I would imagine
we come down here. But if they start
reclaiming, definitely if they reclaim
up here, it's going to be a giant
squeeze over 670 probably. So buyers
came in over 670, sellers came in under
670. That's kind of your level at the
moment that they're dictating which way
we go. So still just waiting to see what
they want to do here.
Let's put some volume on here as well.
There we go. That probably lines up
pretty well. Yeah, not bad to that 670.
Okay, watching here.
Here's the drive.
I still adding liquidity lower at the
moment.
We are definitely not able to get back
over those 670s yet. We are holding
around the VWAP. ES
not really doing much to be honest.
Mag's still all green. All right,
Tesla's 0.28%. 28% up. Uh, Nvidia half a
percent up. Microsoft 1% up. Meta 3.14%
up. Google 1.60% up. Amazon 0.71% up.
Apple 0.93%
up.
This shelf here is the level somewhere
around here. This is the level that
buyers will need to get back above to
take control of this market. All right.
sellers will want to defend this to
complete a rotation down here. I'm going
to wait to see how we act here. Would
not be surprised to see a squeeze up
today, but just waiting at the moment
coming into these levels now. They're
approaching it and do they resell this?
Do we see some sellers step in here and
slap this back down or not? ES trying to
reclaim it New York open as well. So,
this is a good drive now into the 70s.
Watching here to see if we're going to
go through this PC and start to be
aggressive.
They trigger this long back upside here.
If the next dip holds, I'm going to join
long for a squeeze back up towards 95
and then see if we can get through
value. Here we go.
Are you going to fill on a dip?
What's this buyer doing here? Just want
to be careful. This buyer is faking
around 70. He's just pulled his order to
55. Not in yet. Was very, very close to
buying there and then didn't like what I
saw on the tape.
Someone's spoofing.
All right, into value area low. So maybe
they rebid 50 here.
Still no trade. Watching carefully. I'm
interested.
Yeah, they bid in front of 50. So this
buyer stepped in this time at 60. So 60
to 85 is the rotation. Squeeze will
happen over
probably 80. Definitely over 90.
Is this buy legit? It keeps up bidding
and then pulling. It just pulled again,
flashed and pulled, flashed again, and
then came in on the market. What is
feels like yesterday. Same kind of
player. All right. Well, we look good.
Here we go. So, into the 700s. Can we
get acceptance over that now? If we can
get acceptance over that, we're going to
start rocketing.
ES going for higher day, which is great.
Come on. We got to get back over 700s
and then start squeezing. We need to go
back over previous week value if we're
going to really start squeezing. So,
I'll trim some into this just in case.
Long from 62 at the moment. It might
come all the way back down.
Make your mind up.
big trading day. Zoom this in.
We're still holding pivots. Well,
holding 20-day well on QQQ. I think we
want to go back above value area low
here to squeeze. If we get back above
this, we will squeeze. Obviously, if we
get new over New York open
60 is the level where buyers keep buying
dips at the moment. If that breaks, then
we're going to see more of a flush.
They've held that what, three times now.
They're looking for the break through
700.
If ES can get going for the gap fill,
then Q's might find a bid with this.
Come on. You got to get back over 700 to
find acceptance into the old range.
Otherwise, we're going to get stuck
[snorts] here.
Don't want to lose 60s here. If they
lose 60s as a blush back down.
Still early. How much? Not even at the
orb yet.
Come on.
Big buyer getting caught here. Don't
like that. Don't like that. into this
same level. So, they're defending in
front of uh 700 right now. Big buyer
just got caught right there into 90s.
There you go. Flush through six to 60s.
This is line in the sand for buyers. I
will cut if we can't hold this
[\h__\h] buyer at the high. Always
someone getting stuck. Always someone
getting stuck.
Need to be careful here. All right.
Because under here, if we're going to
get acceptance lower, right, buyers need
to hold this and do this. If we're going
to get acceptance lower, there is room
for a full rotation. It's why it cannot
just be uh willing to force in. I'm
really I want to see the flow zones
turn. I'll start adding heavy above here
if we start supporting bids back up, but
otherwise, no.
The fact that buyers just got stuck here
three times in a row in front of 700s is
not a good look.
Yes, made hive day. Pulling back to its
VWAP now. New York VWAP.
What we doing on the spiders? Still not
gap filled there either.
91s.
Okay. Weakness here. Out of this now.
That's a shame.
Flow zone's in a cell. That buyer
getting stuck at 90 caused all the issue
there.
Yes. Back to New York open.
Okay.
Willing to flip bias if we start to lose
bids.
What's this pivot here?
4550.
Where's the next node? 600 and then
500s. Okay.
Oh my days. There we go. There's all the
buyers getting caught. This is why we
said got to be willing to flip bias if
we start to lose the uh bids here.
So, is that a flush which is absorbed?
ES right back down into 24hour VWAP and
previous day high.
If they don't rebid this, then I would
imagine we're going to trade
significantly lower.
Watching value area low here back into
the 50s is key.
So, is that a full sweep and a reclaim
of 50s and VWAP or not?
Are they going to reject this same
level? We just sold from previous day
high 53s.
Yes, bidding off previous day high and
VWAP 50s is the level now.
They're trying to reclaim here. Testing
back into 50s. Current value area low on
the day. Are they going to go rotation
back up again? Was that a flush just to
catch everyone out is the question.
Imbalance here up to what's this level
here? 61s.
This ain't too pretty to start
here. Six is orb now set.
Buy getting caught there again.
Back into 40s where this shelf was.
Sellers can't get it under 40s. Buyers
can't get it back above sort of 60s and
we are stuck.
Big buyer coming in here twice trying to
get a force up. Not happening yet.
Pinned. We're pinned. They need to get a
break through 50s and 60s to squeeze up
to 90s. Here they go. They're trying.
They're trying to get back into value.
Low volume node here is being protected
so far. They need to get through that
for that squeeze up. It's being
protected so far. Again, more buying
coming in here and getting caught so
far.
This is ugly start to the day.
I'm starting to wonder if I should have
just sold 50s when I said if we flip
50s, we should probably sell for that
move all the way down. I'm starting to
wonder if I'm going to regret this. And
we're going to come all the way down
now. That might be a miss. Did talk
about it. That might have been the miss
of the day. Oh my gosh. Is this going to
be three days in a row, Alex, where you
miss a big trade.
I think it is. I think it is. I think
I've just missed that. I said got to be
willing to flip by if we lose 50s. I
didn't take that re rebid back in for a
sale. And I feel like I'm about to
regret that big time.
[sighs]
Man,
that might sting. If we're going to fade
all day, that's going to really sting.
Annoyed myself. Annoyed myself.
Did anyone take that short for that 50
flip? I think you're going to get a fade
now.
>> [\h__\h] me.
[snorts]
Jeez Louise.
All right, sellers came in at 610.
That's the level that sellers want to
defend right now. They came in at 610.
Uh that's your opening range. So if we
get back inside the opening range,
there's a squeeze. Otherwise, you're
looking for downside pressure all the
way down into here now.
All the way down into there.
Yeah, nice. Nice you guys who did it. I
mean, I called it just that's when I get
very upset. This is what happens when
it's three days in a row. Now I probably
can't trade for the rest of the day. I
need to be very careful. I said it
yesterday. Missed the fade. Tuesday,
three attempts. Yesterday, the same
thing. And now I've just called it and
hesitated and missed it. What happens
when you hesitate? You miss you miss
good moves.
Is what it is. is what it is. All right,
Vick's coming back up to that pivot
and previous day value area high will be
your target. Now, if you can fade all
the way down, you'd be looking for this
block down here. I wouldn't be looking
for a fade under that. I'd be looking to
cover into those areas. All right,
covering into those areas. They're still
selling these lows here
and obviously cover on the way down.
This is a pretty good move. You're what,
80 points up from that 50s already.
And you're probably going to get they're
still bidding at 550 down here.
Some volume being built up here. So,
lots of orders coming in here. You're
going to you're going to look for this
area down here, folks.
Yeah. Well done everyone.
Well done everyone.
It's not that hard to flip bias. I said
I had to flip the bias, but it's just
that I didn't do it. I didn't execute
it. That's what's annoying. It's not
money. It's not like money lost. It's
It's money missed. Is that right way
putting it? Frustrating. It's
frustrating for me knowing that I had it
planned out and didn't take it. It is
what it is. All right. So, we into the
top of this shelf here. We can see this
like little node here developing.
Otherwise, they're going to trade up to
600. So, sellers will want to protect
this load this node around sort of 85.
Otherwise, they're going to see a trade
up to 6 and 610. There's a clear target
down here, folks.
Clear target back down below right now.
I'd watch this node 85. If they scream
through it, they'll come and fill some
above.
So, still tapping into this node. You
can see this like top of here. If they
can defend this, sellers will look to
rotate down. If not, there is a squeeze
back up. Lower time frame squeeze
obviously. All right. It'll be a lower
time frame squeeze. And maybe they look
for those sort of 610s kind of levels,
which is what they're trying to do right
now.
Filling [snorts] some of that imbalance.
Here they go. They're going for those
610s now. We just talked about it.
Here's the 600 test. So through the 85s.
I'm grabbing a piece of this up to 610s.
And we can watch that orb.
All right. And if we get acceptance back
through that, it means we don't fill
this. All right. So we're coming back
towards this level now. This and this.
Sellers will want to defend this for
this. If they can't and we see this, we
go rotation back up. This would be a dip
which is bought. Uh I would say sellers
are now caught under 73 on the day. All
right, sellers got caught under 73 on
the day under here. So, this is the
level that buyers must absorb. Sellers
want to get under it. Come on,
rectangle. Where are you? Right, this is
the level where sellers are currently
caught underneath.
Oh, Alex.
Well, at least I made some.
Here's 610s. All right, out of this now
and wait to see if we get acceptance.
So, managed to lock in a little bit
there. paid myself a little bit on the
way up. At least it's better than a kick
in the bollocks for the day, but I am
upset with myself there. I didn't flip.
Okay, back towards the same level that
we sold down from. So, your opening
range now being reclaimed. ES coming
into its 24-hour VWAP. Watch this pivot
very, very carefully on ES. I'd say
46es.
VIX getting stuck into that pivot as
well around the 1625s.
So buyers will want to protect this now
and they will want to get back inside
the rotation for the day. That's their
job.
If we squeeze then we'll need to get ES
will need to go through the VW up which
is not able to do yet and we will need
to reclaim all of these levels above. So
this is still just a pullback which get
sold into. Sellers must get it
underneath this gray box here. That's
really where uh the sellers are stuck
underneath there. If they can't do that,
there might be another leg up.
SPY testing the level we broke down
from. QQQ not there yet. So have to pay
attention to SPY. SPY is reacting very
well to the levels. If you look at like
the pre-market low, we've just traded
back into it, which is also lower time
frame algo. It's also previous day high
and it's also the 20-day moving average.
We're not trading through it yet. So
far, there's a reaction from there. Q's
are nowhere near there. Still have
strength.
So, inside value. Now, do we go back
through this node for 40s,
volatile market
trying to lift through 20 to go and test
40 at the moment.
It's not able to do it. They're stacking
at 25s to 35s. Bids are at 600 right
now.
Here we go. They're trying to fill the
25 now and they should try and get up to
40 if they can. And sellers came in
aggressively at 40. 40 to 50 is the next
big node that they will need to trade
through these buyers if we're going to
find acceptance in current days range.
Obviously, we're outside of previous
weak value area low. So, they're going
to want to reclaim all of that if
they're going to be very, very
aggressive today. Until that point,
technically, we can trade down. And this
is relief back upside into where these
sellers were at 40. All right. This is
relief back upside into where the
sellers were at 40. We have an imbalance
at 34,
which they just rejected. There's the
big sell back down to this gray box.
Remember, this is the key level. This
gray box is your key level,
right? Because we've got sellers stuck
underneath this gray box. This is your
key level. If we sell through this, then
you're going to see continuation back
down to previous day value area high.
This is the key level. Now, buyers must
protect that and sellers must trade
through it.
There are bids lower here.
I'm going to looks like we're going to
trade through it at the moment unless
they get restuck here.
What's this upside for the 605s?
They're adding liquidity much lower now
into 530 and 520 all the way down.
Might very well be that this is sold
through at this point.
They're adding lots of liquidity for it
to come and take out.
SP didn't get to be up. ES didn't get to
VW up. We are back down into these pivot
lows
rejecting pre-market levels on the
spiders. QQQ never got there. So, we're
a little bit out of sync in terms of
where we're at on QQQ versus SPY.
What are we doing here? I would assume
we're going to sweep all this liquidity
that's just stacked underneath us, but
we're still holding gray box for now.
There we go. I'm going to come for that
liquidity. Are we 70 all the way down to
45s at the moment? About 35's now added
and 25's now added.
Yeah, news in three minutes. You're
right.
still all the liquidity is underneath to
come and sweep. Everything's underneath
to come and sweep that. I'm sure there
we go. This is what I'm saying. When
they put these many orders here, it's
just they're going to come for them.
They're just going to come for them.
It's just what they do.
There has been a spoofer on the book
today though. There's one thing I would
say. There's been one guy spoofing
nonstop. Same as yesterday actually.
Maybe we'll wait for this news. Maybe we
can get bids off here.
We'll find out soon enough. We will find
out.
Yes, into its 5day and its pivot as
well.
Target is still down here. They starting
to lose this gray box now. The target is
still down here for those sellers
and they've now added liquidity at 500
as well. So, they're trying to get down
there maybe on the news drop.
box becoming key
towards the 600s again. He's got an
imbalance here just in front of 600.
Just 5 seconds here, folks. Be careful.
News incoming.
Maybe they can get down all these guys
we just talked about and then we can see
what's what
they come.
Some sellers got caught down there
again.
Didn't fill all liquidity. Finding a bid
so far.
How have they not come down into all of
this is beyond me. This is like
yesterday where it's like it's so clear
where they're trying to go and then they
can't do it.
Nice. Nice. Just passed three. Good
work.
Gray box still key. You're under over.
All right. Sellers are in control all
the time. We're under this looking for
that rotation down to there. Right.
Sellers are in control all the time.
They're under this looking for this
rotation down into these targets. Buyers
will take control once they're able or
if shouldn't say once if they were able
to do that, not before.
And still we come down.
VIX now above its pivot, folks. Be very
careful here. VIX now above its pivot.
And if it starts squeezing over this VIX
can get all the way up to 1666es.
Check
that newsp.
[sighs]
Yeah. Core PCE in line. Year-over-year
pretty much in line.
Price index year-over-year in line.
Consumer spending in line.
Yeah, no outliers.
Come on, just come down and do it for
[\h__\h] sake. Because if you leave it
open, there's nothing we can do with
you.
They're reselling. There's a guy chasing
this down now with 100 lot. He's trying
to chase it down lower now. They should
get this move down into here now at this
point.
I'm absolutely kicking myself for not
selling those 650s. I still haven't let
go of it in my head.
It might be a no trade day. If I can't
let go of that in my head, I'm going to
struggle to move on.
VIX starting to get through that gap
now. So, VIX has got a chance to get up
to 1660 now. It's got a chance. Gray box
still absolutely key as you're under
over.
Target is below. There's clear targets
below. There's clear low hanging proofs
below.
Very upset at myself not doing that.
A little bit of front running ES into
fiveday here.
So ES doing a 5day 20-day rotation. It's
never a nice thing to see. [snorts]
SPY doing the same. QQ possibly about to
do the same. Vick still going.
Gray box still key. Gray box still your
under. All right. Gray box is still
absolutely vital.
If you're still short, these are your
cover points, right? TP, TP, and TP. All
right, longs. You don't want to be short
if we start basing over here. All right,
because that is where you have squeeze
potential. If we get over the gray box,
that is where you have squeeze
potential. So, shorts must keep
protecting this, this, this, and this.
for runners. If uh I would expect cover
points to happen in here and here, but
if we find acceptance under here, we can
really get nasty.
What was the news? It was PCE. We went
over it all and just gave you all the
reads. They all came in in line.
Okay, back to gray box again.
Back to flow zones. Back to gray box.
Still got things below to aim for. We're
still adding liquidity lower for it to
aim for.
>> [sighs]
>> Gray box still rejecting so far.
Squeeze relief will come over that gray
box, not before it.
Still rejecting it. Still buyers just
got caught into that gray box so far.
>> [snorts]
>> Still targets are below. It's still not
taking our previous day value area high.
I want to make sure that lines up.
Yeah.
So, I'd say your cover points are 420,
sorry, 420, 520, all the way down to
430. There's 100 points of cover in
here. If they really want to flush it
down into here, they can. But this is
like you must be covering into this. I
would expect if buyers are going to turn
up, they're going to turn up somewhere
in this region. All right? just based on
higher time frame
in a strong sell here so far.
Oh, Alex, what a fade that would have
been from here. All you have to do is
[\h__\h] sell 50s. Ah, [laughter]
cannot let it go. I cannot let it go. I
don't know why. I just cannot let it go.
It's bugging me. Really bugging me.
Big seller just came in at 55.
Here we go. So, starting to flush
further down now
into the 40s. Can we get down into the
20s, which is where they're trying to
get
40 bit just left and then came back on.
Should come down to 20's here. I don't
know what this guy thought he's doing
playing games.
Yeah, exactly. It was the perfect shot.
That's why I talked about it pre-market
was absolutely perfect. That's why I'm
really upset with myself for not taking
it. I spoke about it even when it was
happening. I just didn't
It's just bad trading. It's just as
simple as that. It's bad trading,
but it's all right. It's
There'll be another setup. All right,
back to gray box. Remember, squeeze
relief will come over the gray box until
that point. Sellers are in control.
Big buyers last got stuck at uh 579.25
somewhere around that. So, just call it
580. Buyers need it back above 580.
[snorts]
They're stuck all the time. It's under
that.
You should sweep London. Well, maybe
possible.
Yeah, I know guys. I know what's
happened. You you got what you have to
understand is it's all very well what
you're all saying and and you're not
wrong any of you, but this is the third
day in a row I've missed 100 plus
pointer. yesterday missed like 200 plus
pointer that delta starts to build. It
doesn't matter what you say or what
books say. I can tell you my data says
that when that happens there's very
strong chance I start making big errors.
So I have to like be very very very
careful for the rest of the week. Now I
said it yesterday when it happened.
So I'm just aware of my own flaws. These
are my flaws. Right? These are big tilt
triggers for me is missing stuff. Being
right and missing stuff. That's three
days in a row. 100 plus points without
me. All right, coming to test these 80s
again.
Gray box again. Right, this gray box is
key. Current value area low on the day
shelf there and buyers stuck at 80s. So
over 80s there's a squeeze until that
point like I keep talking about gray box
will be defended by sellers again. It's
being defended.
point of control now starting to flip
down here. By the way, folks, be aware
of that. Hasn't shown you here yet, but
it will probably flip in a minute. On
Ninja, it's already flipped.
>> [snorts]
>> I'm willing to bid on this market if we
trap sellers down here.
I'm willing to bid on this market if we
trap sellers down here. Something like
this. willing to bid on. If we lose this
and lose this, I'm definitely not
willing to bid on it because that
actually opens up this move.
[snorts]
A bit like yesterday, it's going to
require an insane amount of patience
from me now. And I'm not convinced I'm
going to trade it. If if I'm still
feeling like this, I won't trade it. If
I can shake this feeling off, I'll trade
it.
But I'll be here for you and tell you
what I'm looking at either way.
There you go. PSC now flipped on Trading
View.
Okay, I'll get a refill on my tea while
it does this. Hopefully, it doesn't just
squeeze without me straight away.
Hi
What's what feeling, Scott? Sorry, mate.
I might have missed.
And what was that feeling again?
Oh, what I feel inside like like a form
of anger for myself, a form of
frustration,
um
like any of those sort of low frequency
feelings which are all basically
feelings of pain, anything like that, if
I'm feeling any of those, whether it's
to do with trading or not, I have to be
really careful.
Okay. So, coming to test these 80s we
just talked about. It's where the buyer
is stuck.
and rejecting it again.
So the buyer [snorts] remains stuck
there. He's actually at 7975
is like the exact tick 32 I have on it.
So he's still stuck there and he just
became a seller.
Oh, shaking a feeling. Yeah, shaking
that feeling of like uh frustration or
um any any kind of like anything which
doesn't make me feel like I'm
comfortable or in flow on a trade.
10:00 news numbers are in. Yeah, that
they were in 15 minutes ago. We've
already talked about them. Lots of you
keep asking what was the news. We've
already talked about it. I don't
understand why you're asking at 7:15.
Way too late, folks. Way too late. The
news came in in line. It was core PCE.
It all came in in line, right? It's had
no effect on the market. Market's
selling off because we came into a
supply level and we rejected previous
day value. All right. So, we rejected
this node.
I wasn't sure if we were going to
reclaim this and squeeze. And I said the
moment we lose 50, we need to be talking
thinking about the short. We lost 50 and
that was the opportunity and I missed
it. That is my trading today. I'm being
honest with you. I will go back and
chalk it off and watch the stream. All
right. back towards these 80s again.
Squeeze will happen over 80s, not before
that. If they're going to get this
going, it's going to have to break
through 80s and start holding it. So,
here's the 80s. It's got it's got to now
hold above this. Can't just fade back
inside. Nothing will change if it fades
back inside.
[snorts]
I've been on tilt light behavior since
fifth grade.
>> [laughter]
>> I feel you, buddy.
Okay, still not through the 80s. Still
rejecting up there. All right, we just
put in a wick and rejected. We need to
get back above this and base if they're
going to curl it, which they're now
trying to do. Okay, let's see. See if
they go back for these 600s and VWAP.
And I'd be watching SPY
over 8850s. Really
still in this gray box. We poked above
it. We're still in the gray box. Still
can't get a close above it.
So buyers will now want to bend 63s.
We can't do that. This is just going to
be a little trap above here.
Can feel the frustration in me today. Be
a trap above here. If they get under
here, this will fade. Right. Buyers need
to do this.
Not seeing it. There you go. So, a
little trap. If they get under here,
they're probably going to try and
rotate. This is very key.
>> [snorts]
>> It's adjusted since I drew it, but it's
here is where the buyer is stuck. That's
why we put the gray box in. It's not
just the node. It's where the buyer is
stuck. I can see him stuck right uh
here. See this?
This guy right here, this is where he
got stuck. Right,
it's important to understand where
players are stuck in the market and give
you edge.
Right. So, we just lost it. That's the
trap we just talked about. We're back
underneath. If they don't hold this,
then I would imagine a flush all the way
down now. Just done all the damage of
trapping all those buyers who didn't
wait. [snorts]
Starting to look pretty messy down here,
I'll tell you that.
Balance
now is up to 66s. Do they resell this
now?
66es. I'm going to look see how we act
at 66. Is that imbalance in the edge of
the great box again? Straight through 66
is this is where the buyer last got
trapped.
There is a seller here. I'm unconvinced
right now.
I'm more interested in playing longs if
it can prove to myself just because of
the area we're in.
Can I explain the trap? Yeah. Well, if
we have this shelf here,
right, and we know there's a buyer stuck
there and buyers start buying this
breakout here, not waiting for us to do
this, then you have more buying volume
there that sellers, passive sellers sell
into and rotate under. So, if they're
able to hold under here, they now
increase the amount of buy volume here
stuck, which means if they break lower,
there's even more buyers now stuck for
us to move down from. Did we just wick
underneath there? Who's bidding down
here? Double bomb. I don't like that.
We should do this. Really? It's what it
should do. Should do this. I'll be
willing to buy if we can do this.
Ideally, it does this at this point.
70s.
gray box again.
So I can take the big outlying delta is
65s and 80. That's where the buyers
their outlying delta is 65s and 80.
So if we're not above that, they're
stuck, right? If we're above that,
they're comfortable. ES is trying to
curl spy off its 5day moving average.
Probably going to want to test the
20-day if we can get going. All right,
let's see. I don't like the bottom of
this auction, I'm going to be honest.
But I will be willing to play this if
we're going to start to squeeze and base
above
back into these 79s and 80s. Are we
going to base above here? This is the
where they got stuck last time. So
looking to see if we can hold now.
Going to be very careful with ES
approaching VW.
I want to see a pullback hold. really
much more comfortable if we can have a
pullback that holds rather than just
coming in for these wicks
in balance now.
Want to see this buyer step up now and
squeeze.
Come on, mate. Lift it 600. Let's see.
Yes. It's not even getting to be what?
Come on.
Nice. There we go. Lovely.
I'm going to trim some into this
imbalance at 600 just to be careful
and then see if we can get up into here
and then see if we can rotate.
Scalping my way through this because
we're early. We don't know. I don't like
the bottom of the auction. I'm not
convinced the bottom is in yet. So, I'm
just scalping this up, paying myself on
the way. If it goes, it goes and we're
happy. But if it doesn't, and it needs
to come and clean out this, then I
understand because this bottom of the
auction does not look very good.
I'm not sure. I'm not convinced we're
done selling yet. But I'm putting this
long scalping some out into 600. And if
we can lift back into 15s and 20s,
great. But
see,
start there at 600 again. 80s the level
now. They've got to hold the dip. If
they don't hold the dip in 80s, I'll
probably get out of this. Got to flip
this gray box into some support
structure at 80s. If they don't hold
80s, I'll probably cut and then I'll
look to see how we act at 65. So far,
holding 80s nicely.
Okay, come on then. Let's go. Thank [\h__\h]
for that.
Let's go then.
Oh my god.
All right. See if we get acceptance
through this. It's very possible they
reject this here, folks. I just want to
make that very, very clear. You must pay
yourself on the way.
>> [snorts]
>> Nice into the orbit. This where the big
seller came in this morning into these
tens
through 10. We've got VWAP at 23s, but
we can probably lift towards 40s if we
can get through the tens.
Right.
ES into V up like we talked about
rejecting there for now.
Spy into that pre-market low pivot.
Rejecting that as well. be very careful.
I would trim a big chunk of your
position here. If they want to sell this
on the higher time frame, they will. All
right. So, if we look at spiders
Oh, wrong chart. Right here. There we
go. So, this is what I was just saying.
Make sure you're selling into this.
No.
All right. There's your pre-market
pivot. Right. Just selling into it. And
if we go to ES
into view up and selling. All right, I'm
out of this now, by the way, folks.
Obviously, I'm not going to sit through
this.
Like I said, I don't like the bottom of
this auction. It's very possible they
come and clean this up. There's not
enough excess down there in my mind.
And they might have just used this to
resell. So, we hit VW up and then got
the sell. So, no confirmation through
the tens. Remember I said through 10.
It's got a base above 10 to get it
going. No confirmation through the tens.
And we can probably clean up the low of
day here
because there's not a good auction at
that low of day right now. It's uh
there's not enough excess. Remember
yesterday we were talked about excess.
So same kind of thing here. Sellers will
want to now defend 65 and create a new
low on the day and flush down towards
516s.
cannot imagine buyers just being able to
hold these lows. I mean, it's possible,
but it would be a very ugly uh low of
date auction. I would imagine this gets
resold on on the push up towards uh 65s.
We will see. It's been a wishy-washy uh
market the last few days. Here's the
push up to towards that level.
point of control here.
There's the push to 65s.
They're going to break this higher. Nah,
surely not. Surely you clean up low of
day.
Surely you clean up low of day, NQ. That
is disgusting. If you're going to knock
me out and run higher, that is really
horrible. I'm sure you're going to clean
up low of day. You can't leave it like
that. It's gross.
Fix
fix is fading now as well at 16. This is
uh actually really horrible action at
the lows. I'm going to tell you that
that auction at the low is gross. I know
there's a shelf, but there's no excess.
This is horrible to This is just like
yesterday at the high when it knocked me
out.
Mother,
there's no excess down here.
Get rid of this now. I traded through it
too many times.
Really?
I'm guessing 618's a massive gamut level
on QQQ.
I'm guessing that is a huge gamma level
today. Fact that they've done just done
what they've done.
I do not feel comfortable now.
Yes, back to that pre-market level
again. I do not feel comfortable longing
QQQ now knowing that it just came down
and didn't sweep all that liquidity. Um,
and I feel like it's probably going to
just piss me off and just rocket now.
So I was positioned long here. Took some
off out of it. Doesn't sweep. So I'm
waiting for the sweep now to get back
long. Doesn't sweep. Creates more stops
down here. Driving back upside right
now. It is possible they come and
revisit this. But uh like I talked about
this spy level is key and it's starting
to try and get through it here. So be
watching this. So is it previous day
high or previous week high on spy?
Previous day high on spy. Watch this
level into 88s. We trade through that.
We probably get going here on the
market. I can't believe it. Knocked me
out, didn't sweep, and then went
straight back up.
It is yesterday all over again, but
reversed.
Do I have another go at this is the
question.
Do I have another stab?
ression down here now.
[snorts]
Yes, VWOP spy trying to get VW up and 20
day and previous day high
615 is gam on QQQ is it I mean that
makes sense but just how we've reacted
5 10 15 20 25 30 35 for 40 minutes at
618 on QQQ
it's not like there's a giant pivot it
there. There's not there's not much
there.
It's like the after hours close and
that's it.
What are these guys doing? What are they
doing?
What are they doing? ES can't get
through. Oh, yeah. ES can't get through
it. Speed up.
That dip just got bought up again in
front of the uh the 80s or at the 80s
but in front of the 65s. This might go
now. They might have caught enough in
that last move.
They're trying to bid it up. They need
the 600 break and then we got 630 on
deck. Probably
there's 600.
They break this, they'll squeeze up and
look for sort of 630, 625, 630, 644.
It's very ugly.
I do not like the lower day. It's the
one thing that's making me very
uncomfortable about thinking about the
long right now.
Back down to these 80s again
and the shelf down at 65.
If we'd put in a new low of day and had
excess, I'd be thinking about a long
here.
If we'd done that, I would be thinking
about a long here. That's where my
head's at right now. But we haven't. And
so, it's kind of making me question why
we're doing this dance.
SPY cannot get through that pre-market
either.
Very unconvinced right now of this
market.
It might need to trade sideways for a
bit longer until it makes a decision.
Trapping more balls possibly to take out
lower date. I mean, it's possible, but
uh it's possible the other way around as
well.
Don't have much edge here.
All I know is we're holding value area
low, but we haven't come and taken these
lowhanging fruits. There is not much
excess there, and we're getting stuck
here time and time again. So, this is
just it keeps just rotating this until
it's ready.
That's all I know.
But we are now starting to protect 80
and definitely not not letting it under
65s.
Both sides now stacked on the big ass.
It's gone to sleep. Something's going to
give soon. We can't stay here forever.
Something will absolutely give soon.
Cannot just sit like this forever. There
you go. There's the thing giving.
So tens again. Remember 10 is the orb.
If we go back inside the orb,
we're looking for VWOP and then above.
There we go. Back inside the orb. Now
looking for VWOP and above. There's VWAP
and value area high would be 630s if
we're going to test that. We've actually
got a node at 40s which I'm looking at.
And sellers came in at 39 earlier today.
So relief up here. Can we trade through
VWAP and now get going? It's very
upsetting for me. I would have sized
into this if the low of day had a better
auction on it. Buyers getting a little
bit caught here at 20s. Be careful if
you're long in this.
There we go. There's 20s. Let's see if
they can lift now to 30s into these
nodes here. And then if we get very
lucky, we get up to 76s.
Tiny size in this cuz I don't trust it.
is 30s value area high on the day
through this node. Right. Next thing
that we're aiming for is all the way up
here into 73s.
Man, why couldn't they have just done a
better auction at the lows?
I would pay yourself here because we've
just swept all this liquidity here,
right? And we come into value high on
the day. If they want to go into a
rotation, if they want to go into
rotation, they can just pin us in here.
Oh, I'm so upset. I'm so upset.
So, rejection of value so far, but we're
now finding that bullish momentum
into the weekly gap. Obviously, this
gray box is a big weekly gap. Sellers
got stuck under here. All right. Mo most
of the selling happened under 62
certainly under 50 under here but what I
would have liked to have seen what would
have made this like a a B setup let's
say rather than a C setup well it would
have been this here all right complete
low hanging fruit clean this out reclaim
let shorts chase in and then go upside
unfortunately we haven't got that but it
just is what it is we can only trade
with what we've
And we are getting very close to these
pivots up here now as well. All right.
So these sort of pivots 660 650. All
right. Let me put a little line
in here. We want to be careful with this
here where we broke down from this
morning. Right where I should have short
from this morning.
Want to be very careful of that pivot as
we get into it.
of Japan news to tomorrow night. Is it
tomorrow night or tonight?
I can't remember. Let me have a look.
Oh, it's uh CPI, Japanese CPI tonight.
Bank of Japan tonight.
And the decision tonight.
It's tonight, mate. Jan 22nd. Yeah, it's
tonight, not tomorrow.
I guess it's tonight, but it's on
tomorrow's uh candle. I guess that's
what you mean.
might need to build some liquidity here
if we are to expand back upside just
based on those pre-market levels.
We read out on the mag. Tesla 0.88% up.
Nvidia 0.91% up. Microsoft 0.61% up.
Meta 3.97% up. Google 0.85% up. Amazon
0.91% up. Apple 0.84% up. Retesting this
value area high again. Now the 630s.
Like I said, if we get through here,
there is room. There's a 640 where the
big sellers came in. 640 650 was the
pivot, right? 640 650 was the pivot.
They are trying. They are trying. Here
comes the move for 640 to test where
that seller was.
Yeah, I did participate, but I'm small
size.
I'm I've just been small size on that
move up.
640 is coming up here is where that
seller was. And remember 50s is the
pivot from here.
And if we think about this move today,
we've also got to think about the fib on
it.
I don't like that top flat top and flat
bottoms. Those are not nice into 50%
here. So you want to be paying yourself.
We got a flat top and a flat bottom on
this market in the New York session.
Okay. What we have to be aware of is
this here
and this here. And I don't like this. So
I still think this is possible. But if
they are just going to leave this for
whatever reason, this is the next move.
And then over here would be this. and we
would need to respect previous week
value area low which we could not get
back inside yet. So this is saying that
they don't want to go back into the old
balance right now. This old balance that
we left which we've traded away from.
They don't want to get back inside it
yet.
So first attempt this morning was
rejected. That's first attempt on the
week.
hanging around BW right now. Market
feels very sleepy at this point.
Another node here.
40s is still the level where those
sellers were. It's where they're trying
to test to see if that seller is going
to be there.
1450 if they lift
and then previous day high 53s.
It's trying. It is trying. Here we go.
Here's the 40s test. This is where the
seller came in this morning
here to 50. They're lifting. So they can
they push 40 to 50 now. offering 60s now
as well. Imbalance here up into 61s
from 9:43 this morning.
Here we go.
Make sure you're selling your profits on
the way. I'm out of this at this point.
question is, do they put in a giant
squeeze or do they start reselling this
to attack those lows where I don't like
the edge of that auction? I do not know.
I do not know right now.
VIX still trading back down, trading to
its lower day. It's got like another
We're trading at 1578. It needs to trade
down to 1570. So very close.
So 50 is coming up here. Previous day
high coming up here.
Oh my god.
Bullish momentum coming back in. Looking
for this pivot into 16 to see how we
now.
Where did I execute? I was actually a
bit later. Execute here.
These moves here. So, I was long
this
paid myself, stopped out, reflushed, was
hoping it'd do this for me to get long
cheap again on a failed auction. It
didn't. It held. It did all this
nonsense, so I had to join a bit later
and I've paid myself into this. I'm a
fully out of it. This will be your
target. If we get through this, maybe
it's messy though.
Just depends if they put the boosters on
like yesterday or not, you know.
I make some toast here. I'm hungry. I'll
be right back.
All
>> [snorts]
>> right, boosters are on. It's getting
frothy and extended
into this next node. 70s possible
fix near that lower day.
Yeah, exactly. It is approaching that
golden pocket and previous day high and
lower time frame. Algo, lots of reasons
for you to take profit into these moves.
Do not want to hold past these moves.
Not with size anyway.
And just rebid this little box here
though again.
Just rebid that box.
They are now chasing this market up.
What I would say this up here is also
very ugly, right? There's no big excess.
They can come and clean that up the same
way they should have cleaned this and
they didn't.
I would not be surprised to see it trade
through that today. I wouldn't I would
not be surprised at all to see them
trade through that today. My toast just
popped up. Be right back.
Is it me or does today feel like really
slow? It feels so slow to me.
Still holding this node. If they let go
of gray, then maybe there's a move down
to VW. But otherwise, they can keep
squeezing this up.
They absolutely can keep squeezing this
up. If they keep holding, they can
squeeze him. If they let go of this,
there's a move down to 20s. Big if
low day
low of day.
There's the 40 check. They let go of
this. There's a bigger move
maybe down to VW up for that pullback.
It's possible.
Here we come.
Come on, baby. I've been really good,
boy.
Let's go.
Finally got me some today.
Let's go. Paid myself on that. Back into
New York VWAP.
Beautiful.
That [clears throat] might be me done
for the day.
That was aggressive there. As soon as we
broke that, I was like, "Yep, I'm having
you. Thanks very much." into that.
Really nice.
Really nice,
man. You keep asking the same questions.
Let me explain something to you. If I
say if we let go of 40, we're going to
trade down to VWAP. Where do you think
I'm entering?
Where do you think I'm entering? If we
let go of this, we're going to trade
down to this. Where do you think I'm
entering?
Obviously at the level that we're
letting go of, right? Not entering above
that level. Maybe it's your first day
here, but
I will not guess bottoms on markets. I
will let volume prove to me that
participants are stuck. I will let
volume
prove to me that participants are stuck.
And then I will trade down to the next
level. All right. If they want to tag
this all the way down here and clean
this up, they can. The same way they can
clean this up. This is not a very nice
looking market right now. It needs
cleaning up both sides in my opinion.
I will scout my way through this. What
was the confluence there? Value area
high on the session. No acceptance
above. Where did we say sellers came in
this morning? 50s, right? Where have we
just got buyers stuck into 50s. What did
we leave? 40s. What did we trade down
to? Tens. Thanks very much. Job done.
What was the level we talked about on
the upside? Tens. This guy here. Same
level.
Tens. Tens. Tens. Break. Hold. Break.
Hold. Under this weakness.
I do use hotkeys. Yeah,
I have a crosshair keyboard
specifically, so I can use hotkeys.
Thanks to Coupe, he got me onto that.
Also, PD Yeah, PDH retest, lower time
frame algo retest. Look, look at
everything here, guys.
We went over this.
We literally drew this out like 10
minutes ago, right? 50%
golden pocket 61
50s big level that they sold from PDH
lower time frame algo big big level
buyers get stuck leave shelf play back
inside
value error high right
doesn't mean it can't go higher but this
trade here
made sense
this can make sense
this doesn't make sense.
This is a battleground now.
Crossair, not hair. Cross air. No H.
No H.
Okay, not a terrible day now.
I don't feel as bad. Starting to make a
bit of money back.
Feel like I missed huge shreds today.
Tesa just exploded.
Wow.
It did. That's a big move on the 5m
minute
35 almost to $45 move through previous
day high. It's got a base above that
though. If you're trading Tesla, you
need it to base above 3819s, 3820s.
Can't base above that. There's no follow
through. Base above that, then you're
looking to take out the stops in 41s.
>> [snorts]
>> Do I compare M1 with other time frames?
Yeah, M1 doesn't do the work for me. H1
really does the work for me. H1 and
daily.
That's why I keep bringing you down to
here to make you understand where we're
at.
Right? This is the big level.
We had to wait to see this morning if we
found acceptance in it. We didn't. Once
we didn't, we should have got short at
50s for the rejection of that level.
Didn't get short of 50s. Very annoying.
Very stupid. Alex, idiot. Right, since
then, what have we done? We traded away
from it. We haven't actually hit our
target down here, which is a bit
annoying. This blue box, this demand
zone, which was previous days value area
high, previous days point of control.
That's an area where I'm very interested
in bidding off, right, for a rotation
back to here.
If we find acceptance, we get a runner
to go. We didn't get that. We also
didn't get the fade. The fade would have
been a let go of this a retest
uh sorry, a let go of previous days
value area high and point of control and
a rejection back down all the way to
here. We didn't get that either. All
we're actually getting, if I'm honest
with you, is a liquidity build between
previous days value, previous week's
value area low, previous [clears throat]
days value area high. They are building
liquidity in here, right? Maybe tomorrow
we use that liquidity, maybe this
afternoon, but we are definitely
building liquidity in here right now.
Shorts can come into effect if we start
to rotate back inside
uh here. And longs can come to into
effect, I'm talking about higher time
frame if we're going to keep holding and
definitely if we're going to hold this
level here or this naked point of
control, this rotation up.
Right now, we're making up our mind what
we're going to do.
If we zoom out, all we're doing is we're
thinking about this box,
right? Actually dates back further even
onto the old contract.
Think about all the supply. Are we going
to aggressively leave it like we did
here, right? Is this a retest to leave
it again or is this a failure of value
lower? So, we're going to search for
value higher, which will be where? Well,
it would be where we found value for the
last four or five weeks up in here. And
then what would not surprise me
is if we do this.
Okay. And then we go, hey,
tech earnings are mega. Let's rotate
back into tech. Boom. Or, hey, AI
bubble's a real thing. Like earnings not
so good. Boom. All right. I would not be
surprised to see us back in that death
range again.
[snorts]
But trading NQ minis on H1 won't work
for me. My accounts won't be able to
handle that. You don't trade them. Uh
try to make sense of this for you. You
need to create a story line. All right?
So if you come to the market with me
each day at 9:15 market time, what do I
do? Start on the daily. I think about
what my narrative is in on the daily.
Then I move to an hourly. I look at
value. I create a story line. Are we
leaving value? Are we searching for
value? Do we have trapped sellers? Do we
have trapped buyers? Are they above us?
Are they below us? I create a story out
of that. Then we look at the five
minute. What have we done overnight?
Who's in control of the market? Where
are they stuck? Then we move down into
the M1 or you can stay on M5, whatever
is comfortable with you. And you trade
your story line. Today the story line
had to be willing to flip. We talked
about it like I'm bullish if we hold
previous week's value for a rotation
back upside to the naked point of
control. If we lose value and we lose
650, I should be bearish for the move
back down to previous day value area
high. Obviously, I didn't take that.
Hopefully, lots of you guys did.
You don't need to trade the H1, but it
will help you create the narrative.
By the way, last week I subscribe to
your newsletter very clean and clear
with actual info unlike others I would
subscribe to. Thanks for your efforts
specifically right now, Alex. Thank you
very much, man. I'm glad they helped. I
think they've come in pretty pretty
clutch. Um,
what did I put in the newsletter last
week?
What were the levels I gave? Let's have
a look.
It's completely free. The link's down
below. So, if you're not signed up, you
should.
So, what did I say?
Bearish scenarios. As long as 25,900
continues to act heavy, bears
have scope for follow through. Sustained
downside pressure below 25700
opens a door for a rotation to 25 580 to
25500.
A break in continued acceptance below
that will put 25350 back in play. The
old naked point of control, which has
only been defended once this year,
should earnings disappoint, the rotation
out of tech persists. Failure under
will open the door to 25,000. Okay. So
let's see what we got
opened up this week. Shorter trading
week. Remember we had to defend 9700 900
700. We open up underneath it. Okay.
Underneath it. Underneath those levels.
What did I say? I was looking at
580 to 500 zone to be defended. Okay. We
can't reclaim it on Tuesday's push right
here or Sunday. Is it Sunday's push?
Sunday's push. We can't reclaim it and
we can't reclaim it on Monday.
Then we said
350 old naked point of control 350 right
here. Right this zone here. If we fail
350, rotation will start to take place
for 150 to 25,000. So we fail 350 and we
trade to under 150 and then 25,000. So
we see every bearish sector happen early
in the week. Right? We've hit all the
targets by Wednesday
completely free. Won't cost you a thing.
Right mark the reason I'm doing all this
now is the market's just gone to sleep
because it's just it's tagged its level
and we're now building liquidity in here
again. right where our cover points
were. We're now building liquidity.
Yeah.
[cough]
First question you should ask, which
direction are we trying to go and how
good of a job we're doing to get there?
Yeah. Well, I I reframe that. I would
say I ask what's the momentum, what's
the location? Same thing, I guess.
Past two emails today. Nice. Andrew,
how do you subscribe to the newsletter?
Um,
it should be Nightbot will post it in a
minute if it hasn't already.
If not, just go into the information
underneath and it will be there.
It's crazy. I've underperformed every
day this week
and I definitely have money dysmorphia
massively
and I've taken payouts.
consistently from take profit and I put
I haven't take traded my take profit
account today or accounts
because I don't think they've approved
the latest one either.
Waiting for that to go through.
I requested this month, January. 1,000
2,000 3,000 4,000 5,000 6,000. Why isn't
it not put in my payout request from
last night?
Surely that should be pending.
Oh, it is 6,600 from TPT this month.
Love it. They're so good, man.
So good.
Are the boxes on your chart generated by
your indicator or do I draw them? I draw
them.
Since we dipped under 15 minute orb. Oh,
sorry. I need to read up. We're having
hovering around bottom 50-minute opening
range. Both spy and KQ. Market needs to
decide where to go, but I'm leaning
bearish since we dipped under the
15-minute orb. I mean,
you're holding the orb for me.
That's your orb,
right? We've rejected, but we we can
just rotate this all day. What I don't
like is it's both sides need cleaning
up. So, it's not like we've done this
and it's like, okay, our bias is upside.
We need to clean this up. It can like
both sides need cleaning up. It's it's
nasty.
It's pretty nasty.
>> [cough]
[snorts]
>> Can I be successful without book map?
Um,
I mean, I can be, but I don't know why
I'd want to take my edge away.
Find a lot of uh edge from bookmint
certainly like I need at least one of
those. I wouldn't want to be trading
without bookmap or footprint. I do need
at least one of those. But I could
probably make do without one of them for
sure. But they just give me so much
edge.
So much edge in the market that you
won't get elsewhere. You can't see where
the buyers and sellers are stuck to the
tick without some form of data like
that. You're not going to see it in
candles. But I mean, you you don't need
to start off that way. I think the first
thing you need to learn when you come
into the market is understand structure,
understand higher time frame narrative,
understand how we move, understand the
waves, why we move, understand how
liquidity is built, understand market
conditions, all these things, right? Get
used to understanding
even like basic EMA principles like when
we're trading down and hugging them like
this is like when I get annoyed myself.
We go into a cell, we reject flow zones
once, twice, three times, four times.
Like all I had to do was sell that.
We're now hugging it back the other way.
We're buying, buying, buying, buying.
All the time we're holding this. We're
buying. We let go of this. It probably
goes into a sell again.
So, I would learn basic principles
first, which is why I say do the 20our
course. Well, do everything for free on
my YouTube first or someone else's, but
do the 20our course first because you'll
learn, you'll get the,
you know, you'll learn more than most
people will ever learn and you'll have a
good understanding of how the market
moves. Then look at order flow once you
understand all that.
Le, yeah, I feel you, mate. I've been
the same. I've had so many break even
trades. So many like you can you can
laugh. I don't know how many of you were
here yesterday. Um
like my students traded it better than
me.
[laughter]
I left and made toast like today and
then came back and we'd already started
the move and I don't chase.
So where is it?
Just looking on Discord.
There we go. It's very simple.
There's my students. There's Ben in
yesterday. Waiting for supply. Wait for
us to leave the volume. Saw it leave.
Had the point control. Shorted all the
way down. 100 plus point banger. Right.
It's what we were calling on stream all
of yesterday for.
So I've been the same as you this week.
What? Let's look at the horrific trades
Alex has missed this week which he's
been there for. Right. Nailed this long
yesterday. Beautiful. I was in short
three times. I had a go at this
yesterday for this short and this short
and this short and it whipped me out to
the tick and then look the moment Alex
goes I'm just going to make some toast
and the market was toast. Boom. There it
is all the way back downside. Right. So,
you're not the only one. There's a
reason I feel tilty today. It's because
that happened yesterday and the day
before I missed a very similar setup for
the same thing. I got nudged out three
times. So, we had to go from
It was probably under IB, I would
imagine. There's the three drives.
I can't remember. I think it was like
one, two, three, and then I was like,
I'm out of bullets. And then guess what?
These are trades that can make your
month, right? These are trades that can
make your month or your year. You catch
200 points and you size into it. It's,
you know, it gets you ahead real quick.
Expensive bit of toast. Yes. Very, very
expensive bit of toast. Can I send a
link to the Discord? Uh, Discord is only
for people who've done the 20our course.
So if you want to, there's no pressure,
but if you want to look at that,
you come over to the website.
You want to do this trading course here,
20 hour, [snorts] and it comes free with
Discord. No monthly fees, right?
It's 649. It's going up to 699 probably
this weekend. I should have done it
already, but I just haven't had time.
It's going up 50 bucks. [snorts]
That's great though, Daryl. There you
go. I don't use bitmap or footprints. I
only use market structure, market
profile, and volume profile. I've had
three consistent months green screen
shorted two x in the last 25 minutes for
some single print. There you go. Well,
that's also fantastic, mate. You found
what works for you.
You found what works for you. Can I put
the link in chat? Um,
it's it's pinned to the top of chat. If
you just scroll to the top of chat, it's
pinned there right now. Click on that.
You know what? I'll just put it here for
you.
There you go.
What's the red box at 660? It's just
it's a low volume node, but it's the
area at which big sellers came in early.
Um, we will probably trade through that
now if we trade up there because we've
already been up there. Um,
yeah, 660 to
here,
right? This block here is where we
traded aggressively away from them. The
buyers got stuck at the highs. Buyers
are stuck at 89 and above. We can
actually call it 84 and above. So, this
block trades up to 70 is where the
sellers came in this morning. You can
see if they reoffer there. If they don't
reoffer there, we probably come up and
test 88 all the way up to 700. Right.
Yes. coming into its New York Open.
Alex, if you chose between footprint and
bookm bookmark, which is your
preference? Um,
man, that's a really hard question. I
love having a visualization delta
profile on the right of my screen. I
think it's very, very useful rather than
having to watch it on the DOM.
But I think seeing aggressive order flow
step in is very easy to see on bookmap.
So horses for courses pro probably
probably
footprint
probably footprint.
I don't do a very good Michael Kane. So,
Michael Kane,
I'm not I'm not good at that.
Okay, ES coming back up to its 20-day.
So, it's bottomed out at the 5day,
trading up to its 20-day, which is
exactly the same print as the New York
Open.
Horses for courses. Yeah, you never
heard that. Maybe that's an English
saying
comes from uh obviously stallion horses
going racing. Some are good at jumping.
Some are good at longer distance. Some
are good in the wet. Depends on the
turf. Horses for courses.
It's trying to break out here. It's
trying to get up to its New York open.
Big level that New York open. To each
their own. Yeah, it's the same thing.
Exactly. To each their own. Exactly the
same thing.
Fix low of day, by the way, folks. Fix
low of day.
This is also the pre-market, is it?
Yeah, it's also a pre-market pivot right
here. This red box,
it's why the sellers came in there
because we broke down. So, anyone who is
a buyer became a seller here.
This is their chance to get out, break
even as we tag into it.
Uh, I don't trade uh gold, so
I wouldn't want to give you an opinion
on it. I haven't sat and watched its uh
personality too much.
I think they're all looking for higher.
Silver wants the 100.
It wants the 100. There you go. So, into
this pre this pre-market pivot low
volume node where these sellers got
stuck all the way up to sort of 6870
here is where the sellers got stuck. And
if we're starting to get through that,
you got previous week close up at 90 and
that's where buyers got stuck this
morning. Previous week close up here.
Right here, gray box at 90 and this is
where buyers got stuck here and above
this morning.
I do not like these highs. I would not
be surprised if we trade through those
highs today. Really would not surprise
me.
Feels slower today, doesn't it? Is it
just me?
Feels slower today. How big is this
range? Like 100
120. Yeah, it feels a bit slower. Not a
bad thing.
So, yes, banging into that 20-day New
York open. Can't get through it. Can't
get through it yet.
Well, yeah, maybe that's right, Joe.
[laughter]
I think you you're probably actually
right there, Joe. That's probably
exactly what it is. Last few days have
been absolutely insane, so today feels
slower.
All right.
How are we doing
with the likes?
Have a look.
So, getting stuck there again. So,
they're refreshing that ES getting stuck
at the New York Open.
>> [cough]
>> 644 of you watching,
331 likes. At least half of you have not
smashed that like button. So, just smash
the like button, folks, and then we can
do some giveaways. It's really simple.
Let's get it up to 450 plus. Smash that
like button and then we're going to do
some giveaways on stream. Give you guys
some accounts.
What do I think it's going to do? Well,
it really depends if we can find
acceptance above this. If we're willing
to find acceptance here, then I think
it's got a shot of doing this and coming
back inside there. And then it might
very well have a force breakout inside
that. If we keep getting stuck here, all
right, we're going to have to pay
attention to a rotation. If it does a
false break and a rotation down to here
under this, you'll probably see
weakness. But, you know, I'd be somewhat
careful. This is a scalpy day. This is
not a day to sit and hold forever at the
moment.
All I know right now is we're above
previous days value high. So, we're
shifting value up,
but we can't get above previous week's
value. So, we failed and we haven't done
a clean retest and we haven't taken this
out. So, I think we're going to do a
dance in here. That's my feeling at the
moment. We do a dance. Build liquidity.
It's a build liquidity kind of day. We
haven't taken out either side of initial
balance. Right. Both both IBS have been
left completely clean. Same on ES.
Completely clean. Both sides need
repairing in my mind because they don't
have
trap players. Enough trap players
just got here. How do you do today? Any
lowhanging fruit winners? Dean, I've
missed an absolute sitter, mate. I
missed a sitter. You're getting here
just in time. I probably just stopped
moaning about it and you're going to
make me moan about it again. I'm just
playing. Uh, we should have been short
here. So, we were waiting to see if we
found acceptance here for the long and I
said if we fail this, we need to be
thinking about short down to previous
day value. I think lots of guys got this
short. I think I took a little scalp
long here, short back in. We never hit
target annoyingly. And then I had this
attempt long from here, stopped back out
and it went again. And then I rejoined
long here and I just sold on that push.
Didn't hold long enough because I didn't
trust it. So, it's been an okay day. Um,
and then I took
this short here to here as well.
So what I took I can show you what I
took.
I was long or
just a scalp here
and then I was
along here.
And then I was long again.
Scalpy kind of day. Very small in here.
And then I was short
under 40 or this move here.
And that's all I've done.
Small trades. Not not not the biggest
trade. 40 pointer.
How big is that? Even see 21 points. 40
points. 40 points. 40 80 120 140 points
I got out today. Basically,
this this here was the was the killer
move. And this if it didn't if it
if [snorts] this was clean, we would be
in it, right? If we cleaned this up and
did this, we'd be in this sitting in
trend long to come out the other side.
If we'd cleaned this up, I'd be long to
take this out.
It is what it is.
Long to that pullback into here. Nice,
Tyson. Nice. So, 50 60 points. You might
well like like I said, if we can get
acceptance over here, where are those
buyers caught? The the buyers are up at
90s, right? So how we react there is
going to be key. But if you can get
through 90s,
get through here and get through value,
then I think we make a new high day.
Right? If we get through 90s and we get
through previous week value, we will
make a new high day in my mind.
Flow zone still holding bullish.
Okay, we need 25ish
27 more likes here, folks, and then
we'll do some giveaways on stream.
Nice, Tyson. Another big day for you.
Love it.
How do I set my anchor VP? Uh, just from
the 930.
So,
in here,
anchored volume profile, and just click
on 930. That's all I do.
Yeah, still stuck at that New York open.
Where can I get the order indicator that
is above your head? That's Bookmap
Bookmap Pro. You can get it on I think
there might be a link down below, but
you can get it.
It's a paid indicator, paid platform.
Alex, when you're looking for trapped
traders, does price have to move a
certain number of points against them
before you decide they're trapped? It's
a good question, Rob. It's more about
where they come in and volume. All
right, so
let's look at now.
Right.
If we have
volume built out,
let's say here
with a spike and lots of buyers caught
in here, and then we move under these
levels, we can use their pain to rotate
down. Right? So, it's not so much the
points, it's the amount of participants
that are trapped. So, why didn't I love
the low of day? I wonder what it would
show on here compared to Ninja. It' be
interesting.
This
is not a good auction at the lows.
Right, we have buying delta down here at
these lows. It's not what I want to see.
What I want to see at these lows is a
longer wick and this be all red, right?
I want to see this all be sellers
because then what does it mean? It means
under here if we've got, remember this
is delta. So whatever this showing is
aggressive players or market players,
people hitting the market. So if we see
aggressive sellers, but we move up, what
does it mean? It means a passive buyer,
right? A limit buyer is absorbing to
move higher. That is a good end of
auction. Then what we've seen here is
not a good end of auction. That is not a
good end of auction. And that's why I
felt very uncomfortable about holding
the long position.
We're now going to scream upside.
Remember I said where the buyers are
caught up here. They're caught right
here
around these 90s. You see these guys,
right? All these guys got caught. That's
their pain point. So if they they are
either going to get out there or we're
going to trade above and do what? Fill
this imbalance. What do we have at high
of day? Not a good auction either.
There's not many buyers caught up at
these high days, right? This is just
strong selling to open the day. Big
print selling. So, we might well come
and fill
this imbalance, right? It's a huge
sellside imbalance. There are so many
orders there, we just moved away from
it. We might well come and fill it.
Would not surprise me. So, it's not so
much about the points that we move away
from. It's more about how they're
trapped. How many are trapped? What does
it look like? What does it feel like?
How's the volume been built out when we
combine that with like this? All right,
let's say we just talked about this
level here, this node. Let's say that
these are all buyers caught and we can
see it on the footprint and we do this.
Then what we going to trade for? Well,
we can trade down here. The problem is
we're counter trend. What's really nice
is if we build out bigger and do
something like that, then that's where
we get the big moves. That's very
similar to yesterday.
Move that.
It's the same thing as yesterday.
Is this yesterday? That's Friday. Where
have I gone?
This move here yesterday.
Same thing. All right. Even Woff
spring sign of strength trap players. We
knew that there were buyers trapped
above 80s yesterday. I can remember
saying it. So, it's more about
aggressively leaving the level and
joining for that. If there's a lot of
volume built, we will often aggressively
leave without looking back. If there's
not enough volume built, you'll get a
retest. So, like here, we offered
retests, right?
Right. I would imagine if we'd done
something like this, we wouldn't retest.
We would never come back for that
because there'd be so many trapped.
They'll just be forced to cover and
cover and cover and cover and cover and
then we just keep bidding up.
Um, which is kind of probably what we
got on that news print yesterday. Okay.
So, so from here once the news comes
out, it's a rush to cover. We're never
coming back for this when there's a rush
to cover. There's no reason to. They're
all gone. Then we're not coming back to
fill that in. Not anytime soon.
All right, Tyson, you might look good
here, mate. We're coming in for this
previous week close level, the 90s.
Remember, this is the area we just
talked about and show you here. This is
where all the buyers are caught. So,
just exactly what we just talked about.
All these buyers, this is where they got
caught earlier. So if they are still
there, they will might become sellers.
If they're already out, we have the
chance to trade through it. All right.
No worries, Rob.
Recommended
funded accounts for someone who has
never had one. what
what's your trading experience and
what's your budget and then I'll tell
you because it's really depends.
I've got a video on it. If you just want
to try trading futures and get used to
them,
I would say do Apex because it's very
very cheap just for the just for the um
eval so you just can get used to trading
and understanding the market and
understanding all this. If you have like
traded experience before and you like to
set and forget and hold, then I'd look
at Lucid or Traderify
um or Funded Next.
If you like like if you're consistent,
then I'd look at TPT.
What Apex account would be good for a
first-time user of the platform? Looked
at them a lot. Chose 150K interested.
I'd say start off at 50K, even 25K.
You really don't need the big accounts.
They like they're just going to be
harder for you to pass. They just
require more size. And with the trailing
draw down, it makes it harder and
harder.
So, didn't quite make it to those 90s,
just shy of it right now. ES as well, by
the way, is at its New York open. It
peaked above it. hasn't been able to
trade through it yet. Momentum still
bullish right now.
Sellers have come in here at 66s. So,
buyers want to defend these 66es at the
moment.
Level right here. We can like kind of
flip this right now. Right. This needs
to be an important level for buyers to
bid off. If they can't bid off it, you
might see a collapse of it.
time frame I use for my footprint maybe
mainly the one minute and the five
minute. All right. Sometimes I'll I'll
peek at a 30 minute if I just want to
see like big picture especially
overnight and stuff but maybe mainly the
one minute and the five minute. Gosh, I
cannot get my words out. All right, VIX
coming right into a big big pivot level,
guys. So, we're trading back into last
Friday's kind of levels here. Uh
Friday's low would be all the way down
at 15:30, but we're in the congestion
block from Friday and Thursday and
Tuesday and
maybe Monday the 12th and Friday the
9th. So, we're into like quite a big
kind of area we're trading into at the
moment. So, we'll see. If we don't flush
through all this, I would expect the VIX
to potentially find a bit of a bid.
doesn't [snorts] have to.
I've never traded with FTMO, so I can't
tell you.
I have no uh I have no opinion.
Still nine short on the likes, guys.
Nine short on the likes. Almost there
for a giveaway.
Someone repeat the first funded account.
The f the first one I said is if you
haven't traded futures before and you
just want to learn it, just get a cheap
Apex account. All right? Because chances
are you're going to blow it up and it
means you're only going to spend 20
bucks or something. The cheapest one
possible. If you just want to like get
used to the platform, get used to the
market, do that. If you've traded before
and you understand futures and you're
looking to like pass and and start to
scale, I'd look at Lucid Funded Next
um and Tradeify.
If you're consistent already and you're
moving over to futures and you
understand what you're doing, I'd look
at TPT.
Those are the ones that like my top
five. There's a video on my YouTube
where I compare them all and I tell tell
you who they good for. Just check that
out. I'll post it for you. All the
questions you're going to ask will be in
there because I tell you like their
strengths, their weaknesses, who they
good for, what are my favorite and why,
but they might not necessarily be, you
know, your favorite ones,
but these are the ones that I recommend
and the reasons why. All right, so you
can check this video out here.
What videos do I recommend for someone
getting into your content and your new
strategy? Um, I've got a shelf for my
YouTube channel. There's a whole shelf
that I've built on the YouTube channel.
So, if you go to my channel, there
should be,
let me have a look.
If you're brand new, go to my YouTube
channel, start here, right? Trading and
education, beginner to advance. There is
a ton in here, guys. Right, just start
here. Go through all of these, right?
This will give you a lot of edge that
you will not find elsewhere. Once you've
done that,
then I would say move into volume and
market profile and start going through
these. I'm going to add some more and
more stuff into here.
Where's that just gone? There we go.
to join the Discord, I need to finish
the full lessons in the course. I mean,
you don't have to. Um, I'd advise that
you go through it, but if you go towards
the end of the course, there's a module
there. Um, who am I talking to here?
Sam, there's a module that says like
Discord, and it tells you what to email
and where to email. If you just shoot me
an email, I'll add you to the Discord
straight away. The only reason I put it
at the end is so that you understand
what everyone's talking about in the
Discord, but if you want to be added
early, we can do that.
Thanks, Bradley. Appreciate it. I
appreciate any of the support.
I don't really talk about them much
unless you guys ask, but you'll see all
the links down below, all the firms that
I work with. Code FCT for most of them
other than take profit trader, you can
use code flow zone over there.
Right.
Market's still holding this level. We've
got like 25 minutes left till lunch.
You're welcome, Dominic. Glad it's
helped.
Glad it's helped.
On the 5minute footprint, would you now
say buyers are trapped?
Yes, but we're still supporting the bid.
Yeah. So, we have definitely over this
level here from 71
up to here, we have buyers caught, but
we're not breaking down yet, are we? So,
we have to look left. All right, this
was the bid support,
right? This was kind of the overunder
these kind of levels here. So we're
still holding. So like yes, there's
buyers caught here, but we need to do
this to trade away from it. Does that
make sense,
right? So we're still structure can
still be positive here. Definitely they
are there on some caught up there.
There's no doubt about it. But if we
come to this, look at how key this pivot
is. So what what we're saying right now
is above here buyers are caught. But we
need to let go of low volume node of
this shelf and trade away from it. We're
not trading away from it yet. You don't
want to like jump the gun. Look at the
flow zones. We're supporting the bid,
right? We're supporting the bid. You got
to also remember the difference between
this and like some of the trades we took
earlier is we've now built structure.
When we came up here earlier and I
shorted this for the move down, we were
a straight squeeze up and we didn't have
much structure. Look at the difference
now.
They've got structure to bid off, right?
So, if we come down into here and they
keep bidding, they can complete the
rotation. You need to see it start to
lose some of these. So, structure is
important.
The difference between that and like
maybe yesterday and the day before we
lacked structure, right? Some of these
amazing shorts. This is something really
important for you guys to understand.
This where is the structure in here?
No structure, right? So when we trap
buyers up here and we leave it, well,
where are we going to come to? Well, at
the very minimum here.
And if we lose that all the way back
down,
right? because we didn't build
structure. Think about it like building
foundations of a house, right? If we'
done this D nice pullback, reclaimed,
pullback, reclaimed, right? Then this
here, this flush probably would have
only come to there, right? And maybe
they get stuck again and maybe it comes
to here and it would not be this
straight move down. Structure matters
like the building blocks of the market
matter.
Same here.
This was the last piece of structure we
had.
Squeeze up, trap buyers, fail down to
that structure.
We've literally held that since if you
if you zoom out, we've held that the
whole time since
that we're building higher highs here.
[snorts]
I have five top set accounts right now
and I'm planning to buy five more. Which
do you recommend? They don't have
intraday trailown. Lucid if you are uh
uh
if you trade with top step the closest
accounts you are going to get to that
rule-based wise are Lucid. Lucid
accounts um e either of them. I've just
done a video on that and you can use
code FCT. I think it gets you 40% off
right now. Lucid are the closest ones
right now, I'd probably say. [snorts]
And cheapest.
Cheapest for what you want. That is
Scott. That's it for me. Green on a few
scalps on the way up on me. Thank you,
Alex, for your contribution and support.
Love you, brother. Love to you as well,
bud. Hope you're good. Do I trade noon
sessions? Uh, not on YouTube. Sometimes
I trade it in Discord.
Bpo shifted up. Yeah, it has. Um, on
Trading View it has actually for me on
tick data. It's still at 620. So for me,
it's still down here. It's right at this
view up.
That tune sounded like a shark. I have
to remember it. Sharks around ready to
bait whoever gets trapped. Yeah, pretty
much.
Welcome, Larry.
What's the best prop firm for daily
payouts? TPT. Take profit trader. You
can use code flow zone there. 40% off.
No activation fee. Can have five
accounts with them. You can take daily
payouts. That is the best one for daily
payouts without a doubt.
Without a doubt.
Are you looking for a trade? I'm pretty
much done to be honest, my friend. Um,
I didn't execute
super well missing this this morning. I
we had like what one trade there, one
trade there, and then had to join late
there because I didn't like that. And
then that short down and I'm not in this
now. It's too late for me to long now at
this point. And we're not losing
structure for me to short. So, you know,
until we see until I see something like
this, there's nothing really for me to
do. And it's very possible we won't see
that and we continue to rotate. So I
just have to be willing now to be like,
"Okay, well I've made my money. It's not
the best day. There's new opportunity
this afternoon or tomorrow." So I'm just
waiting at the moment.
Yeah. How are we doing on the likes? Oh,
we got there on the likes, right? We're
going to do some giveaways. Don't worry,
folks. How do you join the Discord,
Willie? The only way to join the
Discord, my friend, is to do the 20our
course, right? The beginner to advance
course. I know that probably really
annoys people and upsets them, but it's
for good reason. It's for good reason.
There is no monthly fee for it. The
reason is I want everyone in Discord
trading the same way. Those who are in
chat right now will tell you our Discord
is a very positive, helpful environment.
Everyone's looking after each other.
Everyone's trading in the same
direction. Everyone can support each
other, answer questions because they all
understand what we're looking at and
trading. When you have open discords
which are free or a monthly fee, right,
which will be way more than what would
come to way more than what I charge
anyway, you will find traders trading in
different directions and you will
suddenly start to get over influence in
what you want to do. So that's that's
the reason, right? That's the reason.
But if you do the uh 20our course, it's
completely free for life.
Do I do one-on- ones? I don't do one-on-
ones. I don't do one-on- ones. I just
simply don't have the time. But we do do
uh group lessons. I do actually want to
do a group lesson this week with
everyone.
Aren't TPT payouts capped? Uh they are
payout the payouts are capped at 10K per
account, but then they move you to a
live with the same rules. So, it makes
no difference.
My trading is not consistent. Great day
yesterday, very bad day today. How do I
get more consistent? Um, you need to
define rules and understand why you won
yesterday and why you lost. And then you
need to do more of what you're good at
and less of what you're bad at.
Do I look at structure on a fivem
minute? Yeah, I mean I'm always looking
at it on So I have this chart up on my
other just below,
right? So this is my five minute chart.
All right.
So I do I do pay attention to it. I pay
attention to everything.
Where's the course? Flowzonerader.com.
Flowzonerader.com. I'll post it for you
again.
Me post the exact link so you make sure
you do the right one.
It's here. Okay.
No, it's all right. It's all right. I'll
just post it for you.
What are the column settings
you have on my bookmap? You mean on the
DOM? Price, delta, bid, ask, volume
profile, sell, volume profile, buy. I
don't know why that's squeezed in.
Shouldn't be squeezed in. What's going
on there? And session volume profile.
It's all I care about. The main one is
the volume profile delta that I care
about.
Takes some time to get used to Ninja. It
does. It does, but it's well worth it
once you're used to it.
I have a tendency to get in late to you
to Oh, do you maybe do you have any
suggestions to improve my entry? Very
hard for me to say without looking at
it, but how late are we talking? Right.
Are we talking that you're buying like
up here?
What are we talking about? If you're
buying dips on flow zones,
okay, how to prevent getting in late
flow zones or use a 21 EMA or whatever
you want. You want to be buying when
we're positively moving towards the
target as close to those EMAs as
possible, right? Based on structure,
based on EMAs. You don't want to be
selling down here, do you? You want to
be selling near the flow zones. Near the
flow zones. You don't want to be buying
up here, do you? I sold up there.
Remember, you want to be buying near the
flow zones. Near the flow zones. Near
the flow zones. Near the flow zones.
Right? So just you can use a 21. Make it
really simple, right? You want to be
buying near a 21. You do not want to be
buying overextended moves.
That will stop you getting in late.
That'll be the first thing to look at.
When do I think the market would start
behaving normal again? I think this is
the new normal now. I think this is the
new normal.
How often do I do group lessons? I want
to do it every two weeks if not weekly.
I want to do it at least every two weeks
if not weekly.
So JJ what I'd say to that JJ says his
weakness is overthinking and hesitanting
hesitating missing momentum try and then
build a formula a way of getting into
trades where you just stick to that
formula. is no matter what if your
criteria is there you take the trade
regardless of the outcome regardless of
what you think the criteria is there you
take the trade I did a video on that
recently as well
yes so if your criteria is
let's say dailies in breakout to upside
right let's say dailyy's in breakout to
upside bullish let's say 21's over the
200 on whatever ever time frame you're
trading on. Bullish. Let's say pro like
volumes uh we're moving value higher.
Bullish. Then you're looking for
pullbacks to get long into. You're not
looking to fade it, right? So, you
create that group. That's just an
example. You create something to help
you stick to that narrative.
Yeah, ES looks like it's going to take
out uh go to the high of day. We just
got to still respect these levels.
Remember, 90s is where the buyers keep
getting stuck. I've said it over and
over again. the 90s. You can see it
right here is where these buyers have
been getting stuck. That is from over
here this morning. Look at all these
participants here. 34 34 77. And that's
just delta based, right? We've got
outlying delta there. If we get back
above the 700s, as long as it's not a
fake out, then there's a chance to go
high day. But right now, where those
buyers got stuck is acting as some form
of supply.
Which prop firm do you recommend if you
want to copy 20 accounts other than Apex
and TPT? Well, Apex is the only one that
offer 20 accounts, but you mean like
just other prop firms? My five favorite
prop firms are really simple. Apex, TPT,
uh, Lucid, Tradeify, and Funded Next.
Not in that order, but those are the
five. That's who I advise you trade
with.
So tapping into these 90s, they've got
to get through these 90s and 700s. And
if they do that, then we can think about
that higher day. Look, look at this
imbalance up here, folks. All right,
this we barely traded here. This was the
open print,
right? There was no volume put in here.
None. It's a huge imbalance.
It's a huge imbalance, right? So,
someone asked what like are they stuck
there? And we said yes. And I said, but
structure still holding. You can see
it's stuck again, but structure still
holding until you see this move. You
don't want to frontr run stuff.
People get really excited about price
coming into a level, but it's like
unless we react at that level, there's
nothing to get excited about.
That's footprint, John. That's
footprint.
So, here we go. 90s again. Testing 90s
again. Someone's now trying to bid 90
for the squeeze up to 70705.
So, they are trying to bid 90 for that
squeeze up to 70705. ES is trying to get
up to its IB high here.
We are right at the 20-day as well,
folks. This is the other thing like
these are rotations for anyone that's
done the course.
5day,
20-day.
Look at that rotation.
SMASs don't matter, they said.
[laughter]
Yeah, good one.
What determines the blue and red
candles? Oh, in this chart, uh, the flow
zones, are we above or below flow zones?
So, it's momentum. So, when they're
green, we have bullish momentum. When
they're red, they have bearish momentum.
Right? When they're red inside, bearish
momentum. When they're green, bullish
momentum.
Can I do a dive into ES? You mean just
like now? Look at ES.
You're just coming for IB high.
It's actually cleaner. Look at this.
Right. Huge sell, resell, failing to
make a new low. What's this? Inverted
head and shoulders, breakout, pullback,
holds the pivot, grind back up. Target
is this high. It might need a flush
before it does it. It might be a small
flush. Might need to trap in some more
sellers if it's going to do it.
This is very steep. It might need to do
something like this before it's going to
do it. We'll see. But it's the same
story. It's just trying to get it to
that high.
Right
on. We are pretty much there, folks.
We're pretty much there.
Uh, in the course, Aaron, or there might
be some videos on it. I can't remember.
Do I have a code for Tradeify? Yep. FZT
FCT for Tradeify.
So here's previous week value now. So
this is the key level. Can we find
acceptance through this? We're through
the 90s. We're testing the 700s.
Watching ES come up to higher day as
well. So we have the chance to squeeze
if we can get through this to those sort
of single print imbalances.
Volume indicator on the left. Where are
you looking? On the left. I don't have
volume on the left. on the right. Do you
mean
where do you mean up?
This is if you mean this this is
anchored volume profile.
Anchored volume profile anchored to 930.
Right. And I just change it here.
Basement. All right.
Okay. Giveaway time. We'll give away one
free Apex account. Type FCT in chat and
give you guys a minute to do that.
While you do that,
I'm just going to use the bathroom and
I'm going to be right back and then
we're going to do the giveaway as soon
as I'm back. All right. So, just give
you a minute to do it.
All right. Still stuck.
Still stuck. You might see that pullback
we talked about. Still the same level as
being key here.
Yes. Quite. All right. Thank you,
Miguel. If you spam,
you'll be automatically deleted. Okay.
Pulling this winner.
Five,
four,
three,
two,
and one.
Evan. Evan. Vtor.
Verino. Verino.
Don't know how to say that. Verino.
Vtori. Vtorianiano.
[snorts] Great name.
Evan, are you here? Evan, let me know
you're here.
Give Evan a minute to reply. Still
holding that blue box. You can see that
low vol node still holding up. This
might be this little dip and rip that we
talked about. That's me. Hey, nice.
Okay, Evan, what I want you to do is
email me, please.
info@flowzonerader.com.
Send me a screenshot of you logged into
your YouTube so I know it's you. I'm
making a note of you now and I will sort
you out with a free Apex account. All
right, free Apex account coming your
way.
Congratulations.
making a note now. We [snorts] go.
Two minutes to lunch here, folks. Just
be careful.
He just got banned. It's okay. I can I
can see him. It's all right. It's just
just cuz he's typing in caps. All right,
folks. Uh we'll do one more giveaway.
We're going to give away a beginner
course. All right. Just the 2hour
courses. This is great if you've never
traded before. you don't understand
markets at all. If you're complete
newbie,
type course in chat.
It's just the beginner course, not the
beginner to advance. It's an
introduction to trading. So, just type
course in chat once. Let you guys do
that. I'll give you a minute.
So back to this blue box again. Point of
control shifted up. If they start losing
these nodes then you know again it's
possible that they flush reflush back
down here. I would just be careful of a
trap happening under this like if they
got unfinished business. I'd be careful
of that kind of thing happening there
today. Now, so the type of thing they do
if they want to come higher, I know
we've just rejected value, but if they
want to get acceptance, the type of
thing they do is to trap under here and
reclaim so they have short fuel to go
higher. If we see strong momentum away
though, there'll be a flush back down
towards the VWAP.
I'm done for the day no matter what as
we come into lunch or at least for the
morning session.
Give you guys a couple more minutes to
do this giveaway.
You're in timeout. I can see you. I can
see you though, Evan. Don't worry. Don't
worry about it.
Make sure I've got this set up for you
guys.
All right, let's pull this winner.
Brenda, is that right? Brenda Sang
9894. Do you hear Brenda?
So, here we go. It might be this little
trap we just talked about.
Seen it too many times. Too many
flipping times. Nice, Brenda. All right,
just same thing from you. Can you just
shoot me an email? Send me an email.
info@flowzontrader.com.
I've made a copy of your name. just send
a screenshot of you logged into you your
YouTube. So, just so I know it's you.
It's all you've got to do.
All you've got to do.
Yeah. So, I would say there's potential
for this trap to play out here. Now,
these are the kind of things I look for
when they're trying to get to highs.
They do these like little sweeps and
then they reclaim. We just talked about
this. We literally just talked about it.
If they hold this, then you know that
they're going to come for this up here.
If they stay heavy under here on a
rejection, then you're watching VWAP and
PC down here.
Um, but that is probably it for me. Um,
I'm going to have to take my dog out for
a walk.
How do I interpret foot footprint for
the trap that just happened? I didn't
even watch it to be honest, but there
you go. There. There you go. So, you
tell me. How do you interpret this? You
guys have been with me long enough. What
has happened under there?
What has happened under the 60 level?
The big level that we had the box,
right? The 60. What's happened under 60?
Sellers are stuck. There you go. You
guys are clever, right? So, this is
sellers marketing in. This isn't passive
selling. This is aggressive selling
marketing in. But where are we going?
We're going up. So, what does that mean?
That means some limit buyer, a limit
buyer or a passive buyer is absorbing
all of this because he wants to complete
the rotation. All right, so these are
the kind of things that you will just
get used to seeing over and over again.
I didn't even need to see that. Like I
called it to you. It's likely to happen
here cuz I just I've been in this game
long enough. It doesn't have to happen.
But normally, if there's a target above
that they want to get to and they're
running out of steam, there's only one
way that they're going to get there and
it's by trapping in more shorts, they
pile in now and they've got their stop
there. Guess what happens when we get
there? You get that push, right? So,
exactly. It's absorption. If we trade
back under that though, that's where you
might see this fade into here.
No worries, Bradley. All right, folks.
That's me done. I'm going to get out of
here. walk my dog. Uh those in Discord,
I will see you later. I see some of you
just bought the course, so I'm looking
forward to working with all you new lot
who just bought the course. Have a safe
trading day. I don't think we've got any
news this afternoon. Let me just check
on um financial juice. You're good for
the rest of the day. But yeah, those of
you who are going to trade overnight,
please, please, please, please be aware
of what we're going to have overnight uh
overnight. So, what time is this? starts
at sort of
4:30 my time. 5 6 So 7:30 you've got uh
PMI in Japan
10:30 Eastern time you've got uh the
start of like the Bank of Japan rate
decisions. It can affect the market. We
are if they go hiking again, we're going
to get carry trades. You might get more
unwind. So we're just going to have to
see unless it's already been baked in,
but we we will see. All I'm saying is
please be careful. Don't be forcing your
way into positions. All right, big love
to you all and uh see you tomorrow
morning. Let's close out this week
strong. Take care. Stay safe. Use hard
stops. Peace and love.