All right, morning folks. Morning
everyone. Uh you might hear some uh
sound in the background. I've just got
Trump on at Davos. The nonsense
continues. But hey, we're going to have
volatility. That is for sure this
morning. Lots of news coming this
morning. Uh make sure you're aware of
all the news drops today. All right.
It's really, really important you're
aware of all the news drops today. Um,
I can give you a quick readout of them.
All right, Trump talking now. Um, and
then again at 9:45 and then Fed Cook at
10:00 and then construction spending at
10:00 and then pending home sales at
10:00 and then a Trump uh meeting in
Davos at 11:25. So, a packed morning.
All right, packed morning. Expect
volatility. [snorts] All right, as
always, starting out on the daily chart.
All right, you can see yesterday we
faded underneath the daily Ballinger.
All right, we let me just turn him down
here for a minute. All right, quiet you.
All right, we faded under the daily
Ballinger. Very rare to see us trade
under the daily Ballinger without
normally trying to trade inside. We're
seeing a little bit of relief today.
What is the key pivot? Key pivot very
clearly here, isn't it? Into these 900s.
All right, this is the big pivot that
we've been talking about. We might well
need to build out some liquidity here
and let these Ballingers and the
fiveday, you can see the fiveday cross
and everything start to trend down to
play catch up if we're going to come for
these. It's very possible that we need
to do that. Maybe not. Maybe the market
doesn't like what it hears today and we
just go continuation straight straight
away. We're going to find out, but we're
going to have to like respect some of
these levels. We're going to see more of
these levels on the hourlys. All right,
so let's move into the hourlys. Let's
have a look at what we're doing with
value. All
right, here we go. So, this profile here
is the current week developing profile.
It's really important you zoom out and
look at where we are trying to reclaim,
where we lost a bid, all these key
levels. But yesterday's profile, if we
think about value yesterday, previous
day value area low is 240. We can see in
this developing profile, we have a
couple of very thick areas here. I'd say
it starts basically 200 all the way up
into these uh what's the edge of this
225 and then we get thin um into sort of
230. So what I'm looking at this morning
is is price
going to respect these levels? Is it
going to respect previous day value area
low? If so, is there like a little look
above and fail back under and then this
trade back down and we're going to
respect this node here and if we find
acceptance then we move lower. That's
one thing we could consider. If not, if
this is a failed auction lower, if we're
not willing to trade underneath and
we're going to reclaim and base here at
sort of 225, 230, 240, 250, then we can
expect this rotation up into 350 for
this point of control. So, there's 100
points up for grabs here, right? This
will be your counter trend play. I want
to make that very, very clear. All
right, if we think about what the
market's doing since the Sunday open,
all right, we have been moving low, but
if we see this, then this will be
compression and you can't rule this out.
And if they keep going back to the top
side, it's possible, folks. Anything is
possible in this market. All right,
anything's possible.
So, those are the two plays. All right,
this level here is key as we come
trading into this, which we're already
doing right now, coming flying into it.
This is going to be key. Do we see a
rejection here? It might be a look above
and fail. It might be a rejection in
front of it. It might be a reclaim and a
base and hold and up to 350. So those
are the two plays I'm looking at for
this morning's session. We can see we've
probably got some imbalances here. If we
look above on this 5minute chart, you
can see GloEx kind of went sideways.
All right, London just peaked above and
then lost the GlobeEx bid. All right,
and then there's a big follow through.
Very similar to here. Peak above, lost
the bid, follow through. Similar to
here, peak above, lost the bid, follow
through. All right, that's what we're
seeing. But this is your key pivot. You
can see this developing node here. Very,
very important.
Okay, moving up into the lower time
frames as we're getting very close to
some of these key levels here already.
And we can just have a quick look. Let's
move this up to five minute and ES. We
can look at the same stuff. Yeah, ES
already into that New York VW up. Big
big pivot from yesterday. We can just
put uh you know what, let's just put one
on from
Sunday on here.
Okay, that's current week developing.
Same kind of thing here, folks. All
right, you can see this node here into
sort of 860s. All right, you'd want
bears to defend this. You're into a low
volume node here. You'd want bears to
defend this to cause this downside
rotation. That's from what a 60 or 70
down to 30. So there's 30 40 points up
for grabs there on ES if they reject it.
If you see a reclaim, then the squeeze
is on to try and try try and take this
out. So, same kind of story on it. ES.
If we look at the spiders, they're
matching up nicely. All right. Big gap
down. All right. The question is, do we
see a little poke above and a fail or
are we going to see some of this for the
rotation back up to here? Gap still
open. Of course, cues is going to be
exactly the same. There you go. So, you
see yesterday we lost that pivot. This
is the pivot we were talking about
fading yesterday. Okay, remember I was
looking to fade yesterday because we had
left value trapped. We had a key pivot.
We traded into that. We had three
attempts in the morning session and you
know we talked about sods law. Sods law
says the moment I leave and take my dog
out for a walk it does it. Yes, it's
exactly what happened. And uh don't
worry my team in Discord absolutely
nailed that. They were well prepared for
that which is great.
Dixie, let's have a little look here.
Right. Open opening up PDC. Not much to
see there. VIX is an interesting one.
All right, we're just between these
ranges right now. You can see move this
to blue. We are between these ranges
right now. Stuck and we have to see if
there's more downside pressure down into
this pivot of 18. So, we can set price
alerts there either side of these ranges
for sure. Let's have a quick look at
treasuries.
All right, 30 years. Still holding very,
very high. Remember, we were looking
this for this breakout. All of last
year, we were talking about this
breakout, right? We're talking about
these breaks and we're starting to
really get going now. So, I want to be
very careful there.
Yeah, this break from here starting to
hold and gap. I want to be very, very
careful there. And the 10 and the five,
the lower ones, they look all right.
This is the divergence between the two,
which we commonly see when we go into a
cell. Okay, quick look at the MAG.
[snorts]
All right, Apple trying to gap up and
hold inside previous days range when it
went into a big big big sell yesterday.
That's a huge sell. All right, does it
repric up to 250? Big question mark if
it can do that. All right, and does it
reject here if it does or is it just
going to do a little twoleg not make it
that far and resell down?
Amazon, same thing. trying to like hold
a decent opening print above the
yesterday's close, but again into
previous day's action. So, an inside bar
there on Amazon.
Same story here in Google. All right,
failure pre-market trying to trade back
inside yesterday's range. So, possibly
an inside bar there. Meta definitely an
inside bar. Microsoft definitely an
inside bar. So, Maggle inside right now.
Nvidia. It's a nice push off the lows
again inside bar. You got to watch these
levels into uh 80, let's call it 82 and
83s are the levels to watch from Nvidia
and tests are the same um straight back
inside. So all of them trading an inside
bar right now. All right. So the
question is do any of them have follow
through downside or are they going to
reclaim and come and test the top of the
range created yesterday? Equally
weighted.
Yeah, equally weighted. Same story. All
right, here's yesterday's close. Here's
yesterday's highs. Here's yesterday's
bar. And we are trading probably near
the midpoint of it right now. So, coming
into some interesting levels and Netflix
had earnings yesterday, gap down on the
Netflix. Um, I'm still holding this. I'm
going to start accumulating a very, very
small net. Like I've said to my team,
I'm waiting to see if we offer a bigger
flush down into these pivots and if
there's something worth scooping up
under there. But I've just got like my
feet wet at the moment. I'm just waiting
to see how we respond. We're already 40%
off the highs. I just want to see if
there's a flush moment if the market
starts to get heavy and I can pick up
some cheap long term. I'm talking years
and years and years looking to hold for
this. And um yeah, that's pretty much
it, folks. If we look uh the broader
market probably pretty much the same in
tech.
AMD finding some strength here this
morning.
Oracle weak compared to the rest of the
mag, but still just about inside.
All right,
take your time. Make notes of all these
levels. I'm just going to make sure my
Ninja is up and running properly. Let's
zoom this in as we come into this
previous day value very low.
Where's my trade account? There we go.
Okay, so opening up here in the next
five minutes right on previous day value
area low and view up. Remember a squeeze
above this will probably take us up to
the 340 350s.
I'm just going to turn Trump up just so
I can have a little listen here.
Morning all.
What's the relevance of an inside bar?
Uh well, it's trading versus yesterday's
price action, which means it's building
liquidity. It's not expanding liquidity.
So, it's currently probably inside of
value which is where we are now. We're
trying to trade back inside of value.
All right, we are inside an inside bar
as well because PDC is here. All right,
and we've looked below and failed and we
are now trading back inside yesterday's
bar is here. All right, and yesterday's
value is here. So, if we can't find
acceptance below this, guess what? We're
going to rotate inside yesterday's
value. So, why is it significant? Well,
it starts to help us understand the type
of market conditions. We might very well
go into a rotational market if we can't
find price acceptance outside of 240 and
below.
So, do me a favor, folks. Smash that
like button nice and early for me,
please. Lots of you seem to come here
and watch and don't hit like. And the
quicker you hit the like button, the
more chance we've do got of doing some
Apex giveaways and some course
giveaways.
What's he banging on about? He was last
talking about NATO.
Oh, he's out here mocking other
presidents, is he? and prime ministers.
This is great.
See talking about himself in third
person. It's incredible.
I reckon if you put his uh
speeches into like chat GBT, you can
condense it into like two lines. He just
dribbles on on repeat so much.
It's insane.
[laughter]
The Discord. Yeah, the Discord's for
members only. Uh so you would have touh
do the beginner to the advanced course
the 20our course.
Okay so rejection here previous days
value so far and VWOP
and current week value is down at 185.
So there is a pivot down here if they do
want to hold it on the developing weekly
profile. Otherwise you'll probably see a
flush to 132. So these are the big
contested levels. Now
there we go into this open in what the
next two minutes already rejecting value
like we just talked about. Right? These
are the key levels. We want to trade
around these key levels.
Is this huge pump bullish for the day?
No.
No. Definitely not. Not unless we
reclaim and even then it would be a
rotational day. All right. So, this is a
huge drive off the lows to retest value.
All right, we're retesting value. If we
leave value and close this gap, they
will either try and bid between these
two or if they lose this, we can look
for these 190s. All right, if they hold
back inside here, then arguably it's
bullish, but it's a rotational bullish
move up into here. All right, it's also
possible they do a fail break. So, this
is a big big level and we are going to
respect it. So, I don't not convinced
I'm going to take a trade at the open
today. Not like yesterday. Not unless we
drive straight up into here and I can
think about selling this market back
down because it's an overextension
at the moment. You can see quite clear
rejection of previous day's value. Like
I said, current weekly value is
currently at 185 186 somewhere around
here. So, it's possible they might want
to hold a dip here. [snorts]
Okay. Still going on about Biden. It's
insane. Is he going to do this in 3
years time as well? Still talk about
previous presidents.
Come on, buddy. Jog it on a little bit.
Change your narrative.
You were funny for about a minute.
Alex, did we take that full shelf down
you mentioned yesterday from stream or
do you think There's further to go. Uh
we did the move. Yeah, yesterday we did
the move that we've completed, but
there's more to go. We can come into
this block down here if we want. Haven't
quite got there yet. [sighs]
Okay, folks. Here we go. This is the
open. Let's see what we do. So, coming
back down into current weekly value area
low, developing weekly value area low,
which is where we're trading at right
now. So, we're going to watch this
between previous day value and this
level right now and 24-hour VW up and
see if we catch a bid here. If they
protect this gap or if we're going to
see follow through downside. I can give
you a quick readout on the mag here.
Tesla third of um quarter of a percent
up. Nvidia half a percent up. Microsoft
2/3 of a percent down. Meta flat. Google
quarter of a percent down. Amazon just
gone green to red. Apple 0.64% up. So, a
little bit of a uh shuffle around in
these mag. They're not in alignment
right now. We have time here. We we can
have some time. So protecting current
weekly value. We have to watch this
level here. We have to watch previous
day value. Very very important.
It's amazing the difference. See this
has got this at 340. I've got P on Ninja
at 280.
So I want to be careful here between the
two. Clear discrepancy. So 280 will be a
level as well it seems. that.
So, still rejecting up here. This node
still just trading between these two,
between current week value area low and
previous day value area low. We're
opening outside of value. So,
technically we're bearish until it
reclaims. I just want to be somewhat
careful here.
This a minute to develop. [snorts]
relative strength today in ES so far
this morning. So broader market probably
holding up a bit better than tech right
now.
Okay, so coming to close this gap by the
looks of it, this yellow line and this
gray box and see if they hold a bid here
or not.
Still holding this bid
back towards this New York open by the
looks of it.
Testing current weekly value area low
again. It's 85 that I keep talking
about.
Watch your ATR here, folks. Very high on
that open 73 points.
Back to VWAP. Gap fill is underneath at
28. Remember
bids down here at 150 and 140.
VIX finding a bid off previous day low.
Looks like we're trying to fill the gap.
There's just some bids front running
this at 150 and 140 right now. Still
nothing for me yet.
Want to be very careful trading around
here. Here's the retest of 85 again.
Watching this New York open. And this is
85s again the current week value area
low here. They're trying to see if they
can get acceptance back inside the
current week.
Just going to have to be patient. One of
those mornings where it requires a bit
more patience.
Testing that New York open. Can't
reclaim it. All right. So these big
levels. So we're trading right now. The
rotation is between this. Oh, don't move
it between these two boxes.
All right, there's your gap fill area
here. All right, squeeze potential can
happen over here if they base above. It
can also be a look above and fail and we
can play downside. So, I just want to
let this develop. Either we're going to
get under the close under the lows and
stay heavy or they're going to do a
little look below and fail and come back
into here or they do a look above and
fail and come back down or they base and
go. I know there's a lot of opportunity
here. I'm looking at every direction
because I don't know if we're going to
have follow through or if we need a
counter trend squeeze higher yet. So,
just waiting for it to develop and I'll
play once it becomes clear what it wants
to do.
Spider's getting stuck into their 50-day
right now.
All pushes so far this morning into that
New York open have failed.
Yeah, ES is stronger. RTY is stronger.
YM's stronger. All you have to do is
look at the percentage change. We have
relative weakness in the cues right now.
That's been the same for a while because
we keep rotating out of tech and into
the broader market, right? It's been the
narrative since December.
This guy's already been talking for
ages, like an hour. It's insane.
[snorts]
Okay, so there's 150 buyers now been
filled. There's still some sellers up at
85 and 200. We still haven't really
closed this gap yet. So, just waiting to
see if we close that gap and then how do
we react? So far, previous day value
definitely holding up.
Without the United States, you don't
have a country. Yes, that's right. Well,
you what you meant to say is we don't
have a world, and we definitely do have
a world without the United States.
There's plenty of other countries out
there, Donald.
Gez Louise, this guy's on one today.
Right. See if we can get a gap fill here
and then see what opportunities come
afterwards. Just being patient here.
All right. So, nice rejection of value
pre-market. Coming back down to this big
gray box. We got a big node here.
We're finding bids in at the moment.
If we get under this node and we stay
heavy versus sort of 28s and 20s, then I
think there's a bigger flush in the
market. Otherwise, you want to be very
careful. If you were short from value
area low, you want to be covering some
into here and then seeing if you find
price acceptance lower. I'm not in
anything yet. I'm just being very, very
patient.
back for this 200 test. This New York
open. So, between these gray boxes, the
rotation still. That's why I'm having to
be patient this morning. Very different
to yesterday when I attacked it out of
the gate. [snorts]
Yeah, that's what I'm saying. Josh, it's
still it's like an hour. Like, how And
he's How long is he going to talk for?
I'm just waiting for him to stop talking
so the news also stop looking for words.
Yes. Back through that New York open.
We're back to these 200s again.
So, do they sell this gray box again for
the rotation back down and fill the gap?
or are we going to see the start of a
squeeze
into this gray box? Are we going to
extend now and come up for previous date
value to 240? Is it possible?
Still this gray box being defended for
now. So, we've just got to be patient
here, folks.
Okay, so if they get through here,
possible squeeze to 40s. I'm waiting to
get outside of value. Either a look
above and fail and I'll fade it back
down or a look above and base and I will
play the squeeze back up. I do not want
to trade in this garbage here for me
personally.
Just looking at the owl, it's just a
little bit messy in here. We've had a
big drive up. We've run the stops over
247. And we've come back inside, but
we're not seeing follow through yet. So,
just trying to wait for it to show me
the direction it wants to go in. Let's
have a quick look at the MAC. Tesla
0.61% up. Nvidia 0.60% up. Microsoft 1%
down. Meta% down. Google 0.06% down.
Amazon 0.43% down. Apple coming back
down as well right now trading just
0.19% up. So, they're not really sure
yet. Some of them pulling back in
towards their PDCs.
I could very very possibly see this just
being a choppy inside day with a look
below and fail happening in the in the
early session. So, we will see.
We will see.
Yeah, the United States is keeping the
whole world afloat. That's why gold and
silver have been going up and no one
values the dollar anymore, mate. That's
why they want to DPEG it. I mean, just
the logic alone is incredible. But hey,
he knows what he's doing. He's a good
propaganda machine, that's for sure.
He's got a Duracell battery in him for
talking.
Okay, still trading between these gray
boxes. Still the same thing we talked
about early in the morning.
Here's PDC. So, gap now filled, folks.
Gap now filled.
Apple now gone green to red as well. All
right. So, you're seeing some heaviness
come back into this market. We're still
in this gray box. We just need to see if
we're going to get acceptance below this
or if they're going to rebid this after
the gap fill right back up. It's very
possible they rebid it right back up.
Best sale this morning was probably when
I was uh doing the pre-market show with
you guys here. This look above value and
fail.
Still holding bids on this gap fill
right now. ES still above its VWAP. Not
tagged it yet. It might need a little
bit more of a flush here on ES into its
VWAP, which is trying to do now
into those 44s.
Can I show what indicators I use? Yeah,
Flowzone Pro. It's my system, right?
It's on my website. You get a free
version of it with the course and you
can upgrade if you want. Everything's at
flowzoneer.com.
It is still bidding off PDC so far.
Still looks messy to me.
Definitely some sellers caught under 35s
right now.
And point of control now at 163s. We're
tapping it now. Let me put some volume
on here for you.
Put it on.
There we go.
still being patient. Just rotating
between these two.
Yes, held its VW up. Spy held its VW up.
and trying to get this squeeze back up
to this New York open again over point
of control. Value area high in the
session now into 90s which is where
we're now trading into. Here's the New
York open. All right, I'm starting to
get interested in this for expansion if
they can push and drive. Don't want to
get trapped at the high though.
Watching these 200s, 220s, feathering
in, scaling some out as I go. Just
scalping my way through this this drive
here just in case we fail this gray box
again.
We base a bar that's way more
interesting for big size on
back to these 200s.
Yeah, big pivot up here if we get over
it there. There is squeeze relief over
this up into these these areas up here.
Definitely.
So, I want to be aware of that.
205 was that level of that huge seller
yesterday as well. Worth remembering.
Still back and forth here between these
two. All right, took a little long here
for a scalp into this. Lots of money in
already.
Not sizing into this yet unless we get a
break above and a squeeze.
I know I'm not talking much today,
folks. It's just very slow. Just waiting
for a clean break or a clean trap.
They're [snorts] adding liquidity 220 to
230. So, they might lift up here a
little bit to go and fill these guys.
Where's that strong seller this morning?
212. Okay, so they're going to test him
again here.
This is where he came in last time.
20s. Here's the 12 again. They're going
for 20s and 30s fills now. Fill these
liquidities we just talked about. There
we go. So, they're trying to get through
to fill the top side of this opening
range above here. There is a squeeze
potential if they base above. There's
also a look above and fail.
What is my bias? Well, currently my bias
is rotation.
Um, if we get above previous day value,
when technically we can be sure all the
time we fade this, but it's a rotation
up to here. If we get back inside value,
I'm expecting a rotation higher unless
we peak above and fail. If we keep
rejecting value, then I'm expecting a
rotation lower, but we're going to have
to get under PDC, which has held again
today. So, it's very choppy between
these two levels. All right.
continuation will come outside of this
or a counter trend relief above this.
This is a liquidity build in here.
Right.
Has he stopped or did my phone get so
bored of listening to him?
anything.
Okay, so they're looking for the
squeeze. Value is key here. Look above
and fail or look above and base for the
squeeze.
ES with strength here.
>> [snorts]
>> 250 clear target this last pivot. So,
they're starting to base above this W
here. All right, we're starting to see
one of these. If they hold New York and
they do this, you will see relief up
into here. Probably it doesn't have to
be, but probably up into here. If you
see relief,
nice. Let's get through this now.
So dips now need to hold 205s really
somewhere around that. If they fail 200s
and fail the New York open,
they're just going to fail to break out.
We've got divergence to ES which just
took the highs as well and is trading
back inside. It's very messy here this
morning, folks. Going to have to be very
careful here. [snorts]
So testing value area high right now
into these 205s which I said buyers must
hold. If they fail to hold that there
will be no chance to rotate through the
250s. If they hold this they have got a
shot of going through 250 and then
through that 280 and then 350s are the
targets if they can hold. It's a big if
right now folks. It's a big if.
[snorts]
VIX lower day breaking previous day lows
here.
So if FIX gets followed through
downside, we might see more relief.
Right, here's the test of the sort of
205s we just talked about. Do they rebid
this? If not, then uh there's nothing to
do here. We're just going to go back
inside current value, which will be a
nightmare.
Can't get through that opening range
right now. Failing the opening range
high at the moment.
They need to lift back through the 225s
and 250s at the moment is what they need
to do.
There's the 25 test. They got to get
back through this. There are buyers
stuck at 30s. They got to get back over
30s to be comfortable.
Here we go. It's over 30s. Nice. Right.
Can we lift to 250 and then can we get
going on a squeeze? Come on, baby.
Come on. You got to get through that 250
for me so I can get a big giant squeeze
out here. It' be really fun.
Big seller just stepped in there. So we
now know huge seller at 240. Huge seller
came in at 240. Still looking to trade
this higher at the moment. Want to get
through 240 and 250 and make this seller
stop out.
So currently long from here on this dip
trying to get acceptance through here.
I'm going to trim some into these levels
here because we keep rejecting 240 again
as big seller. But we have got liquidity
all the way up into 60s. I think we can
lift here on a runner.
Come on. Lift it through 260. Here we
go.
Let's go. Let's go.
Okay. So, we're going to watch 280 now
and 350 on the runner. Be very careful
if they look above here and fail.
Really nice. Be very careful if they
look above and fail.
Uh the delta CVD is very strong. It's
very strong upside right now. So, it's
good aggressive buyers stepping in. So,
there was some passive selling, but
we're starting to get through it all.
So, now looking to see if we can go 280
and then 350. All right. So should have
paid yourself here. All right, you
should have paid yourself here in this
move. If we get lucky, we get 280s. And
if we get through that, we can get to
350. But you must pay yourself here.
Please
do not want to see a look above and fail
here because then we come right back
down into this range. So it's why we're
paying ourselves.
We know this is like one of the edges
from the current week developing value.
We've got a little bit of a node here.
If we can get through this, there is a
lift to like 300 and really
340 350. So through 280 there is the
chance to go to 340 350. We will respect
the whole number
but trying to get up into here if
possible.
So that W that we talked about down
here, we just drew it out. If you can
remember this, we said if we can hold
this, there's a chance to do this. And
then we're looking for this. Yes. Let's
go.
Let's go.
All right. So, I'll tell you on Ninja,
I have previous day point of control at
280. That's why I'm I'm being aware of
it. On Trading View, I have it all the
way up here at 350. So, they're both
high volume nodes.
Let's go, baby.
Let's go, baby. Let's see if we can get
a bit more here.
Remember,
we're counter trend, right? So, this is
a relief rally. We are bearish overall
in the market, but we don't expect this
market to keep flushing underneath the
daily Ballinger band to do what we talk
about. Here's 280. Pay yourself some
here. Just pay myself a little bit more.
And then we're going to watch 300s and
350s. Really nice. We don't really
expect much more than that. All right.
We're going to It's likely that we
either hit a block here or here. If we
get acceptance over 350, then you know,
maybe we come out all the way up into
previous days value area high, but I
would find it unlikely. It's probably
more likely we're trying to get into uh
point of control, which we're at one
now. And there's another node up here.
Really good. We're [snorts] really,
really good now, folks.
So, just hold this. See if we can keep
squeezing. This is a straight squeeze.
Shorts got caught here this morning. And
this is the relief rally.
[snorts]
Beautiful
high time frame algo getting hit here on
the ES. Reclaiming the 50-day on the
spiders,
beautiful, beautiful, beautiful,
beautiful.
You should have paid yourself. This is a
really, really nice trade. It's like 80
plus points now already.
Just be very careful into this level.
It's a big level. The 280s I called it
out 280s, 300, 350s, right? You must be
paying yourself into these. Here comes
the flush from 280s. All right, so they
stacked it. We're still bullish in the
intraday, but we're still bearish
overall. Okay.
And uh buyers will want to hold previous
day value area. If we're going to do a
rotation now, right? If we're going to
do a rotation now, buyers will need to
hold this to rotate up here. If they
fail this, this is a look above and
fail. This is what we talked about
pre-market. These moves we've done
today. We talked about pre-market.
There's the gap fill. There's strength
over New York. There's inside value.
Here's the attempt to drive higher. They
must hold value now to drive higher. If
they fail to hold value, this will be a
look above inside previous day's value
and we'll rotate lower. But right now,
we're bullish and we're looking for
expansion now through 280s. We're
looking for 300 and then up here.
And this will be us done for the day if
we can get this.
[snorts]
Let's go. All right. 300 test coming.
Come on, baby.
Right. If we get very lucky, we're going
to get up into here. If we get very
lucky, 300 would be a big level.
Watch this pivot and spy
back inside yesterday's IB. We've done
the same now on uh the cues as well. So
pullbacks, if they're going to hold the
pullbacks, I said they're going to have
to hold value, which is probably
yesterday's initial balance.
A little look. Yeah, pretty much 234s.
So, two 235s we just call it.
So, inside yesterday's value, we should
rotate. We should rotate now. [snorts]
Yeah, number. Thanks, JD. I would have
almost forgotten that. Yeah, you're
right. There are some numbers. We talked
about it right at the open. Uh numbers
are
uh so there's going to have Fed Cook's
argument. Then you've got construction
spending and pending home sales. All
right,
some buyers just c got caught there at
300. Big delta left up there at 300. So
right now we have 121 lot and an 87 lot
300. So we need to trade back over 300
for them to be safe. There we go. Nice.
So still holding this. Still looking
good. We might hit final target here.
Why would we be done for the day? Well,
it's not that you have to be done, but
if I hit my A+ trade, if I catch a full
rotation, what's the reason for me to
keep trading? Unless I, you know, maybe
I can consider
something like this back down. Maybe
there's a short to be had on an
overextension back down into here.
Possibly. Maybe that happens from 300
and I play it back up. But once we go
from a lowhanging fruit to a lowhanging
fruit, you've got to ask what's there
left to do other than build out
liquidity, right? But it's personal
preference. Here we go.
Go team. Let's go.
So 340 345 on deck. That's PC from
previous day. That's where they're
trying to lift to.
You seen some front running in front of
that now.
We have a little node here being
developed. And just mark this guy out
here on that high time frame. Algo,
really good
ES coming into a pivot as well here
into some thick areas from yesterday.
Really nice lift here. Here we go,
folks. So, getting ready to try and take
final target. I don't think I'm going to
hold on beyond this the 45s. And I guess
there's an argument to hold on to 420s
if it really wants to get going.
Here we go. Here we go, folks. So, 45s
here. 40s and 45s.
Expecting a pullback from here at some
point.
We are overextended. Look how far we are
from all the flow zones and everything.
We're way overextended right now.
Beautiful. Beautiful, beautiful,
beautiful move.
Um, I'm out of this now, folks. I just
sold on that last push. I know I front
run it, but I don't care. If we if we if
we keep going to 420, I'll care. But I'm
expecting some sellers to come in at
some point around here. Right. And then
this node here and this node here.
[snorts]
Okay. Uh, one of you asking the entry.
What was the entry? Yes. Well, I didn't
want to trade. We talked about the
rotation from gray to gray, right? Gray,
gray, gray, gray. Okay, this is PDC gap
then got filled. Here's your W. Here's a
base. We're over
uh weekly value, the 85s, over the 200.
So, I started in here, small size, and
then adding and then we got that squeeze
because now we're back inside previous
day's value. Our target is previous
day's point of control. We expect there
to be resistance here. they might well
flush this back down unless they're able
to catch it and complete the whole
rotation of the whole of previous day's
value. So that was the thesis. Go back
to the very beginning of the show and we
talked about it
like 9:15 around that time. I talked
about what I'd be looking for today and
I was willing to play both sides. If we
had acceptance below, I was willing. If
we couldn't find acceptance, I was
willing.
And it's still trying to fill these 40s
and 45s. I'm out of this now, folks. I'm
out of this now.
Vick's just dripping lower.
There's the 40s and 45 fills. So, 42 and
45 left up there. Lots of buyers just
got caught up there, I'll tell you that.
Lots and lots and lots of buyers just
got caught up there again on that last
push.
They probably want to fill these guys at
40 and 45s, but there are buyers getting
caught.
Some sellers trying to force this
breakdown for this pullback probably
towards 84s, but they haven't filled all
these guys on the book yet at 42s. Have
any of them lifted higher is the
question.
Not really. There was a guy up at 370s
left. So 345 to 350 is definitely a big
level. sellers will be looking to drive
this back down to 280s and 245s at the
moment, which is why I'm out is if we go
sideways here and more sellers get
caught, it's possible they can go for
all the way up here into 420. And you
can't rule it out. Can't rule it out.
Yeah, W's in chat if you caught any of
this with me. W's in chat if you caught
any with me.
Here we go.
We know this is a huge level from
yesterday and it's a huge level from the
developing weekly profile. If we get
through 345 350, they could definitely
lift it up to the 420s.
These are the levels. This is a thick
thick level. It's current value from
yesterday. It's what they considered
fair value.
Nice work everyone. Lots of WS in chat.
I love that. 600 on 10 plus Apex
accounts. 86 grand day. That will do,
won't it?
That will do. The key here though is
that this is planned pre-market. You've
got to understand the work gets done
before the trade and then it's waiting.
You see how I like sat out all of this
in here? I wanted to see what they did.
Once they gap filled and we found a bid
and then we started to hold, I was like,
"Okay, we're going to squeeze." Like
they they've set the trap of shorts
coming in here in this area I was
avoiding.
So, we're getting caught at these 340s
now. 340, 350s that we talked about.
There's still a seller at 42 and 45. So,
the longer we go sideways, the more
chance they've got squeezing upside
again. But, we're starting to develop
a node here. So if we lose this node,
then we're probably going to flush down
to 80s, right? Unless they protect this
300 level. So here we go. So they're
starting to try and lose this node or
the pullback that we talked about.
And you can watch these sort of 300s,
this low volume node. If they catch it
here at sort of 315s, they might want to
try and do one nasty resqueeze higher.
Let's have a look at the MAG. I give you
a readout there. Tesla, uh, 1.20% up
now. Nvidia 1.35% up. Microsoft the
weakest one today, 0.66% down. Meta one
uh 0.19% up. Google 1.04% up. Amazon a
quarter% up and Apple back green again
0.17% up. So they held that low volume
node. Right? No followthrough. They're
trying to force a resqueeze through
this. All right. That's what they're
trying to do. I'm not touching this at
this point. If anything, I'm going to
look for a fade. All right. If anything,
I'm going to look for a fade back down
here or if we even poke up here and a
rotation of value again. Right. I'm
definitely not going to be playing long
up here. That's not what I'm going to be
doing. But we have to let it develop
now.
Would that be an A+ for me? No.
Yesterday was an A+ in the afternoon. Uh
if I was actually here for it. All
right. Because yesterday was a protrend
trade [snorts] where we left value. We
had buyers stuck. We trapped a load of
participants up here. Right? Remember we
had this fade and this fade. I tried all
of these and then I left for lunch and
then finally it did the huge move. All
right. So yesterday would have been A+
if I was here for it. Today is a counter
trend long. So it's not A+.
It's a relief rally right on the higher
time frame.
Keep getting stuck up here at the
moment.
starting to leave volume here. It's just
a little bit trappy down here, but there
could be a flush down to these 280s and
even back down to value if they're
ready. I just wonder if they need to do
one more push higher first. Don't like
this flat top up here. I'd rather see
some big exits up there. If we have a
look
and there are some buyers caught over
35s,
there are some buyers caught over 35.
It's not the prettiest setup. I'd rather
see one more squeeze out. I think
while this does this, folks, I'm just
going to get a quick refill on my tea.
All right, and I'll be right back.
Okay.
So, do me a favor. Smash that like
button for me, please. All right. We've
had a nice well over 100 point trade
today. If we look where you guys got it,
if you got full TP,
right, either from here
or 118 points or even if you joined a
bit later for the reclaim up here.
What did you get out of that? Uh,
still 50 plus points. Well over well
over 85 points. really nice.
[snorts] So, still holding flow zones
are starting to play catch-up. You can
see this big node here. This is what's
important right now. I would like to see
this do one squeeze higher. The reason
being I don't love the top of this
auction right now. But it might be that
they will fade it anyway. We are
overextended,
but I would like to see one squeeze
higher here, trap a load more bulls
before we think about a rotation.
What time frame do I use on my
footprint? An M1 and an M5 for me.
So if you think about those in Discord,
if you look at what I said uh
at what was this 7 7:30 or 8:30 this
morning, sellers came in at heavy at
140, buy stuck over 200. So squeeze can
happen on reclaims those two areas. So
140 to 200 140 right down here. We held
reclaimed 200 squeeze squeeze squeeze
squeeze. So we're in that squeeze that
we talked about pre-market.
Do I use daily time frame to draw
previous day value area low? No, I use
the lowest possible time frame like a
one minute and I draw it on the New York
session. I'm not interested in what
happens beyond New York session. Okay,
we keep coming back down and rejecting
this. So then if they cannot reclaim
this soon, you can see it shifted PC up
here. Now if they can't reclaim this
soon, there will be a flush. Buyers are
trying to get up into here right now,
right? They're trying to reclaim the
whole of value. If they keep rejecting
this, this or this is possible. Very,
very, very possible.
This is a big drive. Look how big it is.
And it's very it's lacking a lot of
structure. It's got no structure in it.
Thanks for your read, Alex. Picked up 40
points on that push. Lovely. Nice work.
Nice work. That'll get the day done,
won't it?
That will get the day done.
I would love one more drive higher. Uh
because I'm I'm thinking about now of
fading the edges. I know I hate fading
the edges, but
one more drive high would be nice.
We are starting to build a huge amount
of volume up here now. And we're
starting to leave it.
There are bids here at 305, 300, 292. So
all in this low volume node is where
they are.
Just trying to be patient here.
Some decent delta transaction at 300
today as well this morning by both
buyers and sellers transacted there
[snorts]
leaving this volume now. So probably
looking at either this gray box or this
gray box to see if buyers defend. They
might very well not defend. They will
have to defend 240.
If they fail to to defend 240 is a
failure of a reclaim of the previous
day's value,
thanks for joining. Jeff, thanks for
joining. Appreciate it.
So, we just filled these guys into 300.
There's still a guy small size at 92 and
another guy adding at 80 now looking to
be picked up. So now what you want to
see if you're a seller, if the market's
kind, you want a retest of this to sell.
But this is counter trend and I'd be
very cautious about this at the moment.
That's the only thing making me feel a
bit iffy about this right now.
I don't love Let me see the high of this
auction.
I mean, there definitely has been
passive selling into 40s all day long,
but I just don't love the look of it. I
would love it if there was a bit more
excess up there. I could drive through
to 50 in a failure. When I talk about
that is like we've we've had a passive
seller at 40s and above here, but a good
high would be something like this, you
know, where we leave all the buyers
trapped up here and then can offer this.
But hey, we don't always get exactly
what we want. Like I talk about all the
time.
No, it doesn't, Calypso. Sorry, mate.
No, it's like an add-on.
Thanks, Short NQ.
Are you Are you okay in the head there?
No, I only say when I take profit. How
many times did I draw this whole thing
out for you?
Like I said, do you want me to hold your
dick when you go to the toilet for you
as well? Cuz I showed you where the
toilet is. I showed you where to piss. I
showed you how to piss gold, but you
need someone to hold hold your dick for
you cuz you don't know how to piss.
Like, come on, man. I literally did all
of this premarket for you.
Go signal bot somewhere else. Crazy.
Absolutely crazy.
[snorts]
Do I think it can reach previous day
value area high if it gets acceptance
over all of this? Yeah. I mean, if it
finds acceptance over this, yeah, it's
what exactly what they're trying to do
at the moment. They're protecting this
low volume node. We have we don't have
much excess up here. So, I think it's
possible if they build lots of shorts
into here and we find acceptance. It's
possible. I'm not going to join the long
now. All right. The long the cheap long
was down here. All right. Remember, we
were joining in discount under previous
days value and at previous day's value.
All right, we're now at fair value. I
don't want to join at fair value to get
up to an extreme. So, I'd rather wait,
let it go up there or let it fail here
for the trade back down inside if I'm
going to take another trade now.
[snorts]
Waiting for the pullback, Tim. Yeah. Um,
and if you're waiting for the pullback,
the best area is going to be here,
right? So, if they do
something like this, or maybe it's just
like this, or maybe they don't even do
that. Maybe they just do that. Or maybe
they do this. Right? This is the area
that buyers are going to need to defend,
right? Because this is the edge of value
based on yesterday, right? This is fair
value. This is the extreme high. This is
the extreme low based on value. We
bought discount.
[snorts]
Buyers now caught there. So that's more
excess up there. Let's see if they get
follow through. Buyers now caught above
45 into that previous day value.
That's better excess on this candle.
[snorts] Still adding. They're still
sellers are still adding above. All the
time they add above, I don't like it
because it's like it's attracting the
market to come and grab the liquidity
all the way up into 60s now.
That push definitely trapped some buyers
up there over 35s. It's all buy side
over 35s right now. So sellers will want
to defend 35s to see follow through.
If [snorts] they can't do that, then a
squeeze is on.
So here's 35. Check through the 35.
Squeeze is on now. So they've got a
chance to push this and create more
excess. So still waiting. I'm not
trading this long. Like I said, it very
well might come up here. I'll just wait.
So reclaim. Here's the two leg.
Here's the hold of low volume. We never
get down into this. They reclaim. They
trap at 35 and now they're looking for
the expansion up.
Okay, so lots of sellers came in here.
Sellers came in there from sort of 31
all the way down to 300. So it's all
those sellers stops getting run down.
We're very close. Someone just asked
about previous days value high. So we've
got one node here that we're about to
trade into. Once we get above that,
we've got previous day value high and
then previous day high. You just never
know. You just never know. But this is
not an area you want to be uh a new
money long in. That's for sure.
Big old squeeze. And maybe ES to those
900s is possible.
Big old squeeze out.
And if we come back under all these
levels we just put in, then we can get
very aggressive lower. But right now,
everything's bullish.
ing this excess here. Who's this buyer
that just came in? 54s and 62s.
Value area high now 46s on the day. See
if they rebid this or not.
Buyers will want to hold this shelf. If
we lose this shelf now, then we've now
got excess. Buyers will want to rebid
around here. Previous day point of
control. This shelf, current day point
control to complete it. If we lose this
at any point today though, we are
playing short now under here. if we lose
it because we have a low volume node
with now with lots of people trapped
for a rotation. Not playing it before
that point though. Need everyone
trapped. [snorts]
So these are the 46ers we just talked
about.
How did I know to stay out? I don't
know. Probably just too much experience.
Um just seen it too many times. Lack of
excess at the high is probably the main
reason. Just too much experience.
You want to see like remember when
you're try when you're going to trade
away from where price is, you need
people to be stuck. And if there's not
enough people stuck and you're trying to
trade away from it, then you don't have
enough people's pain to use.
So back to PC's these are the areas
where buyers now want to defend. If we
start losing all of this I will consider
the short
not before that because before that if
they hold all of this we will drive up
here. This is when people say well you
give two options. That's cuz what the
market gives. If we hold this it's going
to try and drive up to here. If we lose
this there's a very good chance of a
rotation back down to value and even
down here today. Right? You have to obey
what the market is telling you. Right?
There's always two options to anything.
There's always, always, always two
options in the market. There's never
just one option.
Any chance for last week's close? What
was where was last week's close as in
the gap fill 256
690?
It's asking a lot.
Any chance? Yeah, there is a chance.
Strong chance. Not today.
I don't think not not a strong chance
today. You you'd have you'd be asking it
for it to move outside all our range and
fill a huge gap when we've left value. I
mean it's possible but it's very
unlikely that we will see that today
during the week if we start bidding and
moving value up. It's possible.
I don't think it's likely but it's
possible.
[clears throat] All right. So starting
to see this back into these nodes again.
Watching this
back into the lower part of this volume
is gray shelf. Remember,
[snorts]
Alex, can you go over the morning trade
again? Uh, yeah. I mean, trying to
actually zoom in and make some money
here in case it leaves, but let's try.
Right. Where did we open? We opened
underneath value from yesterday.
We put in this W. We filled this gap.
All right. This is the cash players gap
where they're trying to bid. We don't
trade between here and here. We let
everyone else do that move. And then
once we reclaim it, we're over New York
open. We're inside value. We create a
flag and we're looking for a move back.
What? Into previous days value, which
means what? Everything up under here is
a failed auction. That means no
acceptance of price there. So what are
we going to do? If we failed an auction
under value, we're going to look for
price acceptance. What's the most
logical area where we found price
acceptance yesterday? point of control
because that's fair value. So we trade
into here, right? So I'm trading here,
adding here into here, and then I'm out
because now we've searched for fair
value. That's it. That's the trade.
We're now going to respect previous days
areas, right? Value area high, previous
day point of control, previous day value
area low, current day value area low.
Everything's matching up today and
yesterday pretty well. Okay, bottom side
of this node, right? If they don't
defend this and we see a break and and
retest and we stay heavy, I'll consider
the short. And not until that point, I'm
not considering it.
Nice.
When's the trend back bullish once we
higher low on a daily? Um, yeah. I mean,
honestly, we'd have to reclaim all that
old range.
we like we can come up to like six and
700s and still reject, right? So, we've
left value. Um, technically,
right, we haven't broken down under like
the 900s, which is a big pivot, but uh
I'd be surprised if we don't do that at
some point.
Yeah, I mean, we get very bullish. This
is a long way away, but we get very
bullish for a break and hold over
26,100. that that's when the market will
really start screaming upside because
we'll have a lot of trapped sellers
underneath. But we we just don't look
anything like that right now. We'd have
to get back above that what was it a
three or four week balance range that
we've talked about where we've rejected
up there. We rejected up there all
through November, all through December
and all through January. We cannot get a
base and hold over sort of 26,26100.
Okay. So, still they're holding here.
Still they defended this volume shelf
still. Then they want to try and move up
into here. We do have a node here from
yesterday. The big level is 420 and then
470. That's where they're trying to get
right now. That's why we don't front. We
don't guess price. We let price leave an
area or we don't touch it.
Nice DCT. And you've got a good name as
well. It's almost flow zone trader.
[snorts]
Vick's down sub 18s now.
You're just in just in just in time for
your trade setup. I' I've noticed there,
buddy. Tyson comes in. Justin, what's
up? S five minutes until we get the IB
trade for Justin.
[laughter]
Perfect timing. [sighs]
Exactly. Tyson's here. Let's go VWAP.
[laughter]
[snorts]
Well, hopefully they set a nice high IB.
If we can squeeze out in the next five
minutes,
right, we're going to squeeze out in the
next five minutes.
You set like an IB and you do something
like this, this is very possible or V
what might be here by then, but we'll
see. Let's just see. Let's Let's not
preempt it. Let's just see what we get.
Big seller just came in there. Huge
seller just came in there. How much size
was that? 271 lot on the market
at 60s.
Don't know why you would sell there.
There's nothing to sell against. But
hey, this looks to me like they want to
lift more and get into those 420s. And
you know, you don't know. Maybe maybe
they have the strength to go previous
day value high.
I'm going to delete this. I'm not too
bothered about that. Maybe I'll leave
it.
Okay.
Do I use CVD? Yeah, I do. But there's no
divergence right now. 5 minute CVD is
matching up very nicely to the drive
this morning.
I'm going to trade right through this.
Don't think there's a reason for this.
[snorts]
That node from yesterday can actually
remove that.
That spike there.
[snorts]
Still trying to be patient.
Maybe I closed my long position. I
closed my long position all the way down
here. I told you I closed long. I didn't
hold through any of this. I didn't add
anywhere up here. I'm not interested.
But I'd rather fade it back down inside
either underneath this or on a drive up
if we create more volume. But right now,
this structure is just a grindy bullish
move. I don't want to fade a grindy
bullish move. [snorts]
I closed my long position probably here
957 or something. I didn't even hold for
uh was it here? I can't remember.
I didn't I didn't even wait for the
final TP. I was a couple ticks short. I
knew it was a big area of consolidation.
That payout finally hit my account. So
stoked. Thank you, Alex. Nice work,
mate. Nice work.
Oh, bro. I'm in the 205 lot seller. Oh,
I got you. The guy from yesterday. Yeah.
Yeah, I see what you're talking about.
They're still trying to push it higher.
They want those 420s. They want those
420s. If you're still in this long, you
look good. I mean, I'm obviously not in
it, but if you're still in it long, you
look good. Uh 420 to 473 is the next
area. And I'll tell you what, the gap is
over 474. Let's just draw this gap in in
case we end up needing to use it.
There's our gap.
This is a big pivot. So, the gap starts
in this gray box and this is a big pivot
up here.
[snorts]
It's grindy higher
bit still trading low 1772 now it's
coming to some interesting areas at the
moment
probably needs to find a bid soon
otherwise there's a
no real pivot until that gap fill which
is A long long way away.
That old spike high 15 1750. That' be an
interesting level. 1750 and 17 sort of
7775ish.
Probably needs to find a bid there soon
on the VIX. Otherwise, it's got a big
old gap fill it can do.
Okay, you can see them stacking at 400.
IB now set, folks. Right, IB now set.
Purple line on your chart. It start
starting to print now. [snorts]
I'm not muted.
So, watching this up here, if any of you
are long, you want to be selling into
this push definitely into 420. Anywhere
near that, you should have sold most
already. And then 472 if you got very,
very, very lucky.
So, here's the 400
through here. They're looking for 420
and then 472.
There's 400. Almost there. Just one big
lift. We'll run through. There's sellers
stacking now. 420, 430, 450s.
So, starting to get a little bit spicy
here. Spicy and dicey.
And we can watch the IB. Remember,
there's no real strong volume until
340s. So, at some point, I think we're
likely to see a fade back down. Um, but
right now, we're still very bullish in
terms of structure. It's just squeezing
and squeezing and squeezing and
squeezing. There's trying someone trying
to bid here at 390 right now. It's a big
big lot. 180 lot at 390 right now.
Trying to bid. Trying to prop this
market up
to 400. They're looking for that 420
like we talked about.
390 never got filled. He held price held
in front of it. He's still there. 180
lot.
That's the big level right now because
he's putting a wall up there. If we
trade under him and let go of it, you
might see
that move under IB.
Little bit of volume at 470, but the
main level is still at 340s. It's coming
into this 90s again. Front ran it again.
Still not filled him. He's still just
sat there just under 90.
420s is the target. See if this 390
player moves up.
See how aggressive he wants to be. 900,
I assume, is probably going to be the
target for ES here.
[cough]
Maybe 85s for spiders.
Uh QQQ about to take out previous day
high. All right. So we're very very very
close on the Q's.
Previous day high on the Q's. Basically
just above the 15s. We're currently
trading at 1489s.
Very close to taking out previous day
high here on the Q's.
I'm talking about on the ETFs, right?
So, value now hit 420 now hit. The only
thing left now is previous day high if
it wants it.
That player at 390 is still down there.
He hasn't moved up. So, he's put a wall
in at 390 currently.
Vicks into that key level of 1750. So it
needs to hold here. If it doesn't hold
here, we probably go 1684s,
which will be a giant squeeze on the
market if we if we do that, I would say.
They completed a full rotation. I'm
kind of kicking myself. Maybe we could
have held a runner for an extra 100
points here. I don't know. But happy
with what I made. Okay, so only thing
left now really is to come up here into
70s if they have the juice. Otherwise,
the rotation now still probably back
down into here when they're ready for
it. And guess what? That buyer at 390
just left. Big seller just came in
there. 102 lot at the highs.
Here's the move back down towards these
400s. Got an imbalance below just above
400.
Buyer trying to step in here at 400.
410.
Still holding the 410. Still didn't feel
the buyer. So, everyone's getting front
run at the moment. Interestingly,
squeeze feels like it's very much on
here at the moment because they're not
even filling the passive buyers.
somewhat surprised there's not a bigger
flush down yet, but uh they've clearly
caught a lot of shorts today
because these moves are aggressive. When
they get going, they're being quite
aggressive. So, still 407 bid,
430 seller. Have we got liquidity added
above? Yeah, 450 now. Is there anything
above that? 49500 is now on the book up
there. Gez,
adamant on squeezing this now. All
right, 420 bid just came in. 180 lot. So
he's moved up from 390 to 420 now. So he
has moved up on the bid. He's trying to
bid previous day value area high now.
Previous day high now been taken on QQQ.
It's about to be taken on SPY. The
squeeze is on. They're just going to
keep squeezing and squeezing and
squeezing and squeezing here. They are
not even coming down for the passive
buyers. This is very very aggressive. Be
careful. These are the type of markets
when big moves come very very quickly.
Both sides
been a one directional tape here this
morning.
900 now hit ES psychological number.
Like the tape's just gone quiet. It's
crazy. And now it's just a 450 and 420
bid. Like where's the rest of the market
gone? Here they come starting to come
back in.
Very aggressive buying still. So
aggressive. There's 450. So aggressive.
SPY
trying to take out its previous day high
by the looks of it,
which is basically the uh the 685 level.
Are they going to come fill this guy at
20?
So there's 172 lot at 420
value area on the high on the day now
moved up to that sort of 425
previous day value area high. So
everything's around here now. Buyers
will want to hold above this now
to squeeze this out. failure to hold
this. That's possible. We've got no real
structure from here, right? It's
straight up. This is a straight squeeze.
Straight up right now.
Nvidia and Tesla leading the charge.
Tesla 2.06% up. Nvidia 1.79% up. leading
the charge here on the comeback. AMD 8%
up. Holy smokes.
Starting to build out a little bit of
volume up here. I'm still wouldn't trust
that yet, but we are starting to build
out a little bit of a shelf here. You
can see it's early days for it, but
we're starting to build out a little bit
of a shelf.
700 lot now up at 465. Okay, they're
coming to try and get this guy at 420 to
see if he's going to fill. Let's see if
he's legit. He did move up to 420, so I
am going to assume he wants to be
filled.
Front run him again.
>> [snorts]
>> Just waiting here.
This little shelf and these 420s are
key. This little shelf here and then the
420s, previous day value area high,
current day value area high. That kind
of level flow zones. That's really key.
We're still holding everything. 420 just
moved up to 435. He's desperate to get
filled this buyer.
He's he's not being filled. I don't
understand. He's not been filled once
today. Why are they front running him?
Just fill him. Let's see if he's legit.
Instead of coming in and then [\h__\h]
getting scared.
So, he's moved from 390 to 420 to 435
and never once been filled.
Right next to him. Still not filling
him. Still front running.
Still front running. Come on market
filled finally.
All right. So let's see if he reads now.
200 lot filled there in these 35s.
So we now know his position. He just
came flying in at 35s
propping the bid.
So we're bullish all the time. We're
over 35s right now. Very bullish over
35s.
>> [snorts]
>> for a resqueeze. So, I'm not saying you
should buy this. Definitely don't buy
it. It's just a squeeze. But that is the
area where he's trying to prop the
market up, which means we the other side
of it. We had a big seller there at 35s,
right? So, we know that's a pain point
now.
Still very bullish here.
715 contracts up at 65. They are just
trying to get price up there right now.
Lifting and lifting and lifting and
lifting. Here you go. They're trying to
go again.
Spy still not taking out the 685. So,
I'm still waiting here patiently. There
is absolutely nothing to do. This is a
giant squeeze. The last thing you want
to do is try and front run against a
squeeze. Not once have we broken down
under a key level. Not once today yet.
We are holding every single key level.
The gap starts here at 76. Look at this.
This uh seller just moved from 65 to 75.
He's trying to lift it. They are
desperate to lift this up. Lifting and
lifting and lifting and lifting.
Spy still not taking out 685. So, still
trying to take out 685. Q's still trying
to come to this 50-day, but already
above previous day high now on the Q.
We're very very close on the uh ENQ.
Still patient
waiting to see like a big transaction of
like buyers caught and we're just not
seeing that yet.
Remember, 35 is the level.
35 and then 20, right? 35s and 20s.
Those are the levels we're thinking
about out loud in our heads. 35 is where
the buyer came in and absorbed the tape.
It's where a big seller came in trying
to force him out. 20s is our sort of
overunder for value
at this level right here.
trying to fill the Monday gap. I don't
think we've filled the gap because we'd
have to go all the way up the towards
700, but
we're trying to get into the start of
the gap, which is right here,
start of this gray box. We're trying to
get into that by the looks of it.
I will fade this market when it is done,
but it's not done yet.
starting to see
VIX try and find a bit of a bid around
the 1750s area we talked about. It's
trying
75 yet. Yeah, they're at 500 now.
Still waiting here. Still just strong
trend up. You don't want to fade. A
strong trend up. That flow zones are
bullish. We are into a level of supply.
We are near the gap, but we're still
trending up. We haven't caught buyers.
We haven't left volume, right? Still
just every dip into volume's holding.
Every dip into volume's holding. They've
got a key level to try and get get into
here. You can see 75's above.
They're right above previous day high.
There's a 700 lot. SP
almost into 85. I'm going to assume
that's a massive, massive, massive gamma
level as well.
Okay, 75 just lifted to 80. So, he just
keeps lifting and lifting and lifting
and lifting. So, he's moved higher. He's
trying to get filled at 80 now. He
thinks they can squeeze through and fill
him at 80.
There's going to be a big transaction
happen around here soon if these guys
now there's a thousand lot between 75
and 80. There will be a massive
transaction happening around here soon
if these guys are real
because you're going to need market
buyers to hit the bid here to fill these
guys and the thousand lot is not a joke.
So let's see if they can do it.
Here they go. One's just left the tape.
So he's just left 350 lot. So the 700
lot was a spoofer he just left. Here's
the move to 75. Previous day high now
taken into the edge of this gap
transaction here. Didn't fill either of
them. So, they were both spoofing.
Surprise, surprise.
ES uh sorry, spy tapping 85.
Small rejection there at 85. Watching
this now. If there's a big transaction
here and buyers get caught, not until
then. But if there is and buyers get
caught, I'm interested. It's into a big
level. But not until then. If they keep
squeezing, you've just got to let them
keep squeezing.
Don't like the height of that auction,
man.
Can't help looking at this thinking,
wow,
could have got another 150 points out of
this on a runner, Alex. Lesson learned.
>> When you think like 120 points is a good
trade and then could have had 300 points
almost.
Okay, they're st they're stacking 75s
75s and 80s.
VIX now losing 1750. So you want to be
careful here.
Building out some nasty looking uh
volume up there.
Not too clean.
And they've just added liquidity now up
at 500.
Some buyers got caught on that last push
a little bit. We've not traded back down
away from them. Delta is still very
strong.
Someone just pulled his bid at 60s.
There's not much for bid down here now.
Where's the next big bed? There isn't.
There isn't much.
276 lot now added at 480s above.
I'm interested in the fade underneath
all of this if we if we drift down under
there. Other than that, I'm not
interested in it. They're going to keep
searching for 480s. I tell you what, I'm
going to use the bathroom while these
guys piss about. Be right back.
Okay, let's have a look. Still no
change.
Still no change.
So, I'm certainly not going to get long
up here.
I will consider a rotation if we get
stuck underneath these. Certainly under
this as well. So, I'll be careful about
this. But I'll consider that. But we're
into the gap now. 500 above.
But I want to see us leave. Maybe if we
create a shelf here, it could be useful
as well. I want to see us at least leave
some volume trapped. I'm not going to
play short against what is a very strong
squeezy trend. Remember, we were long
from here. Sold my position there.
Kicking myself now cuz we've got a
second leg higher.
And now just need to wait. Big buyer
here. 200 lot. This is huge delta up
into 80. Big buyer.
They're adding more at 490. They're just
constantly trying to add liquidity
higher to make it search for it at the
moment.
This is starting to be a little bit
insane here. Let me just
have a look.
What are we seeing here? He's
starting to get into some congestion.
Just check the chips quickly.
Break out.
Yeah, big pivot.
Once those slow down and they see a
pullback and it looks like it's trying
to come in AMD at the moment, we might
see this market
have that pullback leg.
Oh,
okay. Back into volume shelf. Remember,
we've held volume every single time
today. We've come into volume, we've
held it. So, if we lose this, maybe a
drift down further. I am watching this
now to see if it gets aggressive.
Holding that low volume node for now. I
want to see us trade like well under
that.
Tempted to try and feather in here, but
still holding that low volume now.
So semi very very very strong.
Definitely buyers caught at 480. I want
that to be clear.
If we let them out, we're risk queens
again though.
Get a MA chart up here because it's so
this is becoming uh so dependent what's
going on outside of this.
Yeah, Nvidia
through that pivot into its gap. Very
dangerous here. If Nvidia starts going,
it can cause like another rally higher.
Oracle's just not moving.
AVGO isn't. It's AMD, AMU, and Nvidia.
AMD is having its first five minute
pullback.
Nvidia coming into it 5day above. Yeah,
five day above.
Yeah, resqueeze now because we're back
above those 80s. So all the time above
80s. Look, every dip into volume, we
just talked about that. Every dip into
volume's held. Everything is becoming a
buyers market now. Every dip of every
volume node, even if it's small, is
holding, is holding, is holding. You
can't fade this. You need to see it
start coming around the other side if
you're desperate for a fade on it. Um,
why am I not buying? Because we bought
discount this morning down here.
I didn't like that buy off fair value. I
didn't think we'd complete the rotation.
It's obviously I'm wrong because we have
completed it and then we're now printing
upside. But we're also getting into
territory where we can start breaking
out here. Want to be very careful
because we're coming into that gap. Uh
next pivot really through this gap
is all the way at 590s this white line.
So want to be careful if they are
adamant on rebid, rebid, rebid.
So back to volume again. I will consider
if we start leaving volume trapped, I
will consider a fade especially if we
get underneath value and we get
underneath
um the flow zones. Right.
How do you get volume to anchor to the
New York open? Use an anchored volume
profile.
Okay, back into this volume. Are we
going to start to leave this now?
It's perking my interest here, folks. It
is definitely perking my interest here.
Just want to see sellers come through
strong here. Where are these bids?
Big buyer just came back in at 65.
Trying to prop it up. This market's
moving quick. Hang on. 1435s. Okay, so
still the same level. 35 is the big big
level. Should
trade down to that now.
Leave this volume. We should trade down
to it now. Can't keep rebidding on these
low volume nodes. I can't trade it
otherwise. Still rebidding low volume
to get under this volume and then I'm
interested and I'll be watching very
carefully into 35 in case it holds. So,
I'm very interested in the short here.
Very, very close to like entering here.
Just waiting to see someone get caught
on the uh footprint or
book map here.
Big seller came in here at 65. We need
to trade under 65 for me to be
interested. They're trying. They're
trying. They're trying. Can't see
absorption here. They're trying to
absorb now 65. Buyers just come back in.
So, I'm still waiting here.
Vick's trying to find a bit of a bid.
Last push failed. We got to get back
under 65, though. They're just rebidding
65. If we trade under 65, I'm interested
for a flush down to 35s.
Relentless.
Come on, Mark.
You going to give me another trade today
or not? No. Rebid 30 65 again. Jesus
Christ, these guys are [\h__\h] adamant.
Where do they want? They want 500. Like,
where where the [\h__\h] are you trying to
take it right now?
It's the next pivot.
I think this will be a look above and
below. I cannot imagine them getting
this up to 600 today. But
what are we going to do? A 10% AMD day.
Seriously,
if buyers are stuck at 80 and above,
over that will be a resqueeze. There is
a little shelf at 84 and it's tiny.
I'm waiting for an entry for us to
leave. If we leave 65, I'll look for a
short. Not until then.
Buy the dip there. Yeah, I mean, we did
buy the dip this morning. Should have
held it longer, though. I just didn't
think we'd come all the way back up
here, but hey, it's all right. Okay,
here we go. Still watching these 65s.
There's still a guy trying to protect
65. If we start flushing under that, I'm
going to join short for a move down to
35. If we stay heavy under 35 and under
20, I'm going to look for a full
rotation back down to IB. If we stay
heavy in there, we'll see if we can get
a full rotation all the way back down to
here if they really want to do it. But
watching these areas as cover points
right now. I'm not in yet. Waiting for
this market to let go of 65s.
We have a constant bid here still.
Now they're bidding 70s. [\h__\h] hell.
They're stacking nonstop,
mate. I haven't seen it like this for a
while. It goes quiet, quiet, quiet,
quiet, quiet, and then they step on. I
have not seen it like this for a while.
It's definitely feels like a shift in
tone today.
So, they're trying to rebid 70. 65 is
still my level, but they're now trying
to rebid 70s. They're trying to hold it
a little bit higher.
Big volume being built out here. You can
see
here's the test of 65 coming. Maybe,
maybe, maybe. There's a seller. Big
seller just came in at 75s, 180 lot.
Maybe, maybe if he doesn't spoof and be
a Oh, he's spoofed. What a knob. What an
absolute knob.
Okay, 65. Still a level.
Here we go.
65 test. still absorbing it.
They've stacked 65 down to 50s now. I'm
just looking for that 65 break
and not the four.
They hold this, they can resqueeze. Look
how much volume they're building here.
We've got to get under 65, otherwise we
can't touch it.
Patience.
Just got to be patient. Cannot frontr
run it. Cannot guess. Cannot hope. Here
we go. 68. Still waiting for 65s.
Point of control. Now shifted up here,
which is great. At 70. I want to leave
that and trade lower now. Come on.
Come on, stop [snorts] front running
this guy. Here we go. 65s. Right. What
you got, market? Are we going to see
follow through? Are you going to rebid?
He's still not even filled this guy.
He's stacking in front now.
Here we go. 64s, 66. Still not filled
this guy here.
Come on. Here's the delta. It's standing
out like a sore thumb. They're still
protecting it. Come on. You've got to
trade under this and leave it.
Head on brick wall.
65 65 65 any 67s. They can't trade
through the 6. There's only a 56 lot
there and they just can't even trade
through him. Once he goes, there's
probably a flush, which is what I'm
waiting for. Here we go. Testing him.
Still not filled him. How are you not
filling this guy and flushing through
him? Insane.
Come on.
Right on his pivot here. Filled. Let's
see how we react now. Instantly back
inside.
No follow through downside yet. Can't
trade it yet. All we did was fill him
and stack. We need to trade away from
this level. Point of control has now
moved to 70s though, which is good. If
we trade under this now, if we trade
under 65s, stay heavy versus 70s. Heavy
versus 65. There is a flush move down to
35s. We've got to trade away from this
level. We cannot keep absorbing here
over and over again. I need to see
sellers step on the gas. Seriously,
guys, this is absolutely pathetic from
you guys. I really want to short here,
but you're making it impossible for me
to enter
65s again.
Edge of the shelf again.
Seeing strong buying
around this area still. They're still
absorbing these sellers. I just want
this flush. Come on. It's a 30 point
flush. I'm really not asking for much
here. Here we go.
50s. Can we get 50s? Can we get 50s? Let
me see follow through. 35s is the level
that I want to trade down to. If I can
get my first TP down there. Come on.
Come on. I've been so patient for this.
Come on.
There's 50s. Here we go, folks. Here's
50s. 50. Check here. We want to trade
through this to 35s now.
Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come
on. Here we go, folks. Here we go,
folks.
Here we go, folks.
Want
to see them resell this.
Don't let it reclaim. Do not let this
reclaim. 70s.
Oh, you bastards.
Gray box to gray box. I took a little
piece there just in case. But
straight senses out. Not touching this.
They had the chance to do it there. They
had the chance to do it there. They're
absorbing still.
Maybe they resell it now, but they're
they're being tricky buggers. So, we're
doing rotation gray box to gray box,
gray box to gray box. This is why we
have it highlighted. I was looking for a
bit deeper in this the other side of it.
35s. I did pay myself some along the
way, but didn't make too much. And the
real price acceptance would be down
here. If we keep building here,
there is a pivot up here that you can
come for.
So, there you go. Try. I tried folks. I
tried. Didn't get much out of it. No
joy.
Still 80s is a level where we have delta
trapped.
Uh buy side
right here. This level here is massive.
Right. I'm trying to trade down to here.
So this is where buyers are stuck 80s
and above and the seller is stuck at 35.
So, I was trying to trade this 65 break.
You can see a 65 break. I'm trying to
trade it down into this pivot here.
That's what I was trying to do in this
low volume node. Didn't quite make it.
Was a little bit short, but you can see
the thesis what I'm looking for.
[snorts]
80 were just rejected there again.
You going to do it now? You going to do
it second attempt?
Don't like the look of it though.
Still short. It might It might still
work out. I'm We'll consider a read. Um
they stay heavy.
Got to stay heavy though. The thing is
we got to be very careful. We We're are
above initial balance. We're above
value, right? We're going to we've moved
point of control and value up. We must
stay heavy here. This is technic
technically counter trend on the day.
Not on the high time frame, but on the
day we're technically counter trend. If
they start absorbing here,
you just need to be aware of this. Let
me uh they're going to do it now, aren't
they? [\h__\h] sake. I'm out.
Get a re-entry here or not
re-entry.
Let me show you what I'm talking about.
You need to be aware of this on the
hourly, right? If they hold this pivot,
right? If they're very very strong today
and they hold above this, this rotation
can happen. Um the better short comes
when they let go of this. All right? So
if this what does that mean? That means
this would be a look above and fail
and this can happen back down. Right? So
at the moment we've got one of these.
This is a straight squeeze out. There's
been no pullback. We're looking for that
pullback. So we can fade that pullback.
We don't know how far that pullback
comes. It might be that that pullback
you're going to get 35s maybe only comes
to here. It might be that it comes all
the way down to here. So that's why
we're trying to position for it.
35s and 20 still big level. 35s and 20.
You might get it.
You might get it here. This level here
and this level here underneath
underneath this and this. There's
potential for a bigger fade.
This we lack structure in here. So it's
why this is a big level because if we do
this, we can fill some of this structure
in.
Here we go. So 50s.
Can you get those 35s and below?
They're
[snorts]
stacking 50s down to 30s at the moment.
Be nice if you filled some of that for
those of you who are still short so you
could get some profits. And just be
careful between these two gray boxes,
please.
It
video
[sighs and gasps]
still going. Nvidia might go to 84s.
5day 83 58 50day 84s. Nvidia's still
squeezing, folks. That thing has been a
rocket ship today
and it's into its gap.
Um, let me do from EDC
here.
It's right into its golden zone at the
moment. All the way up to 8436 is
just depends.
depends what they want to do with it.
What was the chip news today? Did I miss
something? Maybe some of you can tell me
what was the big chip news.
I see sellers trapped at 450. Um,
no, not really.
470 to 460 is where sellers have come
in.
And they're going to go again. Wow. Just
every dip holding. Incredible. Well,
just a day not to fade. Just a day to
leave it.
There we go. 500's coming up then.
Mental. This is quite the move today, I
will tell you. If you want to have a
look at five minute, this is pretty
steep. This is pretty pretty impressive.
It's a pretty impressive move from these
folks today. I'm I am impressed. I am
impressed. We've now broken above
previous day high. We've gone from under
previous day low with no acceptance to
above previous day high. Like nothing
happened. Like yesterday meant nothing.
That's what's really impressive. All
right. Buyers now will want to control
above 480. Remember that was the level
that buyers were stuck. If they stay
above 480, they can keep squeezing.
Who knows? We're only in a morning
session. Who knows what hits this
afternoon.
So 480 is the level for buyers to try
and control.
I'm impressed. Very impressed. AMD 850%
up.
Wow. All right. Here's the 80s check.
Point of control now back down at 70s.
Buyers still trying to absorb here
around these 80s and 70s.
ES not making new higher there. So
divergence like tech been very strong
today. 1.40% up. Now the mag as a whole
1.34% up. Nvidia and Tesla and Google
doing the work. They're the ones doing
the work.
Okay, back to PC. Was this a look above
and fail? We can think about the same
move potentially if we leave. If we
leave volume
still not filled that 500, that guy at
500.
So, same levels as earlier, 65s.
And we're going to start to leave this
and drive lower.
Small piece on here now. Not added
sizing just in case there's a retest,
but small piece on.
Let's see if we can get to 35s and
below.
That was a failed breakout. Come on
market, be kind to me. Been very patient
with you today, market. You are really
testing me
back to these 50s. Want to see flush
down to 35s, please.
Don't want to see you pop up and fill
the imbalance. Just flush down. Don't
want to retest of 70s. Don't want any of
that. I just want to see it stay heavy
now.
Don't retest 70s. Please stop [\h__\h]
around.
Just going to test my patience.
Okay, let's see. I was really hoping we
just flush straight through here.
Retesting point of control. Couldn't get
through it. Still okay. Please come to
35's market for fudge sake.
Oh my god. Give it up. Give it up into
70s.
Need them to stay heavy here. I don't
really want to sit in this back to 76s.
I need them to reject point of control
up here. Oh, it's relentless, man. It's
[\h__\h] relentless.
Don't like it. The aggression. Where's
this buy stuck? This size 172 187.
What's this pivot here? 75 to 80. I
don't know, man.
I don't know about this. I do not know
about this right now.
Might have been a bit early here, folks.
This might be an error.
We will see.
Still holding that shelf, which is good.
We just got to get under 35.
Come on.
Trying so hard to be patient. Come on.
Very nearly took my stop there.
There's just a aggressive rebid. Wild.
Come on.
We need these buyers to be trapped. We
got to move aggressively lower. I'm
getting impatient. Come on.
Very impatient at this point.
Yeah, exactly, Peter. It's where my
head's at. Are we just going to go
sideways?
They don't have The problem is they
don't have to dump it. If they're not
going to leave, if they're not going to
aggressively leave away, then we're
going to bid up. I'm trying to tell
myself, I have to remember, we're over
value. We're over IB. Trend has been up.
We're in a squeeze. I'm trying to play
from here to here to here to here, but
it's just not giving it to me. And if it
doesn't give it to me, I have to respect
it. So, I'm trying to sit in this with a
stop here to protect it, but it's it's
just not behaving right now. AMD still
[\h__\h] going, man. Oh my god.
They're trying to retest the high again.
Is Nvidia right into that 5day on
Nvidia. We're close. It feels close to a
top here, but if they resqueeze it,
Nvidia can it's going to go 848450 and
this thing's going to [\h__\h] fly again.
[snorts]
I don't think this has got anything to
do with Trump's talk. I'm going to be
honest with you. It's got absolutely
nothing to do with his talk. I don't
think anyone pays much attention to him
now. [snorts]
Okay, come on. Still protecting it.
Well, come on. Here we go. 50s. Let's go
through 50s and go 35. Look at all the
stacks here. 50, 45, 40, 35, 30. All
stacking up bid side.
I want to try and get a piece out
towards the 35s if I can. Just looking
for one more flush. There's so many bids
here. I'm hoping that we go and fill
some of them.
Come on. Come on. There's so many of you
here. Come and get filled.
Nice. Need to break this little pivot
down here. [\h__\h] me. They front run it
again.
That gray box is tough, man. They are
front running it hard. Here
we go. Come on. Here we go. Come on.
They're all there to be taken. Just come
down so I can at least move my stop.
Oh,
come on.
Going to go insane.
It's not that hard to do 20 point flush,
guys. All right, I give up. I [\h__\h]
give up.
I'm going to show you what I'm looking
at. But Mm. It is absolutely ludicrous.
We've got all these guys stacked and
they are front running it every time and
rebidding up and rebidding up. All I
want to do is fill these participants
and get a cover out into here and it's
just not flipping happening. It is not
happening.
So, I have to respect what I'm seeing.
I have to respect what I'm seeing. We're
just going to keep getting stuck between
these gray boxes.
[sighs]
Edging us like crazy. I love it.
[laughter] It's a good way to put it. It
feels close. Nvidia is starting to put a
five minute sell bar in.
It feels close. Come on.
Still holding the edge of this gray box.
Still can't get down to 35s.
I'm still stressing over this.
Yes. Do it. Do it. You mother clucker.
10 more points. Do it.
Oh my god. Come.
Oh my days.
Has 20 points ever been so hard in all
my life? I don't think so.
Need to be very careful here, folks. I'm
watching the hourly. You need to be very
careful. If it starts holding here into
sort of 420s and even above this, this
can be a 1 hour flag that then breaks
higher. You need to be very very very
careful here.
I've been here 40 minutes now going
sideways.
It's not been a [\h__\h] I mean, we made
really good money today. I'm I'm like,
look, we for those joining late, we were
long here today and here for this move
into here. I sold that cuz I thought
we'd come back for a retest of this and
then I could think about that if I
really wanted, but we just went straight
squeeze. And so now I got stuck waiting
to try and fade this back in. Um, it
doesn't have to do it. It really does
not have to do it. So, this why I keep
telling myself, if it doesn't want to do
it, it doesn't want to do it. You can't
push away. Nvidia with a stronger sell
here now back down to the 83s. It's into
a 5m minutee pivot here though.
There you go.
[sighs]
AMD about to break out, folks. I'm
telling you, AMD's right at its highs.
Just resqueezed.
We are rejecting point of control,
though, which is a start. I guess it's
it's something, right? It's something
is better than nothing.
The problem is if is is is this an
hourly hold? This is the like the big
question I've got right now versus
current uh developing profile 420. So
that's I'm going to have to be very
careful. 435 and 420. I'm still in this
Yeah, I mean it's all the semis. It's
it's all the semis Cara for sure
other than ABGO.
We have a look at the breadth. Let me
get fizers up.
Yeah, I mean big winners today. Google
3%, Nvidia 3%, Tesla 2.2, to AMD, MU,
ADI, TXN, INTC, QCOM, empower, Mchip,
um ACN, Eli, Lily, like broader market's
doing okay. Uh insuranceances are down
today. Consumer defense is down.
Entertainment uh down off that Netflix
earning that utilities down to flat.
Stop loss the other side of this node
just above here. This node I'm using
this node to protect me. Right. So I'm
assuming
right buyers are I know buyers are stuck
over 80.
Right. We talked about that
buyers are stuck over 80. I'm using this
to sell into to try and trade down. And
I'm going to use the other side of this
node as my protection.
[clears throat]
All right, we're almost there. We're
almost there to TP1.
Come on, mother clucker.
Previous day high down here is well,
previous day value high 20. So, we're
we're almost there.
35s is the big delta I'm looking at. All
right, 35s is the big delta. I want to
see us trade 35s. And if we trade under
35s into 20s, I feel pretty good about
stuff.
We watch ES into IB high as well. Very,
very important. Nvidia starting to
really pull back, which is good. It's
helping us out a little bit
into this gray box. Be careful if this
holds, folks. Like you can see the
rotation, right? No acceptance over
here. Rotations between here. All right.
Just be careful if this holds and we
build out lots of liquidity. You need to
be careful with this hourly move.
We just went over that hourly move
right here.
I be careful
of this hourly move if they're
absolutely adamant and doing it.
Today just might not be the day. It just
might not be the day.
There's the squeeze and I'm out.
Taken out there on the stop. Maybe I
could have used 80s protection, but
there we go. I tried, folks. I mean, we
kept I kept it green, but it's just
it's pretty annoying. [laughter]
Pretty annoying.
I tried. Right. How are we doing for
lights? Like to do some giveaway. I'm
sorry about today, folk. Well, I mean I
am and I'm not. I mean, we made 100 and
plus points out of the longs, but it
could have been a 300 pointer. I'm bit
gutted about that.
Bit gutted about that. I would have
loved to have got you guys. You
better not screw me over here. Market.
All right. How many of you are watching
right now? 625 of you watching.
340 likes. Let's get up to 450 likes
here, folks. Please.
450 likes, we do some giveaways. While
you do that, I'm just going to grab a
quick bite. You write that
Oh, it's going to do it while it's
taking me out. Well, isn't that just
Brilliant.
[sighs]
Well, this is trading, folks. This is
what happens. Here's 35. [laughter]
Here's your 35 test.
I tried. I tried. I tried. I tried. Oh
god. It's very funny.
That's very funny. Hopefully you guys
didn't stop out where I did. You might
get a flush now. They're going to stay
heavy here. Oh my god.
Dear. Oh dear. Um, I sort my dog out.
I'll be right back. W's in chat if you
got this. Uh, you can hold runners now.
If you get acceptance under 20, all
right, just understand it's so thin
here, folks. Oh my god. This what I was
position. All right, cover some into
here. If you get acceptance under here,
all right, we can travel all the way
back down. All right, so if you're short
from any of these, all right, trim some
into here. And if you get a flush
moment, we might find it all the way
down. All right, you you might be
absolutely laughing. And um well, I just
hope it works for you. But make sure
you're covering some here. This is the
edge. Remember, we talked about the edge
of where the hourly might want to stop.
You need to be very, very aware that if
we're going to find bid support here,
they can rebid. But if they lose this,
this trade here in this low volume can
happen.
Hopefully this has helped you guys at
least. At least hopefully I've helped
you even if I can't get paid out of it
properly. Right, let me get my food and
come back.
Lots of you getting it. Nice work,
folks.
Lots of you getting it. You can sit in
this now. Sit in this. As long as you
paid yourself, hold a runner here. Um,
if they start letting go of this, it
will be fantastic. We really lack
structure in here. Okay, we lack
structure in here. might very well be
that it comes and fills all of this in.
All right, it very well might do that,
which is why I was trying to position
for it. We were so patient. I mean, we
were so patient waiting for the peak,
waiting for the trapped uh uh
participants over 80s. We had like one
more push in, I stopped out and sort of
gave up on it then. Probably shouldn't
have given up on it then. That was
probably the next chance. And now you've
got this cell on the flow zone trying to
rotate. So watch initial balance es into
IB now. So, you want to be aware this
area here is key.
Um, just to manage your position here.
Really nice trade. Really nice trade.
Nice guys. Nice work.
Nice work.
As long as you're paying yourself, you
look good. You look good. Remember,
you're comfortably in the money now. I
cannot believe that stopped me out. That
is my fault. I probably should have put
my stop at 80. I was short in here.
TP1 was
such a shame. TP1 was 35.
TP2 somewhere down into here. And TP3
down here.
You might get 100 plus point banger
here, guys. It's very, very possible.
nice everyone. Now, I'm really happy.
I'm happy you guys all got it.
I just lit my wounds a little bit, but
it's okay.
All right. Node here
starting to let go potentially.
So, we can mark this out. It's like a
little bump in the road. It's not a big
one. Little bump in the road here is
important for follow through.
Well, there's 50 60 70 points for you
already.
Oh, I'm going to like tell you right
now, the amount of tilt I currently feel
is huge.
Huge part. Huge tilt right now. Shows
I'm human.
[snorts]
Shows I'm human.
All right. IB here.
Big level here. Initial balance.
I know, Tyson.
[\h__\h] it.
It happens. It's tw It's two days in a
row is why I'm annoyed if I'm honest.
Very similar setup to yesterday.
I left yesterday. It happened after
stream, didn't it? Yesterday. Very
similar setup.
Same kind of area.
I had a go at it. Here, covered. Here,
covered.
here covered and then I left stream and
then the moment I took Luna for a walk.
There we go.
[laughter]
[snorts] I know now I have to be very
careful for the rest of the week now cuz
these are like big tilt factors for me
when I have like a few in a row like
this. Here you go guys. Here you go.
You're going to hit TP. [\h__\h] me.
Pardon my French everyone. Congrats
everyone. All right. You must pay
yourself here, please. You absolutely
must pay yourself. Your previous day
point control VW up in a high volume
node. There you go.
There you go.
You saw me walking my dog in Plyier. You
probably did, Brandon. I was what
yesterday? I was out walking my dog for
about 3 hours yesterday.
Well, congrats everyone. Um,
that is a phenomenal trade.
What a shame.
Nice work.
And it's respecting previous days point
of control really well here. So, really,
really nice trade. You never know like
if you get I wouldn't I wouldn't expect
it, but if you got very lucky, you'd get
this move here. Now,
this is still a squeeze, right? So,
we're just repricing that squeeze, but
I'd be out most of my position here.
This is very similar. It's like the
reverse of the first long we took this
morning. Remember the long we took from
here from one side to here. And now
we're taking a short from here to here.
So, we're getting the meat of the move,
the meat of the move. But you never
know, they might collapse the whole
thing. It's very possible.
Single Prince Field. Yeah, quite right.
Rick
Jonathan got it. Nice. Alex, you're the
best brother. Just made a lot of people
a lot of easy money. Hopefully.
Hopefully.
That's my job, right? That's why I'm
here.
Where's that guy earlier? It says I
don't tell you where to enter or
anything. [\h__\h] me. I like we were
drawing this out for the best part of an
hour.
Must be his first time on stream.
Big Dude Canary. Nice. Is Trump done? I
don't know. I'm not even paying
attention to him anymore. I've lost like
lost so much interest in him.
I'm not blowing my trumpet,
but there will not be many guys on a
free stream giving you this.
And what was the other one?
Where's my long
and this today? They just won't
They weren't.
They would have got chopped most people
got chopped up in all the mess.
Those are this the trades off stream
today. Two good trades. Granted, I
actually didn't get this one. Well, I
tried three times. Made some money on
it, but the moment I went and made made
my breakfast, obviously then it does it.
So, just keep showing up, man. Yo, bro,
I recently discovered you. I got to say,
I love the way you trade. It's very
similar to my system. Good to have
validation of my own system. I trade
strictly on volume. Volume is king. Hey,
I agree. Volume is king, baby.
All right. So, I want to do a giveaway,
but I want to help you guys manage this
position. So, I would be out at least
80% of this at this point. At least 80%.
You never know. You might get like
really deep here. It's trying. It's
trying. So, if you can get 20% for you
to go and do damage down here into sort
of 240s, 260s,
that will add some decent wedge to your
uh day.
So, next target
you guys is kind of down here. Well, I'd
respect this value area low on the day.
Let me just check that marks out. Yeah,
it is. We just tapped it 409 309, right?
Value area low.
I know you're like, it's not value area
low. Um, on my M1 on Ninja Trader, it
is. Otherwise,
we're very, very close, but I'll show
you so you can see it.
Right.
Valo just got tagged for the day. All
right. So, they're trying to rebid that.
So, I'd be out a lot of my position.
Job done.
You've made your money. Anything beyond
this is a bonus.
People need to I missed that.
People need to know what they're doing.
I started listening last Thursday. I
watched your videos over the weekend.
I'm up 6K today, 3K yesterday. Thank
you. Nice work, man.
Got losing early, but still in profit
and stop too tight. Thanks always. Wait,
no worries. 4K on those 100 pointers.
Thanks, Alex. we're on the same page.
Nice Wrath. Do you think we can long
this after this movement? I mean,
you got to remember the protrend is
down.
Um, we're inside current weekly value.
Like, there might be there's it's
possible there's like relief, right,
which is sold into. It's also possible
that they're just like they're done with
it. This was a straight squeeze. Do you
remember I said like this is not it's
not a healthy market. Um, I haven't seen
a market like this for a while. This
wasn't too bad, but from this point on,
it was just non-stop bid. It was
non-stop bid. And we weren't feeling
like there was a passive buyer trying to
walk up. We were not filling him. It was
aggressive
buying. Um, and we can see that
in the CBD. Look. Uh, where are you
guys? We can see it right here. All
right. Move this up for you. This is a
very aggressive bid. All right. This is
aggressive market participant. slamming
in. Once we broke this level here,
right, then we got the breakdown and you
can see everyone who was aggressively
bidding it is now caught and we're in
pain cave for them. So, this is why we
wanted to trade down again today because
once we get to an extreme,
then we can see stuff like this happen
because we go back to protrend squeeze
is over. We're underneath these pivots
now. VWOP's your next target here. This
is your next target and then previous
day value area low. This can end up
being
just a ginormous trade for you.
226 point trade honestly.
Is that right? Yeah.
Into VWAP it' be almost 200. So 200
point banger.
Alex, thank you for being one of the
most knowledgeable technical traders
I've seen. I just passed my Apex
challenge thanks to you. You're the best
without a doubt. Cheers. Hey, thanks
Rob. Very kind of you. Green on all
accounts. Nice work, everyone. I'll be
buying the flow zone course with the
first payout. I'm looking forward for an
orderflow expert to learn from. Nice.
What was that chart you showed with the
levels that look like CBD and some other
levels? I just see the VP on the current
chart. Uh this one it's just a five
minute chart. Uh this one here you mean
it's just a five minute chart. This is
where my uh what's it called? Trend
trend friend pro flow zone trend friend
pro. This is just CVD down here. It's
just a five minute chart. That's all it
is.
Yeah. New York VWAP didn't hold. So look
they back tested it three times.
Failed 24-hour VWAP. Previous day value
area low. Next.
What a trade. What a trade, folks. You
lucky folks. You lucky lucky folks.
I'm not jealous at all. I don't know
what you're talking about. Not one bit.
>> [sighs]
>> Okay. So, if they don't hold previous
day value low, the next level for them
to check is 180. So, I'd expect some
bids to come in around here at some
point. If they don't come in, it's going
to be very, very, very dangerous for the
market. We are picking up big downside
momentum here right now.
But you would expect some bids to start
forming around here, which is starting
to see some relief right now. So value
area low on the day 300. That's your
overunder. If they reclaim that 300, uh
they can try and retest 312, 315 and
this nugget here. Right. So
from here to here can be a retest above
this squeeze back out. fill in some of
this possible otherwise just more
liquidity built to move lower this area
here. This area here very very key.
Do I think we get back to market open?
Uh well, we're not too far.
It doesn't have to though. It doesn't
have to. I mean, look, we we have
previous day value area low and current
value area low as like the first points
of call. Let's call it. So, you go. So,
back to the 300 like we just talked
about. This is current value area low on
the day. Now, for me,
relief back here and now back to this
gray box probably. So, 300 and then gray
box. And then the question is very much
like earlier, right? Do sellers resell
this? Are they going to try and complete
this move here and lower or do bids
start to take over again? All right,
that's literally what you're looking for
when you're looking at these areas. If
we come flying in here and you see
aggressive buyers in here and we don't
move higher, then you know they're going
to try and resell it. If we come in here
and sellers keep trying but we're not
moving lower, then this becomes
available. That's why there's always two
trades at key levels.
the gray area. Do you chart that or does
that indicate? No, these are me draw.
I'm drawing this on. The gray boxes are
stuff that I draw on.
Is it Jean or or Jean? You're welcome.
Sorry, I probably butchered your name.
I'm sorry about that. But you're
welcome. Thanks for joining.
4K on the day and I'm out of here. Great
job, everyone. See you tomorrow. Nice
work, Tyson. Man, look at you. Look at
you. I am so flipping proud of Tyson.
You guys don't understand. Tyson came to
me last year, did the course. We've had
some very deep and meaningful
conversations about getting him on the
road to profitability, which came from
just simplifying trading and focusing on
one setup. And now he's absolutely
crushing it, which is what I want to
see. I want to see you guys crush it.
That's all I care about.
I want to see you guys be able to do it
without me here so that when all said
and done, you can do this whenever you
want, wherever you're living in the
world, from whatever laptop or computer
you're on. That is the beauty of
trading. It's the freedom that comes
with it.
[snorts]
Okay, so they're trying to lift 300 to
come and test here. Right. This is what
they're trying to do
at the moment. We're seeing buyers get a
little bit caught over 300 the last two
candles. So, they've tried a couple
times to get back inside current value
area low.
So, it' be highly contested area here
all the way up to sort of 330 340. How
long we've got to lunch? 10 minutes left
and then we're going to do those
giveaways.
Back to VW up 24hour view up. Same on
the ES.
Oh, nice, Teresa. That's your son.
Congratulations. That's That's awesome.
Nice work.
Look at Nvidia. Look at that fade on
Nvidia all the way back down to VWAP and
lower time frame ALGO and IB.
Crazy. What a crazy squeeze out into the
5day moving average. [snorts] More sell
pressure coming here. So, we trapped
buyers into the 300 again. Didn't even
quite make it up to here and they're
trying to sell this back down. Their
target right now is these 240s is where
they're trying to go.
And VIX, you know, we drifted under that
1750 I talked about, but we only came to
1730, reclaimed 1750, and now we're back
at 1860 previous day low here on VIX.
This market is getting whacked. They're
playing whack-a-ole on this market right
now. Back to previous day value area low
here.
Back to the uh sort of opening range
level on ES.
Is it the same for us? Not too far. 23s
is the opening range high.
So, these will be contested levels now
because we contested over them earlier
today, which is why we know they're
contested levels.
What level do I have for previous day
value area low? Right here. 240s
right here. 240s. This gray box
basically where we just tapped into
240s.
SP
doing Q's. What are you doing now?
Q's coming back to a pivot from
pre-market.
Yeah, premarket high pivot here on QQQ.
So big level here on the NASDAQ.
Big big level around here on the NASDAQ.
Previous day value area low pre-market
sort of high uh in the cash ETFs. VIX
coming into previous day low. Let's see
if there's a reaction around here or
not. Sellers currently in control, but
this is where I'd be covering. If you
were short, I would be covering. I'd be
basically all out of here. Here's comes
the relief on this level.
Back to VWAP. Now, can they squeeze this
all the way back up for a little bit?
They're trying to step on the bid here
with that counter trend move back into
this gray box. So, they're definitely
relief from here. This is a big cover
point like we talked about.
Alex, I just found you your channel the
other day. I follow most YouTubers. You
do a great job of explaining the market,
trading live, and keeping it real.
Thanks, Brian. I try. I try.
I try do my best
try and educate as much as I can rather
than just say I'm short here or I'm long
here. I don't think that achieves I know
lots of new people coming here saying
that's what they want you. It means
you'll never be able to do anything for
yourself. I want to teach you to fish.
One runner left, Dean. Very nice. Very,
very nice, Dean.
Okay, so VIX into that previous day low.
It's kind of stuck here at the moment.
Lunchtime coming up in 5 minutes. New
hourly bar coming. Sales are still in
control, but you're coming into a very
important level for this market. It
might well be that everyone covers here.
We do not know. If not, then uh you
know, we can have a look at this on a
hourly.
Right? You can see these pivots here
become important. If we start losing
these pivots,
especially this is current week's
developing profile. If we lose
what's this sort of 220s, 200s and 220s.
If we lose that, there's a very good
chance we fade all the way back in. But
if we hold that, you can see some relief
back up for a little bit. It would make
sense. So, coming into some big key
levels. Here comes target. We just
missed it by what, a tick.
really to the tick. There you go.
Filled. So you guys should have been
filled there. And anything beyond this
is now a bonus. What a trade. I am
absolutely devastated. Look. Look how
tight a trade that would have been.
Left 200 points on the table because it
stopped me out. That's painful. That's
[\h__\h] painful. I don't care what
trader you are. That that that stings.
That hurts the ego. That definitely
hurts the ego.
That hurts the ego.
Oh my days.
[laughter]
Why didn't I get back in? Um, I was
making some breakfast.
I was making breakfast. So, it had
faded. I came back and I saw it here and
then I came back and we'd already
started puking. And you know, I don't
want to chase down here. I've lost my
edge at that point.
I also had it's I had three goes at it.
It wasn't like I had I tried one and
done. Like I had a couple a good few
attempts at it. Right. They're trying to
bid down to 220 here
which will I think was that level we
talked about. Right where they probably
need to hold.
It's the start of a node. 220 to sort of
180 190 is probably where they will want
to hold. If they don't do that, then
it's the market's in so much trouble.
Yeah, they they got me. Trader on tilt.
They got me. They knocked me out three
times. I mean, I made I made money on it
all three times, but
I could have risked the 80 because
the delta
was at 80, right? I risked here to the
edge of this node and I got wicked out
pretty much to the tick.
Maybe maybe it's my fault. Maybe I
should have lit like been willing to
risk 80. My problem was if I risked 80
and I got caught in a squeeze, then the
fill would have been awful.
Um because we would have been back above
by side um delta and I would have been
in big big trouble.
So we can see this contested level
[snorts]
220 is coming up that we just talked
about. Market is just sliding giving
everything back. Giving everything back.
So 25s here
gray box. Uh this is New York open. This
is edge of current value. So sliding
away from this now.
buyers in big big trouble so far.
So that relentless bid all day has
turned into a relentless sell, isn't it?
There hasn't been much relief. I will
say that you got to be careful. This
feels very much like yesterday. There
has not been much relief. So just be
careful when we have like these big
bearish days. You know, too many bears
get stuck at the lows into key levels.
You can see like really big aggressive
reliefs where they get caught. So just
manage your stop. For those of you who
are still holding
level 452s
seen some bids trying to come in here.
Haven't even retested value yet.
So 45s and then I'd say sort of 80s are
important. 45s and then 80s. So far sell
is in absolute control. Things melting.
There we go. There's the squeeze that we
just talked about. There's the test of
45s that we just talked about. If it
goes through there 80s. So 45s and 80s.
We literally just said it. So be careful
when too many shorts get caught at the
lows. This is what happens. You just get
a nasty wick out to test a key level.
Sellers are still there so far. But if
we get through 45s, we will go 80s. So
if they start to do one of these,
they are due some relief into the new
hour. It's very possible they do that,
right? And then maybe they resell it or
they resell it here. We don't know. But
I would just manage your position.
That's all I'm saying, right? Hopefully
that made sense to you. I think I said
it just in time for you. Gave you the
exact levels again.
Pretty accurate.
Um, let's do some giveaways. All right,
let's do some giveaways. I would not
hold on beyond this guys. If you've been
short in this for those 200 plus points,
all right, if we start reclaiming value,
this squeeze up to here, you don't want
to be giving back 50, 60, 70 points,
okay? Don't do don't don't do not give
it back. I just talked about the rallies
on these days. They [snorts] can get
very aggressive very very quickly.
Volatility is very high.
Everything is like a bare market. Yeah,
I know what you mean, mate. I mean, the
volatility's high, isn't it? We're We're
at 18s right now. Um, how are we doing
on the likes? That's the big question.
Did we get to 450?
We need a few more here, but we do a
giveaway anyway because I'm feeling
kind. But yeah, let's just smash that
like button, guys. Most of you should
have made lots of money with me here.
And let's set this up. Give me a second.
Oh, I'm feeling tilty, guys. I'm telling
you. It's It's in me. It's in me. It's
is in me. Yes. Remember, if you spam,
you get removed. So, don't type it more
than once. All right? Do not type it
more than once. Thank you, Adam.
FCT, just type it once. Remember, that's
the code for most the prop firms. It
would get you the best deal. Whether
you're trading with Apex, Tradeify,
um,
Lucid, Funded Next, any of those, most
of the prop firms, FCT. The only one
where you have to use a different code
is for take profit trader. Just put flow
zone in and get you 40% off.
Give you guys a couple minutes to sort
that out.
Only good news is I can take yet another
payment from TPT today, which I love
daily payouts.
Love daily payouts.
My account was down to $17. Thanks for
helping me out that hole. Oh, awesome,
man. Glad glad it helped.
Oh yeah. I mean I I I I know I know I
shouldn't tilt. I'm just I'm speaking
candidly with you. I feel tilty. Um I
also know my trigger points are trades
which I have good thesis on. Getting
knocked out break even numerous times.
That's a big tilt factor. Having that
happen two days in a row increases that
tilt factor. So I actually have to be
very careful now coming into tomorrow
based on my own stats. I need to be very
cautious with my size and positioning
tomorrow because it's very possible I
get emotional tomorrow. That's just
based on me knowing myself.
That's me being honest with you. I am
not a robot. I'm human. I make errors. I
have emotions. And as some of you know,
I have a lot going on off the charts as
well, which also impacts my ability to
think clearly sometimes.
Okay, give you guys a couple more
seconds.
Still heading downside. So, the only
next target we just failed 45. It tried
to reclaim 45, pushed through it,
failed, rejected previous day value. The
only thing left really for them to come
to
current week, New York open and previous
day close again. I mean if we get under
previous day close remember at the start
of the day I said if we get under
previous day close there is a big fade
opportunity right if we if we get under
here whether it's today or tomorrow this
is crazy D right if we get under here
900s is the target we're looking for
same as yesterday
All right let's pull this winner
five
4 3
2 1.
Currency flipper, are you here? Currency
flipper, let me know you're here in
chat.
Nice. All right. Congrats, Currency
Flipper. You have won a free Apex
account, any size that you would like.
All I need you to do is send me an email
info@flowzonetrader.com.
I'm just making a note of your name
here.
And uh send me a screenshot of you
logged in to your YouTube so I know it's
you, not someone faking it. And then um
I will sort you out with an account.
Easy as that.
All right. So info@flowzonerader.com.
Alex, if you get the opportunity, can
you explain when there was a change in
character and break structure? Yes.
Right. There's multiple ways to do it
here.
You could simply look for a trend
and a break which happened in supply.
Remember this red box is supply. If you
want to mark out the low that made the
high
right,
this low made this high. Correct. This
low made this high. Once we break this
low, that's when we have the change in
character. Okay. The problem is from
that point, you you're just going to
look at a flush. Why? Why was this so
aggressive? Because
we'd been in here since what was my
level? 35s was the first level was it?
35s here. We've been building liquidity
or this edge here from 10:42.
We're basically there an hour. Okay. So
for an hour we built liquidity here. We
can see it here. When we have this, it's
very possible and very common that we're
not going to do one of these, right?
Because once everyone's stops are here,
right? If you think about if you were
one of the buyers, think about this
aggressive bid all morning. Buying,
buying, buying, buying, buying, buying,
buying, buying, buying,
boxed in, point of control. If
everyone's got their stop here from the
last hour, what's going to happen when
they all stop out? They all become
sellers, right? And not just sellers,
aggressive sellers, market sellers. So
we tank off that. So if we look here
and this is the [\h__\h] that pulled me
out, you absolute
bastard. Right. [laughter]
Okay. So 35s
was
here.
Why was this an important level to me?
because I knew we had
a very aggressive seller here who got
absorbed. All right, so here there was
like I can't remember how many lots it
was. It was like a 300
limit buyer and a 300 market order
seller. So I knew that this was a big
level. All right, these 35s into here
right here in this push we run the
stops.
This is all buy side aggressive buying.
Look at this gap. buy side, aggressive
buying. Do they sustain the bid? No,
they flop inside. Okay, so this is the
chance. Now, we're looking for
breakdowns underneath. Uh, and I start
to add in to wherever that gray box
would have been. So, somewhere
around here, I think.
Right. So, I'm short here looking for
that breakdown. I get stopped out
when they fill that imbalance. That is
my fault. My stop should have gone above
the 80s where I know we had a buy side
imbalance, right? My stop should have
gone above the 80s. I'll show you this
right here. If I move up
this right here, a big delta at 80. My
stop should have gone there. My stop
didn't go there. It went the other side
of this shelf. It went here at 77s.
For the sake of three points, I should
have given it. I got run out. It's what
happens. It It happens, right? So a
short at 65s was covering some each time
on these flushes and I got run out at
77s. If I risked 80, we would have got
it. And then after that, what happens?
Well, we return back to where we have
volume, right? So this is so thin in
here and so thin here on the way up that
we're just going to return straight back
in because we lack any structure. Right?
When we lack structure, this is what
happens.
Hopefully that makes sense. So you put
it all together when you have your break
of structure, your break of trend, your
build of volume, your trap participants,
your auction high, right? Your auction
high where we have buyers trapped at the
highs of day and then we start moving
away. There's only one thing we're going
to do. We're going to return back in
price. Where are we going to return?
We're going to return to areas where
there might be support. We return from
areas to where there might be support.
where there might be support. Where
there might be support, where there
might be support. Why do we not bid on
this? Because we're in a strong sell.
What's the protren? Sell. Higher time
frame is in a sell. All right. So, we're
rotating down. This will be done when
it's done. It might never be done. All
right. This might just be getting
started. This might be a retest of
supply. We might be zooming out here on
a daily.
We might be expanding to come back down
into these 900s, which I keep talking
about the newsletter. And then under
that we have a gap fill here still
possible and lower. Okay. So the main
premise is still
all this trap buying volume. Right? We
want to lean against this short. At any
opportunity we have to lean against the
short. We expected some relief today. We
then want to lean short. These are the
targets. Right? Higher time frames.
One, two, failure. Yum. Right.
Hopefully that helps.
Oh, the it's not my indicator, mate. Um,
this these are just large orders. If you
use orderflow on Ninja Trader, you can
get it for free. Yeah, there's a video
on my channel. If you're trading with
like any of the prop firms, you can have
a version of that for free. It's it's on
my channel. Have a look. Um,
I'll post it for you.
Got to get out of here in a minute,
folks. But I'll I'll do this for you
just quickly.
Right,
this video will show you how to get
autoflow for free.
Um,
could there be an upward force at some
point today? I mean, there could be like
it it could offer relief, but right now
we're coming all we're now under new
open. We're coming right down to the
gap. We have previous day low and we
have targets below. I mean, could there
be a relief? Yeah, absolutely. I mean,
this is straight down the straight same
way it's straight up. Like, maybe we we
get relief. Maybe we come into here and
then we lift into here and then sell
back down. I don't know. I Anything's
possible. This is the thing when people
tell you it's have it has to do. It
doesn't have to do anything. The market
doesn't have to do anything. If it
didn't want to do this today, it could
have done that. It like the quicker that
you understand that and don't become
fixed in a bias. You can have thesis,
but understand that the market literally
does not have to do anything if it
doesn't want to. [snorts]
I don't use channels for view up. No,
Alex, thanks for the explanation. Very
insightful. No worries. Um, after IB
high, look above and fail off. Yeah,
exactly. It like Exactly. It's it's a
great setup, right? We talk about this
all the time. Look above and failed of
IB high. What else did it look above?
Previous daily value area high looked
above and failed. So, what we going to
do if we can't find, right? If we can't
find value up here, what we going to do?
We're going to trade lower and search
for value. It had a chance to find value
here. This was yesterday's value. It
didn't. It's still searching for value.
That means at the moment, everyone's
saying that this is too expensive. This
was a squeeze which was stupid and
they've said, "Hey, this is stupid.
We're coming back down. We need to
search for value." Right? Market's
always auctioning for value. It's trying
to find value. When does it find value?
When it goes sideways.
[snorts]
All right, guys. I've got to get out of
here. I'd love to stay here all day, but
I've actually got an appointment at
10:00 and I need to walk my dog before
then. All right. Love you guys loads.
Um, don't forget if you want to support
the channel, all the links are down
below. If you like how I teach, start on
my YouTube channel for free. Tons of
stuff for there for free. All right,
make sure you like how I teach. Go
through that. If you're new on this
channel, you're probably thinking, "What
the hell am I looking at?" Go through
the free videos. If you like the free
videos, if you like how I teach, head
over to the website, flowzonetrader.com.
There's tons of courses on there that
you can do stuff on orderflow and
bookmap or the 20our beginner to advance
course which comes with the indicator
you are seeing on the chart or a version
of it and discord. All right, peace and
love. Be kind to each other. Be nice.
Remember, I believe in karma. You will
get out what you put in. See you
tomorrow.