Morning
everyone. Morning. Morning. Morning.
Hope you all had a good long weekend.
Oh, let's get that off. There we go. Uh
hope you had a good long weekend. Some
of you would have taken yesterday off.
Some of you would have traded it. There
were some opportunities yesterday.
Wasn't as uh bad as expected. And you
can see we're seeing weakness in the
market. If you didn't know, over the
weekend, tensions started to rise
between America and the rest of Europe
who are not okay with uh Trump's
positioning on Greenland and threaten
them back. He said, "Well, I'll tariff
you then." And so, this is what we're
we're now getting as a result. Um, back
into tariff wars, it seems. What are we
doing? Well, we're leaving this low
volume node. You we can see these
clusters here. We failed to break out.
All right. So,
this is starting to break. We went over
this last week. this wedge pattern and
we're starting to leave 5day, 20-day,
50-day all stuck in the lower volume
node above in and around the sort of
650s and we've come down back towards
this naked point of control that we
talked about. Uh I'll go over this in
the higher time frame. This is all from
the weekly newsletter and you can see
where we're finding a bid for now.
Right. If we start to lose this bid,
whether it's today or later in in the
week, then we've got some clear targets
down below the lower Ballinger band,
next low volume node, 24,800s, even this
200 day. Everything's possible.
So, we're definitely starting to leave
it. The question is, are we going to
reject here this morning or because this
is such a big drop, are we now looking
at a sideways movement? Time will tell.
Let's look at the higher time frames,
and you can see what we've got. All
right, here's the gap down uh from
Friday to Sunday. This is yesterday's
price and you can see this was the key
level that we were looking for an
overunder in 25300. This is what we
talked about in the newsletter. All
right, we're expecting that drop down to
there. Then what happens? Well, we're
starting to lose it. All right, we're
starting to lose it. If we look at the
volume we created yesterday, it was in
here. If we look at the current
developing profile, it's here. And we're
not finding acceptance back inside those
levels. So it's not the ideal position
to short but momentum is definitely
short biased. Right? The ideal position
to short was up here or even on a
rejection of this. So I will be watching
this morning into previous day's value
area low which we've rejected twice this
morning already 25750
and the current uh weekly developing
profile 25 uh 250. So 250 750. I'll be
watching this area here. Does this hold
as resistance in this area here? If the
answer is yes, then we can look for
downside pressure. We're going to look
left. Okay, we want to see can we get
underneath, right? Are we going to get
underneath this old level here? All
right, so 25 um sorry, we'll just call
it 250 to 27 uh 275. If we reject that,
do we start rejecting 170? So there's a
maybe a 100 point drive here. If we
reject 170, we're looking for deeper rot
rotation down. We want to be very
careful getting short near the low of
day, though. All right, very very
careful. If we find acceptance back
inside this, then I'm expecting a
rotation inside yesterday's range. All
right, we're going to respect previous
day's point of control, 325 and 380. So,
if we start reclaiming a bid over 300,
then we're looking for 320, 380, see if
resistance comes in. If not, then maybe
a squeeze up to 450s. All right, so both
things are possible here. Just remember,
if you're getting short, we uh we're
just trying to play momentum. We do not
have the best structure of the day down
here. We are short in deep deep
discount. Remember, we've left, right?
The balanced range that we talked about
has been in here for a number of weeks.
Okay? And we've left it in gapped, which
means we've got one week, two week,
three week, four weeks of buyers now
caught above. All right? And all they
have to support them is this guy down
here where we had that first reaction.
If we lose that, it is a good night
market. Very simple. momentum is
absolutely downside right now.
Absolutely downside. We're leaving we're
leaving trapped buyers a uh above us.
It's just about how uh
where price comes and can we get a good
price to get short off really is what
we're thinking about. Uh on a 5m minute
you can see if we just look in here.
All right,
Asia kind of went sideways and then lost
the bid and then London's really started
attacking it. The question is does this
pivot hold here? So, if you're desperate
to be a bull, you're going to need to
see this pivot of 180 hold and a reclaim
inside 250 275. All right, that's what
you're going to need if you're a bull.
Let's go through the other time frames
and have a look at what the ETFs and the
ES are doing. Most things will look
fairly similar today. ES
exactly the same. All right, leaving
this huge balance. Remember, if we zoom
out on here, all right, ES did that look
above and fail. All right, if it can't
catch a bid here, it is good night. It's
going to come into these 780s. And if we
start really letting go, it's got quite
a long way down until it hits some form
of structure down here into the 6,000s.
I mean, take weeks and weeks to develop,
but I'd be watching 6000s, 6450 swing
shorts if we start letting go of sort of
780s. All right, if we start letting go
of here, but the same structure here.
It's a look above and fail. And we just
want to see if on a back test, does it
stay heavy? If it reclaims, then it's
got a chance. But if on a back test, it
stays heavy. We're going to move lower.
That's going to be shown in the ETFs the
same way. So, you can see that look
above and fail. This line that we had in
for last week, big reaction after that,
right? Little poke above and then we all
we've done is roll over and gap. So,
we've gapped and trapped above. right
now. Q's same story. Gapped and trapped
above this blue line which now becomes
red.
Gapped and trapped above and this is the
next pivot down into 600. So it's really
do we react there or in front of there
or not? If we have a look at the Dixie,
it's starting to fall off and that drive
back towards the 100 that we talked
about.
Right, same kind of story. If we look at
the VIX, it's very high. All right, here
we talked about this, didn't we? We
cannot do this forever. This grind up
and it's starting to accelerate. That is
a big move. That's a big gap. It's a
four almost five point gap on the VIX.
We're watching it into sort of these
21s. If we start to drive through 21s,
then
especially through 2180, then we're
going to come all the way back up to top
to test this top level. And you best
believe the market will get weak if we
start breaking out through that. But uh
you know, let's just see. It's Tuesday
morning after a uh sort of bank holiday.
Let's have a look at the mag.
Big weakness in Apple
continues. All right, same kind of
story. It's left this gap. If we mark
this out, balance range here. All right,
we've gapped down and left it. All
right, very very weak. So big sell
opportunity. Um
just have to see if we retest it and how
we when we retest. I might actually add
an alert there. It's just unfortunate
it's done such a big move overnight.
Same probably story here on Amazon.
Yeah, same thing. Waiting to see do we
retest this kind of level up here.
You would imagine on a retest we stay
heavy unless they're going to force some
gigantic squeeze. Same story on Google.
All right, leaving this balance range.
It does have a bit more support on
Google compared to the others, but we've
definitely left left participants above
trapped. Meta
big old gap down. Get this line now. All
right, coming back into where we found a
bid before. All right, so the question
is, does does uh Meta hold a bid here
and start to drive out or is this going
to be a breakdown under 580s and start
to see major weakness in the market?
It's definitely possible. Cannot rule
that out right now. We're going to go
into these big sales Q1 that I've been
talking about. This might well be the
start of it. Uh Microsoft, same story.
You can see the balance range here and
we've left it gapping down, starting to
drive away from it. Nvidia
failed to reclaim the highs. That's a
little bit stronger though. It's just a
little bit more in no man's land here.
Pivot here. Pivot here we can get back
into. All right. Nvidia is not too bad
compared to the others.
Tesla
look above and fail
support system here. So, does it hold a
bid here? It's tried. This is a double
bottom. It's trying to hold a bid there.
Is it able to hold it? If we have a look
at the broader names, Oracle got sold on
to into on the push over 200.
AMD got sold into on the push over 30 so
far, but it's holding up pretty well on
AMD.
And what was the other name moving
today? Netflix. I am long Netflix but we
have uh earnings coming up later this
week. Is it on Wednesday or Thursday or
is it after the bell today?
It's today. Okay. So, might get a mover
today. Um I'm very very small position
in Netflix.
There is a very good chance they sell it
off. The market's staying weak, but I
think it's due a bounce. But it's uh we
will just see how we operate and act.
Let's have a look at the treasuries
which are starting to break out. All
right. This is what we were talked about
all of last year. I kept talking about
this. If this happens, this market is
going to get weak. Well, there we go.
This has now happened. All right. We
talked about this so many times on
stream last year. The importance of
this. This is what we're now going to
start to see if these higher um the 13
start breaking out. You're even seeing
it in the five. I was expecting to see
more divergence there to be honest in
the five and the two. But yeah, it's not
good. It's not good. America, you're
you're in a pickle, mate. You've been in
a pickle a while and it's starting to
really play out.
Keep threatening everyone, having a
tantrum. This is what happens. You just
do damage to yourself.
Okay,
let's just see what we get here. Um, if
we think about the news,
what have we got coming up today?
Nothing today. When are the big movers
this week? Uh Thursday and Friday. All
right, Thursday and Friday this week.
It's when we're going to get the big
movers. Uh do me a favor, guys. Smash
that like button nice and early for me.
I obviously want to do some nice
giveaways on stream as always.
Yeah, market's heavy. Market's been
heavy. It's just about what happens
next.
How are you guys all doing? Did you
trade yesterday?
Did you have a good day? Did you trade
overnight? Maybe some of you caught this
fade in London.
Hopefully some of you caught it in
London.
Yeah, I'm back fresh. Yeah, I'm back.
Got back live Wednesday last week.
Thanks for your patience, everyone. I
should be back to normal now. Hopefully.
You might need the odd day off, but uh
hopefully hear most
passed 50k yesterday. Nice work.
500 enjoyed your holiday.
No, I think the tariff decision is
getting pushed again from what I
understand.
Let me have a look.
Um,
I'm pretty sure it's getting pushed
again or no decision.
Yeah, I'm looking for it. I can't see
it. I'm pretty sure there was uh no
decision
or is getting pushed. Where's my
Discord?
Unclear if court will publish
anticipated ruling on the legitimacy of
Trump's tariff as US president doubles
down on Greenland and threat. There you
go. So unclear. I mean maybe we get it,
but they've pushed it every day so far,
haven't they?
We'll just have to see folks.
Okay, bell coming up here
about 20 seconds. Good luck everyone.
I'm going to wait to see. Oh, I'm
interested in this. We're trying to
reclaim current week value area low
already.
I'm going to wait to see if we trade
back up to these sort of pivots towards
sort of 300
300 320 and see if they fade it or not
there. And if not then um well we're
going to have a inside rotational day.
Here we go then folks. Here's the move
up to the sort of 300s and 320s we just
talked about is the drive opening drive.
Big old squeeze. All of the mag opening
up red
coming into these 300s. Want to see do
we get participation here?
Do they resell it?
Drive into 300s and 320s.
Do they resell this is the question.
Yep. So far buyers being trapped into
the 300 for sure.
We got this uh block up here that I'm
watching. So just waiting to see if more
buyers get stuck here still very very
early in the day. But interested in a
short here if they start to get stuck up
here.
If they find acceptance, they're going
to drive much much higher. But so far we
are finding sellers up here. I've joined
this short just to snap short back down.
Lovely. Oh my god. Going to lock this in
towards VWAP. Pay myself a little bit
here. Beautiful. Nice start to the day.
Nice start to the day. That was very,
very quick.
So, once I saw the buyers getting stuck
here, started to short here, back down
to here, and we'll see if we uh find
acceptance back under. This is current
developing weeks value area low. So,
just want to see do we find acceptance
under there now for a big drive.
Beautiful. Let's go, baby. What a nice
start to the week. Covering some into
this
buyers turning up at these lows. This is
where we just broke out from. Not going
to hold too much. If we snap under all
of this, then I expect a retest of here.
But this was the first play that I was
interested in from the 300s to 320s for
a drive back down. That was almost 100
pointer out the gate.
Yeah, I've just got a tiny piece left in
case we want to move lower.
But yes,
we hit my levels very, very quick there.
And we're at the opening print of the
day, right? So, I'm not looking to hold
on too long at the opening print of the
day.
We're still through, you know, all the
uh big institutions have got to get all
their orders in in the next few minutes.
Might see follow through here. We'll
see. Just got a tiny piece on now.
That's a nice win at start the day.
We are holding previous week. Oh, these
have not changed, are they? Great.
I'm going to hold this.
All these look wrong.
700.
Okay, my levels are all wrong on Ninja.
Let me just sort this out.
750.
Okay, we're coming back up to these 320s
again. These are the big levels out of
this now in that runner. Sorry, just
trying to sort some of these out now.
Sorry, folks.
Okay, here's the squeeze. So, if they
squeeze back through this, the next
level to come and test the chatting
previous day point of control will be
all the way up here into 400s.
So, I'm out of this now. Sorry, just
give me one second to fix these levels.
I don't know why Ninja has deleted all
of these.
So, 700
26,000. Okay,
there we go.
All righty.
Okay, so they held the dip into this key
level. So, we're finding acceptance now
inside the current week value. We're
going to drive up and test these 330s.
Now, if we get through that, we're going
to test 380s all the way up here. All
right? So, if you bought the dip there,
remember I paid played the fade the
first attempt here from here to here. If
you bought this dip, you're now looking
for this for your continuation. And we
are now inside previous day and current
week value. So, we're in a rotational
market again.
Uh it wasn't just yesterday though. If
you if you look at the current week and
you look at the structure of the week
starting uh 15th of December,
that's what we're also looking at.
I'm going to let this just sort itself
out. Let's have a quick look at the mag
here. Tesla 2.33% down. Nvidia 2.33%
down. Microsoft 1.87% down. Meta two
over 2% down. Google 1.80% down. Amazon
uh 2.51%
down and Apple 0.76% down. Netflix the
only one catching a bid here this
morning in runup to earnings. We just
faded those same levels. We couldn't
quite get to this PC
from current week. There's a big node up
there. All right, I will draw this on.
There's a big node from current week up
here that we can use as like an
overunder.
this red line.
Has the ENQ been hard to read lately?
No, I don't think so. I think it's been
um it's actually been quite nice. It's
actually been playing ball for a change.
Some volume on here now.
Okay, as you can see, they keep getting
stuck up here.
250s is a key level today. 250s is a key
level today. If we stay inside 250s,
then we're going to look to rotate
upside. If we lose 250s, there's more
downside pressure.
It's a big level.
Just letting this settle down a bit now
after that first short of the day.
Don't fully trust it.
It's rejecting that same level. There's
a really clear pivot between the two
VWOPS and and just in front of uh 890 on
ES. Really, really clear pivot there.
So worth watching. We are above the New
York open though. They are trying to
force a squeeze up. Remember we have
gapped down significantly. We've come
into some big big levels all the way
dating back to that Monday the 15th of
December. These are straight out the
newsletter. All these levels that we're
trading around right now. So if you read
the newsletter, it should have been in
your inbox Saturday morning. We talked
about this old naked PC being retested
as it's only been tested once.
And I think we're just we're going to be
in these sort of rotations now unless we
get political weakness come in. Then
we're going to be in rotations until we
get to earnings. And the big question is
is how do we operate in these earnings
really next week all the big big tech
starts. We have Netflix today and some
more banks. But banks earnings haven't
been too strong and we have not held the
bid well.
They're
still holding this dip. They're trying
to come up into here like we talked
about 380s. They're trying to retest
380s and if they get through that the
four what's this up here? 430s 440s
Asia high up there
value area high for this current week up
here. And if we get through that gap
starts above 475. If they really want to
push, they've got to get above 475 to
close it all the way to 700.
I don't think we're going to see that
today.
And they're trying to force this squeeze
up towards these 380s, 400s. That's what
they're trying to do at the moment. Yes.
Coming into its VWAP.
There we go. Back to these 300s again.
Just letting this develop. You can see a
bit of a D-shape developing here at the
moment. I'm just being patient. We had
that first trade this morning. Made good
money on that first trade. That first
short when the buyers got stuck,
almost paid us 100 points in uh the
second minute of the day. This one right
here fading back down. Let's see. Yes,
rejecting that clear pivot. We just
talked about that big pivot on ES. It's
still rejecting it. If they come below
beneath the New York open here, they're
going to be in trouble.
That's what ES is trying to hold right
now is that New York open.
really nice.
Here's the New York open and value area
low on the week. So, this is the area we
talked about. 50s are going to be the
key area today. If we start losing the
50s, you might well see some weakness in
the market. It really would not surprise
me in the slightest.
Yes, we went over the trend before the
market opened ironclad. So hopefully you
joined for that. It's also about how
many buyers we've left trapped above.
Hourly trend is down. Location is not
prime on the day to be short at lows,
which is why we're trying to fade pops
at the moment. I'd really like a retest
up here to fade. But if we start
snapping,
we can think about how we might operate.
Heavy heavy market here. ES coming back
down into its New York open. We're at
the New York open right now into these
50s we just talked about. These are the
key level. This is sentiment for day. I
would say these 50s.
So there we go. New York open. They're
trying to find a bid is what I'm saying.
this if we zoom out here to give you an
idea of what we're looking at. Right? We
talked about the importance of the
current developing week's value here and
this node here, right? And we keep
rejecting up into here, but we are
holding current week's value. We're
going to have to let go of current
week's value if we're really going to
look for expansion down. And we have
some key levels here. If we look left,
right, this is the edge from the uh
December 15th I keep talking about. So,
we're going to need to find acceptance
under there if we're going to move
lower. Otherwise, I'm somewhat expecting
rotation because we've had a big gap
down. All right. If we think about where
we closed last week or value last week,
we've moved from 700s into, you know,
the low 200s today. So, we want to be
careful if we're thinking about shorts.
You have to understand your location is
not ideal, is it? Buyers are trapped at
700 and above.
All right? So, we're not retesting any
key levels yet even of uh Friday. And
even if we look at the daily,
is this on a daily? Oh my god. On a
daily, we are at the lower Ballinger
band. Let me get you guys over.
Right. On the daily, we're at this lower
Ballinger band. Right. We got a
contracting Ballinger band. So, we're
going to need to wait for if we're
really going to get weak, we're going to
need some crosses to start happen here
and this to open up and then this to
close down and the 5day to give us that
hug. All right. So, it might take a
little bit of time to develop just based
on what we've got on dailies at the
moment.
Unless we see absolute panic, you're
probably not going to see no straight
downside moves.
You keep buying the top and the bottom.
Well,
at least you know at least you know your
issue. I guess that's that's your first
thing. At least you know what you're
doing wrong. So, just don't do it.
You've identified your issue. You're
chasing. That means
Okay, ES still holding that New York
open. Trying to find a bid here.
Like I talked about that sort of 90s is
a big big level on ES. 90s is a big
level. 24-hour VWAP up there and a clear
pivot over 90s. You see there a failed a
look above and fail or you're going to
see a squeeze back up into sort of the
tens and 15s potentially on ES. Right.
So just waiting here patiently. Now, we
didn't see a breakdown under here for me
to trade. We're still inside this
Dshape. We're still inside current
week's developing profile and we're
inside previous days value. Remember
values here and value area high up here.
So, if they want to rotate previous day,
this is their target. We're in a
rotational day. I know it's not going to
show an inside bar on uh the daily
chart, but we are on an inside bar
if you include yesterday's volume.
This is their attempt. They're trying to
get up here right now.
It's where they would like to go.
There's ES stuck into the 90. Exactly
like I said, tap 90, the VWAP. We got an
89.75 print there. So, it's big big
pivot on ES like I've talked about. So,
we're either going to see a rejection
here or a look above and fail, or we're
going to see a base and hold above for a
squeeze.
Just going to be patient now.
Fixes into a pivot as well.
Waiting to see if we put a squeeze in or
if we're going to fade underneath 250s
today. I don't really want to trade the
midpoint of this range. Right, here's
your current profile on the day. Here's
your where's current week?
Current week
between here. So in and your previous
day between here. So all very tight in
here, right? This is your range. Trying
to leave that alone for me personally.
You know, I dislike trading ranges.
Well, quite right, Josh. Yeah.
Uh
move
passing EVA on the first candle. Nice,
nice work, DS
seems to be weaker today. I mean, ES is
1.42 down. ENQ is 1.58 down. I think
they all look pretty pretty much in line
to be honest. Um, let me have a look at
the breadth of the market. It's probably
all pretty reds because we're all
gapping down. Yeah, I mean the breadth
is awful outside of energy,
right? So if we come outside of energy
right pretty much everything getting
destroyed definitely tech's getting
destroyed
it's uh I think many outliers in here
right now
this is anchored uh volume profile who
asked me that John anchored volume
profile anchor to the 930 open anchor
volume profile
Okay, we're right at this previous day
value area low again.
ES trying to find a bid here again. It's
trying to protect its New York open.
We're still just in the midpoint of the
range. If we start losing the bid here,
we might well retest these 40s and 50s.
If we lose that, there's probably a
trade down to 170s. So, that's what I'm
waiting to see how we act at each side
of the range, trying to leave this
middle part out, leave it alone.
Vick's starting to find a little bit of
a bid. I will say that. Got a gap above.
Let's see if it can get into its gap. If
it does, you're probably going to see
some weakness come in the market. But we
will see see how it operates.
Yes. Back to these levels. It's found
dips at all morning
trying to protect them, but it can't get
through those 890s I've talked about.
That's absolutely clear. It cannot get
through 890.
Keep rejecting point of control on
retests here. Are we going to get
squeezed through it that top side or do
they just let go of this whole thing?
He's gone to sleep then. Did no one come
back from holiday?
is the drive back down to previous days
value area low still absorbing here for
now still no change right still inside
between blue and red between blue and
current red and red above and they're
going to come and test like I said this
is what they want to do if they want to
get an extreme test of value they're
going to go for 450s
this is just not going anywhere sideways
at the moment and you just require
patience
falling though fix is not falling it's
found a bit of the bid. All right. So,
we gap up from VIX, right? From
pre-market, we traded between sort of
1990 and 2075.
We opened up, we've caught a bid at
1924. We're now trading at 1970. The New
York high is 1975. If we blast through
that, we're going to go 20.30. So, it's
not really falling. So, it's a big gap
up and so far it's finding a bit. It's
going to have to trade under 19 to
really start falling to get into a gap
fill of 1587.
All right. So, understand what you're
looking at.
Okay. Testing value area high on the day
now. Let's see if they break this out
and they can get this squeeze up to here
or not.
I'm just waiting patiently.
How can you get your anchor volumeing
profile to the right? It's just a new
settings
style placement. Right.
Here we go. So through current value,
three point previous day point control.
Next target for them is up here. 360 to
380 and then through that 450s and
above. That's what they're trying to do.
Remember this is the counter trend leg.
Here we go. into the squeeze.
ES again into 490s. So, two things, one
of two things are going to happen now.
Well, one of three things. We're going
to get a look above and fail at 890 on
ES or we're going to get a squeeze out
all the way if it can base above all the
way up to the 10ens and maybe even the
teens on ES, right? Which would bring us
up into here, which is a level of
interest for me.
still hasn't traded through these 90s
yet on the think they're going to get at
least a look above and fail if not more
at the moment struggling
Still seeing sellers step in here.
I'd really love them to come up here. I
think it would give us much better
opportunity today if we do.
So ES poked through that 90 by one tick
and has not been able to base above yet.
So still stuck there on ES. I'd like a
squeeze higher first.
10 a.m. news. Yeah, I'm like we will see
if we get it because they've already
come out this morning saying they're not
going to release the documents. So let's
see. Maybe maybe we get it. The other
thing is is it priced it? And if they
come out and say it's not legal, then
what happens that next? You know, it's
some big long court battle
and then uh the other thing is how are
you going to pay the tariffs back? Who's
keeping count of that?
Crazy. What a crazy world we're in in
2022.
So, they're trying to flip this into
some sort of support level here. this
old naked P and the and the previous day
point PEve
is up into 400.
And you can see it's really struggling
at that 890 pivot. Really struggling. 10
points down from it already after taking
it out by one tick. It is struggling up
there.
Back to previous day point control
again.
Still rotating and rotating and
rotating.
If they turn this into bullish
structure, they'll go for the squeeze up
into here. If we lose it, well, don't do
that.
I'm going to make this gray for now
because it's kind of neutral. It could
be bullish, but
observe it.
If we lose it, then uh I'm going to
rotate right back down to the edge of
value again.
So, we're bearish overall,
but we're rotational based on current
day volume, current week's volume,
previous day's volume.
Peter, there's a gap to 22.
I see what you're talking about. Yeah. I
mean, we don't have to do it today.
I actually see a spike up there from in
a New York session. So, I think that I
don't see the gap as still open.
I don't know. Maybe you can send me a
picture in Discord or something of what
you're seeing.
I don't have it on Trading View. Maybe
you have it on Inca Swim or something. I
don't know what you're using.
Okay, Vick's trying to get going now
through these uh hive days. If they get
through hive days, then it will try and
get all the way back up to 2030 like we
talked about.
And it's trying they're trying to flip
this old naked point of control and the
previous day point of control. They're
trying to flip this for a squeeze up.
Yes. Weak though.
Selling out 360. Just sat there. Passive
seller looking to get build up there. Is
there much above him? Yes. Still stuff
above him.
Maybe we'll wait four minutes for this
new hour.
You've got a gap of you. All right, I'll
double check that.
Just doing this grindy channel at the
moment.
Starting to lose some bids here.
Write that down into this key level.
Passive buyer now 290s. If they flush
this, they can go right down to 250s
or definitely value on the day 280s.
Let's see if they protect that, I guess,
first.
Hey Scott, I'm good mate. Just one one
trade to start the day. the first test
of supply here. So, this has faded this
back down into this. That's all I've
done so far. Now, just waiting. Let them
build out some volume and liquidity for
the next move.
Right,
I'm going to refill this tea. We've got
like 2 minutes until 10 a.m. I'll be
right back.
We're definitely not uptrending.
Um, unless you're talking about this New
York, maybe you're just talking about
the New York open. Yeah, in New York
open. Yeah, we're doing this.
But if you zoom out, you understand that
we are most certainly starting to break
away from some key levels, right? So,
this is if this is the uptrend, then
it's a higher time frame pullback, isn't
it? If we've left, if we think about
this, all right, we're pulling back. How
we operate here is going to be
important.
Watch your volatility here, folks. So,
we're starting to see spikes in
volatility. We're up towards 50 points
per M1 candle at the moment. Just be
careful.
You do not want to oversize in this. You
get caught the wrong side, it will hurt
you.
Nice, Rob. Nice. Nice.
They're trying to get use this as
support now and trying to expand. These
are the levels they'll be looking at.
380, 395, sort of 400s, anywhere up
here. And then a squeeze will be all the
way up to previous day value of 450 and
above.
Right? So those who've been buying bids,
they'll be offloading into each of these
pushes. And if they get really lucky,
they're offloading to here. I would have
thought
every push up here is getting sold into.
As you can see,
down to this same level again. It's
10:00 a.m. and we're starting to see the
sell follow through. Aggressive seller
stepping on the tape here. There's a
passive seller up here at 360. He's
offering 360. Still hasn't been filled
up there yet.
He was filled a bit and he's come back
on the tape. So he's got another 100 lot
up there.
Yes, relative weakness nowhere near that
pivot of 8.90.
seller trying to step on the tape and
force this lower at this point. We're
right at point of control on the day at
310.
Do they rebid this? Do they let it go
for a swipe? They're letting it go. It's
10 again. We might get some weakness
here if they really start to step on
this tape cuz overall we're bearish.
Remember, back to trend again. Back to
VWAP.
Messy, messy, messy. So, we can't find
acceptance over 340. We can't ac find
acceptance under 277 right now. This is
our range, this D-shaped profile. I'm
just trying to wait to see if we find
acceptance outside of either side of it.
ES right down to its New York open
again. So, relative weakness there. ES
is right down here right now,
having failed that 890 push that we
talked about.
big levels here. We're starting to
reject. Here's value. Back to these 80s
again. Finding a bid on edge of value
again. So, this is still in a rotation
until we expand value. Remember, we're
still above the New York open. We're
still in a rotation until we expand
value.
The sell is still not walked down. He's
still just sat there at 360s.
It's still inside right now.
H val VWAP previous day val.
Are we going to expand underneath these
or do we go back in a rotation back to
top side again?
Yes, this New York open. They're
starting to bid a bit lower here.
still holding value for now. Wonder if
there's expansion coming under these. I
feel like if they start losing the bid
here, they're going to be in big
trouble, but uh can't be early here.
Back to VWOP and PC. There we go. Back
to VWOP and P. Rotate, rotate, rotate,
rotate, rotate, rotate. These are the
markets I don't enjoy.
300s again.
Yeah, they're just stacking both sides.
No one knows what to do here at the
moment.
Both sides stacked. No acceptance
outside of the current value on the day.
You can see the rotation is just 280 or
275 to 340.
We're not finding any move outside of
that yet. Nothing.
Yeah, exactly.
Exactly. Just worth waiting. If we move
outside of that, we can think about
attacking it, but we're just not seeing
it.
VIX is into that gap starting to try and
fill. All right. So, through that New
York open high, it's trying to fill that
gap up to sort of 2030s at the moment.
Still seeing absorption on VWAP and
value area low on the day.
There we go. So, just absorbed again.
Just drove back through 300 again.
Buyers is trying to be aggressively
coming in here. Big buying coming in
here.
Is that guy still at 60s? Yes, he is.
Daily VUP is It's right where we are
now. Everything's stacked. Everything's
stacked.
So, your New York View up, your daily VW
up, your point of control are all at
300, right? Everything's just stacked
there.
That's where we are now.
Oh my god. Should we go back to bed,
folks? What is this? Thank god we got
that first trade of the day because
there's nothing to do since this is just
terrible.
No follow through either direction.
Uh back to value.
Come on.
Big seller trying to step in here. He's
trying to get down to 60s at the moment.
Can see his bid down there for a cover.
Here comes the news. Feels like the news
anyway. It's getting washy.
There's some covers down at 60s. This
looks like where he's trying to get to
at the moment.
This feels washy.
They're pulling bids.
Still holding inside of value area low
on the day. Still no movement.
Big buyer trying to step in here and
absorb. If he loses, we're going to wash
hard. He just came in with a 100 lot.
They're trying to get to these 60s. You
can see it on the tape. His 80s. They're
trying to get to 60s right now.
And if they lose 60s, I wouldn't be
surprised of a big wash
into VWAP into value area low. If they
lose 60s and 70s, I would not be
surprised of a very big wash here.
These are where they keep rebidding and
rebidding and rebidding over and over
again. So if he gets stuck, that's where
we'll see the pain. I'm not going to do
anything early. We have to move outside
of this and prove that he's stuck.
They're bidding 75 to 60 again.
Here
we go. They're going to fill in all the
way down to 75 and 60s. Here's 75. Do
they wash down to 60s now? They're
trying to. They're adding more lower.
Big seller coming in here. Here's the
wash we just talked about.
Right. Question is now, do we stay
heavy? All right. The question is now,
do we stay heavy?
Do they stay aggressive here and they
start to rinse this down or are they
just going to instantly reclaim? This is
the key thing now.
ES under its New York open. We're not
even near it yet.
Heavy on rejection so far is their
follow through. They're still trying to
bid. It's amazing. There's relentless
bid down here. They're going to get
taken out, I think.
Now bidding all the way down to 40s.
What a mess. What are you lot doing
today?
Look, look at the stacking there. All
the way down to 35s. Now we're going to
wash. Surely you're going to wash and
fill them. Big buyer stepping in being
very aggressive. I don't know what he's
playing at.
Psychopath move here.
They keep rebidding here. 65s.
I don't trust it that it holds this, but
they keep rebidding it. It's worth
noting they're rebidding value over and
over and over and over and over again.
And again, he's stepping in again.
Relative weakness. ES. They keep bidding
here. I think don't trust this one bit.
I really don't trust this. There's been
so much bid down here, but they're
trying to get this break above. I don't
think they're going to get it. You never
know. They're trying to get back inside
value.
ES weakness
back down to its New York low.
What are these guys doing?
It's not quite filled the gap yet. See
if it holds 20 here on a bid. If it
does, then it can have a little push
back up, add more weakness into this
market.
Supreme Court does not issue the ruling
in changing to legality of Trump's
global tariffs. Exactly what we heard
pre-market. So, they kicked it down the
road again.
It's a joke, mate. This country is a
joke when it comes to news. Cut the
books and don't do what you say you're
going to do.
Relentless bid here.
edge of value. Do we get expansion down
here is what I'm wondering right now.
But uh it's relentless bid here. It is
literally relentless joining in at 70s
and 60s.
There's the bid up to 300s again. It is
relentless. It's amazing. This guy is
just un unloading bids down here.
Right, ES back into New York open market
back into point of control. We're back
inside value. So the edge of value now
at 330 topside.
So if they get a resqueeze, that's where
they're going to go. If they reject
point of control, then we're going to
come and retest this. And if they snap
it, having trapped buyers, then they've
got a chance. But it just looks a little
messy for my liking right now. I'm going
to be honest, folks. I don't think they
know what they want to do with this at
the moment.
Yes, no ruling on tariffs. Like we said,
we said pre-market, they suggested that
would be the case and it was the case.
No ruling on it. They're going to keep
kicking it down the road. This is what
they do and then they're going to do it
when no one expects it.
And by that point, it's probably priced
in anyway.
Just the way it is, right? ES so far
rejecting that New York open.
This is a really, really ugly day so
far. Very, very ugly. Not much to do
here, folks. We had that one trade this
morning. If we start leaving value, we
can think about trading lower. If we
start leaving value upside, we can think
about the squeeze up and then a fade
higher. I just do not want to bother in
here. Look what we're doing in here.
Absolutely nothing. Do you want to trade
this? You really want to trade this?
There's nothing to do in here. Not for
me anyway. Maybe if you if you like
trading edgeto edge, maybe that's your
bread and butter.
Back down to VW up again. I've got a
24-hour view up on my screen just under
here. I don't know why there quite a big
discrepancy there between the two, but
we will see. Back down to value area low
again.
Are they going to see follow through or
this little bare flag and snap or do
they catch it?
Just everything's flat. Look at EMAs,
VWAP. Everything's flat right now. We
need to see some of these open up either
direction to have a potential trade day
here.
I'm somewhat surprised we haven't come
filled these guys at 60s and 45s yet,
but this is where this guy keeps bidding
all the time. Non-stop bid. Nonstop bid.
Trying to gobble it up.
Wow.
If this breaks, it's going to be so
nasty.
Non-stop bit again. There you go.
Gobbled it again.
Yes. Back through that New York open.
sellers trying to step in now. They know
they need a break under and this guy's
[\h__\h] Here it goes. They're trying
back to value area low on the day. Can
they get follow through down to these
40s and 60s that we've talked through
talked about numerous times now.
Bid stepping in again here at 70. It's
incredible. This guy's like got endless
money, right? If they hold 70s now,
they're going to be in trouble.
Because these sellers are trying very
aggressively here. 70s again. This guy
passively just got absorbed here again.
Is there follow through now? They're
trying. 70 70. They're looking for 70
snap to get down to 60 and 50. This guy
stepped on the book twice now.
Still absorbing. My gosh, this guy's got
endless capital. Endless capital. All
right. 70s snap will lead you to sort of
60s, 50s, and 45s. But there is a buyer
just absorbing absolutely everything
here that he can. It's a really big
battle here.
That 70 hold. Wow,
man. I'm not I'm not messing with these
guys. They are uh
too big for me. Sit. I would love it to
trade down into here and then see
weakness, but there's just a guy in here
just non-stop. Just bid bid bid bid bid
bid bid bid. Let me have it all.
Then this retail I doubt this is retail
buying this uh amount non-stop. No, this
this won't be retail.
Here comes the 70s again. They're trying
to get this snap of 70s. They're
desperate to get this snap of 70s.
sellers.
Someone is saying no. I'm telling you.
There is a guy on the tape saying you're
not going down.
There you go. Look at that. Straight
back up.
Right. If they hold 80s now, then
they've got a shot at a squeeze out to
be honest.
There you go. They just held 80s.
Yeah, this is uh I'm not touching this.
This is
This is uh mental. I'll touch it when I
see momentum. Clear one side and one
side stuck. All I know right now is
there is a guy trying to absorb it. I
think we want to move lower, but he is
relentless.
Okay, back down to these 60s. Do we see
follow through now?
Just stuck at previous day value low and
current day value area low. If we see
follow through, you're going to see it
down to this New York open and then it
really the fun and games can start
underneath that. So, they're trying they
are now trying to get down to these 45s.
If they reject 70s and 80s here, there's
a chance for follow through downside,
but it's a big if based on what I've
seen so far.
If they reject this value, there's a
chance for this wash and rotation.
But I'd say it's a big if.
Not uh not sure I'm liking what I'm
seeing here. Look, they're restacking
now. 60s, 55s, 50s, 45s. There they go.
Just hanging around these 70s. Same
level that this buy has been up all day.
Well, I say all day for the last I know
20 minutes. If he gets stuck though, it
will get very aggressive. I tell you
that much because it's been nonstop
here.
They're off. They're bidding at 35 now.
So,
let's see if they stay heavy versus
these 870s and 80s. If they do, there's
a wash.
Maybe we can get these flow zones to
like come and trend and do something
rather than just be sideways all day.
Here's the attempt back into 70s and 80s
that they're trying
over 300. They have a squeeze. This is
the attempt back into value, back into
VWAP, back into this same level we've
talked about where we have just had a
little imbalance here.
Yes, right at that New York open.
We're just so stuck here, folks.
So, we're failing that so far on that
first attempt. Still not close this
candle, but
back into value if they don't reject
this. So, sellers will want to reject
here. If they can't reject here, they're
going to get squeezed out right to the
300s again.
And they haven't done a very good job.
Yeah, this is a leave alone for me. Let
these guys piss about with it.
Let them piss about with it. They don't
know what they want to do, so they can
just piss about with it.
There's the squeeze up to the 300 we
just talked about. Over 300. We can come
right back up to the 320. I mean, it's
just ridiculous what's going on here.
This is just like
huge battle over a level and then a
straight move up and then we'll lack
structure again probably. Look at this
bid. Look at this bid. Holy [\h__\h] This
guy has just absolutely gobbled
everything from 60s and 70s and is now
non-stop trying to bid up to the 360.
Oh my gosh.
Well, they're going to have to get
through this level, find acceptance
above 325s now, which is what they've
just tried to do on that last dip. And
if they do, they're going to try and
complete the move all the way to 400
Amino. But we lack structure now on this
straight move upside.
I don't know what to tell you folks.
We're inside a rotation.
They're holding it. They are holding
this
non-stop bid. I told you down there
there was non-stop bid.
I don't touch it when one side's just
being like that
when we can't break down and there's a
guy just like bye bye by bye bye. Like I
can't tell you like how much he bought
down here. It was ridiculous.
He just bought absolutely everything
non-stop, non-stop, non-stop, non-stop,
non-stop, non-stop. And then he chased
it all the way up.
I can show you it. Uh,
non-stop
buying, non-stop buying down here. Every
time it came down here was relentless
and then just chased this huge squeeze
up.
Okay, so ES back to these 890s now. If
they get through the 890s, there's a
squeeze. Otherwise, this is the edge
again.
890 is key on ES that we talked about.
Can hold a bid over it or not?
Delete this.
Let me There we go.
Yeah, just nothing to do here, folks.
Really, unfortunately, it's a bit messy.
Maybe some of you want to bid, try and
force this squeeze out. I mean, I'd be
watching for ES to hold the 890s and
find acceptance. It's I guess it's
trying.
Just remember we lack structure under
here. You want to be very careful.
There's a seller at 360s over over this.
Maybe we can start squeezing
and targets would be up here
70s and 90s and then through that right
up into 450s again.
Yes. Now going through that n that 90
level nicely. Can it hold a pullback
there? That's the key. You don't want to
look above and fail. Can ES hold a
pullback? Looks like it actually has
held a little pullback there
at 60s again. through here. We can go uh
yeah, definitely 80s and maybe 400s.
I'm just not interested. I'm not
interested in how they're setting this
up right now. I'm looking at a daily and
an hourly and just like doesn't look
very good.
Yes, trying to get going over those 90s.
Trying to force this squeeze up. It is
trying.
Into these 60s we go.
So, there's a seller here stacked up to
75. He's just sat on the book selling
everything that comes his way.
We can't get through him.
Fix right back down to lower day.
into this opening range high. Failing at
this opening range high. Buyers are
stuck above this opening range high
right now. You have delta above it into
60s caught. We had a passive seller
there that we talked about all morning
long. So buyers really need to get back
above that. If they don't, we're going
to go back into this rotation again.
We have got a seller up at 400 though.
So 60 is the key level. ES looks really
strong here. It's just can ENQ get back
above this outline delta into sort of
60. If it gets back above there then
maybe we go 80s 86s and 400s is on debt.
But we will have to see
the moment it's struggling every push.
CBD looks awful, by the way.
It's just like barcoding.
Okay, testing these 60s again.
ES really starting to get going. It's
going to come into these 900s soon. So,
you got to imagine that whole number
might be a level for ES into this trap
buyer again. And still no acceptance
above the 60s. Above 60s there is a
squeeze out possible. And they keep
offering here into 75s all the way up
into 75s which is the edge of today.
What a boring day. What a shame. Or at
least we had a really nice trade to
start the day.
Yes. Uh someone's front running that
6,900 in ES. Be aware of that that whole
number.
Lower day mix
telling these 60s are big big levels
here. They got to get back above and
base above this if buyers want a shot of
getting up to these 400s. They are
trying. They cannot do it. Initial
balance now set as well folks.
So you can think about an IB rotation
day which might fit the profile
especially if we look above and fail.
Here they go. Trying to get to that IB
high the 70s failed again. Couldn't even
take out high of day. So weak
protecting that IB high. Did ES take it
out? I think it might have taken it by
tick or it just printed it.
Somewhat surprised there isn't like one
more squeeze up leg here for them to
sell into. Maybe they're going to try
now.
This is like the market last few weeks.
Compression rip compression. Can they
come and do a pop and then do they fade
that straight back down? Okay, taking
out that's the squeeze up we just talked
about. Take out these stops.
400's really the next level. 380s and
400. What's this here value?
You can watch ES here into that uh 900
we just talked about. Buyers just got
caught high day there on NQ for sure.
There's still someone trying to sell up
at 400.
This is ugly, mate.
It's ugly.
All right. How are we doing on stream?
Let's get these likes up. 650 of you
watching and only 200 likes. Come on,
folks. I want to do some giveaways.
Let's get this up to 400 likes, please.
Okay, here's the squeeze.
So, PDC will be into these 400s. ES now
into the 900s. That whole number.
And we can think about whether we go IB
uh initial balance look above and fail
or if we're going to hold and try and
actually come all the way up into here.
Both of these are possible right now.
QQQ coming up to 50 day and a big pivot.
It's trying to get up into this pivot
615 616 and QQQ.
Does it have the juice?
Let's measure from that gap. Hang on.
Give me a second. Coming right into 50%
off the gap actually on the cues on the
ETFs.
So, I might find some might struggle a
little bit up here. Let's see how we act
at IB.
rejecting
uh previous day value. Is that wrong?
Hang on.
Measure this out. I've done that.
That's way off, mate. What is that?
What's wrong? I must have moved it.
Okay, good to know. All right, into
previous day value high here. That's why
I was just checking. Sorry, folks. Just
looked different to Ninja and it was it
was wrong.
Okay, previous day close up here into
400. ES trying to find acceptance over
900 right now. There's lots of buying
activity coming in up here. They might
well get trapped soon. We can think
about an IB failure. Right? If we do a
look above, right into previous states
value into the 400 and we start failing,
we can think about that rotation back
down. It's very very possible.
So here's IB.
They set this up for us.
So, if we take the IB trade today, we're
going to have to be careful of a few
levels. A value area high into those
350s. The buyers that got trapped at
360. So, or they're not trapped. They
could have been trapped. They weren't.
So, we need to trade back under 360
really for us to really have
continuation follow through. Downside
that is right at the moment, we're
holding IB. Now, it's still printing IB
and holding. Same on ES. It's absorbing
IB.
Um, I'll consider the fade if we do
something like this. And otherwise,
we're probably going to squeeze all the
way up into here if we can't do that.
Holding IB for now.
We're right at the daily Ballinger low
as well.
Maybe a tiny little bit more room for
the QQQ.
if it really wants to come and back
test.
What was that pivot? 1455
to 16s.
The only thing I'm aware of is the cash
market. If we're going to really want to
back test
this level here, uh if I zoom out to my
15 minutes, make it easy for you to see
right here. This is also the 50-day,
right?
But if we look at this, this is the gap.
This is 50% retrace, right? from the gap
to the low. We're right into it. So,
we're coming into a level of interest.
Here we go. Starting to see that fade.
Watching these uh 60s now.
That's where the big buyer came in at
60s.
And he's rebid there again, folks.
He just rebid there again.
I'm saying I'm gonna wait for 60s
because this is where remember the big
buyer that was in here and we said we
had outlying delta. He's just rebid
there again. So twice. So he bid there
at 1027 and he just bid there again on
that last flush down exactly the same
level.
[\h__\h] hell. He's not done. Hey,
he's got balls of steel just bidding
this market nonstop.
What's our high B range today? Feel very
big. It's all right. 190 is actually
quite good. Bigger than I thought.
just not moving.
I'm going to wait for them to create
some volume and leave it.
buyer again.
Absolutely [\h__\h] relentless bid.
I am somewhat surprised he's got that
bigger bollocks.
Thank you.
seller up here at 400 and then 420s
is kind of a nothing area. What's this?
Previous week low. Okay,
that's the start of the pivot then.
Okay, so 420 is they're going to try and
go to previous week low then
planet protection team. Yeah. Yeah,
that's a good way to put it.
Okay, into sort of the edge of current
week's value as well. So here to 420 is
the next key level and then up there
this is like supply untested really
we're coming into the edge like we are
in past the edge of the last two days
balance.
So previous week low about to be tagged
here. This green line on your screen.
High time frame algo above Globeex above
that.
Where's the outlier? 400 is the first
outlier. So see if they rebid this 400.
And then it's still the 60s, right?
Still the 60s. There's a big shelf down
there now. This level here. So, we're
bullish all the time. We're holding this
uh in the short term. That is
delete this now as well. We've traded
through it.
So, this is the level here
where that big buyer came in.
the previous day value area high trying
to rebid this at the moment.
I don't think this lasts forever. I
don't think they can just keep bidding
and bidding and bidding and bidding and
bidding. Uh I think he's probably
bidding to get his exit. It's just
where's his exit? Is it previous week
low? Is it up in in this like untested
supply?
They have to hold the gray box. Yeah,
they have to hold gray box. The buyers
Just trying to be patient. Wait for
something to stand out to me.
Definitely trapped buyers at 400 so far,
but structure is still bullish.
It's trying to catch a little bit of a
bid at 1875.
No man's land though.
No man's land. Next pivot now is 1925
for a back test on VIX.
Right in this previous day value area
high right now. If we don't find
acceptance in that, then we're going to
rotate previous days value again.
Here
we go. So, do we come back down towards
IBM 60? They still bidding above
previous day's value.
See if they build out a node here and
then leave it.
Then we might have a trade back inside
the range if we're lucky. If we're very
lucky.
Yes, still holding initial bands. We
kind of need some of these to start
seeing some weakness. Here we go. Back
to the IB, back to the 70s. Big seller
trying to force this market down into
60. He wants to retest that level I've
talked about a few times.
61.
Yes. Still holding initial balance.
Need to get under this level. Right. If
we leave this, if we leave this trapped,
we build enough volume up here
and we trade under this. This is
possible.
Not until then.
Trying to get down there.
Yes. Still absorbing.
Lots of bids down here. 75 to 55 stacked
up at the same. It's the same level.
It's basically the gray box that I'm
looking at.
same level.
We need to get un if we're going to stay
heavy, we got get go under that and see
a look above and fail basically of the
IB. A look above previous day close and
fail.
Yes, still absorbing for now. Here comes
a big seller. Big seller. All right,
here's the 60 test. This is what we're
looking for. Now, do we stay heavy now?
Do we see absorption or we going to see
a snap trade?
They've got a resell 60s now. 60 to 70s.
They've got a resell for me to really
like this.
It's a retest of this same level. So 60
to 70 is what is this guy? Well, they
started selling at 75. All right. So
they've got to stay heavy at 75.
And if they do, I'll look for a join.
They are starting to sell this more.
Here's value area low. Value area high.
Sorry. on the date.
So, already starting to see that. Can we
see further rotation under it or are
they going to try and increase value?
The 75 is the trigger point. You do not
want this back over 75. Really,
there is an imbalance up to 7750s,
but the big seller stepped in at 75. You
want him to remain in control for this
rotation. Now, bid at 50 and 40. Let's
see if we can trade through these. I
want to trade under 46es here.
If we go sideways for too long, I'm
going to lose interest very quickly. I
need sellers to step in aggressively
now. They've done the work. We've
trapped the buyers aggressively now.
Aggressive, please.
Come on, baby.
We can watch previous day point and
control F30s as a as a um first cover
point all the way down until VWs if we
can.
Go away, Mr. Buyer. [\h__\h] off. Here we
come. Come on. Get him. Get him out the
way. Don't let him rebid this, please.
Oh, come on. Institutions, step on the
tape. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come
on. Come on.
Need to see it soon. I don't want to go
sideways too long here or we'll get
relief to 70s very very quickly.
Step on the tape, please. Step on the
tape. Here you come. Step on it now.
Step on it. Thank you. More.
More.
Come on. Let's go. 30s. Come on. Come
on.
Jesus Christ, guys. Come on. Please.
making my life harder than it needs to
be today.
Here we go. Here we go. Thank you. Thank
you. Thank you. Right. Looking for a 30s
cover and then BWAP. Really nice. Don't
want to reclaim with this now. We've
done all the hard work. So you can trim
some on the way down. This is what we
just talked about. Leaving this trading
under this rejection and we're looking
for this ultimately.
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank
you. Thank you.
Jesus Christ.
Let's get me my VWAP trade. IB to VWAP.
Let's get it.
The Tyson trade. Come on.
Let's go.
[\h__\h] yeah, man. That required so much
patience. It's insane.
All right, you can cover some here into
previous day point of control and the
VWOPS. These are our cover points for
the shorts. And you can hold runners all
the way back down to value area low.
Let's go, baby.
Undefeated. Unfucking defeated that
trade. I'm telling you, beautiful.
There's your cover point. Really nice
team.
Really, really nice. W's in chat if you
got that. Oh, it was not easy. I want my
entry in this little guy here. 1048.
You can hold runners if they get very
weak because we lack structure in this
this candle here. We lack structure. All
right. So, if we get underneath this and
stay heavy, there's a very good chance
we come all the way down to the low.
But you must cover the majority of
position here. Nice work, team. Yeah, I
love it. Absolutely. There you go.
There's Tyson. Nailed it. It's the Tyson
trade.
Nice work, folks. Look at all you guys
with some nice winners here. Really
nice.
Really, really nice.
Great work.
Had no idea I entered. I mean, I think I
called out what I was looking for for
quite a long time. We talked about the
VWAP trade. We talked about trapping
buyers above the 400. I told you
numerous times buyers have got caught
above 400. I told you I will get heavy
if we come under here and we stay heavy
at 60 because that's where the big buyer
came in. All right, he came in here and
here. And once he becomes my point that
I can get heavy against, I get heavy and
the cover is here. We talked about it. I
literally drew it out for you. I told
you I'll be looking for buyers to be
trapped above here. And I drew this out
for you. Rewind it. I literally drew
that out for you. That exact when we
were up here, I drew that out for you.
Told you what I'd be looking for.
So now the question is, do we reade this
again?
This right here is a retest.
All right. This right here, this guy.
Right. If we look at here,
this guy
right here. Get stuck. All right, big
sell. There's your retest.
There's your flush.
Right. The buyers came in here at 60s,
65s to to 70s. They came in and got
stuck.
We're going to come and revisit. There's
an imbalance here up to 76. So now
you're seeing does this stay heavy? All
right. Do we protect this level or
further downside is the question now?
No, it's all right, Breezy. But like
it's not that you're tripping. I'm just
saying like we're not always going to
get perfect structure. Remember, the
market isn't always perfect. So like
this move here, see this wick? That's
your retest. It's not always going to be
like a two, three bar buildout, which
would be lovely. Don't get me wrong. It
would have been better if we did that,
but we don't always get that, especially
when one side's caught. Remember, above
400. If I can show you,
right, this guy here got caught. This is
delta. This buy side delta got caught.
And this is the guy I traded against.
Remember 100 lot, 100 lot. And I said
he's caught at 60s. This is his pain.
So, we the moment we fail to reclaim
that, he remains stuck. So it means him
and the big player at 400 are all stuck.
So we use their pain to move downside.
Yeah.
It's not always like unfortunately with
trading it's not always going to be
picture perfect. We're not always going
to get like a retest like this. Like
this is like if this had come reached up
into here like is the perfect retest.
We're not always going to get that.
Sometimes we will. Sometimes we get
lucky but we won't always get it.
No, no, you're good. You're good. You're
good.
Okay. Still holding runners here. Maybe
break lower under VW up. We will see.
Nice rejection here. I wouldn't want to
see it like again, you don't want to see
it reclaim anything up here. You do not
want to see it reclaim anything up that
top side. You want to see heaviness stay
in the market for runners here.
It's trying to break down here. It's
desperately trying to get under these
VWs.
ES into a key pivot level here as well.
Rejecting 90 at the moment. So, rejected
over 900. There's no close above the IB
um since we've rejected. We're coming
back down to VWAP. It's got New York VW
up left. Heavy heavy market for these
runners. You never know. We might get a
full rotation if we get very very lucky.
But this here, remember, is key. We
talked about it. this guy right here.
This is where the imbalance came in,
right? Question is, can we fill some of
this downside? Now,
looks great for our runners here, guys.
We very well might go back down to um
value area low on the day if we get
very, very lucky here.
Would be nice.
Just manage your position. You should be
short from up here somewhere. Maybe some
of you added here. You should be short
from somewhere up here. So, just manage
this position and let's see if we can go
lower.
Where did this guy reid earlier? 87ish.
So I'd like to trade back in sort of 90s
if possible where he started bidding
earlier.
90s would be good for the next cover
point. 90s down to yeah 80s would be
nice under there. We'll see very very
like strong weakness if we can get under
those.
Is it an A+ setup? No, probably not.
It's It's a decent setup, but it's not
an A+
mainly because of the daily
There's a chance for more downside here.
They might need to come and revisit the
70s first, but we will see.
trying to find a bid coming up for that
um pivot that we talked about that 1925
point on VIX. So you want to see VIX
reclaim that really if we're going to
stay short in this
don't want VIX to come up and reject
this pivot.
So here's the squeeze and they're
probably going to retest some of this
now that we just talked about. Here we
go. So retesting those levels we just
talked about
ES holding its pivot as well. So this
gray box becomes absolutely key now.
And the 60s again, right? The 60s are
where those buyers came in. So this is
going to be key
cuz do they become sellers? This is the
first retest to see if they become
sellers. If they don't become sellers
and we reclaim IB, you do not want to
touch this. You've probably taken all
your profits now. I'm just waiting to
see if I should consider a re-entry here
or not.
getting this buyer. Look at this
relentless bid. It's actually quite
insane that we're getting these huge
candles up and drip downs.
IB being retested here.
Still holding the 60s. He's just rebid
60s. This is a dangerous take today.
He's going to play games like this.
He's still rebidding 60s and 70s. Wild.
Wild. So, he's still comfortable right
now. So, the next level's 400 really.
So, I'm not touching this right now.
We're going to have to close under some
pain points for him. And we're not doing
that.
We are definitely not doing that.
And Vick's just rejected that pivot.
[\h__\h] me. What a mess.
400 we go then.
Well, this is ridiculous. I'm not
trading this. No chance.
Too many games going on here today. We
have had like two nice trades. There's
no way I'm gonna play this guy's game.
He's relentless bid
on the key levels and gets a squeeze and
then no one shows up again. So,
I'm not going to fight him. He's way too
big for me to play. Well, I'm not going
to play upside and I'm not going to
fight him. So, I'm just going to leave
it.
Best way I can put it.
Look at that. [\h__\h] insane, mate. 400
test. This is was the pain point,
remember? And now back there. Now back
over this 400 again.
Absolutely insane.
In a quiet dull market, he's just ripped
it 100 points by himself.
It's also like news dropping like
Lutnik. The US trade deals with Europe
are durable. They're not durable if
you're going to keep threatening them,
mate. Like this is what makes me laugh
about news. You've just had your
president threaten UK nonstop for like
three or four days.
Okay. So, I couldn't hold over 400.
Probably
new shelf being developed here now.
And just move this up. This is messy,
man. This is so messy.
I'm leaving this alone now, folks, until
something drastically changes.
Back to IB, back to these 60s again.
Honestly, it's like straight up,
straight down. It's absolutely insane.
Probably moving off the news more than
anything off silly comments.
Okay, if they rebid IB, there is a
chance to complete the rotation up here
for sure. But, uh, I'm not going to play
it. I'm going to be honest with you.
It's too risky for me right now how
we're operating.
This is the same kind of level we bid at
earlier. He was actually a bit lower
earlier. He was more like 60s.
You can see he's here again. He keeps
bidding
70s75s.
Has he got his exit is the question. I
don't think that was an exit.
rebidding again. It's It's absolute
relentless.
We were supposed to go down because it
break gray box. It failed due to Ricky
Rich playing around. But was the model
right? No, we
the model was here.
This was the model. We waited to see if
there was a retest to add. He squeezed
up. So, we don't add.
Now, if he wants to hold this and
complete rotation, he will. I'm not
going to really try and reade this. When
we're back above IB, we've built
liquidity and there's a chance to
complete rotation. They needed, if I was
going to add more size on, I would have
needed to see a rejection here, which we
haven't seen. And the thing is now he's
come firing in here and firing in here
with massive size. So, I don't feel
comfortable trading in here now in this
slope. So, I'm just going to leave it
alone. It's a messy day. The thing is
with everyone that like looks for
models, like a model just based on
levels, you got to understand the
environment as well.
Yes. Back down to VW up again. Back into
this pivot.
We're Yeah, we're within the frame, but
there's a big difference between this,
right, and this.
That's a very big difference where we're
holding. You have to understand the
nuance of this. These guys are now not
trapped. So, we're not we can't play
against them, right? Do you understand
liquidity? These guys is what we used to
break down. Did they become sellers? No.
We're back inside their range. So they
can now resqueeze which is why I'm now
not interested in the market. We did not
show any ability to trade down from
there. We are not using their pain to
move lower right now. We're adding
liquidity in the same level. So, I need
to wait now to see what they want to do
cuz it's very very possible they do this
if they want.
Uh,
yes, Breezy 360. Yes, potentially for
the squeeze. This is that exactly what
we're seeing now.
As we always said, if they hold IB, they
can do this inverse head and shoulder
look and they can try and complete
rotation.
That's why I'm not interested in the
short side right now.
Weekly gap. Um,
we'd have to trade all the way up to
I mean 700s. I mean it's asking a lot JD
but
in this market
who knows
or do you mean the edge of the weekly
gap like so four sort 475 to 700 is
basically the weekly gap the actual gap
who knows JD yes it's is it's definitely
possible this market will do whatever it
wants to Okay.
Just requires patience today, guys.
Like, I don't want to trade this upside.
I don't know. Maybe I'm being stubborn,
but I'm not. I just don't want to get
stuck in it.
It would be the counter trend relief
trade. I'm just trying to avoid that.
US wants to colonize UK.
I mean,
aren't you just us?
It's just the whole thing's [\h__\h]
ridiculous what's going on right now.
Can't believe anyone's okay with it.
He's telling Europe to react to UK at
the moment. Like,
Europe doesn't like you, mate. You've
pissed them off nonstop. Like it's
mental.
Absolutely mental.
Okay. So, they're trying to do this uh
inverse head and shoulders we just
talked about
and 420 would be the next target.
It's relentless bid, man.
Here's
Relentless Bid. Here we go.
Bid, bid, bid, bid, bid.
We go. There's the 420. So, it's
previous sweet low now. And then the
pivot. We're into that big old pivot
now.
I'd say all the way up to sort of
515ish.
So, into this red block
and then you just have to see what it
wants to do. It's uh kind of wild. I'm
impressed. I'm impressed by it. Let's
put it that way.
Impressed by this bid on the tape this
morning.
Divergence here to ES VIX at low of day.
And I just think Q's is very close. So
we talked about Q's coming into 1450s
or for 15s even. It's just hit 15s. We
got the 50-day at 16. So we've got like
a dollar range there on the ETF where I
think there is a chance we will see
failure. If it squeezes through that,
it's going to be a giant squeeze. This
is the same kind of levels here. We're
looking at the same kind of thing here
really folks.
Black Tuesday.
It's just another Tuesday. I mean,
they're calling it what? Because we were
gapping down. I mean, Ed, you'll
understand it. Like things that sell um
the most as in when I say sell, create
news the most are extreme views, right?
So like the market's dead. It's the end
of the world is like going to cause an
extreme view. So people love to put
names on stuff.
You just tra just trade what's in front
of you. Forget forget all the hyperbole
and hysteria. Just trade what's in front
of you. All right. previous week low
here acting as some form of resistance
for now. There's still offers above into
440s.
They've rebid this and just forced the
extension. We are technically bullish
over all these levels at the moment. I
want to be very careful thinking about
fade here. So I said I'm going to leave
it alone. The moment it didn't react to
this says to me, okay, if we're not
going to respect this volume, if we've
traded away and we've caught this first
trade, we've covered most into here.
Waited to see if there was an ad
opportunity. We traded straight through
it. cut the rest and we've rebid this
same level. Now we're expanding higher.
It's just going to keep doing this until
they've got their exit. I don't know
what their exit is, folks. Maybe it is
previous week low. Maybe it's GlobeEx.
Maybe it's into this bid. What's this?
Is that Friday's low? That's Friday's
low. Maybe it's all the way up there.
We're certainly not bullish overall.
Okay. This is what you to understand the
different uh time frames
back to these 400s.
We're not talking about Greenland being
in Europe. Who's saying Greenland's
Europe? No one said Greenland's Europe.
I'm talking about his comments today to
the UK about UK territory. I'm not not
talking about Greenland.
All right, previous day value area high
and flow zones are down here. see if
they're going to rebid these same
levels,
60s kind of
and 80s,
or if they're going to let it go.
They've got their exit. Now, you got
divergence to ES for sure.
QQQ definitely reacting off that pivot
which is Wednesday's lows supply from
Wednesday.
Okay, previous day value area highs this
rotation again to this gray box. Do they
rebid this or not? If you lose this gray
box, then I guess we have the same trade
setup as earlier.
consider it. I could consider it. I
guess it's just me. It's very messy how
they've set it up, though.
If they lose this, I'll consider the
rotation underneath. Not not in front of
they would have to lose this again. I
would need to see this, right?
And I need to see trap buyers come in
here. So, I'd need to see this move here
for me to be interested at this point.
Otherwise, I'm not interested.
We are rejecting the developing value
which is 407s.
I just keep looking at the hourly
thinking this looks not very good for
upside.
But uh it just depends if they want to
squeeze over it or not. Okay, here back
to the 80s we go. And do we rotate
underneath this gray box or not? This is
what we keep talking about over and over
and over again. Right. So I'm my eyes
are firmly
in here right now. I'm looking at this
pivot
which we've come into on QQQ on the ETF.
Right, we're rejecting this. I'm
watching value for this week. We've had
no acceptance below. So we've come back
to the top side, but we're not finding
acceptance above. So the question is, do
we then rotate back down again?
Rotation. Okay, rotational market.
My least favorite market, but it's what
we've got.
So still holding gray box. Still no
trigger for me.
Right,
first bathroom break of the day coming
up. I'd like to do some giveaways. We're
almost time to do giveaways. Smash that
like button.
Okay. Okay. Still building out here. Big
shelf being built out here now. Lots of
volume being built out here.
Okay.
Big buyer got caught, did he?
The 400 lot again, the 400 level. I
mean, they're still holding for now.
We're not We're not traded away from it
yet. Once we start trading away from it
and we know that they're caught, it'll
be good. Um,
we got to get back under these 80s
really.
So 4 400 to uh to 380 is your current
rotation, right? They're just battling
over. We're building out volume
basically. This will start to thicken
up, right? Like this, right? We're
building out this volume shelf at the
moment.
Let's see if we can leave the shelf, get
into IB, and rotate. under here again.
Remember, I got to remind you 60s was
the level that they bid at all day long.
He's been very aggressive at 60. If he's
had his exit, he won't be there. And
that would be nice. If he got his exit
into pre maybe he just needed to get
into previous week low or something to
get his exit. So, if he was long from
here all last week, he needed to bid up
just to get out as possible.
I mean, he had some serious size to do
it.
Uh yeah, that value area will certainly
shift up if we stay up here, if we don't
leave it soon. Point of control will
shift if we're here too much longer as
well. You can see we're developing a lot
of uh volume up here at the moment.
So, we're finding price acceptance here
at the moment. We're we're looking to
leave this area and we're not leaving
this area. If they hold it, we can't
rule out coming up here. We cannot rule
that out, right? which is why we need to
have patience for this next trade. If if
it sets up, might not set up.
Yeah, 10 year. They they all they all
went flying. Maybe you missed this
morning, JD. They all did that move.
We've talked about that breakout Move.
They want to trade 75s here. They're
trying to get these 75s going.
This guy's still bidding 80s.
They're sat trying to absorb at 80s and
below at the moment. Let's see if we
trade into them and how we act.
Be nice to get one more trade here.
Yeah, I'm sure it did, Dave. I don't I
don't give any uh credit to MQ
because no institutional player is using
MQ, right? So, I need to know where the
volume is that institutional players are
using.
Oh, sorry to hear that JD. Hope you're
okay, mate. Okay, buyers trapped at 400
again there. They came in aggressively
at 400 again and got sold into. That was
a big lot there or decent size 75 plus
lot into 400. He just got trapped again.
We need to see this move away from this
gray box. I'm trying not to uh front run
this, but definitely
developing weak value area high 400 is a
big level. They keep fading that. Every
time a buyer steps in here, he's being
sold into. So that's one good sign. We
just need to move away from this level
now and we have to be aware of 60 if
we're going to trade it. Starting to see
volume come in for downside. So here's
80s again. Can we see some aggression
step in here and some momentum start to
take over
back to the 80s. We want to see this
trade back down to 60s. We want to lose
this PC now and trade downside.
And we're going to have to be very
careful in and around 60s. Okay. I don't
know if they're going to rebid it.
Need to see follow through. Come on,
guys. Hello. Wakey wakey. Just snap it.
Yes. Doing it. Coming back down to VWAP
already. Here we go. Okay. Beautiful.
All right. Be careful into 60s here. If
you're trading this with me, you can
cover some into 60s and we can look for
continuation under now. Same trade as as
earlier. Be very careful into this level
here. If they start absorbing the tape,
I want this buyer to just disappear. If
he's not here, we can go lower. We're at
value area high on the day here. So,
cover a little bit here and let's see.
Yes. Let's go. Give me more. Give me
more. Give me more. Let's rotate the
whole [\h__\h] value now. Right, Alex,
calm yourself down, mate. Right into
this imbalance. Be careful here. Right.
This is where we squeezed up. So, we're
going to fill some of this in. We have a
node here into sort of 50s, 47s, and
50s.
Yes. Beautiful.
Taking a little bit up off there so I'm
not greedy. And let's see if we can
rotate the whole way.
Next stop I've been looking at. It will
be 530s.
Again, took lots of patience. I wasn't
even convinced I was going to take it.
Let's go.
ES letting go now. Thank god. Right. I
want to see VIX trade through this pivot
that we came and failed at earlier into
1925. Coming into point of control here.
Make sure you're covering some into the
330s here. Please into these VWAPs.
Please make sure you're covering some.
And once we bleed below this, it would
be really fun, but we got to assume that
might not happen.
the same setup as earlier really. They
just have to do one more squeeze out. So
my assumption now is the guy that was
relentlessly bidding these, he needed
his exit up here into that weekly level.
He's got his exit because he's not
appeared again at 60. So if we reject
60s now and reject this, we should wash
hard. If he's done with it, we should
wash hard because he's been propping it
up all day.
Let's go. Right. Here are the 30s. VWAP.
So, IB to VWAP again.
Pay yourself here. Please
want this node. Now, really, if we pop,
this has to act as resistance. Don't
want to reclaim of that.
Certainly don't want to reclaim at that.
Go. We're going to come test this level.
So, same level, right? 60 is where he
was earlier. We don't want to just
squeeze straight through and we
certainly don't want it through 80s. All
right. That will be a leave alone
scenario for me, just like last time if
we do that.
set up 80s and above
VWAP. Do they resell this now? It's a
good resell there.
Mr. Bid still here at 60s again,
mate. This guy
All right. Well, it's now or never. They
either sell this now or they will sell
it never and we're going to go back
upside again.
Very ugly if they reclaim this shelf
above this gray level. So, we want red
and gray to reject. Otherwise, well,
this market will be screaming upside
again.
Watching carefully, waiting to see if I
see a buyer come and get stuck here.
sellers last time came in aggre
aggressively into 75s. Thanks.
Take my runner off here.
theory me.
Well, it's now or never. If they squeeze
through this, then it's a leave alone
all the way into lunch for me probably.
They've had enough opportunities to get
it done here today and they haven't done
it. That's uh that that's a relentless
bid again. So, he didn't catch it and he
came back in his 60s and look at that.
[\h__\h] me. What a [\h__\h] market. Can't get a
runner to go today. What a [\h__\h] market.
No follow through. Well, at least we
paid ourselves. But [\h__\h] hell, man.
How can they let one guy just go bid bid
bid bid bid bid bid bid and not defend
twice?
It's the same play again. So, we break
away. So, what we did earlier, all
right, we break away, retest, straight
through. We break away, retest, straight
through. It's
It's bad. Like it's bad. It's bad.
There's no sellers defending levels.
There are no sellers defending levels.
That's That's not good. That is not
good.
You went long at 340. Yeah, I don't mind
like that. But the fact of the matter
that we've traded through this and this
uh is not good. We're not respecting
levels here on ENQ. We're not respecting
volume.
We're just one-sided when we go up.
We're one-sided.
Like, we're ripping through, ripping
through, ripping through. If they
recatch this on a bid now,
what are you going to do?
Can't can't sell it again. It's had the
opportunity, right? I can't sell this
again. Now, this is just like earlier.
We're back over the level. So, I don't
My feeling is we're not respecting
levels uh at the moment, and that's
problematic.
What a squeeze. If they sell this all
the way that down after running my
runner out. Oh my god. You absolute
something or others.
Big buyer here again.
You absolute something or others I won't
say on stream.
And they're now using this low volume
node as support. That's disgusting, man.
Yeah. Done with this for the day. No way
am I touching this.
No way am I touching this.
Look at that.
would have really liked to have uh just
got a follow through today,
but no. Well, at least we paid
ourselves. It's just a shame, man. It's
just a shame.
And they're rebidding. They're not done
with it. [\h__\h] hell, man.
Right, let's do some giveaways. How we
doing for the likes?
Need 40 more likes here, folks.
Sorry, 30 more likes here. Let's get to
400.
and they would do giveaways cuz I'm not
touching this rest of the day. Now,
this is just this is what I would call
sloppy. So, protected this, which is
fine. That's why we cover into here. But
the fact that this isn't protected and
we run straight through and this isn't
protected and we run straight through,
that concerns me
of the lack of respect for levels and so
I need to be very very careful. They've
clearly not got their exit.
Overall, we're bearish. Daily is right
on lower Ballinger band. We've extended
outside the lower Ballinger band a
quarter bid, which makes sense. We don't
want to extend outside of that. It's
trying to hold up and let the market
catch up to it. But, uh, how we're
playing intraday, trading through stuff,
that concerns me when we do stuff like
this. That really concerns me.
Five and 15 look ugly. Let's have a
look.
Yeah, it's just straight bit up back to
this level. Right, here's your gap.
There's your gap.
Here's your supply.
And they're trying to retest this. It's
what they want to do. They're trying to
come into this, which they're already
there's divergence because we're already
into this in the ETF. This is just 615s
in the ETF.
It's why they keep getting stuck here
every time.
[\h__\h] hell. Trading View piss me off.
There we go.
Right back into that same level again.
There you go. Just straight squeeze back
up. This is what I mean. They're not
respecting levels. The sellers will will
not step in at the moment.
At least we got some
three for three. But it was
this this
and this. But no follow through
unfortunately. At some point probably
when I'm off stream they probably do the
follow-through trade.
Sods law, right? Well, probably when I'm
done with it, they probably give the
follow through when they're done messing
about.
No. Well, I'm trying to I'm trying to
stick to the higher time frame, right?
I'm trying to stick to the higher time
frame. So, that's why I'm trying to
trade the extremes on the sell. I'm
trying to trade the protrend, which is
in a cell. Trying to ignore the bid up.
It doesn't mean it can't go higher. It
doesn't mean it's not a valid trade for
you guys. But if, let me zoom this out.
Right? If the main trade
right now is
is leaving all of this, right, we've
left four weeks worth of volume, right?
I want to sell this down into the next
block. The counter trend bid up is
possible, but I would rather wait for
buyers to get stuck and sell it down,
which is what we're trying to time
today. I don't want to play this this
trade here, right? I'd rather lean on it
back down. It's a safer trade for me.
Hopefully that makes sense. That's the
only reason
it's the higher time frame.
Okay, 400 likes. Let's do a giveaway.
Wait for me to set it, please, folks,
because I haven't set it up yet. So, if
you type it too early, nothing will
happen. Let me set it up.
Okay, first one, we're going to give
away Apex account. Just type FCT in chat
once.
minutes. Please don't spam, guys. Please
don't spam. We only need to do it once.
Blowback's hanging out here. 440 still.
You guys 30 more seconds and we'll pull
this winner up so it's ready.
Okay. Three, two, one.
Danny Snipes. I'm sure Danny's won
before. Danny Snipes, you here?
Let me know you're here, Danny.
Nice. All right. Just shoot me an email,
info@flowzonerader.com.
Send me a screenshot of you logged in
and I we'll sort you out a free Apex
account any size you want. Give it
another 15 minutes, guys, and we'll do a
course giveaway as well.
You never won. Okay, cool. Oh, that's
good. There you go. New winner.
New winner. Right. New hive day there.
Just about just about nicked the hive
day. Missing GlobeEx still. Still not
taking out GlobeEx.
Back to these 400s. It's amazing the
chop going on here.
Multiple drives now into this key level.
We know that they're going to keep
selling this key level. It's just when
is there going to be follow through if
ever? Hopefully soon. Back down to
previous day value area high and point
of control. Now big node down here. If
we start losing this, do they rotate
again? Probably. But Alex is pretty much
exhausted from having a go too many
times into lunch. So, is this the time
when they do it? Like I said, it's
probably going to happen when I've had
enough goes, right? It's probably going
to happen when I've had enough goes.
It's kind of what we're seeing at the
moment.
Certainly feels that way.
If they reject this node, it's probably
going to happen. I just uh yeah, I've
had a few attempts here already, folks,
haven't I? So, having to just say to
myself, hey, you've made good money.
There's not been follow through. Do you
really want to keep forcing?
You're going to really do it now when
I'm out. You are, aren't you? You
[\h__\h] horrible bastards.
If they flush this low of day,
you are gonna see a grown man cry like a
little baby on screen on stream. If they
flush this love of day.
Oh, you can only laugh.
You can only laugh. I know it's coming.
It's just [\h__\h] sod's law. It's sod's
law. It's going to do it. It is sods law
that this is what is now going to
happen. Boom boom boom boom boom boom
boom. I guarantee it.
This is trading chat. It's funny. You
just got to laugh.
No, here it comes. Oh my god.
If you want to play it, if you want to
play it, you need to do what I just
said. Really? You You need a reaction
from here. This is what we failed to
react off, right, each time. But they're
flushing through again. If they don't
protect this low now, if they sell this
and don't protect the low, they will
collapse the the move today. There's lot
lots of people keep trying to attempt to
bid this up and if they haven't got it
like one two three as your three drives.
It's just a shame we haven't rejected
underneath but I think it's probably
coming. This is a big strong flush.
I'm just a little bit upset that I'm not
uh not getting it my way.
Sods law. Oh, it's an English saying. Um
what that be the equivalent of? Um,
I don't know how to explain sods law.
It's like it happens when you're not in
it. Like you're positioned for something
and it does it when you're not in it. Or
like you buy a lottery ticket every week
with the same numbers and the one week
you don't buy it, you would have won.
That's sods law. It's like an English
saying.
Yeah, they watch my live stream. They
definitely don't
You're riding the triple top. Oh, you're
short at the highs. Very nice. Very
nice. Everything over 400's been a good
short today. Basically,
you see they're stacking here at um
65 and 70s. They want to sell this down.
Yes, back to V up. They want to sell
this down, folks. They are trying to
sell this down. You're probably,
honestly, you're probably going to get
the move I was waiting for all day.
You're probably going to get it. I'd
watch point control into 330s. And if
you lose that, it is good night,
sweetheart.
So, if you lose this down here, it is
good night. You're going to get full
rotation.
At least you can see it. It's uh at
least you can see what we we were
looking for each time. Well, we're three
for three. It's not like we've lost.
It's just like if this does the follow
through where I would have made all the
money.
What does that mean? Uh Matthew,
what's that?
What does it mean?
Yes, Victor Meldrew. I don't bloody
believe it. Yeah, I don't bloody believe
it. Showing our age there. Um, so I'll
be watching for a rejection here. Either
of this. This is literally is exactly
what we're looking for earlier, right?
Either here or here needs to reject full
follow-through downside. That's what I
would be personally looking for. I'm not
going to trade it now. I've had three
attempts on the day.
Ronaldo.
Ronaldo for me.
People will hate me for that, but
Ronaldo Messi for me.
I did go and watch Messi last year
uh for into Miami against LAFC and
Suarez and all them lot. Right. So, here
you're going to get this retest. This is
what's important.
this retest here.
So 370 380s. Where's this edge? 380s.
So how we react here becomes key.
Remember the last few times we simply
haven't reacted. We've traded straight
back through it. Which is why I'm not
having a huge winning day because my
runners just won't go for me today. So,
we're going to do the same thing.
They're still trying to bid the same
level.
And it's all depends whether they reject
this low volume node and sellers protect
this high volume node for downside
action or do we trade straight back
through it to the upside. I don't know,
folks. We should be trading downside. I
would That's how I've lent on it all
day. Right. Been looking for
acceleration downside.
There you go. So, you're starting to see
that reaction in a good way. You want to
see a lower low here. You want to see a
bare flag and a lower low and a snap.
What I'd want to see is
this and come and clean out these guys
here. If you're lucky, you get down
here.
It's looking good. It's looking good. If
any of you have taken that, it's looking
good.
Miami's Bambi. Yeah, it's true.
It was all right. I just got annoyed
like it was just a stadium full of
children screaming Messi even when he
didn't have the ball. He found it
annoying.
accidentally deleted the newsletter.
What was the zone for you this week? Uh
it was the old point of control
uh around 3
25 330s
and looking to see if we find acceptance
under underneath 25175. Right. So we
we're at the moment we're not finding
acceptance underneath which means
potentially we're going to back test uh
the edge of sort of balance. So all the
way up to 25700 but 25500 25700 seeing
if sellers want to reject there for
lower prices or not. The problem is
because of the gap we're going to need
like a day or two of consolidation just
for the Ballinger bands and SMAs to
catch up. So are we going to trade
straight through this again? Am I going
to be happy that I didn't take this
trade? If we trade straight through this
again, it is an awful This is awful.
This is awful. It just doesn't care. It
doesn't care about the nodes right now
in Q.
I get annoyed fast at things.
put you in my shoes right now, mate.
We'll see.
You're lucky I'm even here, honestly.
And that's not me being arrogant. If you
had going on in your life what I have
going on in my life, you probably
wouldn't be here. So, how about you
It takes a devil to drive out another
devil. That's a good one. Quite like
that.
Look at these washes, man. This is
crazy.
Crazy market. Back to point of control
again. Look at this. Wash up, wash down,
wash up, wash down.
Volatility still pretty high.
Well, that's it, Adam. That that that's
that's the problem. We're not respecting
enough well enough. My bias is downside,
but we're just not respecting. So, it
makes it very hard to position against
stuff when they keep doing these. And
now it's going to go. Is it mate?
It's crazy, isn't it?
Feels heavy to me. I tell you that. It
feels like it wants to move lower.
Starting to look like a little bit toppy
in my mind.
This is still the key level. Same levels
node here at 40.
I think there's a drift back down into
these at the very least. And I think
really if you see weakness, you might
see this come all the way back down. Y
it's very very very possible
if that buyer who's been in all day
starts telling turning into a seller the
tape will change very quick.
Someone's trying to sell down to 30s
again.
Yeah, I know. They've been steady rise,
but you got to understand,
guys, when you're looking at the mag,
we went over this,
like they're being sold into, right?
They're being pops are being sold into
on the MAC. Pops are being sold into.
Google hasn't. And that was the one this
morning that we said might have to gap
fill up here to be sold into. Right?
It's probably going to be sold into up
there, isn't it? That's where people are
trapped, right? If you understand what
support and resistance is and supply and
demand,
it's just trapped participants, right?
So anything that's driving higher,
you're just waiting for it to come into
a level where participants are trapped,
which is what we have here. If we zoom
out here, right? What's the level where
participants are trapped?
It's here.
It's here, right? This right here. If we
go QQQ,
why do you think we keep rejecting up
there? It's a big pivot, right? That's
why I said 15s and above. Big pivot. We
keep rejecting it.
It's not rocket science. It's just
they're making it harder today than it
needs to be
because they're not allowing you to have
follow through downside.
What platform I'm using? Ninja Trader. I
execute on Ninja Trader. This is Trading
View that you're looking at here. So I
can chat with you guys.
You want to test the jan low?
What? The 250s.
That's what you mean? Down here. Yeah,
very possible. today. You mean follow
through for 250? That that would be a
nice level to play to.
All right. Still they're trying to bid.
These are still the same levels, folks.
Same levels coming into lunch. You got
four minutes into lunch. Let's do one
more giveaway. Let me sort this out.
Okay, I give away a beginner course for
you guys. Just type course once in chat.
Back up to this same zone.
Incredible.
Incredible strength.
Goes a minute longer.
I really hope we get a follow-through
day this week. Really hope.
Definitely, Adam.
Definitely.
I mean, I got caught in it. Not for a
for a uh not here here but covered most.
Was it this one or this? I can't
remember. Or both. But runners got taken
out both times. Was so well positioned
for those runners to work. But look, we
made like 50 plus points. Just I'm
trying to get all the way down here. I
think there's a 200 plus point trade in
here. Just
do they need to come up for this first?
Do they really want to get into here?
It's a hell of a move. If they do,
we'll see. We'll see.
Yeah, I'm nice and green, but uh still
got caught in the [\h__\h]
Not not getting as green as I'd like.
It's horrible watching trying to be
patient with a runner and watching it
coming all the way back on you. It's
like just the worst feeling in the world
giving something room and giving 50
points back on it.
It's It's how it goes when you want to
set yourself for the big ones. All
right, let's pull this winner.
Three, two, one.
Jason Mackinson. I think I've said it
right.
Jason Mack
Maxon. There you go. Jason Maxon, are
you here? Jason.
Yeah, nice one, Jason. All right, all
you got to do, shoot me an email,
please, buddy. info@flowzonerader.com.
Just send me a screenshot of you logged
in. I'm just making a note of your name
here for the course and I'll get you the
introduction to trading course. Save
yourself 100 quid.
So, info@flowzontenttrader.com.
Send me a screenshot of you uh logged in
so I can see it's you.
That is probably going to be it, folks.
I am not convinced I'm loving this right
now. Um,
but this is what you've got.
We are in a cell. Believe it or not,
we're in a cell,
right? We're in a cell.
every popup into this block is getting
sold into. We're just not seeing this
follow through, which is what I would
really like to see. Uh the reason I want
to see that follow through is if we look
at this on the hour, so this is setting
you up for later in the day or tomorrow.
If we look at this hourly chart, right,
we cannot find acceptance so far
underneath here and we're trading to an
extreme of this. Okay, I want to sell
this back down to here, right? Cuz we
haven't retested this in a New York
session. So, I would like to sell
somewhere up here back down for this
retest. If we stay heavy under here,
then I think the market gets very very
weak. The reason being is if we start
zooming out, right, we're going to leave
all of these players trapped
and likely use these stops, which means
everyone here is now out of the money.
And it's at this point that you've
really got to think it's night night
because this is all on the new contract.
We'll be under the new contract lows and
it means, you know, we can start really
getting aggressive under 24.88 and start
diving back down for a retest into the
24500s and below. All right. So, that's
that's what I'm looking for with this
market. Um, if we reclaim this old
balance, if for whatever reason it wants
to reclaim this old balance, then I'll
respect it. But this is a area where
we've now left balance. All right? I
cannot stress that to you enough why
this is important. 1 2 3 4 5 weeks of
balance
in here. Think about all the buyers in
here who are stuck. We're under their
pain point. We want to try and sell
their point pain point for downside
pressure, right? But we have to respect
this one here.
So, we're selling pain down to here. If
we get acceptance under it, we're going
to look for new value probably down into
here somewhere and below. That's why I'm
focused short side right now. If we
reclaim this, fair enough. But if we
come up here and fail, I'll still be
looking to sell it. I'm not going to get
long unless we reclaim all of this and
start to base for a rotation. Okay.
Okay, so there's my sort of bias for the
week. Hopefully that kind of helps you
make sense of why I'm trying to fade
pops right now. Why I'm looking for
buyers to get stuck at highs is because
I know the higher time frame has a lot
of buyers stuck above.
Um, yeah, exactly. I would agree with
CB. Good day. Good green day. Same with
me. Good green day. Well into four
figures green, but not as good as it
could have been. If there was follow
through, would have been much bigger.
There we go. Any
questions, folks? You're into lunch now,
remember. Any questions? Anything you
want to ask before I get off?
I should probably tell tell you about
the prop firm, shouldn't I? So, never do
that. I'm not a very good affiliate, am
I? Uh, code FCT, what do you get right
now? Apex is 80% off. Um, with code flow
zone, take profit trader is 40% off.
funded next. I'm not sure what they've
the biggest discount there at the
moment. We can have a look.
Might be 20%. Maybe more.
Tradeify is 40% off at the moment as
well with my code FCT.
I can see these coming in at
It's not that bad. 14 $15 off right now.
Funded next on a 50k. I think there's
some big sales coming there soon.
Uh the VP indicator I got MT5 changes
the values when I change the time frame,
but I can't dock it in a certain time
frame. Which one do you advise me to set
up for accuracy when I trade with one
and five? I don't use MT5, so I couldn't
tell you, my friend. Sorry. I I don't I
don't know what to tell you there. I
don't use MT5. What size do you trade
and do you do props or live? Uh uh
futures, I trade props. And for uh ETFs,
I trade live account.
FCT didn't work for TP TPT. Yeah, it's
sorry, it's flow zone for TPT. The links
are all under there. Flow zone for TPT.
What indicators do I use? Just my flow
zones really. And VWAP.
Any resources I recommend to study? Um,
just anything for free. Do everything
for free on my channel first before you
do anything else. If you're looking for
stuff outside of that, um,
just all the usual key books, psychology
books really. Once you know the
technicals, it's just psychology. It's
all it is. Yes, Adam, don't worry. I'm
well aware. AP settings. Of course I
will. Of course I will. Here you go. So,
width 20, placement on the right. Sorry,
you want this, don't you? Ticks per row
and row size two
and leave value area as normal. And then
I have it um set to volume profile and
set for 20% width and placement on the
right. That's it. That's all I do. Very,
very simple.
How's payout with TPT? Payout with TPT
is very good. Very good. Very quick. Um,
it normally takes a day or two.
What have I taken this month?
Where are we? One, two, three, four,
5,000 out of it this month. Normally
takes a day or two. You normally put in
the request and then it takes uh maybe
12 hours after you put in the request
for them to approve. And then once the
request approved, you can transfer into
your account and that was normally done
same day or the next day. It's very
good.
Greetings from Oklahoma. My first visit.
I enjoyed your input on today's session.
What prop firms are you using? Um the
five down below. Uh Apex, Funded Next,
Take Profit Trader,
Lucid, Tradeify. Those are the five, my
favorite five this year.
How much adverse range do you allow per
trade? How do you size your position
around it? Uh I size based on the swing
points, right? Based on ATR and swing
points. So this is also one of the
problems today. So the ATR gets tight,
tight, tight, tight, tight, and then
we're having these huge candle rippers.
Um ATR was pretty volatile this morning.
But I size based on swings. So if I'm
where was I a breakdown? If I'm short
here for this breakdown, I'm risking up
here. I have to risk the other side of
this
And then depending on my account size,
right? If I'm short here, I have to be
willing to risk the other side of that
node. TP1 is into VWAP. And then TP2 was
down into here, which what I was hoping
to get a 7 and a half trade, 7.5 trade.
Didn't get it. We didn't get it. It's
okay. 150 point trade that would have
been. So it's all my sizing is always
based on where my stop is. My stop's
based on the technicals, right? Stop has
to be based on technicals. You can't
just do a 20 point stop cuz you feel
like it. If the ATR per 1 minute candle
is 20 or 30 or 40 points, then your 20
point stop doesn't mean anything.
What size accounts do I trade? Mainly
50ks.
Mainly 50ks.
You're currently This is a one minute
Any
books I advise to read? Yes. I give you
my book list. I should probably put all
this in my website, shouldn't I? Make it
easier for you guys. Um,
where's my Audible?
Do you ever reby blown TPT Pros? No.
Waste of money. They're like 600 bucks
to reby or it's like a hundred bucks to
just pass in two days. I wouldn't waste
that money.
Okay. Audio books.
Atomic habits. These are going to be
ones you all all be well aware of.
Atomic habits.
I don't like any of these ones.
Outliers. Malcolm Gladwell.
All of the market wizards. All of them.
Start with the old ones, but all of
them. Uh, trading the zone, Mark
Douglas. Mental game of trading, Jared
Tendler. Best loser wins, Tom Hoggard.
Um, I would say my favorite one, like I
always talk about though, is golf is not
a game of perfect by Bob Rotella.
Um, and then I would do like meditation
type stuff like Joe Despenszer or
anything like that calms your mind down.
And the world is for sale. Um, Javier
Blast if you want to understand the the
crookedness in trading and fooled by
randomness as well.
Very good book. All of those.
Oh. Oh. Hello market. You going to do it
while everyone's at lunch? Are you
bro any point video you can point to
show how to set up your indicators on
trading view? Do you already have my
indicators on trading view? It's just
one. It's the is my flow zone pro like
it's just one indicator. There's there's
not really anything to set up.
Golf. Yeah, golf is not a game of
perfect.
Why does TPT with trade? It's not It's
not a TPT thing, mate. It's just trade
multi-count stock capability. I I I
don't know. I don't I don't use it. I
use Ninja Trader. I don't trade anything
web- based, man. These absolute cretins
going to sell this. Chimp paradox. Yeah,
I know all about Chimp Paradox. The
first time I found out about Chimp
Paradox was
uh
Do you know who I don't know where
you're from. Do you know who Gavin
Henson is?
It's a Welsh rugby player from back in
the day.
And um they sent Gavin to uh they flew
him in like a private jet or helicopter.
Do you know this story? Otherwise, I
won't tell it if it bs you, but they
flew him in a helicopter to see that
doctor and he sat sat with it wouldn't
have been with Gatlin. It would have
been with someone else. He sat with his
coach, maybe his uh one of the Wales
coaching staff and sat in a room and the
guy questioned him and Gavin just felt
like why am I in a room with this guy
and why did my coaching staff here ask
me like at the same time listening in.
They didn't get anywhere. And then after
like an hour, he turned around to his
coach or the psychologist said, "His
chimp's in full control. He's got no
chance." And he never knew what he
meant.
And that's what it was. That's the first
time I heard of him. And then Gavin said
he saw the book like 20 years later and
realized.
Uh but yeah, that's also why Robbie
Williams
film, I don't know if you've seen that
film, is him as a as a chimp. Same
thing.
You're on NT and still have problems
copying my setup. What problems do you
have, Peter? I've got a video on YouTube
on how to do that.
I had to read it at uni.
Oh, there you go, Danny. Well, then
where where you from in Wales, mate?
Wales.
Price
action is just messy today, folks.
It's messy. All I'd say is
you have a lot of volume built up here.
And if price cannot find acceptance
above that, then the protrend is down.
it can if it can find acceptance above
that then it's going to come into these
levels up here that we talked about
where I expect sellers to be hanging out
waiting.
So it's just a question like my my thing
is I this feels like a small cap to me
right now. All right. So let's say let's
just play let's just play a game.
This is the game that I think's been
played at the moment. Let's say
some funds have been caught a little bit
offside here. Right. Let's say that what
what do they need to do? They need to
get price back into here, right? So that
they can get out flat. So how do they do
that? They bid the tape up relentlessly
and then they unload their position and
then next time it comes down here when
people expect there to be support, they
won't be because the guys that were
propping it were just looking for an
exit. That's how I feel about this
market right now. I think people are
just looking for an exit. I think this
will be sold. I think this gap will
probably remain open unless something
drastically changes. I can't really see
us doing this. And if we do, that will
be sold. This will just still be
protrend, right? Because we've left
the value.
or is the win rate of your indicator
setup? I wouldn't know actually. Uh you
have to ask someone who just trades the
indicator alone. I I wouldn't be able to
tell you because I don't use it just by
itself. Not being a dick, I just
wouldn't be able to tell you. Probably
pretty decent other than in choppy days
it will struggle.
When you go flat, you don't want to you
don't want to use it.
Can't find AP. Uh it's not an indicator.
down here in this one
volume based right. So in projections
uh anchored volume profile.
Stoic traders helped me a lot this year.
Yeah, Stoic's good. Sometimes I think
some of his reads are are off, but I
think he is good. He trades
What's his model? His model was
something like
I don't know how we do it.
Something like that, isn't it? It's
basically a two-leg to be rebid
or it might be like
something like that.
What does he use? Uh like a 21 and 200.
So like this
and this. I guess he'd be long from
there. So maybe he was maybe this would
be his model. Uh
is it in the New York session? This
might be his model.
One, two, two leg down. Sweep. Go.
That's probably his model. Something
like that.
previous day high and low. You've told
me to plot daily. Do I also plot
previous day point control? I do. Yeah,
it's right here. It's just hard to see.
All right, last few questions, guys, and
I'm going to get out of here after that.
No worries, John.
uh Rocket. Um if you're using Bookmap,
you will need a data feed. Um some
people on here might use it with data
from one of the prop firms if you're
using a prop firm. Otherwise, you'll
need to pay for it. I pay for it.
What's my name? Alex.
What about initial balance?
Yeah, it's these purple lines. OB.
What are the ribbons? Uh 13 21
7289.
Is that right? Or is it 21 21 34 45
7289? God, my brain's not working. Those
are the main ribbons. Rolling Fibonacci.
That's why.
But I mean, if you want to make it
easier, just just use this indicator.
This is probably it. The model here is
it um JD
21 200 two leg breaker structure upside.
That's probably the model. I'm assuming
it's something like that. Anyway,
what a absolute mess.
I think it will go down as soon as I
leave the desk. I think is exactly what
it's going to do. It's literally exactly
what it's going to do cuz the market
is annoying.
Oh, it said book. Okay. Ryan Holiday.
I'm going to look that up. Thank you,
mate. I didn't know you were referring
to a book. I thought you referring to
the trader.
All right, folks. I'm going to get out
of here. Um,
I would set price alerts, guys. Set
price alerts for the key levels,
especially for this level on VIX. All
right. If you want to help your bias,
this level on VIX where we keep
rejecting is key. All right, this is
what I was talking about earlier. Look
at the same kind of setup.
If VIX gets through this level
and VIX starts to squeeze, right, you're
going to see downside pressure in the ES
and hopefully that broader market
pressure will come into ENQ. All right,
we're finding a bid on this level. This
is an old resistance level which
surprise surprise is now support. Okay.
So I'd be watching VIX to see if it can
break through 1925. That's when you're
going to see much much more follow
through. Much much more follow through.
All right guys, I'll see you guys
tomorrow. Um, all the links down below
if you want to check out uh any of the
courses on my website or any of the free
material on my YouTube, all the links
are down below and any code that you use
for the prop firms. Obviously, that
money just goes straight back into the
stream. Peace and love everyone. I'll
pop in Discord in a bit. I've got to
take my dog out for a walk and uh yeah,
take care, be safe, don't do anything
stupid, don't get trapped in all this
nasty little choppy action, right?
Basically, first day back for the week.
So, we'll see where we're at into
tomorrow. Take care.