You guys hear me now? There we go.
That's better. Morning team. Morning.
Morning. Morning. Morning. Morning. All
right. Tight range this week, folks.
Nothing's changed yet, right? Nothing
has changed yet. We looking uh what
we're starting to build out. We talked
about this weekly range. Fortunately,
it's not really playing out. We haven't
left this range. So, other than Monday,
right? Monday set the low of week and I
mean Tuesday
Monday Monday set the low of week. Come
on Alex. Uh Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday
all set high of weeks which we've not
been able to break out of and we are
just transversing in this range here.
Right. So we're about 400 point range.
400 4 500 point range. You can see we've
reclaimed lower Ballinger band 5day
started to curl back up. We are probably
looking for a back test up here at some
point. All right. 20-day and the 50-day
and you know in here is where we broke
down from. All right, there is a big
call uh call wall up here. All right,
and we will have to see how we act into
that. We get more information out of
this as always in the hourlys and we're
looking at the same kind of thing as we
were looking at yesterday and the day
before. All right, nothing's changed.
All right, I am very very very aware of
these stops here. All right. I'm very
aware of these stops here dating back to
the 4th of Feb. So, what I'm thinking
is there an echo on my mic? Not that I'm
aware of.
It's coming from my webcam. Okay, hang
on.
Hang on, folks.
There should only be one mic.
All
right, guys. I'm just
Jesus.
There's an echo. Is there
not what we needed to start the day
here?
I don't know what to do here, folks,
because it's not giving me another
option.
Is that any better?
Okay. Worse. How about now?
Better now.
Much better. Okay. Good. Good. Good. All
right. Sorry about that.
figure out later. Yeah, let's figure out
later. Let's just get through this team,
do the best we can, and then see if OBS
wants to stop being annoying. Otherwise,
I have to close the stream and reopen
it. Okay, so this is the current weekly
profile,
right? This is the weekly profile. We've
dipped under it uh overnight and
absorbed straight back inside. All
right. And we dipped under it and we
came down to this area, this node we
talked about yesterday where we said,
"Well, we're probably going to see
absorption if we can get down there."
All right. That's probably a buying
opportunity. We eventually did that
yesterday. So, we did a failed breakout,
eventually came all the way down to
there before bidding all the way back
up, and we're now stuck in this again.
Nothing's changed, folks. There's quite
literally nothing has changed since
coming to the charts uh really Monday
morning. All right. From New York
session, we are stuck in here. So, this
is the buildout of liquidity, right? In
ranges, you tend to want to fade the
edges and buy the edges back inside. We
have been here so many times. One, two,
three. This is the fourth attempt at the
high. I'd say down here, one 2 3 4 5,
right? We're really, really stuck. There
are lots and lots of stops being
developed. My thought process on this is
we want to take these stops out here and
I think there is chance for a bull trap
to live in here somewhere. There is a
chance. That is what I've been aware of
all week. Okay. So, I'm wondering if
we're going to do something like this
and then see some form of failure up
here back down. Maybe six, maybe seven,
maybe eight. Why those levels? All
right. Six cuz it's an old node. Uh
seven whole number, but eight old point
of control. All right. So, I'm really
watching six and eight. 6 and 8 is a
level where I think the market might get
stuck if we get up there. If we just do
this and we base there is a long
opportunity from let's say 440s 500s up
and towards the sixes. All right. And
then maybe if you get lucky get seven
and eight. Uh the fade will come
somewhere up there. I would imagine we
would go uber uber bullish if we start
reclaiming all of this. Okay. Because we
will be looking at this side of the move
then. All right. So we are technically
coming buy side of the curve. But I
think up here is dangerous. I really
want to be buying down here. This is
where I want to be buying for this move
back up. Otherwise, if they do this
move, I think reliable for that coming
back down. So, that's what I'm watching
today. If we fail this edge again and
keep selling underneath previous day's
value area low, then I will look for
that fade back down to the 800s. I don't
really want to trade inside yesterday's
value area. All right. I really don't
want to trade inside here. And ideally,
I don't want to trade inside here. So,
I'm going to have to be extra extra
patient today to get that move outside
of it. All right. All right, we're going
to have to get a real move on here and
go through everything else. We're
looking exactly the same thing on the ES
and spiders. There is no change. You can
see inside yesterday's range. Here's
your initial balance from yesterday. All
right, you are pinned inside. There is a
slight gap up. All right, there's your
gap. All right, maybe they fade the gap
and dip it. I don't know, but we are
still pinned. There's no edge in here.
For me personally, how I trade, there's
no edge in here. Spiders, same thing.
You can see three days worth of price
action in here. QQ, you're going to see
the same thing. All right,
that's where we're pinned. All right,
this could could be the spring to go
back upside. It's arguable that we can
do that. Dixie still trying to find an
area where it can catch a bid. Right, it
tried. We are also in a range here.
They're still making their mind up. They
probably see the same on metals. VIX,
same kind of thing. We're floating under
the underside of this. I think this
might be need to be adjusted because my
computer wanted to do an update last
night. It's very annoying.
Uh let's broaden this out a little bit.
Bring this in a bit. There we go. So,
still sort of hanging on, watching the
VIX to see if it retests 17 uh sorry, 16
75s or not. If we start to get over this
gap for a push. Let's go through the MAC
very, very quickly.
You're going to see the same story here,
folks. All right, range. Here's the
range is what Alex tries to avoid.
Here's the range. Look below and fail.
Look above and fail. Apple opening up
slight gap down.
Amazon
starting to look a bit more bearish
here. Rolling over. Uh this gap here is
important. Do they want to close this
gap? All right. So somewhat of a range
fail breakout above. Never got back up
into this. They had the opportunity to
try and base. They couldn't. They've
rolled back down. Do they fill this gap
now? And if they fill it, are we going
bare flag for deeper on Amazon? Uh, Goo
doesn't look great out there for stocks
right now. I will say that. Goo, same
kind of story. There's the range after
breaking down. So, Tuesday, Wednesday,
Wednesday fail. Now, we're trapped
underneath Tuesday's low, right? That's
your pivot. So, 14s. If we can't reclaim
15s, let's call it, we're going to fail
further on Google. Meta, this is one of
the better looking stocks at the moment.
It's uh a bit more undervalued than some
of the others, but really we're watching
this pin down here, right? Where this
big buy came in, they're repricing the
whole thing. And yet again, this range
now has been developing since last
Tuesday. All right, so we're not moving.
This is tech not moving while we start
to rotate.
Microsoft,
right? Softy tried to reclaim. We can
talk about this big downtrend failed to
break lower had the push above the pivot
head and shoulders failed back down into
here. So this is where buyers are
hanging out. So softy buyers are hanging
out at 400 and below. If they can hold
that they will have another attempt to
reclaim 20s and 30s or 20s and 25s.
Again a bit of a range really 400 to
420s 20 $20 range there on softy. Nvidia
is the one where possible it can get a
breakout. All right, it's looking a
little bit better. Gapping up slightly.
We can see we've built out all this
liquidity for this downtrend. All right,
left shoulder, head, right shoulder. If
we can get going, you can see I've got
price alerts here. If we can get going
over that, there's a chance we need to
be very careful with the fail breakout
as always. And Tesla's trying to get
that recovery. Same kind of story. All
right, built out some liquidity here. We
see this here as you look below. There's
your shoulder line. There's your
neckline. All right, so it's trying to
get up to 440s right now. It's trying to
hold 20s to get to 40s.
Have a quick look at Oracle.
All right, might want to flush back down
to here soon and recheck that before it
comes higher. We will see. Looking a bit
better though for the recovery.
Lucky we sold on that big drive up. All
right, we sold a good chunk of that. I'm
still holding some now to see if it
holds this for a higher low and has
another go at it. So I've got piece
still in this and
Netflix starting to come down to the
levels we want. We want to get to down
to those 70s. So, let's see. And these
now starting to catch a bid again, which
is great. All right. Uu
starting to catch a bid. US doesn't look
so good, but Yuyu looks okay.
And let's have a look at some of these
semis. AMD trying to call back again.
Range on AMD is uh not great out there.
Have a quick look at gold and silver for
you. They are doing absolutely above
all. Right. Stuck as well. And silver
stuck as well. But we went over those
levels yesterday where maybe we're
looking for a daily on these which can
start to drag down. All right, bounce
fail somewhere in here. I'd be short and
same on GC level in here like we talked
about. Probably looking for the
rotation. If they do that, Dixie will
catch a bid. So, lots of things to look
out for at the moment. All right, folks.
Um, haven't got much news today.
zoomed in.
Let's double check.
Yeah, existing home sales 10:00. And uh
that's it. That's really it. Not much
for the day, folks. Not much for the
day.
Do I pay for Trading View? Yeah, I do. I
have like the top subscription, but it's
it's I think it's on sale now or it's
about to be on sale, so you're better
off grabbing on sale. Thank you so much.
Who's that Blake? Very kind of you
grabbing me a coffee this morning.
Yeah, overall today we're looking at a
very choppy market. We basically we need
to see if this market is willing to hold
previous day value area high and try and
bid or previous day point of control and
try and bid. If we do this to here and
failed that, we will come back down for
value again. This will this is
yesterday's chop. Yesterday's chop
happened in here. Current chop on the
week. If if we just zoom this out. All
right. Current chop on the week. Where's
my blue line?
Uh this one. Okay. Weekly profile. This
is how tight we are. Weekly profile is
here to here.
Right. Daily profile is here to here.
Right. Very, very, very choppy right
now. building out a ton of liquidity.
You do not need to be overly aggressive.
You definitely don't want to be buying
the highs in this and you definitely
don't want to be shorting the lows. You
need to see it leave leave the liquidity
30-year auction at one. Yeah, there is.
Sorry. Uh obviously it's after stream. I
won't be here for that.
somewhat
upsetting that it's not seeing that mic
properly.
Let's try.
Probably need to shut OBS down and start
again. Unfortunately,
I can't, guys. And some of you are
probably joining late that can't see my
mic. Oh, it's just found my mic, I
think.
There we go. Back to normal now, I
think. There we go.
Yes. Perfect. That little unplug worked.
Okay.
Got to love technology. All right. You
have to love technology.
Let's see then. Let's see how we go
here.
So, at the moment can dip down towards
the gray box. Previous day value high
has caught a bid. Come up to the current
developing week point of control. So,
we're just like trapping between the two
like we tal about. Let this get through
the uh opening range for a bit. I have
left my glasses next door overnight. All
right, let me just grab my glasses
quick, but I can't see it.
Sorry folks, nothing like a blind man
trying to watch a uh a screen.
Not a good start. I'm sorry, Tim. Not a
good start. Yeah. Yes, he's burnt out
right now. All right. Couldn't get his
mic working. Couldn't see properly.
You're saying it's worse now. It
shouldn't be worse now.
Good, good, good, good. All right. Still
catching a bit of previous day's value
area high. This we're getting very tight
down here. I'm just watching all the
liquidity come in this area. I'm not
interested in trading right now. Like as
you can see, I'm quite genuinely not
interested in trading right now. We have
to start moving away from these areas
one way or another.
Give you a quick read out on the MAG.
And you can see even on the MAG, we've
got a split book. So Tesla 1.23% up,
Nvidia 1.21% up, Microsoft pretty much
flat, Meta 0.62% up, Google slightly
down, uh like pretty much flat, Amazon
half a percent down, Apple 1% down. We
are a complete mixed bag. Complete mixed
bag right now.
Think we will want to try and lift into
600 today. That's what my gut says, but
it's just whether they've got the juice
to do it. And then it's making the
decision. Do I want to play long up to
the sixes or do I want to let them do
all their nonsense and then fade them
back down for the fail breakout and the
trap? That's where my mind's at. That's
what I was looking for yesterday as
well. I think we are really going to
struggle that if we do get through
sixes, we will probably go eights pretty
quick. All right. The reason I'm saying
that when we look at here on the hourly,
right, I am watching to see is today
willing to move outside of this range
and run these stops and come up to here,
right? Where we have this and this. Are
we going to fade that? If not, if we get
through that, look how thin we are. We
can go straight up to eight. So, I
really don't want to be long at the top
here. I don't want to be short at the
bottom down here. We need to see a
breakout hold. Maybe there's a long
opportunity up to here which we then get
out of. We see money take money. If
we're going to stay in the range, Alex
is probably not going to do anything
today. Alex does not like trading ranges
as we all know.
So trying to be extremely patient today.
We're quite literally not moving here.
Market's stuck since the open. Let's get
some volume on.
Nothing to do, folks. In my mind, we're
not doing anything yet. Back down to
value area high from previous day again.
What is going on here? [\h__\h] hell.
That's better.
Tech on one right now. Clearly my tech
inputs.
Make sure there's 20. There we go. All
right. So, they're still holding
previous day value area
for now. Uh I'm just watching these
blocks I trade backwards and forwards.
There's not much going on here.
I'm too soft compared to other streams
opens. I don't know what that means,
mate. Uh I'm not looking to attack when
the market doesn't know what it wants to
do.
Thoughts on or strap? Yeah, I mean orb
strat is good strategy. If you want to
play 5minute orb or a 15-minute orb,
won't work every day. You've got to
understand the conditions that you're in
for it.
Yeah, volume pro. I think Trading View
has just been on one.
They want me to do something. I can't do
something if there's no trade here,
folks. Like all you noobs who are
turning up for the first time, there's
no setup right here right now. Not in my
mind. We have to wait. Let's take this
histogram box down. Don't want that.
There we go. All right. We have to wait.
Currently, dips are holding previous day
value high, but you'd have to be fairly
brave to be buying that. Looking for a
rotation up up top. I haven't seen
enough shorts get trapped down here yet.
So, we're watching it. I mean, there are
sellers coming in under 47s,
but there is a buying block that got
caught at 65.
So, basically, we're trading 50s to 70s
and that's it since the open.
I'm not just going to uh click a button
because you guys want me to. My job is
to make money and it is also to keep you
guys safe where possible. So that is
what I will be doing,
right? You make money where you don't
lose it. Just remember that.
It's like going to casino. If you play
like poker and you see someone's you
notice their tail playing poker, you
want to sit on that table. You don't
want to sit on a table where a guy's
not really doing anything. When you're
just going around in a circle, there's
no edge.
Blew my 50k account yesterday. Managed
to get 9k profit from it. Now I'm back
on the horse and go again. Would you
recommend 100k over a 50k or vice versa?
50k is fine, especially if you've
already made n grand out of it. I don't
think you need to be uh giving yourself
a harder task in passing an eval, but
know if you want the bigger draw down,
then obviously you're going to have to
go up.
Ain't this a bull flag? Someone says,
"Well, I mean, you could argue it is a
bull flag, but where are you placed?"
Zoom out. Zoom out. Look at where you
would be trying to do a bull flag if you
were trying to take this. Right. Look at
this. This has been a grind up the whole
time. Grind up.
And you are thinking about taking a bull
flag right at the top of the range
right where we think we're going to have
fail breakout 20-day there as well 5day
we are just trapped this is a big
liquidity building zone it might very
well be like we talked about that we're
going to start breaking out but I would
rather see it do this and hold and try
and risk down here when it's in a range
and doesn't really know what it wants to
do so let's see okay got to watch the
tape here can't answer so many questions
buys came in here at 70s again so are we
going to find acceptance over 70s to get
to 2420 20s is the question now. So,
watching now, here comes the fours. Can
they dip down and hold 70s for me or
something? Can they show me that they're
willing to hold 70s? So, here we go back
to 70s. Are they willing to bid here is
the question. If they are, I'll consider
the long. If they're not, which they're
not right now, we go right back down
into range. No trade. They have to hold
70s there. So, we're back down to
towards VPO at 50s again. So, that's a
failed breakout and a clear out now. And
we're coming back down to the 50s. And I
will tell you, a big seller last came in
at 46es. So buyers now need to protect
46es to keep that seller stuck at the
lows. These guys need to make their mind
up what we're doing.
Do I keep positions overnight only on
swing accounts?
Okay, back into current day's profile.
You can see very, very tight here,
folks.
So, just failed that breakout to the
gray zone. Failed the 400s, failed to
hold 70s. We're right back into this guy
at 46 who last got stuck here, and
they're trying to absorb versus him at
46. This rotation is going to keep
happening. I'm not interested in taking
this until this market makes it mind up.
All right. Maybe this is something that
you like playing. Definitely is not
something I like playing.
Do I trade ICT concepts? I do not.
I do not. Unless you want to talk about
something like a failed breakout, which
he would call a Judas swing, right? If
you want to call that his concept, it's
just a failed breakout.
Then yes, I would say I guess I guess I
do if I trade in and bounce. Okay, back
to these 90s. So they protected that
seller at the low. Back to these 90s.
Big buyer just came in there. 70 lot at
the high is now caught at 87s. All
right, so 70 lot is now caught at 87's
buy side. Buyers I still think we need
to protect 65s here if they're going to
get a continuation move higher otherwise
they're going to get caught again. Yes,
starting to break out.
Missing on ES.
VIX trading back down into its block
from previous day low.
So, we definitely have a buyer caught up
here in front of 90. Right, we have a 70
lot caught up there in front of 90. We
have a big uh sell lot caught at 58. So,
we're trading between 58 and 90 right
now. while they make their mind up. Can
the buyers protect 58s and look to take
out this high or not? That is what
they're trying to do. They've got to get
back above 90. If they get back above
90, they have the squeeze on to get to
420s here. Big buyer coming in trying to
step on the tape to force here. Here we
go. Back to 90. They've got to get back
above this now. Very, very important
these buyers get above this now for this
squeeze. We can consider this if we do
it. It'll get back above this for a
squeeze up to 440s probably.
So far, you can see we're just building
liquidity out up here where this player
keeps getting trapped. All right, this
player right here keeps getting trapped
at 88. So 87. You can see every time
he's adding market size up here. Guy
stepped in at 80. We're not getting
acceptance higher, right? We keep
getting stuck up here. this where the
buyers caught a seller is caught down
here at 47 and a little bit at 58.
So it's just a rotation until we see
otherwise. So still no trade for me.
Still waiting. So fail breakout of 90.
Buyers caught up at 90s. They're going
to trade downside. We're losing BPO now.
And then probably if we lose this, we're
going to trade to 47s and test to see if
that seller stays stuck. So the rotation
just keeps moving.
CVD selling. Yeah, CVD is selling, but
we're not selling. So, what does that
mean? I mean, we are in the opening few
minutes, so you got to be careful. We're
only 12 minutes into the day. But if CVD
is selling and we're not moving lower,
it means there's buying uh absorption on
the tape. Someone is absorbing it
because CBD is breaking down and the
market isn't. So, you've got very
aggressive selling here and someone
trying to absorb the tape. So, until
this guy who's absorbing the tape gets
out of the way, well, if if and when he
gets out the way, you might get a big
sell. But if he doesn't, you're going to
get divergence with CVD where we can
potentially squeeze higher. And that's
what I'm aware of right now. But we have
buyers stepping in here again, being
aggressive, trying to protect the 47s.
If we start breaking under 47s and under
VWAP, there's probably going to be a
sell and we can watch under previous day
value high for this rotation for gap
fill, I guess. Right. So, here they go.
So the sellers coming in here aggressive
at 47s again. Very aggressive at 47s.
Do they get follow through now? I'll be
waiting to see if we get back inside
yesterday's range. Don't really want to
sell in front of that. So the sell for
me, if we're really going to take the
range, which is very dangerous, would
have to be like this. Partials into
here. The buys will be protecting this.
I'm not really keen on taking this for
this move up here. I'm more keen on
taking it when we let these buys out.
Lots of sellside activity taking place
here at 50s and 47s. Lots and lots and
lots of sellside activity here taking
place. We are not moving lower. There is
someone trying to absorb the tape. How
much he can absorb is
only he knows how much size he's got
today to absorb.
So right to VW up
they're going to try and sell through to
previous day valuary high. We can look
now to see if we reject this to move
lower. All right, here's the rejection
potentially. Oh, you got to give me a
retest here, you [\h__\h] You can't do
it in one go. Don't you do this in one
go. Right, watching to see if we trade
back up and reject now. Now that we've
traded inside it,
got to come up for me. Cannot chase this
down here.
Right, watching to see if we come back
up. Be very very careful. ES now at
VWAP. So, waiting to see if we come up
and offer a rejection. Anywhere up to
46es, anywhere from 28s to 46es. I would
be interested in the short if we trap
buyers and reject it. If we reclaim it,
this would be a look below and fail,
especially if we fill the gap and hit
280s already.
So, you have to be willing to play both
sides right now. So, we are watching for
something like this down to here or this
down to here. All right, we need to see
that pop down to there. If we reclaim
this, I will not play short because it
means this will be a look below.
Especially if we do this first means we
will be efficient and then reclaim and
go. So waiting to see if this drive up
is resold into or not.
Needs to come up a bit higher there.
We've definitely caught shorts at 310s.
Need to be aware of. Needs to come up
higher for me to be interested. You need
to come up higher for me to be
interested to get this. Please. No. You
[\h__\h] You're just going to fill the
gap now without me.
All right. Gap fill there. Oh my god.
Nasty bugger. Nasty bugger. Says as soon
as it left volume
all in one go. We just needed this all
in one go down. Some of you got it.
Nice. If you got that, congrats.
Okay. And the next cover is here.
Previous day point of control. And if we
lose this, your next cover is 33s.
Right. Two 33s now. And if you lose
that, your next cover is 140. So I'm not
in this short currently. Unfortunately,
it hasn't given me an entry that I want.
But you can look for covers into here.
All right, 30s and then all the way down
here. If we're going to rotate the whole
of yesterday's value, all right, then
that's what we're going to do. You need
to be paying yourself some now already.
All right, because you're at previous
day open, you're at previous day point
control, you're under previous day
close.
Okay, here's the rip back up back into
the orb. We have a shelf here at tens.
So sellers need to reject tens if we're
going to get follow through. Tens to
18s. Basically tens to 18s need to be
rejected. Basically this this gray box,
it's this node above it though. It's
right here. This needs to be rejected if
sellers are going to get follow through.
Big if right now. So I'm looking to see
if sellers are going to look for follow
through. If they're going to look for a
retest of that kind of area and resell
it down. And then I will look for the
short.
I want to see it lower. Please folks,
please. Sorry, higher. I need to see it
higher first.
Please don't just start going without
me. I really want an entry here.
Come on. Give me a second leg up. Come
up. Come up. Come up. Come up. Get
through those 300s. Here we go. Right.
Waiting to see if we can get up to tens
and how we operate when we get up there.
Be very careful fail breakout here. If
they reclaim like tens and 20s, this
thing can scream. So, just looking for
this drive up to be sold into. They
retested 300. Some buyers got caught
there into 300. Still not high enough
for me.
Uh, can't get my entry. It's very close.
I'm looking to get short up here right
now.
So, the short I'm looking for currently
is kind of around here. I'm looking to
see it come into here or this next leg
to see if we can come all the way down.
It'll be TP1 into this and TP2 down into
here. I need it to lift a bit first.
They're just going to keep selling it.
Alex is not going to get his entry
today. They're too heavy on the tape. Oh
my days.
Oh my days.
They are puking this. All right. So,
next cover point here into sort of 30s,
please. Why into 30s? That is your value
area low on the developing week since
the Sunday open. Once you get under
that, you can look for this move into
141s. I would say even down into the
110s again, right? Yesterday. So this
move here to 110s again. 110s. This gray
box. Same same trade as yesterday,
right? So partial here. And if you get
follow through, we're looking for here.
And then we can see if today they really
want to let go and get down to that
previous weak point of control. The fact
that we still haven't taken out this
block here, though makes it a little bit
tricky cuz we haven't run all the stops
yet.
So, this is the trade I'm still looking
for. We need to be careful if they take
all the low hanging fruit out first.
Biggest [\h__\h] ever.
Not really. I can't trade if it doesn't
give me the setup. We're waiting for it.
It built the liquidity. God, you guys
are [\h__\h] morons.
I'm just not going to even bother.
Not going to give it time.
Okay, waiting for a 10's retest here
somewhere up there. Possible they reject
90s here based on this node, but I'm
would much rather they squeeze up up
here first.
Mag rotating.
Tesla's giving a lot back now. Just half
percent up. Uh, Nvidia 1% up, Microsoft
0.72% down, Meta 0.33% down, Google
0.14% up, Amazon 0.72% down, Apple 1.17.
This thing's puking now. Just need an
entry. Very aggressive selling here. I
just need an entry here. Please give me
something.
Give me something to get involved in.
There's a seller at 250 now. They just
want to keep diving this down to fill
those imbalances from yesterday.
seller at 250 and then at 275s.
There's the 250 check. He's still there.
77 lot. We're very very thin through him
all the way up to 275.
So we're coming back towards that 275
now if they can reach it.
We're watching this 250 over under right
now.
They squeeze to 75. Here they go.
There's the squeeze to 75. All right.
Are you going to give me an entry here?
They're still selling 270s. I'm not I
don't like this shorting down there.
Really, it's got a chance to get to 310s
before I do anything. But watching 270s
here if they trap this buyer.
Good wall there. Held up well.
Do they squeeze the tens? They're going
through 70s now. So potentially back to
the 10ens like we talked about. Here we
go. So back to this level. So from
current week. So the person who said
this is [\h__\h] You don't know what
you're talking about. Okay. This is your
current week value area low developing
which we just covered into. Right. We're
coming back to PDC and we have a node
here. So yeah,
told you what I thought was going to
happen. It just didn't give me the
entry. Can't control the market, guys. I
really cannot control it. I'm looking
for a short on a retest up here. I'm
watching 90s. They just rejected 90s.
Tens would be better if we can lift in
towards 10 somewhere up here. We need to
be very careful if we're going to hold
this all day. I'm looking for an entry
to get short at the moment. That's a
good rejection of 90s.
Buyer just got caught at 70 there on
that last lift. Definite buyer got
caught at 70. So, we're watching him
right now.
See, right here, buyer just got caught
here at 70. So, if we're over that, he
becomes comfortable and they can squeeze
up to 10. If he keeps getting stuck
here, we've got a chance to move lower.
So, I'm watching this level.
It's going to trap the sellers. I mean,
it's a very heavy take at the moment. I
don't think so, but we It's possible.
I'm just looking for a bigger retest
before we go lower. We start breaking
down here, I'm going to be forced to put
some on, which is not what I want to do.
Maybe under this, I can add heavier.
Still at 70s and it's lifted to 80s now.
Here they go. They're going to look for
the squeeze back up now. So, maybe we're
going to get the 10 test.
Maybe we can get this 10 test. We want
to be careful if it reclaims this level
here. We're going to go squeeze straight
the way back up. Right.
So 90s again.
ES back to to VWAP. So it just poked
back to VWAP and got sold into there.
See how they act back there if they
reclaim. Very washy here. A bit like
yesterday, right? We're just still in a
range. Need to be very careful. This is
the value area low on the developing
week. So we need to be careful here.
Looking for a retest for them to trap
buyers that we can sell into. If they
don't trap buyers, this thing will just
squeeze all the way back up and there's
nothing we can do. This is nice into
90s.
Some buyers getting caught here into 90s
for sure, but it's still stacking
sellers above all the way to 300. So,
still waiting here to see if I can see
this flip. Starting to see aggressive
sellers come back in. Watching 70s,
under 70s. I've got a piece on now.
Under 70s, I've got a piece on now.
They reclaim 70s and make me very
uncomfortable here. O, stay under that.
Stay under that. Do not give me a
squeeze out here. Stay under 70s.
Stay under 70s. Don't like what I'm
seeing. I'm out. I'm out of that. Don't
like that tape. Wait for the retest of
90s again and we'll see. Maybe they fade
this again. Maybe they go to two to
310s.
Big buyer keeps stepping in here. So, he
was uncomfortable at 70s. He got back
above it. I will consider trying again
here. The same move.
Maybe they go tens first is what I'm
very aware of.
Get back to these 70s. This is the big
level. 70s is the big level. A close
under 64 will be a very good close.
Sellers got caught under 60 which we
need to be very careful about if we're
going to see follow through or not.
Is there anyone up at 10 passively?
There's a guy at 20. Is no one at 10?
Right. Think we can break down here. Big
seller coming in again. Still holding
these sort of 70s levels.
Really want to get back in this here.
We're letting go at 70s now. Little
piece back on again. Now in case we're
going to do the flush now. We got to
stay heavy though. Second attempt here.
Here we go. Get under this shelf. Get
under this shelf. We need to get under
this shelf. Oh, I don't like it if we
can't get under this shelf.
Need to get under this which is
currently holding.
Come on. Get under it. Close under it.
Close heavy. Please come down to the 50s
and wash them out. We've got an
imbalance in front of 50s. Here we go.
Get under this shelf. Get under it.
There we go. Okay. Get under this 50
now. Nice. All right. Let's see if we
can get follow through under 50. Buyer
here stacking up in the imbalance. Can
we get a wash under him? We get a wash
under him. We get should get a new low
of day. Here we go, folks.
Here we go. Big seller stepping in.
Moving my stop down now. Looking for a
new low of date. Here we go, folks. Come
on, baby. Come on, baby. Had to be so
[\h__\h] patient just to get this
bids showing up at 25s now as well. So,
this gray box, if we get under this,
we're looking all the way down here.
Okay, little piece off into this gray
box. Here we go, folks. We're looking
better now. So, we didn't get the lift
all the way where we wanted it. Had to
play it here from 70s. Okay, I'm TP1
into this gray box already. All right.
And I'm looking for this down here now.
If we can get there.
Lots of buyers stacking stacking up 25s
to 200. So, we can cover some in this
next flush. Come on. Come and fill all
these lot. There's a big bid down at
200. I think we're going to get it.
There's a 236 lock down at 200. Come on,
baby. Come on, baby.
All these people yapping at the
beginning of the stream.
Shh. Be patient and wait. Just be
patient and wait. I do give you edge.
You just have to wait. I can't do
anything if the market doesn't give me
the entry. Right. We had to wait after a
big flush for a buildout of liquidity
and someone, this guy here, to get
trapped. and now we use their pain,
which is what we're doing. So, if you're
new to stream, please just be willing to
sit and learn for a minute instead of
trying to attack me when I'm trying to
help you.
All right, here into the 210s.
Can we get all the way down into here?
News coming now. So, if you want to move
your stop, you can move it tighter now.
We've got news coming in the next what,
two and a half minutes.
So buyers are currently keep coming in
at 221. All the time that stays heavy,
we can move lower.
Nice.
Very nice. You see it right here is the
220s. This where the buyers are caught.
So we need that to stay heavy. Might be
that they give a little price back up to
30. Resell it. Be very careful sellers
at the low here. This is not good. 210s.
That's not a good look. We do not want
sellers caught at the lows. We do not
want these sellers caught the lows at
210. So any break over 220s or
definitely over 230s, I will cut this
now. Now that I've seen that,
do not want these big sellers caught the
lows. So still a chance to break lower,
but if we break over 220s, I'll cut. Get
under this guy. We need to go to 200s
now. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's
go. Let's go.
Come on.
Here come the 200s.
The 250 lock down here, folks. Be very
careful. If we sell through this guy, we
should get 185 quick.
And we've got some imbalances. 190, 185,
and 167s.
Get through this guy at 200. Come on,
fill this guy. Fill this guy. Fill this
guy. Get through him. Be aggressive. Be
aggressive. Be aggressive. Be
aggressive. Be aggressive. Get through
him. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's
go. Let's go. All right. Covering more
here. And let's see if we can fill these
imbalances and get all the way down into
here.
So 185. Now we're filling these next lot
of imbalances that we talked about. All
right, just here this imbalance here.
We're filling this big sellers at the
lows now. So just be aware of that. You
do not want to be adding now at these
lows. We're looking for a wash all the
way down to 145s if possible. All right,
really good folks. All right, really
good. So currently, if you just got this
one with me, you've made what about 80
points. If we get down here, you're
going to get your 120 pointer. If you
got this up here, which I was waiting
for and couldn't get, you're up, I don't
know, 190 plus points already.
Okay, big seller at these lows. You do
not want to reclaim of 20210s
here, folks. 2210 should stay heavy.
Definitely any break about above 220s.
This thing can rip. Here we go. Wonky on
this news. Be very, very careful. I am
down to tiny size now. Covering some
more just in case. So, just looking for
this final TP and maybe even down here
if we flush. Let's [\h__\h] go on stream.
Sh.
Thank you. Thank you very much. Thank
you very much. Here comes the news. My
stop has now moved to 2011's. All right.
2011's. My stop's now at 2011's. Uh why?
Because of this guy here. All right.
Because of this guy here. I'm not
willing to see it spike and rip this
whole thing back up. So, my stop's now
2011's.
Let's go. All those W's in chat.
Maybe I'll move it. I'm going to
actually move it to 203s. All right. I'm
actually moving it to 203s only because
there's a little imbalance at 2011 202
just in case. So, I'm at 203s
for a tiny piece left about to get
knocked out and I'm out. There we go.
I'm out. Fine. Brilliant trade. Happy
with that. We can still think about
short if it rejects 222s, but I just
didn't want to give too much back. So,
here's into the 222s. If they reclaim
222s, they can go straight up to 64.
This is what I did not want to get
caught in is why I'm being careful.
Great trade, guys. All right, I'm going
to have like a two-minute break here.
Mentally, I mean a two-minut break here.
Mentally, just let this do what it
wants. After news, we are coming.
Nothing's changed. I want you to
understand one thing.
Current week's value is here. Current
previous days value is here that we
talked about. Current day's value is
here. All right.
All we're doing is ranging between this
and this. I just didn't want to buy up
here. All right. And I didn't really
want to sell like yesterday. Unless we
clear that out would be the idea. But
once we trap enough, all right, you can
see this flush. I'm looking for a retest
to get short. It just didn't quite fill
me up here when I'm waiting. So, we had
to play this one here. All right. So if
we think about structurally bare flag
breakdown, bare flag breakdown, and we
use a buyer who's trapped for their
pain. All right, so there's the lift
back up. So hopefully you guys should be
pretty much out of this, and you could
think about a reshort here into 64s, but
obviously the news has just come out. We
now have lots of sellers caught at 200
and 187. So remember, we said these
selling at the low. Look at these big
blocks down here. You can see them here,
200, 187. You can even argue at 210. All
right. So, back probably towards value
area low here, 260 and then make a
decision. So, just let this do what it
wants a bit because we are in a range,
right? If we trap enough sellers at the
lows and we take low hanging fruit out
of the lows, we can always think about
the long back up.
Rob Miller, great job, Alex. Another
payout for me. Nice.
Nice.
Can I go long now? Um,
it's a good question. I would say you're
fishing, right? If you hold 210,
you could argue there's this move back
up. The one thing I'd say is this is a
lowhanging fruit down here. All right,
this here is previous week close and
this here is previous day's value area
low. We haven't taken it out, but uh
it's possible, but currently the trend
is this, right? So we kind of you would
kind of need a fail to break lower and
then a reclaim to get long. Otherwise,
this can still happen. Remember this
build liquidity. This can be a liquidity
build to come back down to here. It can
still do it. So I don't love the longs
at the moment. This is a bit like what
we had up here, right? Once the sellers
got caught, right, we've moved away from
them. Once the buyers got caught, we
moved away from them. We've not come
down and retest and held. We didn't come
up and retest and hold. All right? So
it's tough. uh unless you love if you
like trading breakout inside ranges. I
mean
it would it's never something I would
ever do inside a range. But um if that's
your strategy then you could argue
there's uh positions for you.
Okay. So if you're looking long you need
a hold of 220 and 200s. All right. And
you would be looking for a relief. You
haven't got much room here to 260s and
280s. I personally would not be looking
long here. I think we can still move
lower first into this personally, but it
is up to you. Like I say, it's up to you
to manage your risk.
The short air was better. Yeah, I would
say look at the node, right? Think about
the node.
Where did we just reject? Where those
buyers got caught? All right, so the
short here is better. And you'd be
covering some into 220 and 200, wouldn't
you? So, if you just took this short up
here where the buyers just got caught in
this node, you can see buyers got caught
topside. I'd be covering some into here
now 200 and 186. And if we break down
lower, you're still looking for 145. So
this level here is massive. This 200
level is massive. You can see they're
covering into that 200. Exactly what I
would be doing.
All right. So you won't see this unless
you are using orderflow. All right. So
I'm the reason I'm specific with my
levels is it's it's not a guess based on
a candle. It's an actual level where we
have people caught. All right? Where we
have people caught. You don't have to
use footprint. You can use bookmap. You
can use whatever you want. You can just
use the tape and if you can read uh
this right here. All right. You will see
that if we came up to or down to I
should say down to 200s. Right. You see
this guy here.
If it will just stop jumping around. We
have a 231 lot seller caught at 200. And
if we come up a little bit,
we're jumping around. Sorry.
Two. We're jumping so much. I can't move
it fast enough.
There. There. 210. All right. 210 as
well. All right. So, there's lots of
ways to see it. Find a way that works
for you. I have all three up. In case I
miss one, right? So, it's like in case I
don't see it on one, I probably see it
on another.
What's the other chart I pull up? Ninja
Trader. Ninja Trader. Um, I use
something called Twin Peaks. It's just
an orderflow tool. It's just footprint.
It's all it is with delta down the side.
So I have delta on the vertical axis. So
right here I have delta. Okay. So they
held look what they just held 200s,
right? They held 200s, right? So we're
coming back up to value area low on the
day. We have a node here. If we move
this up, right? We have a node here,
don't we? So we just held this node
here. In this node here, like we just
showed you, there are shorts trapped.
All right? So buyers have tried to
absorb this. This can still be a
liquidity bill to go lower. This is what
I'm trying to say to you. So maybe some
of you bought that 200s like we just
talked about. You better be selling some
into 40s and then you can see if you can
get up to 60s and you can see if you can
get up to 80s. But just know this can be
built out. All right, this could be a
one two to come lower. This is all I'm
telling you. Manage your risk. If you
are taking longs today, you are counter
trend long on what we've seen this
morning. But technically, you are
playing value, so it's not the worst.
You are trying to play discount back up
inside. But I still think there's a
chance to come back down here first. But
we will see, folks.
Will there be a third push to the
downside? Very possible. I think the uh
we have low hanging fruit to go for, but
like again, you can be short here at 40s
and you can be long here at sort of 210,
200s. Right now this is look at the
nodes right this is where we're building
liquidity. If they get under 200s right
all right we will revisit 185 and under
that we will make a new low. All right
under 185 there is a seller at 185. So
back towards the 10ens again. All right
under this under tens we go 200s. If
they don't hold 200s we will probably go
185 and then see a new low. So if you're
short from this gray box you're covering
a piece here because you're short near
the low. Right? So if you're short here,
you're covering a piece here and 85s and
then holding for this. Here you go. So
in towards 85s now.
See if they can get you down to the 85.
So you're holding 200s, 200, 200. You
want 200s and two 10s to stay heavy. And
you want to be covering into 85 and then
holding for a new low of day into uh
145.
Here you go. So here's towards 85s. You
need a new low of day. Now here it comes
under 85. That's your new low of day.
And now you're looking for 145s.
But I don't know what I'm talking about.
Don't worry about it.
Am I planning entering? No, I'm I'm just
taking a chill for a moment. It's not
cuz it's not a good setup, guys. It's
cuz I'm also like having to deal with my
own uh let's call it stress right now.
So, I'm just like trying to manage how I
trade. I'm trading much smaller size
without my accounts linked at the
moment. Not because the charts aren't
good. The charts are amazing. The reason
I am doing that is because I don't fully
trust myself right now because I have a
huge amount going on. The biggest stress
I've ever had in my whole entire life,
my 40 years on earth going on off the
screens, which means I need to be
careful on the screens. Right.
Okay. So, you need a 200 rejection here.
If you're short, you want to see 200
sort of 202 or 200 to 209 must reject.
200 rejects, then you are good to look
for this down here to hold onto this
short. So, if you're short in a gray
box, you need 200 to stay heavy. This
level here must now stay heavy, right?
You want that to stay heavy. All right,
to keep those sellers comfortable, you
must now see this. All right, and you're
covering here and then down into here.
If they reclaim 200, I'd be very
cautious because you can see an
imbalance at 220s to 230s be filled
quick. So, I wouldn't really want 200
and 210s uh reclaimed at the moment. You
look good. Look, it's rejecting 200
pretty good at the moment, but you just
need to make sure I would I would have
my, you know, if I was short from that
gray box, I wouldn't want a 210 reclaim
or let's call it 214 to give yourself a
bit of room based on the node I'm
looking at.
There's a seller up at 220, a 300 loss.
So, he's looking for the imbalance. So,
I wouldn't be give letting it come all
the way back up there. So, here's 200.
They're testing 200 over and over and
over again. You want them to step back
on the gas and trap these bulls here
now, which they're trying to do.
Can I explain how to identify whether a
buyer or seller is trapped on the
footprint? Yeah, just use the delta. The
delta on the footprint. So, they're
trying to lift. Look at this spoofer.
Spoofer at 220 has just left. Big buyers
coming up here into 210. So this is the
level, right? 200 to 210s. You do not
want them to rebid 200s now because we
just traded through it. Good rejection
of 210. You're okay. You're still okay.
So they just trapped a big buyer up
here. 100 lot just got trapped into 210s
up here. All right. 100 lot just got
trapped. Let me see if I can get it up.
Right. Look at this squeeze back up.
This buyer just caught caught. Someone
just asked how do you see them? Uh this
is buying. This is aggressive market
ordering buying, right? Same as here.
Aggressive buying. Aggressive buying. We
use their pain to move lower. This guy
just got caught. You now need to trade
under 85s again. This guy here, you want
to trade under this guy and you should
see a collapse.
So 85 still a big big level. I think you
look good now to hold because we just
rejected the 210s. So the gray box just
rejected. As long as you trade back
under 85s now, you should come to 75 and
then you should see a new low of day. So
under 85 now you should come 75 and if
they get under 75 you'll see a lower
day. You do not now want 200 reclaim
again. It's been too many times. I would
be starting to considering getting out
of this fully if it start to reclaim
this.
I'll probably be out now at this point.
Doesn't mean it can't move lower. Look
at these even on the tape. But you just
managing your position at lows is hard,
right? Get you on foot map. See these
big buyers stepping in. 157 lot, 27 lot.
Where's he stepped in again? 200. This
is a huge level, right? And we had a
spoofer up here at 220, right? So we got
this these big guys stepping in. They're
starting to hold 200. All right. If they
break through 210s, if we zoom out,
right? If we break through 210s, we're
going to visit this guy who's trapped up
at 230. All right. And if we break
through 230, we're going to start
revisiting these guys at 250.
Do I consider fair value gaps? I do not.
I I do, but I I don't use them in the
same way as as you guys using ICT. Um,
so if I tell you there's an imbalance,
all right, for me, there doesn't have to
be a gap on the screen. All right, it's
it's a quite genuine imbalance, right?
So, I've got some imbalances up here on
a five minute, right? But these are
actual volume imbalances. So, they might
line up with your fair value gaps, but
sometimes they don't. Sometimes the
imbalance will be in what you call an
order block because it's a true
imbalance. It's not that fair value gaps
don't work. They do. They work. I'll
tell you when they work. When there's a
natural imbalance there. When they don't
work is when there's a gap on your
screen, but in the order flow there's
actually no imbalance. That's when your
fair value gaps will fail.
Which data feed do you use for bookmap?
I use the one that bookmap provide CME
data.
pallet goes to the restroom and get
coffee at the same time. I bet you get
the ultimate trend in the market. Yes,
it's true. Should we try it? Should we
try it? Should I go to the bathroom and
we'll wake up and we're 500 points
lower?
How do you get footprints on Trading
View? There is a free video on my
YouTube, mate. Um, I'll post it for you
in chat. Now,
you will need the what do they call it?
Is it pre premiier or I always call it
pro and it's not pro. Now is a great
time to upgrade on trading view by the
way because they have a big sale. Um if
you do want the footprints right I'm
going to find the video for you my
friend.
But yeah go to my make sure you're
checking out my YouTube channel guys not
for me for you. Uh there's lots of stuff
on there on how to set up things like
footprints. I'm going to pop it in chat.
Where is chat?
So, whoever just asked that is uh this
link here I've just popped in chat that
shows you how to set up footprint in
Trading View.
Can we short now? I wouldn't be as keen
for the short now. Buyers are starting
to step in, aren't they? You're coming
back to this same level to the 50s,
right? So, I would now say shorts are
caught at the lows. Shorts are caught at
and 75, right? So that you had one
opportunity, right? You had your first
opportunity. It doesn't mean we can't
trade lower, but I would need to see
more buyers caught, right? So you had
this and this down to here. You want to
be very careful now. You now know under
here shorts are caught, right? So if
buyers keeping these shorts caught, we
can drift back up. So we've got this
node here. If we get through 40s, we're
going to visit this node here at 70s.
And by the time we get there, we
probably got VWAPs. All right. I would
say over 80s, look at this low volume
node. You want to be very careful. So if
they reject this here and we see buyers
caught here, which arguably might be
starting to happen, we could think about
a reshort for the lows, we just the
difference is now the first time we came
down, think about the structure now,
right? If I make this make sense. The
first time we came down here, was there
any structure? Is there anything down
here? No. The second time we came down,
is there any structure? There's a little
bit here. We broke below. Now if we
short, is there any structure? Yes. All
right. We have this structure here now.
All right. So now if we short, we have
sellers caught underneath us for the
first time today. Right? So you need to
think about that.
Same as when we looked for this short
here. All right. Think about this. When
we're shorting under this, do we have
structure that we can use? Yeah. If we
can get back into there, we can use
these buyers trap to move lower. This is
what I was looking for. The retest when
the guy was like, "This is bullshit."
Whoever said that in chat, it isn't.
This is how you play proper trading,
right? We don't guess if you are taking
a breakout short here. For me, inside a
range, a breakout there is very
dangerous. Very dangerous that that
doesn't happen to you, which is why I
wanted it to lift and show me. I
wouldn't be thinking short at this
point. We're starting to curl. We're
probably going to go sideways for a bit,
right? It's possible. It depends how far
they relief. It's possible that we
develop in here for a bit, right? And
then we can see who gets caught. If they
catch buyers up here, we can think about
that sell back down. If they catch
sellers down here, we can think about
that rip back up.
I don't want to trade sideways. All
right, this is what I'm saying. Let me
just back off the charts for a minute.
Let it decide. 250 is rejecting. Well,
there we have this node here. Let's just
make sure these are all accurate for you
guys.
And this should be great.
So, I didn't get this one.
Unfortunately, maybe some of you got
this one. This is the only one I got
today.
Which software do I use for using the
trait? Are have you applied my any
contract volume filters on the tape? Uh,
no. Uh actually there's a filter on my
uh uh DOM on um for the bubbles on
Ninja.
Um but yeah, I use footprint on Ninja
via Twin Peaks. I use Footprint on
Trading View, the one that they give to
you for free if you well if you pay for
premium or whatever it is. And I use
bookmap. That's how I see them.
Yes. So JB, what does it mean when you
say fair values gap gaps work when
there's an imbalance? I thought the gap
was the imbalance. So this this is what
I'm talking about with order flow. Okay.
So how can I give you an example of
this?
If you were to look at the candle at 957
957 uh where's that? Is it this one?
Make sure this is the right one because
it's going to 957. It might be 58 on
here. 9.
Okay, this this candle here, right? This
candle here. So, it's 56 on it, 57 on
Ninja. If you were going to draw out a
gap, right, you would draw it out like
this, wouldn't you? If you were doing
doing a fair value gap, let's just do
this as uh red, right? That would be
your fair value gap. The truth of the
matter is the gap in there was at 30,
right? So, the gap in here, the only gap
that actually existed was down here. Was
this, right? There wasn't a gap up here.
They There were orders were filled.
There's no imbalance up there. That's
what I mean. So, I know where the actual
gap is. It's not like, "Oh, I know. I'm
not It's not like I'm a genius or
magic." Footprint's showing me where
that gap actually is is what I'm trying
to tell you. Um, so here,
can I move this over here? Right. So,
this is just on a five minute. These are
imbalances. These are true imbalances.
We have some old imbalances under
underneath us. You see how we come down
to true imbalances, we find a bid. All
right, true imbalances. We find a bid.
These are not you would not even see
these on your chart on a five-minute
chart. All right, because you don't you
don't have that data unless you're using
footprint. All right, that's all I'm
saying. It the the the concept of fair
value gaps is a good concept, but
sometimes there's not actually an
imbalance in that bar.
More precise. Yeah. more more and
they're not mine. I don't want you to
think that, oh, I made this. I did not
make footprint. I have I did not create
imbalances. All right? This is not my I
don't own this. I'm just trying to teach
you the difference between a true
imbalance and not. Okay? So, they just
bid again off what level? What level did
we just bid off again? 200. All right.
200, which is now point of control,
which is where that seller is stuck.
This is what I talked about. would be
less inclined in the short now because
we know sellers are caught under 200.
We've talked about it numerous times.
Sellers are caught at 200 and at 85. If
they can get a lift through 40 here,
they can come and test 64. But I'm not
going to trade what I think is very
possible to be a sideways range down
here for a bit. We'll avoid that and let
it let it develop.
Let it develop. We're just going
sideways, right? it. This can be a
sideways build. I want all you guys that
are saying is it long now? This can be a
sideways build to go lower. I don't know
what it's going to be. I want to make
that clear. Main trend is down. This can
be a sideways build to go lower. But we
will go lower when we get under 200,
under 85 for this move down into here.
But ask yourself, what's the riskreward
here? Not great. If we get down to here,
it's pretty good, right? The best move
here, if we're going to go short, the
best move, which ENQ just feels
unwilling to do today, would be to swipe
up, trap breakout buys here. Think about
how many breakout buys would come in
here and reject that. This would be your
spring, right? And we could use this
then to move lower. That would be the
easiest and best move. I don't think NQ
is going to do it because it hasn't done
it the high for us, which we've waited
two days for. But you never know, folks.
You never know. We might get lucky and
get it.
It looks like your candles are easy algo
on trading view. No, these are my flow
zone. This is my system.
There's my system. Uh there might be a
thing very much like my system. So, I I
don't know. Okay, 1,700
of you watching. We are setting records
here every day for the stream. I love
it. Smash that like button for me,
folks. We will stalk this next trade.
We're going to stalk this next trade.
Thoughts on TV uh Trading View Footprint
versus NT Footprint or Sierra? I prefer
Ninja Trader. Here we go. We're We might
get it. We might get it. Let's see if we
trap big buys. Oh, hello Mr. Buyer. Mr.
383 lot at 350s. Let's just see how
trapped you get up there. All right. So,
we just caught someone 334 lot at 850s
just got caught right at 850. So, if he
becomes the breakout buyer, we can use
his pain to move lower. So, if we retest
him and we stay heavy, there is a chance
here that we're going to use his pain to
go lower. And that's ES rejecting VW up
as well. So, let's see here. It's too
early yet, but we are watching this.
This guy might end up being the
liquidity we need to move lower. Yeah,
at 250. at 250 right here. All right, at
250. If we look at bookmap
at 250, 250. Look at this guy here. 334
lot. He just got caught up there. All
right, he just got caught up there. So,
if we keep him stuck, we can trade lower
because he will start stopping out,
right? And that's what we're looking for
now. We're looking to see if we can use
his pain very well. This is what I was
talking about. We might poke through,
run these stops, trap a breakout buyer.
This is what we just had. a breakout
buyer or a short sell stop. All right,
here. And if we then trade under 200,
this can really start puking back down
because now we've got some size caught.
Now we've got some size caught,
but we need to stay heavy versus 250.
All right. So, watching this to see if
we stay heavy versus 250 and if we see
more buyers get caught and we reject it,
if there's some selling up there and
then if we can break under 200 and start
puking.
So, anyone who does like a a woff this
could could potentially be a woff fail
breakout right under 200. This move
here, this is what we're looking for.
I don't always wait for the retest of
the trap buyer. No, it's just that we're
holding 200s or 210s right now. So, I'm
assuming we're going to come and fill in
imbalance up there and see if they keep
him stuck. If we come straight under 200
and stay heavy there, I can join there
if I want. It's not ideal. The
location's not ideal down there, but the
momentum would be good. So, let's see.
Do they let this guy out or not?
At the moment, no is the answer. They
can't get back on into there at the
moment.
trading right at point of control. Don't
want to enter around point of control.
That's for sure.
So, we're either looking for them to
trade up and reject it to show us or to
trade under 200 and show us. Either way,
we don't want to trade in this location
here because we're still building
liquidity. It's possible that we get
back above 250 and we squeeze all the
way up towards 300. So, we don't want to
be early here.
We don't want to be early here. We want
to see this reject and this ideally and
then we can probably get this move here.
This is what I'm going to look for if
we're going to do it. Want to be very
careful because if they reclaim this,
this squeeze up here can happen very
quick.
That's the first imbalance filmed. The
next imbalance here is at 41s. So again,
you would not have an imbalance here if
you're trading ICT. I have an imbalance
here up to well 40 or 41s here.
Back to VPO. back to these tens maybe.
Can we get under the 200s is the big
question and we can start selling. So
that's a good rejection so far. We
haven't let that player out. I want to
see us move under the 200s for a big
confirmation here.
Still holding it. I want to be very
careful because we're building. There is
an uptrend starting to develop here. So,
we're just trying to see if we use this
big player and come under 200s and then
we can snap.
Remember, we must remember these 200s,
right? Because we have big sellers
caught down there. So, if I show you
here, this player up here, I know it
says 79 lot. He's actually 350 lot up
here. So, this is the guy that we're
trying to see if we're going to use him.
We must get under these guys for
confirmation. These sellers are stuck
right here at 200. Maybe I've got to
move this up. I don't know. Right. These
sellers here are stuck at 200. This
buyer here is stuck at 250. So, a 50
point range here being developed. Once
we get either side of that, we can see
what happens.
There's that imbalance tag. Back to
point of control. So, imbalance just got
tagged. Sort of 39 into 41 there.
And we're still holding point control.
Uh, it's just the way it's calculated
it. I don't know why, but I know for a
fact there's a 300 lot up there that got
filled because I can see in my book
bookmap it's 334 lot was the buyer, but
it probably just paired off um in terms
of size, but I know he was a 334 lot. I
can see him.
Are we bullish on structure? Uh, for me,
no. Uh, you're sideways on structure.
are probably bearish overall uh because
this is your swing high. We have not
been able to get over it. It's a failed
break. This guy here is who we're using,
right? So, if we think about structure,
this high made this low. This is a
failed break right now, right? This is
where we trap the guy. So, all the time
we're doing this, this is possible. We
get over this structure can change, but
I'd be somewhat careful being bullish
today. You'd be better being bullish if
we do this and clean it out, I would
say. So, let's see. All right. imbalance
now fully filled into the 41s. So that
imbalance that you would not have seen
like we just talked about, you do not
have that imbalance if you're not using
orderflow. We just filled that imbalance
into 41s. We still have this player call
at 50s right now. ES trying to find a
bid off its 5day moving average.
Still no entry.
Here's the retest towards the 50s. If
they let him out, we can squeeze. I'm
not going to play the long. There's
still no short cuz we're not under the
200s.
Still not letting him out of 50s.
50% off the course, mate. You're never
getting 50% off the Are you joking? It's
$699 for 20 hour. It's not like I'm
charging three grand. $699 for 20 hours
and Discord and an indicator. I mean,
it's not No, you're not getting 50% off.
Sorry, mate.
Okay, back to the 20s. Back to Vpock.
Why is it changed my VOT color as well?
Lipping annoying, mate.
I have to tell Trading View to remember
this chart. I'm worried it's gonna skip
it again. There we go.
Uh it's like 399 or 499 for the
indicators on my website. Okay, 50 is
still trapped right now and we've got
some buy side imbalances now stepping
in. All right, so in this current
candle, they're getting quite aggressive
with the buys. They're trying to force
it up. So being very aggressive
back towards the 50s. We're testing this
guy at 50. Remember, if we let him out,
there is a squeeze up to 80. I'm not
going to trade it. There's through the
50. So, he's potentially getting let out
unless they're going to trap more guys
here.
Still stuck at 50. So, this guy's still
stuck.
Market slowing down here. That D 50
still caught.
Still caught
the technically the the delta on that is
118. But he was a big lot buyer. He was
a thill caught. He's still caught there.
Back to Vpo again. All right. So back to
23s again. So 50s to 20s is the
rotation. Under 200s is the
continuation. I would say
it's tempting here because he is
definitely caught up there. But we keep
holding this BPO here.
Repo again. Do we let go of this and go
200s now? Is what I'm wondering.
Big seller trying to step in here at the
20s. Not getting his way yet. still
being absorb absorbed. I can't talk
properly today.
Unfortunately, if they let go of this,
if we go to 200 is what we do,
we're just stuck here. We got to get
under this and then start rejecting.
Here we go. Can you see follow through
here, Mr. Seller? Still being absorbed
down here. I think we're going to go
200s and then if we get under, we can
have some fun. Here we go. Is the move
to 200s.
Got a small piece in this early. And
here we go. All right. Let's see if we
can get under this and have some fun now
and go for a new lower day.
So, we want to watch 85s now. Small
piece on only still because it's not
giving me a pullback to get into. So, if
we reject 200s now, we'll add into this.
I'm going to cover some into 85. Need
this cell to stay heavy at 200 now. Need
the cell to stay heavy at 200. Big
seller stepping in here. We want 200 to
reject here and I'll add on. Come back
up a little bit and let's see if we can
sell through this.
Nice. Here we go. Covering something to
85 if we can because there's a seller
here. Here we go, guys. Here we go. The
exact trade we just talked about. Okay,
we want to stay heavy versus 85 now.
Ideally, this is the exact trade we just
talked about. The guy at 50 became the
liquidity for us. We retested him at 50.
We broke under 200. And now we're gonna
see if we can stay heavy for a new low
of day and get down into 140s.
Here we go. Here we go. Here we go. All
the sellers are now comfortably in the
money. Comfortably in the money, these
sellers now. We should break lower.
There's no reason really for us to not
break lower. ES just made a new low of
day. Just be aware of that. ES has just
closed its gap and made a new low of
day. We must be aware of that.
Where are we at the cues? Coming into
the 10s. Maybe we need 200 to stay heavy
here or I'll cut. I will not let a
squeeze back over 200 happen. Did cover
some into 85s like I talked about.
Please don't knock me out of 200s and
then do your usual [\h__\h] where you go to
210s and then puke and then Alex has not
got any position on.
So far so good. Risking 2011's for me
now. Come on, baby.
Come on, baby.
Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go.
We're under 85s. Let's go. Accelerate.
Just flush it. Just [\h__\h] flush it.
Flush it. Come on. ES is doing it. Come
on, ENQ. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come
on. Everyone's doing it but you, ENQ.
Stop [\h__\h] about. Go, go, go, go, go,
go, go. Give me that big [\h__\h] candle.
Three, two,
one. Half a second. Here it comes. Give
it to me to the IB and then crack. Come
on.
I'm willing you to do it. I want them to
stay heavy 85 now if possible. I want
them to stay heavy at 85 as possible
there through back through the 85s.
Don't want don't want to squeeze out
here to 200s. Really, come on. Please
stay heavy here. We have divergence to
ES which has cleaned out these lows,
right? We're trying to take out these
lows to get down here right now.
Please,
come on, ENQ. Stop being a pain in the
butt. All right, we've got relative
weakness in ENQ and it won't [\h__\h]
wash. It's quite annoying.
Do not want a reclaim of 85. It's
possible. Like, it can come up to 200,
but I'd rather we stay heavy at 85 here
for a wash.
Come on. Come on. Come on. Just do it.
Just swipe it down to 145 here. Oh, one
one lot filled there into previous week
close. Give me it. You're finally
coming. Come on, baby. Come on. We want
45s. We want this gray box and then
we're runners down here now. All right.
Want this gray box and then we're
runners down here now.
Really good. Here we go, folks. Here we
go, folks. Here we go, folks.
This was all from that guy getting
trapped. So maybe you guys are starting
to understand how we trade over here at
FLO. The main trend was down. We needed
someone to get trapped. I talked about
this happening before it even happened.
Right? We talked about this happening
before it even happened. What I would
look for if I wanted to play more short.
We're almost there now. Right. So this
guy here, this 300 lot, he got stuck. We
retested him. He stayed heavy. We broke
down once we let go of uh 220s and 200s.
I had a small piece on. I added in here.
Once we stayed heavy at 200, I covered
some into 85 here just to be proactive.
I'm looking for some cover here and then
here now.
And I don't want to hear anything like
you didn't know what to do. I literally
told you exactly what we're looking at
way before it happened.
Come on. Come on. Come on. We want 160
to stay heavy now. Here we go. Get me
those 45s. Get me those 45s.
Get me those 45s and then let's tank.
Let's go. Watching ES very closely. It's
coming into its 20day SMA. Okay. Just be
careful there. We know that can be a bid
opportunity.
Let's go. Let's go. We're almost there,
folks. We are almost [\h__\h] there for
the next TP. We should probably draw
this out, shouldn't we?
right here. 200's reject. I was in a
little bit earlier than that. I did tell
you. Peace out into here. And we are
going to look now to see if we can get
this. But we are peace out into here.
Okay. Be peace out into here. Here we
go, folks. TP1 hit. And now let's see.
Here come the aggressive sellers.
Maybe Peter. Yeah, maybe. I mean, if we
get lucky, we will get those uh 24,800s
that we were looking for yesterday. It's
possible. All right. It's possible we
get this. It is possible. We're not
going to rule it out. We want this
ideally. If if you get this, there's
going to be 400 points, right? But we're
looking for this now. This is the next
point we're looking for. So, we're TP1
in here. We will get uh 135 points down
to here. All right. And we'll see if we
let go of that.
We are going to respect uh 110s again.
Okay. Uh these levels that we're at, we
must respect this. This is I'll show you
why. This gray box, same level as
yesterday where we covered yesterday.
It's exactly the same trade um high time
frame, right? Remember this node here
from the previous week. This is what we
respected yesterday. We covered into it.
Look at the reaction here. Right? We
will respect that. We get under this
node. I'd say a break of 25,30,
we'll start to opening up this room to
960s. And then down here, remember this
is still naked, right? It's still naked
down there.
But respect this node, please, from the
previous week. Pay yourself some money.
in this gray box is this node.
It's crazy, isn't it? All the guys at
the beginning of the stream like do
something, click something, do
something, do something. All you've got
to do is wait. Like, you have to learn
to wait for the setup. You have to
learn. All right? The whole principle of
the market, this is not me preaching.
I'm trying to help you. All right? We
will get good moves when we build
liquidity. When we build liquidity, when
we build liquidity, especially when we
do a failed breakout with someone
trapped, that's when we get good moves.
We do not get good moves when we are
building liquidity. We get moves when we
use their liquidity. When we use their
liquidity, when we use their liquidity.
All right? That is the same on higher
time frame. It is the same principle. Do
not get caught into their [\h__\h] of
playing in here. Or look, if you're a
range trader and you want to do that, do
what the bloody hell you want. But for
me, I would much rather be in this than
be in this, right? This is easier for me
to manage my stop and be patient in.
This is frustrating to play in. Okay,
let's see now, folks. Bottom of this
box. We're looking for a break outside
of 110s ideally, and we're going to see
if we can get into 25,59s.
I will check gold when I'm out of this
trade, bud. I know a few of you asking
for gold. I promise I will check it all.
Let's just get through this first. All
right, there's 1,800 of you watching.
Only 700 likes. Let's smash that like
button for me, please. Okay, Alex,
you're the best educator. I love the way
you explain stuff. Finally, the trading
makes sense, why it's doing what it's
doing. Yeah, there you go. There you go.
Great. Alex, can you explain
as to why you're comfortable not to get
a swipe up on the last nine red candles?
That always scares me. Uh, it's just I
mean, it can swipe up. It can always
swipe up. Sorry, croaky throat. Uh, it's
more about who's stuck where, right? So,
all the time we're under 21s, there's a
seller, right? So, why am I comfortable
right now? There's a seller here at the
21s. If we swipe through 21s, we have a
little bit of buyers and an imbalance
here. Again, an imbalance you might not
be able to see, but imbalance here. But
all the time we're under this. Look at
the aggressive sellers. They keep
stepping in. We're going to get this
fill, guys. We're going to keep
stepping. Look at the aggressive sellers
stepping in. And this is why I'm
comfortable because the tape is heavy.
It is a heavy tape. Big seller down here
at the lows 150 into 100. So you could
cover some into the whole number here.
We have a big seller here. But we have a
200 lot trying to cover some into 25,085
right now. I still think there's a
chance to move lower here, folks. There
could be a snapback for sure. We're very
steep and extended. We're trying to get
down to here. This is an obvious
liquidity level. We're under the
hundreds at the moment. So, big sellers
stepped in at 100, at 110, 122. Here we
go, folks. Here we go, folks. Let's fill
this guy at 85. And hopefully, if he
pulls his bid or we slap through him, we
will get this filled down towards 60.
Here we go, folks.
Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. All right.
Big seller just got a little bit caught
into 90. All right. There is a passive
bid down here at 85. I still think we
will take this guy out at 85. And he's
here for a reason. 250 lock down here at
85. We should be aware of it. You can
cover some into this. I'm going to try
and get all the way down into here if
possible.
Watching this node. Where's the edge of
this node? It is where we are right now.
Okay. We need to be careful on the
previous week here. Definitely need to
be careful. Pay yourself some if you
haven't. So, we're bidding in front of
that 25,085. We haven't taken him out
yet. If you're like, where are you
seeing him? Look at bookm. All right.
There's a big 200 lot right here. Right.
We just sold very aggressively into him.
120 lot into him, but we haven't taken
him out. I want to see this take out
flush down into these uh 60s for us and
then we can be pretty much done with it.
Pretty much done with it.
You do not want to reclaim of 122s. I
tell you that much. You do not want to
reclaim of 122s here.
There we go. Get through this guy.
They're trying to protect 95. Let's get
through 85 now. Let's accelerate through
85. Let's accelerate through 85. Let's
get this cover if we can down here. We
need to break 85. I keep trying to put a
bit of a wall up here. And also, it's it
is uh the 20day on the spy. Let's get
through 85.
Let's get through 85. Here we go. 85.
85. 85. Get through them. They're trying
to stack here. Get through them. We're
starting to bid here a little bit. We
should swipe. Here's the 85 test. Get
out my way. Mr. 200 lot. Please get out
the way. Get out the way. Get out the
way. Get out. Huge seller here. We
filled 200 of that. So, a big big seller
here. 241 lot. If we can't get break
down here, I will take the rest off.
There's a big seller coming in here
trying to force us through the 85. We
need follow through. We do not want this
guy stuck. 222 lot stuck at the low
right now. We need follow through under
85 for the snapdown.
Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come
on. Come on. Come on. That's huge
sellside delta down here. We must see a
breakdown. Here we go. 85s. We need
follow through now. If I do not see
follow through here, I will cover.
Think we're going to get 60s. They're
now adding down to the 60s. We might get
this full cover, guys.
Be very careful. That is a huge seller
down at 85. It must stay heavy under 85
here.
Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come
on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on.
Come on. Come on. Come on. Do it. Do it.
Do it. Do it. ES looks great. Everything
looks great. Come on. Come on, ENQ. Come
on. Give me my final TP, you mother
clucker.
Bidding off it. Be very careful. We need
to flash through 85 Howard here. They
cannot hold this on a retest. I will
cover if they hold this retest.
I will cover at 100 if they hold this
retest. Stop. It's going to move to 101.
Here we go. Here we go. Here we go. Here
we go. Give it. Give it. Give it. Give
it. Give it. Go. Go. Go. Go. Go. Go.
Step on it. Step on it. Do not [\h__\h]
reclaim. Step on it.
Like I said, stops move to 101. The
reason being that the last pain point
for the seller was 100. I do not want it
lifting through that whole number.
We're looking for 60s.
Come on, stay heavy. They can afford a
pop right up to 40. So, I'm not going to
let them do that. For me, it can stop me
out at 101's. If it's going to do it
very tight to stop me, I'm out. Out on a
runner. That's fine. We tried, folks. It
was good. It was good. But there were
too many sellers down here. There's a
big seller here at 115. 475 lot at 115.
I'm not going to sit through this. So,
we can wait. We can think about a
revisit up. But the reason I covered
here was that big lot down here getting
stuck. All right. This again, I can take
you to bookmarking
hell. If they do it now, I'll be upset.
But I'm going to miss my TP. Never mind.
All right. So the reason I covered that
was just this guy here. All right. 186
lot uh 87 lot 245 lot. All these sellers
getting caught at these lows. We were
needed to see breakdown under 85. Right.
And they have just pulled all their bids
down here into 60s which is where I was
looking to trade. So we can afford
relief right back up here which is why I
do not want to sit in this and give too
much back. You guys are can hold here. I
guess technically all the time we're
holding, but I just didn't want to give
too much back on this spike cuz if we
hold now over 85, they can revisit 122s.
If they redo that, they will probably
revisit 145s. And if they get through
45s, they can revisit uh 180s. But you
might you might get your move here.
Let's see. You might get it. I'm out of
it though. I'm done with it.
I'm done with it. Too much selling at
the lows without moving lower for me.
All right.
Sorry we didn't get all of it, folks. We
uh my final cover here was uh here,
wasn't it? So, we got 92 points. I mean,
we if you covered the lows, you would
have got uh Oh, sorry. We got over 100
points. Well, I'm reading the wrong
thing. You would have got 120 points. I
got 100 points out of that. We almost
got this move down here. We can watch
for a revisit, but look how thin we are.
So, we're developing nodes here. We know
they're starting to get some sellers
caught down here, right? So, if we start
reclaiming this, we're pretty thin up to
here, right? You don't want to get
caught in this, which is why I've
covered down here. It might be that they
reflush it, but that's fine. I need to
manage my position how I'm comfortable
with.
Hey, brother. Just started the course.
How do you apply for Discord? Uh, Gak.
uh scroll down to the very end of the
course you'll see there's a module uh
all about Discord just do that
probably Kim
Alex you did wonderfully the cheering
helped me get resolved to join the short
nice
I traded 125 shares of SQQQ nice I'm up
$60 it's small but it's a win there you
go 100 point banger 100 point they're
going to do it now that they [\h__\h]
take me out I don't like this spoofer on
the tape So
probably if I didn't see him, I would
have been more willing to stay in it. So
this spoofer here, this 520 lot, you can
see he was here at 10. So once he came
on the tape, you can see no one was
here. No one's here. No one's here. Once
we got to this point in the day, I don't
know what time this was. 10:46. We had a
400 or 500 lot come on the tape trying
to trap price come up. Came up to me,
lifted. That made me think, no, I'm not
sitting in this for sure. He's now up at
520. He's trying to get them to lift
price higher, which is not what I wanted
to see. If you get a rebreown under 85s
here, you might get the full TP. Maybe
some of you are still in it. I'm out of
it. Like I said, I'm done.
Does the course teach you the gray
boxes? Yeah, it's just le volume levels.
It does. The orderflow course teaches
you.
You don't see the bookmap. It's right
above me. Did I have you on the wrong
screen? Sorry. This one here. You see it
now? this guy here. So, he was on the
tape here for a second. Once we came
into he lifted and he's added 500 lot
higher, right? So, he's trying to
attract price higher right now. And he
is a spoofer because when he was here,
he lifted and went back on the book with
the same size. So, he's on the book for
I don't know a second maybe. Let's see
when he came on the book. He came on the
book at 10:45 and 46 seconds.
He was on the book for a second. Just a
literal ten a tenth of a second. A
second. And then as soon as he came on,
he lifted. Still think there's a chance
to trade lower, but I can't get an entry
here. We are trading far too low. So now
I've lost location. Right, we have
momentum. I've lost location.
First time here. Thanks a lot. You're
welcome. Do you need bookmap to trade as
well as you do? Uh not necessarily. I
just just something that I found very
useful for me. But you know, each to
their own. Like there's a million ways
to trade. Like there's a million ways to
trade. My guy isn't the my guy my way
isn't the only way.
Thought spoofing is illegal. Yeah. Well,
it is. I mean, you can argue he's a
liquidity provider.
Spoofing never gets prosecuted, though.
They It's very hard for them to track
it. How can you track it? If you put an
order in and pull it off, how can you
not? You could just say, "Oh, well, I
like that price and then I didn't like
that price." It's very hard. Just wanted
to say I was 1,300 down on my new 50k
account and now I'm only down 670.
Thanks a lot. You're welcome, William.
You're the best trade in YouTube. You're
welcome. Thanks, man. What's it called?
Where you can see the buyer and seller
volume trapped on the right. This this
this you can't see the buyer and selling
volume. You can only see volume. This is
anchored volume profile. When I show on
my screens, it's delta volume profile.
Alex, can I swap from Trade of Eight to
Ninja? Yes, you can. If you trade with
Trade of Eate, you can get Ninja. It's
the same mother company.
If you can only buy one. Would you
prefer Footprint or Bookmap? Well,
Bookmap has both. So,
it's up to you. It depends depends what
you prefer reading. So, look, we're
trying to lift up to this guy now. His
500 lot is trying to retract price
higher that we just talked about. You
can see him above me on the screen,
right? See this big red line? He's got a
limit order here at sort of 37s 500 lot.
Do I trade prop firms or live capital? I
trade both, but most my live capital
goes into swing positions.
You don't have to do as me, but this is
my game, right? This is what I do. I
trade prop. I make my money from prop. I
take it out. I put it investment
accounts. I swing in those investment
accounts. I probably make
arguably more money in my swings than I
do trading props
over the course of a year. You only need
one or two really good swings to go your
way. And it's uh you know, we can you
can get five 600% gainers in swings in a
matter of months. We had the last big
one was open last year. We had uh I
don't have any big movers this year
because at the moment I'm positioned
mainly in mega cap. I'm mainly looking
for this market to pull back
aggressively
for me to position in. So we made 20% uh
on Robin Hood from last Thursday to
before earnings. I'm just holding a
small piece of that left because I still
think it's a bit of a pig, but there's a
chance we're due uh a little bit more.
Really depends what this market does.
But either way, I'm up on that. I've got
a small piece in IBIT. Um, I'm long
Meta, I'm long Oracle, I'm long AMD, and
I'm long Apple. Uh, Apple and AMD I've
been long since like June, August last
year, and we sold a lot of our AMD for
big profit. I'm only small size left.
I'm waiting for this market to do a
decent pullback. I'm also long
Microsoft, Amazon, Netflix, uh, US, uh,
Rare Earth, and Yuyu Yuyu. All right.
So, I'm actually down on those positions
very slightly, but small size. I'm just
waiting. But these are swing positions.
All right. So, with stuff like Netflix,
Amazon, Microsoft, um, IBET, Meta,
Oracle, AMD, Apple, I'm I'm looking to
hold for many months, if not many years.
All right, you're getting the breakdown
now, guys. You're going to get full TP.
So, they rejected this gray box. You
should get full TP under this. All
right, your next TP is a little bit in
here and then all the way down here. So,
I'd be covering some into 58s.
Oh, you just wonder is today the day.
Is today the day? But this green line
you must cover. A very aggressive seller
down here again. 324 lot on bookmap
selling at 75. So green line I would be
covering no 80 plus% of your position
here. And there you go. There's your
green line. So I'll be taking a good
chunk out here now folks. God dang it.
Had to stop me out before doing it. It
was that spoofer on the tape who got me
stopped. If he wasn't there, we would
have done it in one go. What a pain in
the butt. All right, there's your TP.
So, there's your 140 pointer. Uh, what
is this gray box from?
Oh, this is a an old node. Okay, so
there is some liquidity here previous
week under this. I wouldn't cover some
here. If you've covered here, don't
cover more here. Don't bother. Wait and
see. Now,
next low I'd be looking for is here.
All right. So, I'd be covering 80 90% of
the position and just hold it now. See
if you can get this blue box or ideally
you might get a 400 pointer down into
this. 800 would be your your best cover.
What do I think about CPI tomorrow? I
have no idea. If they cook the books,
who [\h__\h] knows? Who cares? Doesn't
matter if uh the prints good or bad.
They're going to do whatever they want
with it. I really don't care what they
do with the prints, but uh it it's not
looking good. But if you look at like
what's going on with the treasuries and
bonds overnight yesterday, it really is
not looking good out there for this
market. It could get very dangerous very
quickly. I would have preferred if this
market had done the fail breakout like
we talked about. So for bigger moves
this week, what I really wanted to see
was this move into here and a big sell
and cover some here and see if we use
that and then we come lower. That would
be really nice because we've now got
room on the daily Ballinger bands
whereas last week we didn't have room.
Right? So if we think about how we trade
in flow zone now the Ballinger bands are
expanding
20-day 50-day cross. We're looking for
5day to come back down again. Ballinger
bands to come back down and you know
traps in here to resell down to here and
maybe start doing one of these for a bit
until maybe the Q QQ hits 200 day. We we
haven't undercut this yet. I'm still
waiting to see an undercut there. A run
of liquidity on this for a drop down
into here
would be really good. All right. And if
you like that's way too much. It's
really not off the highs. That's really
not. It's only 12%. It's fine. It's
absolutely fine. This market might do a
lot more than that if it starts to get
ugly. But that's what I'd like to do.
And um I've already positioned, if you
think about the stocks that I'm long in,
right? I'm long in tech that's down here
right now, right? It's already puked all
the way down there.
Doesn't mean it can't go further, but
that's where I started started position.
So, if we think about like
RCL,
look, just look at like the software
stocks, right? OCL,
I think about where we are. Here we go.
I've positioned myself long in here,
right? Looking for a rally back and sell
into pops.
Uh, some of these are pretty weak.
Softy,
same thing, right? We think about where
we are. Position myself long in here to
see if we can rally back. It might be
that it undercuts and drops, but that's
fine. I'm going to hold this forever.
So, position myself long in here. So,
we'll wait and see. Does the market want
to do the same thing? I mean, that will
we we'd need NQ would need to come down
here for a catch-up trade, right? But a
QQQ is what I'm watching to see if it
wants to go to its 200. That's
There we go. Right. Does QQQ want to
come to this? Right. We have relative
strength in the cash market versus the
future market. Does QQQ has not retested
this level since 9th of May. Right. Do
we want to come down here? Remember ENQ
has been rebalanced. uh rebalanced has
had numerous new contracts. We are
waiting to see can we get down here. All
right. And if we get down there and
break, are we coming down here? If we're
coming into any of this area on the QQQ,
I'll be long-term swing long in cash,
right? Not in everything anything
leverage. You could take leaps, right?
I'll be long-term swing long as in 5 to
10 year swing long
in like a retirement account. So, Roth
IRA for me and Isa. Hopefully that makes
sense. But again, I am not a uh
financial adviser. You should be
managing your own account as you see
fit.
Yeah. I call that swing trades in
Discord. Yeah.
Every time I say box, it reminds you of
Formula 1. Yeah. Box. Box. Lewis box,
do I come live daily? Yeah, live daily.
Monday to Friday, 9:15 open. All right,
585 lot here at 25,000. Uh, we are
absolutely puking here. This market is
heavy, heavy, heavy, heavy. Absolutely
no reason to bid on this market today.
By the way, folks, in case you were
looking for longs, look at the VIX.
There's no reason to bid on this. We are
approaching uh the old high here. Is it
previous day or previous week?
Wednesday, Thursday. We're approaching
previous day high here on VIX.
Be watching that level on VIX. Yes,
already under previous day low. We're
under previous day low. We're watching
these boxes and maybe down here.
Honestly, maybe down here. I'm not
joking. I'm being very honest. You might
get a 400 point move today.
Using a volume footprint. If you get the
chance, show how you can see trap
traders on the last huge trade.
Um, okay. See if it showed it on the
footprint.
All right.
Think about this bar.
Right. We have an imbalance
on the cell here. See this imbalance?
Right. We go sideways here for a long
time.
We failed to break higher. We sell. This
is the first point of the sell. We sell
down the next part of the trade here.
Let me just make sure I'm getting my
timings right here. What time is this?
10:30s. Yes, that was what we looked
for. So 10:30s. Yeah, this is the guy.
So remember when we were going sideways
here? So we caught this flush today. We
played the We played this short today,
right? First short we played was
was here 300
and we add and we're out. Right? Once we
go sideways, this is your liquidity
building stage because we know the
market doesn't go straight down. The
market goes here, here, here. Correct?
Right. All so far all makes sense. So if
we are
if the liquidity building part if we
think about this as a range. All right.
If we think about this as a range, this
is the range.
I do this as a yellow box, right? Stay
with me. Hopefully, you can see it. This
is a range.
What happens at the top of this range in
general? What happens at the top of this
range? Think about newbie traders.
There's a break of 25,000, folks. You're
still moving lower. You You've got a
chance to go 24800s. I'm telling you, if
they get aggressive, all right, at the
top of this range, what happens is
breakout buyers come in. All right,
breakout buyers come into this market.
They think we're going to squeeze
higher. What else happens? Shorts who
are positioned here have their stops
run, which means what? A short seller
who gets his stop run becomes what? A
market buyer. All right. So, if we got
short sellers who become market buyers
because they get stop hunted and
breakout buyers here, what does that
mean? We get lots of buying activity at
the market. Aggressive buying. What does
that mean? It means a institutional
passive seller can pair off. Remember,
no deal is done in the market unless we
have an aggressive buyer and a passive
seller or a passive buyer and aggressive
seller. They have to be both sides. So,
in here, what happens? This is where all
those big buyers come in. Look at this
delta. There's the failed break. And we
don't move higher, which means what?
There's a passive seller sitting here.
And then we move lower. How do we know
he's stuck? We retest that level 250s.
Remember, he was stuck at 250s. There is
his retest. We stay heavy. Okay, we know
there's a passive seller who's not going
to let him out. We break down. We start
looking for joins. All right, as we
break down, I joined a little piece
early, but where I really got heavy was
under 200 because I knew that the seller
was originally stuck at 200. There was a
seller here stuck at 200. Once he got
out of the money, we got a break. We
come to the other side of the range. All
these buyers now stop out and become
sellers in the market. All right. Same
thing. This is the same thing here,
guys, where I stopped out except we've
now done it. We go sideways. We fail to
break higher. We trap buyers. We break
down. We go lower, right? We go lower.
Hopefully that makes sense.
Uh but again, do the course, folks, if
you want to learn more about this. So
I'm I'm giving away they are not uh well
they are advanced principles I guess but
just do the course do the course you
you'll learn all of this I know Bart
you've done the course so
exactly Dean stock players become
liquidity Alex just joined it is it too
late to short now uh oh we are let we
still letting go I all it is is momentum
is great your location is is very very
poor now um you can maybe think about
rejoining
somewhere up here. All right. May maybe
there's a rejoin up here if they build
out. Maybe they do a two-leg get stuck
roll if they're going to do this move.
But I mean it it's much harder now.
Remember the short the main short we
wanted today was all the way up here. We
wanted to short up here once we broke
down. We were looking for a retest of
350s.
The guy was so impatient today. Oh,
you're [\h__\h] Whatever he said. Just like
all right. So, our first short today was
in and around these 270s and our second
short today was in around the 200. So,
we look good. Uh, let me check liquidity
on the tape.
Uh, really, you need to stay heavy
versus sort of 18s and 20s here. There
are some sellers starting to get
aggressive under the 25,000. So, you can
use that whole number. Like I said, I
think 800s is possible today. You can
cover some into this blue box, but this
is very possible today.
Very, very possible.
How can I join the course? Uh links
pinned to the chat above or just go to
flowzonetrader.com.
Can you trade just using footprint? Yes,
you can.
This is anchored volume profile on the
right, guys. Long here. No, I would be
not be long here, guys. Just why? Why
would you be long here? Okay, we've come
into an area of interest
and the tape's very heavy. Is there a
reaction? Have we changed changed state
or are we just going to keep knifing
through? Like I said, it's very possible
we come down to here today. You would
need to see a reaction to get long. You
would need to see this reclaim, hold,
leave sellers trapped, reason to go
higher. You are not seeing that right
now. You are seeing a blue box thinking,
"Oh, I'm just going to try it." Well,
what happens when we do that? This is
where people go wrong. Just because we
come to an area does not mean anything.
It is the reaction in that area that
matters.
Alex, any advice for
any advice in fear of trading? I keep
selling early. Uh, yes.
Lower your size. Lower your size and
just move your stop through each swing.
All right. and move it down and trail
it. If you lower your size, you'll
probably be more willing to sit in it
longer.
My cousin was the guy here yesterday
blaming you for his losses. He
apologizes and says, "Your speech
genuinely set his mind straight. Much
love." You're welcome, Real Race Films.
You're welcome. And like I said
yesterday, it wasn't done in hate. I've
been him. Every trader goes through
that. I can remember getting absolutely
cooked on a short um when I thought I
had perfect position and I had like two
or three attempts and I got cooked five
figures and then it [\h__\h] puked after
it spiked me out a few times and I
blamed the guy I was trading with. Um
because it was easier to blame him than
it was to look at look at myself in the
mirror. And you know what? He stopped
out two times for small losses, took the
third trade, and he had a [\h__\h]
whopper of a trade. and I blamed him for
it and it was just me. I've been there.
I've been there. Every trader goes
there. It's so easy to blame everyone
else. You know what guys, that is a
lesson for life because in life, the
importance of I'm going to get preachery
here. Guru Alex, and I'm going through
this at the moment. The importance of
self-reflection is massive. All right?
If we go through life blaming everyone
else for our problems, if we're
constantly like, "Lord, why are you
doing this for us or to us? This
person's an [\h__\h] to me. this person
did this, this D. Right? If you go in
that negative mindset of it's everyone
else's fault, you fail to look at
yourself. And at the end of the day,
you've got to look in the mirror. You've
got to be able to tell yourself that you
love yourself. You've got to be proud of
how you go about your life. You've got
to be able to put a flag in the ground
and be like, "This is who I am." And I
don't mean your ego talking. I mean core
key principles. All right? Key key parts
of how you act. Can you selfreflect? Can
you find acceptance? Can you find
forgiveness? Can you find love? Can you
improve as a person 1% better each day?
Can you stop pointing the finger at
other people? Can you look within
yourself? If you can do that, you will
improve trading very, very quickly. It
is the hardest skill in trading. Like I
always talk about, the hardest skill in
trading is the ability to change. All
right. Some of you will probably be here
and you will chase trades and you will
keep chasing trades and keep chasing
trades and keep chasing trades even
though you know you keep losing getting
it wrong. Can you journal? Can you stop
yourself doing it? Can you change your
habit? All right. Same as bottom pickers
and top pickers. Guess who used to be a
top picker in the market? This guy.
Right. This guy used to pick tops all
the time. Guess who used to add to
losers? This guy. Guess who's blown up
lots and lots of accounts? And I'm not
talking about prop firms. I'm talking
about big money accounts. This guy.
Guess who had to have a [\h__\h] hard
look in the mirror and make some
changes? This guy. All right. So, when I
say stuff like this to you, it is not
digging you guys out. I have been there.
And I there is no trader in the world or
a very few amount in the world who have
not gone through these journeys of like
making errors over and over and over
again and not making the changes. It
comes from being a better version of
yourself. Trading is going to show you
all the bad parts of yourself. I promise
you it's what it will do. It's it's the
biggest stare in the m mirror you will
ever see. And you know the person the
other side of the trade, if they're
better at reflecting at themselves than
you are, they're going to win, right?
they're going to win. We think about
this here, right? The person picking
bottoms again and again and again and
again. All right, the person doing that
versus the person who's waiting for them
to get trapped and playing the momentum.
Right? This guy wins because he
understands patience. This guy doesn't
understand patience or the girl or their
person I should just say. I'm sorry.
Right. Same as here. The people that
were trading in here wanting to click
buttons, not learning from their
mistakes, wrong. the person who's
learned that mistake. We're going to
wait for a failed breakout and look for
a trap buyer and then we're going to
play their pain. Easy money, right? It's
not because I'm amazing. It's cuz I've
learned doing this is how I blow up
accounts. Okay? It's not me better than
you. No human on earth is better than
someone else. We are all made equally.
All right? So, that's all I got to say.
Just trying to help you guys. So, I'm
really glad to hear that. Whoever said
that to yesterday, I hope it's had a big
impact in their career.
It's so funny. I do all that and I the
first thing I see is what your anchor
volume profile settings. That's not a
dick at you, Chris. It's just it's like
I'm literally asked that a hundred times
a day. It's so funny. Even though it's
Nightbot keeps posting in chat. All
right, here you go.
Width 20. Placement to the right. Ticks.
I have it to tick, not rows. And I have
it to two. You can have it a thousand
rows if you prefer. I have it to two
ticks.
Welcome to the team. Welcome to the
team. Who's this? Uh D Carson Davis.
Thank you. Thank you.
James Bond says, "I was humbled like
that and God humbled me. We have to take
responsibility for our own actions."
100% buddy. 100%.
Yeah. Such the lux. So, you're talking
about me? Yeah. Well, if it sounds like
I'm talking about you, I'm talking about
you without talking about you. I'm
talking about all of us, right?
Absolutely all of us. We're all the
same.
Dix Gaming. See you tomorrow. Yeah. Take
care, mate. Have a good one.
I took my P&L off the screens when
learning the process. Yeah, I think I
think honestly I think that's a great
thing to do. Don't trade P&L because
it's not the winners as well, it's the
losers, right? One of here's another big
thing. You know I say size down all the
time. It's not just for like to sw stop
the swings. Your mentality.
If you are the wrong side of a trade, if
you are the guy trying to get long here,
for example, right, and you are using
too big a size when this starts to drop,
even though you know I'm wrong, right?
If you look at your P&L here and it's
down 3,000 bucks,
right, you won't stop out. That's too
much money for you. So, you'll add in
and then you'll be down here. This is
again talking from experience. You'll be
down here and now you've added more size
on like a [\h__\h] Now you're down 10,000
bucks. And now that's such an
unfathomable amount of money to you. You
are completely unwilling to stop out
even though your stop was up here. Your
first stop is the best stop. You didn't
take it. So you add on more, right? You
add to your loser more and now you're
down 25,000 bucks and maybe you know if
you're trading stocks that's your PDT
and maybe Mr. Broker says, "Hey, you've
been margin cooled. You're [\h__\h]
done." And then what happens? You crawl
in bed to your wife and you cry and you
can't believe what you've done because
this felt like a huge vortex and you
knew you should have stopped out and you
didn't. And maybe you do that another
time and another time and another time
and another time because you don't
self-reflect. You just blame it on
something else. Oh, it's the market
makers. Oh, it should have done this.
This is what I used to do. I'm telling
you, it's what I used to do. That's
[\h__\h] them. They [\h__\h] do this.
Truth. Alex didn't have the discipline
to stop when his trade was wrong.
That's the truth. That's the truth.
There's no way of getting away from it
until you can admit that to yourself.
That's the truth.
To get good, you got to suck really bad.
Once the fire burns you enough, you'll
learn. That's it. Yeah. I always say
you're going to ride a bike, you got to
fall flat on your face, right? You have
to fall flat on your face. I don't have
a wife. Well, then you're probably just
crying to yourself or your dog or maybe
you got a fish. Maybe you're crying to
your goldfish. I don't know. But you you
get the point, right? You get the point.
Is 860 final target? Uh 800 for me. I'm
out of this, folks. I got knocked out
here, unfortunately. But my final target
is down here. Right. It's not to say
that we won't bounce before we get
there. But I would think this is a naked
point of control. This is where I have
thought we will trade to this week. This
is what we had in the weekly newsletter.
This is what we tried to play for
yesterday. This is what we've been
prepared for in Discord all week. I
would have preferred to see a failed
breakout of the highs, the swing highs
on the hourly before we got here. But
this is what we are looking for. This is
the same like nothing's trade changed,
guys, from this week. Anyone who's in
Discord will know that we have been
looking for this all week long, right?
All week long. We we would have
preferred the fail breakout. If we got
the fail breakout, I'm telling you now,
I would have taken SQQQ on a swing. Um,
we looked at this same trade I showed
you guys yesterday. We're looking for
the same thing. I will find it for you.
It was I'm pretty sure I put it in the
newsletter. I'm fairly sure I put these
levels in the newsletter. Here we go.
Same thing. Right. We started talking
about this, reminding everyone on
Discord. What's this on the 9th? So,
like 3 days ago. Here's the play. Right.
We're looking for a push fail break
above here all the way potentially up to
800. But I think 600 would have held.
We're looking for this trade back down
into the naked point of control. And you
can see here if bears set another trap,
it will look like this. All right. So,
this is what we were looking for. It's
been there the whole time.
So, this is your your covers should be
down into here. This would be what do we
say? It's a 400 point of those that got
it. 400 points. I mean,
400 points. And yet, there are still
people who are willing to come and
challenge me here every day.
That's what I find upsetting, guys.
That's what makes it hard for my ego.
For my ego, that's what I struggle with
because I feel like I give a lot out for
free to help.
My ego struggles when people
say things like I don't know what I'm
talking about. That hurts my ego. That's
something I have to deal with.
Nathan Lee, appreciate your insight.
What What would you have to see to go
long? Would you ever long or just play
the rejections all day? Uh yes, you can
long once enough shorts get trapped.
Right? So ideally, ideally at this
point, right? Ideally, we want
lowhanging fruit to be taken out. But
like let's say we come down here, we
build liquidity like this for a while,
right? And then we break down under this
and shorts come flying in and then we
reclaim this and do this. Okay? Then you
can think about a long. You better know
it's counter trend, but you can think
about long. So you'd be TP TP TP TP,
right? And it wouldn't go straight up.
It would be like this, this, this, maybe
a dunk. This all right, for example.
Right, this move here is the same thing.
We build liquidity, we trap shorts, we
take out low hanging fruit, we reclaim,
we go the other way until that point.
What's your trend? Right? Where's your
initial balance? There's your IB. What
are we doing? We're doing IB expansion,
right? We're in a trend day. Leaving
volume. We tried to leave volume twice.
This is the same play. Anyone who joined
me yesterday, what did we look for
yesterday when I said if we leave trap
volume, the volume yesterday was up
here. If we leave trap volume, we're
going to try and come down here. All
right, it's the same play. Anyone that
joined me, we left the volume moved down
a bit unfortunately today to these sort
of 200s. We've left trap volume. Where
is the trap volume on this week? There
it is. This is all the participation
from Monday to now. So, if these are all
buyers, remember these buyers are all
looking to get up here. All right, I
wanted them to come flying in here to
then play that. This would have been a
swing short position for me. Um,
unfortunately, we didn't get that. Like
I said, we don't always get what we
want, but we are getting this right
naked point of control from last week.
Our expectation is to come here. Now, we
might bounce back off there and revisit
there. That might be the new range for
Friday next week. It might be that we
puke and we start doing this now. I
don't know, folks. I don't know. We can
only trade what's in front of us. But
the high probability move was from here
to here. That's a very high probability
move.
Gold is on a crazy drop. Well, it looks
like they're just selling everything
right now. It looks like we're just
we're d-risking in the whole market
right now. That's what it looks like to
me. There's a full d-risk going on. Like
everyone's out of everything right now.
That's the truth, right? So, we are
riskoff environment at the moment. So,
if you've been,
you know, think about everyone who's
been long since um
March, April last year, right? Think
about how much of a percent they've
made, right? And also gold. Remember we
said gold and silver. Anyone who's
joined me, we were looking for failed
followthrough. You're going to see the
same thing. Uh, sorry. Uh, GC
GC1. Hopefully, I've still got the
drawings on here. Right. Remember, we
talked about I said I would be short
here. Anyone again who joined me
yesterday, where would we be short from?
Where's the volume? Look at the ledge.
We went over this yesterday. You want to
be short in here. You do not want to be
long in there. Right. Here's the volume.
Have they found acceptance above? No,
anyone who bought here is trapped.
Here's the sell. Here's the revisit.
There's your short opportunity. Here's
your cover point. Run as if it breaks
down. Even better on silver. We went
over this yesterday, guys. This is not
like, oh, he's making it up. We went
over this. That's not silver.
You can see I've had it drawn back on.
Same thing. It's the same principles,
folks. Draw this on. Where's everyone
stuck? That we have a node up here. If
they can't get back over this node,
all the buyers here are stuck. Here's
your sell. They can't even pivot up into
that. That's how weak this is. You'd be
covering some into here and you'd be
looking for this now at this point.
Honestly, that's why folks, this is how
the market moves. It is not some magic
thesis, right? It's just trap players.
All it is, it's an auction of trap
players,
right? You are almost there guys.
Another 100 points or so. Another 80
points or so. Uh might be that they find
a bid soon but we will see.
people being punished. Yeah, exactly.
We've talked about it, right? We've
talked about this range on the cues.
It's really important you guys get in
the habit of uh looking at higher time
frames, right? We've talked about
even here if we just measure out from
this high,
right? Where is everyone stuck? Why does
it keep changing my volume color? It's
very annoying. Right, everyone's stuck
here, right? We're thin under here.
Hopefully, it's got my Oh, it's lost
everything. This is [\h__\h] Right.
Give me a second, guys. It's literally
lost everything. We're going to change
this. All right. From the pin high.
Jesus Christ. Give me a second.
Save a new PL template.
Jesus. All right. From the pin high,
look who's trapped. All right. So, like
someone just said, I' I've been calling
it from 5th of November, uh, which is
like here from this high. This is where
we failed, right? Here's all the trap
volume. We've talked about this. The
same principle we talked about today on
the lower time frame. What is this right
here? Hello. Guess what happened there?
Same principle. Okay, exactly the same
principle. Buyers move this down so you
can see it. Sorry. Buyers came flying in
here. Did we hold? No. Failed breakout.
Rejection. Same level. We are trading
lower now. All right. We have buyers
caught above us. Where are we going to
trade to? Well, we can
attempt to go for the last year. Can
always do it from the swing low. Let's
see if it would develop it.
Uh, would it do it for us? We were about
to find out.
Get rid of this histogram. Give me a
second.
Okay. So, if we are going to leave this,
we've talked about this again. We are
very very thin in here, right? We are
very very thin
in here. So from I don't know what we
call this July to September right if we
leave this right here which is where
we're coming down to test and we get the
Ballinger bands expanding and the 5day
and the 20-day and everything trading
down we come back down to this 200. If
we lose this 200 and we undercut this we
will probably wash to this node here
right sub 24,000. If we start losing
that and we cannot hold these pivots
here all the volume is way down here at
22,600. So we are currently looking for
a breakout underneath this swing point
here from 25th of November. If we do
that, we'll cover some in here and we'll
then look for expansion into 23. We to
go over this in the weekly news
newsletter 23,500 and if we get very
heavy all the way down here. You might
say that this is impossible. Uh this is
very much not impossible breakout
pullback. This is still very very very
possible. if they want to do the dirty
undercut, they'll come and take these
stops, turn inside, and then we'll see
how we go the rest of the year. It's
very, very, very possible.
Same thing that we look at on every
single time frame. Look at flow zones
just selling us down. So, your your
final cover, remember, we are looking
for 800s.
We're looking for 800s.
Sorry, there's so many questions here. I
can't see all of them. What's my win win
rate? I always talk about this between
sort of 68 and 74%. But I think that is
skewed. All right, remember when I'm
trading, I'm looking for big winners
where possible. Lots of those wins are
like break even plus one tick. It counts
as a win for me. It's not a win. You
will see me on stream, if you turn up,
you will see me numerous times take like
three attempts at the same trade. The
first two might count as a win. They're
not. They're break even. The third one
goes for me. Or sometimes it doesn't and
then I miss it, you know. Yeah, I'm live
every day. Monday to Friday.
Monday to Friday. 9:15 uh Eastern time
all the way until lunch. Half an hour
left. How we doing on the likes, folks?
How are we doing on the likes?
Almost at 1,000. Let's get this up to
1,000 likes if we can.
Is this all CPI positioning? Lots of
stops to tear through tomorrow. I mean,
maybe. But like I said, we've just left
all the volume. I mean, even if we te
even if we hit this target today and
turn around, where are we going to turn
around to? 25,200. What do we expect to
happen there? Sell, right? Sell. So, we
can do exactly what you're saying,
controlled selling.
Maybe today, maybe tomorrow. Right. They
might do this, but this is still a back
test to sell then at that point. Right.
Right. Very, very close. Start moving
your stop down here a little bit. If I
was you, you were getting very, very
close. You don't want to give like too
much size back here. Oh, I wish it
hadn't stopped me out on this. in his
second day in a row
the spy swings. Uh I mean VIX is still
going. We're in the 20s. I mean
this market can really bleed guys. You
have to understand that. Uh I wouldn't
be Can there be a re rebalance? Yeah.
But what if CPI is bad and and we go
really risk off? A lot of you guys might
be new new like we can go really risk
off really aggressive when we have
multiple time frame buyers trapped for
months and months and months and months
and months and months and months. A
catalyst event can cause us to go really
really really risk off. Right.
Who are you using for prop firms right
now? My top five like I always talk
about Lucid, take profit trader, Apex,
Traderify, and Funded Next. They're my
top five. There's a video on my YouTube
on them explaining which ones might be
best for you. All right, QQQ coming into
that 600 level.
Very, very close. You're almost here,
folks. Is anyone still in this for this
400 point banger? I would love to know
another streamer who's giving you 400
points today
for free.
Some of you still in it. Oh, [\h__\h]
hell, guys. I love it. I love it.
Nice.
Nice. You're almost there. You are
almost there. Expect reactions to happen
soon. I tell you what, there is a buyer
down at 24,775.
We are getting very, very heavy. You're
very close. You're very, very close.
Oh, you stopped that with me. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I can't believe they stopped me out.
that it was that spoof on the Here you
go. Here you go. You're basically there
into the 800s. Uh you can pay yourself
on this flush. Do not overhold. Right.
Do not overhold. They're being very
aggressive down here. You're basically
there. Don't be a dick for a tick.
You've got 400 points. Don't try and get
the last two or three points if it
doesn't give it to you. Right. At least
pay yourself. At least pay yourself on
this swipe.
Do you have used or have content on
using footprint candles? Uh, I have a
course on it. I don't do it for free. I
give away too much.
Floan as everyone taking dubs. I hope
so.
Wave Gaming, I'm out. I was down 1K. I'm
now up 3.2,000. Thanks, Alex. This will
help my wedding funds this year.
Amazing. Oh, congratulations. Get
married as well. Best thing I ever did
in my life.
Uncle Hoodie logging off. Thank you,
mate. Made $10,000. I love it. Nice
work,
Nathan. Getting my daughter ready for
school. Okay. Are you going to be
looking for reversal back up? I will
consider it, but it's uh it's not the
main trend I'm looking for. Remember, if
you are going to t play that counter
trend trade, we are currently in a
riskoff environment. I cannot say it
enough, folks. We're in a riskoff
environment. This can keep selling. We
have volume so much volume trapped.
Right? Look at the mag. I'll give you a
readout on the mag. Tesla 2.11% down.
Nvidia 1.42% down. Microsoft 1.24% down.
Meta 3 and a half% down. Google flat
relative strength. Nice to see. Amazon
3.05% down. Apple 3.35% down. Look at
some of these broader names. Thank god
we took some profits on Hood. Hood
almost 10% down. That would probably be
SSR tomorrow. Netflix 5% down. Coming
into key levels on Netflix. We are
coming into some key levels. A lot of
this market getting whacked right now.
We are going full risk off on this
market right now. There will be some
good buying opportunities if we can keep
dumping in this market. Hopefully we
can.
Hopefully we can
want to just have a look at GooG finding
relative strength here. That is
interesting to me. Where are we?
And it's nowhere near where we need it.
I'm surprised they're holding that up.
That is going There is a big old gap
down here on Google. Couple of gaps.
squeeze out on Google. All right, look
at that. Tag off that red line. You were
pretty much there. Look, like I said,
don't be a dick for a tick. You You
missed it by like two, three points. Be
done with it. I would be done with it.
Or be be like the tiniest size ever
left. You've just got 400 point trade
live on stream with me.
How many did I get? I think I gotund and
something 120 points out of it before.
It's this guy here. I think it was one
of these guys here who stopped me out by
spoofing the tape higher and running me.
Happens quite a lot to me at the moment.
All right, so you got 545 lot down at
800. Let's see if they take them out.
545 lot down at 800. I would not be
bidding on this, folks. All right.
Please, please, please, please. All
right, we still there are some sellers
caught at 16s, but I don't like this
yet. Like, it can squeeze higher, but
you are asking for it trying to dip by
on a day like today. Just be happy with
what you got.
Hey, thanks for all of this. On my TBT
Evo, I just hit the original profit
target, but I was over 50%. Does that
account reset once I hit or does the
money go towards the buffer?
You're on an eval. What do you mean? On
an eval doesn't go towards the buffer.
So, if you've hit over 50%, you'll need
you'll need to make a bit more money on
the on the next day. They will tell you
how much you need to make.
Kyno NM was down 200, almost blew the
account. Caught the short now up 1,300
on the day. runner got stopped out when
you did, but normally give my profit
back for market. Walking away. Yeah,
good for you. In the buy zone. Yeah,
potentially in a buy zone. Potentially
in a buy zone, but just know how heavy
this market has been.
Know how heavy the market has been.
No clear box drilling above. I mean,
this blue box is your biggest note, but
look, look how thin we are. Like,
there's some spikes, right? But this is
a trend. This is typical of a trend day.
This profile here is typical of a trend
day. We can move this down. This gray
box can come to here. And this maybe can
come to here. And this can go gray.
It needs to be thinner technically, but
I would not be bidding on this
personally.
How do you set up runners on the stop
strategy on NT? Uh if you go to the ATM
strategy, you can split them into the
amount of uh like TPS you have and you
can set them to like 50 points, 75
points, 100 points and then you just
drag them on your screen to where you
see liquidity being
up 2K done for the day. Nice work,
Prrisa W. The whole move but in and out
with micros. How do I change this? In
and out with one or two micros. Chris,
that's still good. You got the whole
move in and out. We can go over it.
Like, you can always send it in in
Discord. We can go over that stuff and
try and refine it.
Aza, you absolutely rock 100. We'll be
buying the course. Thanks a million,
mate. Hey, thanks for the for the super
chat. Appreciate it.
Tesla, how low can it go? Um,
today, do you mean or in general? I
mean, you still look okay. You're still
holding 420s.
Remember that last pivot last week was
down towards that 200 day. We still have
not undercut, though. If you look at the
pivots on Tesla from November 21st,
November 17th, you haven't undercut
them. It might need to undercut those.
If not, then you would need to see sort
of 420s, 409s hold. So, I think if you
start losing those, you're going to
undercut 385s and then you can fill down
to 370, 350 and lower. We have to just
see like it's just a sell day, folks.
Just like calm down. Calm yourself down,
folks. It's just a sell day. It happens.
You know, overall, we're down 1.60% on
the ENQ. It's not like we're [\h__\h]
you know, it's game overtime. It's not
game overtime yet, but uh we are
definitely de-risking.
What is your stand in Bitcoin? Uh I've
made that pretty clear.
I will tell you
this thing
can come much much lower.
Here is my stand on it. Here is my stand
on it. Right? So, I have nibbled I bit
and took a bit here. But this thing can
come down towards 30,000. And no, I am
not joking. This is my stand on it. If
you're new here, this is why thousand
day we we've done the thousand day plus
cycle. We expect 70 to 80% pullback.
Thousand day cycle, 70 to 80% pullback.
Okay, this is why we've completed a,000
day cycle. It is possible they do a 78
to 80% pullback. Maybe they don't, maybe
they don't, but I would not put it past
this thing being able to get down to
30,000. It might scare the [\h__\h] out of
you. It's very possible. Okay, it's
very, very, very possible.
Market environments can change very
quickly.
Right, look at that bid off that red
line.
Like I said, do not be a dick for a
tick. All right. Not be a tick dick for
a dick.
Would I consider going long some stocks
today? I mean, you could if you're
looking for a rebalance for tomorrow,
but like I said, what happens if we're
if this is just the start of the
de-risking environment?
What happens? You're just fishing,
right? Are you fishing off structure?
We just faded value. So for me on uh
Ninja Trader, we just tap value area low
and fail and we're failing it.
So you need to see a higher low here.
You would need to see if you're adamant
on going long, which I am not. But if
you're adamant, you would need to see
360 to 340 protected. If you don't see
that, I don't see how this holds up.
Alex, I just want to say you've helped
me so much. I'm kind of mad I didn't get
in this trade, but I was at class. I'm
super excited for it tomorrow. Yeah.
Awesome, man. Just remember, it's just
one trade, right? There'll be another
opportunity tomorrow and there'll be
another opportunity the day after. And
like every day in the market, as long as
we are leaving liquidity, we have
opportunities.
So, they're starting to hold the dips.
They haven't come and retested these
60s. I'd like to see them test 60s as a
big seller at 90s. if you're adamant of
getting along for the relief.
As soon as I get off stream, I I um
approve your any emails or requests for
courses or rooms. I promise. As soon as
we're done, we've only got 20 minutes
left.
Previous week value area low. I mean,
possible,
possible, but this is a big area, right?
This this remember this is fair value
from last week. This was considered fair
value, right? Could we get over last
week's premium? No. Could we get over
yesterday's premium? No. Could we find a
bid at yesterday's cheapness? No. Where
do we come back? Previous week's fair
value if we lose this. Yes. Here. And
then maybe there. We can look at that
tomorrow. Don't ask for too much today.
I would say might see relief here.
Starting to rebid versus this now. They
haven't come and tested this, but they
might get relief up to here. I'm not
going to take the longs today. Way too
risky. the hardest trade in the book in
my mind.
Do I trade minis and micros? Both.
Depends on the account I'm trading.
Your VP looks different to mine because
you don't have tick data with your
central pan. Maybe. I don't know.
Just explain my last question. My new
profit target is 2,900. Once I hit that,
does that mean I am now 1,400 up on the
account or does it reset back to 25K? I
don't didn't see the other question. I'm
sorry, mate. I don't know what you're
asking.
ETH. Yeah, ETH for volume profile for
me. Uh, unless it's on the weekly,
bro. I'm 3.16% on my account and I've
been wondering how and why, like why
this kind of community
cuz I've never seen such kindness.
Thanks a lot. You're welcome, ma'am.
Here to help. Here to help. What do they
call it? like the the the pass it on to
the next or whatever they call it. Send
it forward. Sending forward
passed a 50k eval ran consistency to the
high on the second eval. So I need 900
more tomorrow. Thanks Alex. You're
welcome Scott. Can you show the volume
profile thing on gold?
Yeah,
lots of you love gold, eh? Lots of you
love gold.
All
right, they're stuck. Buyers are stuck
over here. Simple as that. Buyers are
stuck up here.
Bounce, it's probably a fib fade. Cover
some hold runners on a daily.
Pay it forward. Yeah, there you go. Pay
it forward. Delby man who gets 400
points on the live. I know exactly.
Still learning Ballinger. Is Ballinger
ending on previous week? Let me have a
look for you.
We're right there.
We are pretty much right there. And move
you to a daily. We're very, very close.
Right. We're very, very close. So, think
about what we've done.
All right, mean reversion
fail Ballinger. Right, we don't expect
this is a two standard deviation move.
We don't expect it to move down under
that. If we get black swan events, if
CPI, etc., etc. give us black swan
events, we will do we will expand this
Ballinger band, right? We will we will
do this and we might undercut it first
and then do this in the 5day and 20-day
and we'll support this action down. All
right, when's the last time we saw that?
We can have a look.
Clean this up a second.
Last time we saw a big bare market.
Okay, here. Same kind of thing. I'll
delete that for a second.
Bull trap fade expansion. 5day, 20-day,
50-day, mean reversion, expansion, mean
reversion, expansion, undercut, the end
of it. All right. So, that's what we'll
be looking for. or if we're going to go
into a bearish trend, we want 5day
Ballinger to start supporting that kind
of work here as well. Sometimes you get,
you know, wicks underneath. We don't
expect to trade under it. Sometimes
we'll get black swan. Co would have been
one. If we go back to 20,
was this it? Co. Yeah, that was probably
one. Even then, it held the bowl pretty
well.
All right. Just undercut it. Just
undercut it. All right. So
can happen but uh you'll see the bowls
are very important. We don't like doing
more than two standard deviations. Even
here 2018 even 08 I think we held the
bowls.
Is this the bowls 08? Yeah. Right. Even
08 financial crash we held the bowls.
Right. Look at the bowls and 20 day.
It's always the same guys. It's always
the same. So, if it's always the same,
statistically, you want to be placed the
same way, right? You don't want to be
looking for overexpansion.
But yeah, good eyes. Whoever said that,
I forget who just said it. Good eyes.
Get this back on for me.
Should
we give away some stuff, folks? We
haven't done it yet.
The main thing you've helped me with
today is confidence and being patient.
Nice. Awesome.
Does the 20-day B 20-day bolds holding
work for upside moves too? Yes, it's the
same same thing, right? So, it's always
the same thing. We don't expect markets
to expand outside of daily Ballinger
bands. The mean reversion is the 20-day.
Your trend indicator is the fiveday. If
you just
think about why this is, I teach it in
the course, but I'll tell you now. Five
days, that's your weekly average, right?
We trade five days a week. 20 days,
that's your monthly average, right?
There's five trading days in a week, 20
trading days in a month. Your Ballinger
bands, two standard deviations each side
of that. That's a maximum uh like
expansion under and over each.
Yeah, please stop typing stuff in chat.
Thanks, Adam. Nice one, dude. Um as in
stop spamming. Should I be framing my
eval certificate and and sign it for me?
Sure, I'll sign it for you.
Yeah, Twin Peaks is what I use. I can
post it in chat for you um if you are
interested.
All right. You get 5% discount here. Um
how do you get in Discord? You have to
do the beginner to advance course.
Discord is private. There's no like
weekly or monthly fee. It's just for
people that do the course, right?
Flowzoneer.com beginner to advanced
course. They're going to try and revisit
this. Like we talked about, there are
there is some selling caught, but not a
lot. Right down here, not a lot. There's
a couple guys caught, but like I said,
if they hold 60 to 40s, that might be
your first higher low. So, you can see
sellers piling in at the moment. If they
hold 60 to 40, it might be the first
higher low. And then if they get relief
back inside here, then. So if they hold
this dip reclaim there can be a swipe up
towards these 25,000 what they're trying
to do. It's why we kept saying if they
hold 60s to 40s but again I would not
personally be bidding on this but that
is where they will need to hold if
they're going to do that move. We are
very very heavy and very very bearish on
the tape. For me it's not something I
would bid on but just telling you maybe
it fits your appetite.
How much does the course? Uh $699 for
the beginner to advance 3.99 for the
order flow.
Thanks for the old sold wisdom. Well,
old man wisdom. That's why. Well, I know
lots of you be very upset when I call
myself an old man cuz I'm 40 and some of
you in chat are older than me, but I
still feel old. How do you get the
newsletter? Uh, just click on the tab,
the the thing pinned in chat. Just click
on newsletter. It's completely free. It
doesn't cost you anything.
How much for the combo? Um, let me have
a look.
Don't even know my own prices. Terrible,
isn't it? Uh, so if you get the main one
and the order flow,
if you just want the two courses, comes
to 998 currently. So, if you want the
20-hour beginner to advance and the 6-h
hour orderflow course and with those
you'll get uh Ninja Trader and version
of the Flowzone Momo indicators
998.
Alex, my first week as a paid member and
I'm extremely happy with your
explanations. I'm starting to understand
why it moves certain ways. That's
awesome, Joe. That's all that matters,
right? Honestly, when you start out,
people get so fixed on making money in
P&L, but you don't know the game. You
don't understand the game yet. Um, this
is a giant game. That's all it is. It's
a game of who can be patient and who
can't. Who can be patient, who can we
trap, and who can we use? Who can be
patient? Who can we trap? Maybe. Who can
we use? Big [\h__\h] maybe here. if
they're going to do it because there's
still a chance to do this but we could
do relief and then sell. It's all it is
is a big game. Once you understand the
game, right, how the game works, then
you need to understand the tells. All
right, what are the tells? Tells are
when people get stuck above levels or
below levels. Tells are when people get
stuck above levels. Tells are when
people get stuck above levels, right?
Then we need to understand, okay, well,
they've told us, they've show shown us
that they're in at the wrong place. How
do we exercise their pain for us? We
wait for them to start stopping out and
we use them, right? It's the game.
That's the game. The other part of the
game is when we're building, waiting for
people to tell is having the discipline
to not be involved. the discipline. If
you're playing poker, it's a pass. Pass
pass
like I did this morning. Pass pass. What
have I got here? Jack, Jack.
All right, small blinds.
All right, let's see the flop. Oh, my
jacks suddenly look really [\h__\h] good.
And that guy's just show me that he's
bullshitting. All right, I'm betting a
bit more. Oh, my jack looks even better
now. I'm betting a bit more. I'm betting
a bit more. Okay, thank you. I'm having
all your money. And then we wait again.
Pass. Pass. Pass. Pass. Pass. Pass.
Queen ace. Oh, [\h__\h] I'm licking my
lips. What's that guy got over there?
Oh, he's bluffing like he's got this. He
hasn't got it. Okay. Little bit on. Big
blind. Little bit more of a bet. He's
starting to sweat. All [\h__\h] in. Well,
maybe never all in, but like big
position in. Okay. Money, money, money,
money, money, money, money. Done. Leave
the table. Go have a cocktail. Do
something fun. Right. Make sense.
You want my DJ skills? Well, I don't
have any decks here with me,
unfortunately.
They're all back in London at the
moment.
The Ninja Trader software, guys. I I
just posted it in. And let me see if I
can post it again.
Right, it's right here. The the stuff
that you're looking for in Ninja Trader.
That link there
will give you 5% off. Yeah, I got 1210s
and I've got um 2000 Nexus Moss or
whatever they were and a load of other
stuff from Pioneer, which I should
probably give back to them that they
gifted me.
Yeah, boiler house set. We will do a
boiler house set. I promise you guys,
we'll do a boiler house set. I will I
will do a a border house DJ set. I'll
get some decks soon. Maybe I'm really
considering moving house at the moment.
So maybe after that so I got get some
nice bass
somewhere you can go to hear my my
music. Well, my old music is under tough
love. You can look it up anywhere. And
uh some of my new aliases uh I haven't
really told you guys this. I do have an
alias. It's very small. I do it for my
own pleasure called Adion.
All right,
you guys have smashed the likes. I need
to give back to you guys. Let me set
this up. Please don't do anything yet.
Please, please, please don't do anything
yet. Let me set it up.
Okay, the best code for Apex and all
your prop firms. All right, FCT. Other
than if you're trading with take profit
trader, use code flowzone. Type FCT in
chat once now. Please don't spam it.
Just type it once and uh we will pick a
winner for a free Apex account.
I promise guys, I can see lots of you
emailed. As soon as I get off stream,
I'll get on to all of it. Like my
there's been like 34 of you email me
since been on stream. So just give me a
chance. I promise you I'll get round to
it. Anyone who's like asked for access
into it, I I will sort it all out. I
promise you.
Okay. So, still seeing them try and bid
off these levels. Giving you a chance to
do that. So, we can still see these same
participants where this seller came in.
Remember we said 60s to 40s. Another
seller came in. They're still trying to
absorb 60s to 40s. Right now, buyers
know if they absorb that and they pivot
over 900, they have a squeeze. If they
fail 60s to 40s, there will be a reflush
all the way down here and fill some of
these imbalances. All right. Bids
underneath. I'm going to have a quick
look. There is a bid at 800, a 550 lot,
and there's a 100 lot at 780. I'm
keeping going down. And then there is a
bid at 700. All right. So, there are
bids lower. You might get a breakdown if
they uh can get under these 40s. I would
not be entering short down here, guys.
You've had the 400 point trade. Be
disciplined. Do not chase it.
Alex, the lightning at the bottom of the
screen, uh, it would be news. So, it's
just news. Wall Street on track to open
higher as markets pass econ economy
data. It's just news. Jolts, uh, jobs,
jolts, rare bets. It's just news. It's
Reuters stuff. It's not important. It's
already been and happened. Okay, pulling
the winner here. How many trades do I do
per week? Uh, I cannot answer that my
friend because how many setups are there
per week? Sometimes there are three or
four setups in a day. Sometimes there's
one, sometimes there none. It's whatever
sets up. Okay. Mopar 300s. Are you here?
Mopar 300s.
Mopar 300 here. Nice. Mopar. Okay. All I
would like you to do is email me,
please. info@flowzoneontrader.com.
Right, info@flowzonerader.com.
And send me a screenshot of you logged
into your YouTube so I know it's you.
And if you do that with you logged in, I
will send you a free a Apex account of
any size you want.
Supertoid, any advice how to break out
of patience and watching waiting? I
watch my setups come and go and never
take them and play out perfectly. It's
like I give myself PTSD. Um, so you're
not taking the setups, you're saying.
So you are you waiting or you're not
waiting? So you're watching and waiting.
I watch my setups come and go. So that
means like you're not taking them by the
sounds of it. You need to get you need
to start putting risk on. If you see
your setup Start sim. Prove to yourself
that you understand your setup. Then
start with one micro. All right? And get
used to taking that setup so that you
get you got to build up your tolerance.
You have to build up your tolerance. You
don't want to be putting trades on and
instantly feeling anxious. And when you
start trading, you probably will feel
like that. And if you start trading with
too much size, you will really feel like
that, right? So, you need to get used to
like putting risk on, having your stop
in the right position. Be like, "Okay,
I'm going to risk $100 on this trade.
There's my stop. There's the swing
point. That makes sense. I'm in this. If
I lose that trade, I lose $100. I'm
absolutely fine with that." All right.
What you don't want to do is put risk on
and be like, "Uh, my stop's there. It's
five grand. [\h__\h] I'm anxious. I can't
afford to lose that." Take the trade
off. Right? So, that's why I say size
down. You've got to build up the
tolerance. It's like going to the gym.
You start doing bench press. You don't
go straight up to 300 lb. All right? You
build your weight up to it.
Yeah. Contest over, guys.
Alex, can you do your bookmark analysis
magic on gold? Uh, I don't have Comx, so
I can't. I'm afraid. I don't pay for
Comx data on gold, so I can't actually
look at it, I'm afraid. I only pay for
CME data because I don't trade gold
actively.
Yeah, I'm looking forward to working
with lots of you saying you're going to
do the course. It' be fun. Okay, we're
going to do a G giveaway. It's the
introduction course, right? It's not the
20-hour course, not the other course. It
is just the full introduction. It's two
hours long. It's very good for complete
noviceses and beginners. All right, so
just type course in chat once
and uh we'll do a giveaway for that
person.
Just type course in chat once.
It's what we should we look at for a
possible afternoon long.
Uh it's exactly what I said. Remember
when we said about the longs? What I
would need to see is a lot of liquidity
build out
a swipe with bears entering in and a
recovery of that. So we now know bears
have entered at the lows. We've
recovered volume and we can look up.
That's the only way I would look long.
Personally, I'd want this to swipe
people out. I'd want shorts. who think
about the psychology all the guys who
didn't get short up here with us
and now like right I'm going to short
the lower day right it's them it's them
that we want that's the most ideal at
the moment we are still holding 40s and
60s there is a chance they squeeze this
up at the moment but the problem is
without swiping all of this out this can
be a second leg which is then just sold
back into all right but the most
preference the best trade for me if
you're going to go long will be a swipe
shorts entering big blocks down here
being absorbed absorbed turn around this
and this maybe up to there if you got
very very bloody lucky. But that is the
hard I will tell you now this trade here
is the hardest trade in the book. That
is the hardest trade in the book. The
easiest trade in the book is this trade
here and then ignoring all of this. That
is the hardest trade in the book. It can
pay very well. It is the hardest trade
in the book.
Talk about it all the time. It's not the
protren. The counter trend trade hardest
trade going
I give you guys a couple more seconds to
do this.
I'm going to pull the winner. Five,
four, three, two, and one. FX by Hunter.
Are you here? FX by Hunter.
Still looks like it wants to trade lower
here at the moment. really does.
If they don't absorb 40s and 60s, this
will snap. We still have a bid down at
800. FX Buy Hunter, let me know you're
here, mate. Otherwise, we're going to uh
reroll this.
I'm going to give you another 30 seconds
to tell me you're here in chat. FX Buy
Hunter. Yeah, there we go. All right.
Congratulations, mate. Same thing for
you. Please email me
info@flowzonetrader.com
and I will sort you out with the
complete beginner course, introduction
to trading.
And if you complete that course, I tell
you now, you do get a discount off the
main course. So hopefully if you're
interested, you at least complete it. is
uh good for complete noviceses.
Let's see what you guys are saying and
get out of here soon. We just got into
lunch, folks. Just remember that.
You're watching me and Jaded live from
DJ Mag. Man, that's a long time ago.
[\h__\h] hell.
That is a long time ago in the old DJ
Mag offices.
Is that the old offices or was that
downstairs? I'm going to have to look at
it now.
Uh,
I think we did it twice with them. I s I
a them and signed them. Oh, here we go.
Yes, the old offices, man. And the other
one is get twisted with uh who do we
have? Kadecco and someone else. We done
a few. Done a few.
Does my strategy work as good as gold?
Yes, it it works on It works on
everything. It's not
Trying to think how to explain this.
Here's the lift, guys. They're
protected. They're going to lift up to
here. Now, if they get through this,
there's a swipe. Like potentially over
lunch, they swipe it up a little bit. Be
very careful, though. Um, this is just
how the market works. It's not like this
is how I play it, but this is how all
markets work, right? All markets work
the same way. So, like we always talk
about, it doesn't matter if it's gold,
if it's a physical asset, if it's oil,
if it's anything, right? If we deem this
price is too expensive and too many
buyers, let let's just do the old Rolex
thing, right? Your Rolex Daytona,
right? Let's say this is like COVID
times and up here a Daytona was costing
you 50K.
and news comes out that we're now going
to produce more Daytonas and there's a
new Daytona. Okay, well that 50K is
suddenly worthless. So everyone starts
dumping it. They're getting out. It
comes down here and it's now worth 20K.
All right, that Daytona is now worth
20K,
right? That is now cheap. All right,
that's the same price. I know this is
previous week. Let's just pretend it's
COVID. It's now the same price as it was
in 2016. Oh, that's fair value. We like
that. We'll buy that at 20K and hope
that we get back up somewhere towards 30
or 40 or 50K and then we sell. It is an
auction. We leave one side of the
auction because we're too expensive. We
search for fair value. Fair value is
deemed by price going sideways for a
bit. If we deem this too cheap, we will
leave fair value and look for fair value
somewhere else, which might be here. For
example, it doesn't matter what you're
trading, what you're talking about. It's
the same thing. Think about this. Think
about the very basics of a like a
market. Like for me, I always talk about
Ridley Road market because I used to
live in Dston. But think about your
local market or or fair that you go to,
okay? That selling apples and pears,
right? Just think about this. This might
be stupid, but just hear me out. They're
selling apples and pears, a fruit store,
all right? And it's like up here, maybe
it's five apples
for $10. All right.
Right. But it gets to end of day and
they want to dump their inventory.
They're like, "We don't want to sell
these apples tomorrow. They're not worth
as much." So, at the end of day, it's
five apples for $1. All right? Cuz
they're like, "Let's get let's get rid
of this. We don't want to hold this,
right? And we'll come back tomorrow."
That's that's like a good example of it.
And now everyone bought everyone waits.
They don't want to buy it here because
they know, hey, we know if we wait long
enough, we can get it for $1, for
example. Right? That is how the market
works. That is an auction. Doesn't
matter what you're trading. That's the
auction.
How can you back test order flow or
practice without live markets? I don't
know if you can do it in Trading View. I
don't think you can do it in Trading
View. Um I'm not sure. I'm not sure how
you could necessarily back test it. I
think you dump lower here, folks. I
think you're going to come and take that
out. They're really trying to get under
these 40s.
Is there a method to recognizing a
V-shaped reversal? Vshape need to come
immediately after no drop or the Vshape
will be when there's big excess, right?
It's the same thing. So, if this is
fairly controlled, but if we done like
this down here, big wick and this is all
sellers, heavy sellers, and we turn
around and they're huge size, then they
will cover very quick. Right? This isn't
a Vshape. Now, this is potential if they
hold to do a bit of relief. But again,
you would have to expect respect every
single node in here. So they are
battling right now. They are really
battling. I haven't looked at the order
flow for a minute. Let me just have a
look. This seller is still caught. This
seller here is still caught. 55s. Same
guy. He's still caught right now. He
can't get price under. So if we pivot
now over these buyers at 900, there is
release I would say up to 60. So if they
can get over 900s, there is potentially
again it's counter trend hardest trade
in the book. There's potentially a move
up to 60 where this last block of big
sellers came in. Right? So if they can
get over 900s, if they leave this
seller, we got to move it up for you.
They leave this seller here caught. This
seller here caught. If they hold above
him at 50s and they get above this shelf
at 900s, there's potentially a move back
up to 60s where these last big sellers
came in. But I would not be playing it
personally. It's very, very, very hard
to trade that in a very heavy market.
Right, that is going to be the last
question I take today, folks. Um, thanks
for joining me this morning. Hopefully,
you learned something. Don't forget,
smash that subscribe and like button.
Um, I will be back here tomorrow
morning. We're going to close this week
out strong on a Friday. Those in
Discord, I will be popping in there this
afternoon. Um, the only thing I'm really
looking for at this moment would be a
swipe of low hanging fruit and to see if
we trap players. I don't really want to
look for more downside unless we push
fairly aggressively higher and I don't
really want to look for upside unless we
swipe actually which ES has done and
starting to recover. So, we should watch
that carefully on ES. So, ES by the way
those looking ES has actually done the
move I would be looking for right there
right here. That is the undercut. I
would prefer more excess on this, but
this is the kind of move we want.
Breakout sellers. We'd prefer excess
down into here and then a turnaround and
then relief. All right, trap sellers
under here and then relief. That's the
only thing I'd look for for the rest of
the day. Otherwise, you know, it's going
to keep selling. Um, thanks everyone.
Thanks for all the new members.
Appreciate you all. 257 Joker, thank you
for joining. Thanks everyone. Love
trading with you guys. Be safe. Be
smart. Don't forget, follow me on X and
all the other stuff at Flowzone Trader.
Drop me a tweet or a message or
something. Let me know if you got those
400 points today. And I'll see you
tomorrow morning. Peace and love. Use
hard stops. All that good stuff. Be kind
to each other. Take care.