All
right, morning team. Happy Friday.
Happy Friday. We're back at it. Let's
close out this week strong. It's been a
uh a little bit of a messy week and uh
we're opening up right in the midpoint.
So, let's go over it. We're going to
look at the extremes so far of this
week, which would be Tuesday's high,
okay, and Wednesday's low. And you can
see right now we're opening up well
inside coming into this sort of 61 to
070 kind of fib of the range of the
current week. All right, that's what
we're seeing so far today. Uh we did
have a drive down yesterday. All right,
we uh open up low, drove lower, closed
back inside the range. You can see once
we got to this 50-day,
this red line, we found a bid. This is
also a low volume node. Uh, we can try
and get some VP on here. Why does it
keep forgetting it every time?
See if we can get
maybe
visible range. See if that will go on.
There we go. All right. finding a bid in
this like low volume node on this old
shelf and we're trading back upside now
into like this thickest area that we've
traded in for quite some time since uh
basically October. All right, we keep
getting stuck up towards these 900s. So,
the same thing applies. It's exactly the
same levels as yesterday. We can refine
stuff a little bit this morning. We have
caught a bit on the 20-day. We're
trading back upside. Um chips have had a
little bit more strength this morning of
some news. Um, we can go through all
that shortly. Right. Let's just make
sure you're set up here and can see
everything on the hourly.
[snorts] All right.
So, where are we at? Well, yesterday you
can see we came outside the previous
week point of control. We faded down in
the afternoon session eventually losing
that bid. We talked about in Discord
this fade of the 800s, right? Once they
lost the 800s, it was game over, right?
It meant all the bulls got caught who
were trading inside and we got that
flush down. Uh this same trigger point,
right? This flush down. Same trigger
point as we had here. Flush down. Same
trigger point. So the same levels are
playing out over and over and over again
for this move here. Same as this move
here. All right. This is your trigger
point up into these 800s
overnight. All right. Once we tagged
this previous week point of control, we
reclaimed current week value area low,
this little node, and we started
drifting upside. And now we're getting
stuck at the current week point of
control, right? Current developing
profile point of control and the
previous day point of control.
Everything overheads right now. So we
are stuck in a small rotation. If we
zoom into this, if we think about
yesterday's value area low right here,
we are back inside yesterday's value. So
if we think about this, this was most of
yesterday's. It means we're not finding
acceptance outside of yesterday's value.
We are still inside of this current
week's value. Okay, when we think about
this current week, we are not able to
trade outside for downside pressure,
right? We absorbed the bid there
yesterday. So, we're trading in a
rotation. It is as simple as that.
Mainly in this node here, same as
yesterday. We spent most the time in
this node before we faded away and we're
right back in that. No acceptance below
it. So, really, we're stuck between 800
and 900. All right. This is your kind of
key level. this 800 here. All right,
this low volume node is being protected.
Every time we come down there, we're
finding a bid. So all the time we're
holding 800, it's looking to rotate back
into what? This high volume node. All
right, so we're trading between these
building out liquidities. The same
levels as yesterday. Okay, if we find
acceptance through 900 and certainly
through the edge of this 925, then maybe
there's a drift higher. But just like
yesterday, you got to be very careful of
a failed breakout. If we come under the
800s and we start getting stuck, okay,
then maybe we lose the bid and we trade
back down into the first point would be
this node here, 55, 755s. And if we lose
that previous week point of control,
it's really gets interesting if we lose
previous week point of control. That's
when we then suddenly have room because
we're trading outside of current week's
value and we can look for some of these
nodes, 550s,
uh, 500s, and even lower. So, these are
the edges I want to play for. I don't
really want to participate in here. I'm
going to be honest with you. All right.
Market showing in here. Doesn't really
know what it wants to do. But chips are
a little stronger this morning. So, it
really depends if we're going to find a
sustained bid on those chips. Okay. So,
if we have a look at this 5minute chart,
you can see overnight, right? We closed
down here. We caught this bid, right?
20-day, 5day. Look at that mean
reversion complete. 20-day, 5day.
Remember this low was also uh the uh
50-day down here somewhere. All right.
So, we've caught the bid and we trade
back upside in Asia. Trade back upside
in London. Little dip back down to the
200. Find the bid on a 5m minute back up
to supply up here. Fail supply and
trading between these levels. 100 point
range like I talked about.
All right, let's have a look at some of
the broader markets, some of the mag
name, see what we've got going on.
Oh, did not mean to do that. Sorry,
folks. Right, let's just clean this up a
second.
Move to a five minute.
Okay, so back inside previous day. We're
back inside previous day and we're back
inside
current week and previous week. You need
to be aware of that.
Yes.
Same kind of story,
right? Afternoon flush
came at what, like 1 2:00, 2:00
afternoon flush, but we've instantly bid
that back up into yesterday's supply.
All right, so we're trading between
these two levels. All right, here's
potential demand. Here's potential
supply. All right, so we are just stuck
between these until we find acceptance
one way or the other. You need to be
careful of look aboves and look belows
here if they fail. So, I really don't
really want to participate in here to
start my day off. Let's have a look at
the spiders.
95 is that big level. It's probably been
big level for some time now in terms of
uh gamma exposure.
So, right here you can see stuck there
yesterday. It's the same trigger point
today. In fact, we've put a little alert
there at 95s
and I'd say probably 90 is the downside.
It's got a way to go to get down into
there. So 95s. Why is alert failed?
Okay, we've got some problems, have we?
They added some more bugs in here for
Trading View. Fantastic. Right, so 95s
is the trigger. If we get above that,
let's either look above and fail or look
above and base. So look above and base.
Look above and fail and back inside
range. And I'll watch the 92s to see how
we act somewhere down here. See if we
find a bid down here. That would be
important. Q. Same kind of story. All
right. It's trying to get back above 26s
and 27s really to get going. If we lose
this bid at 20s, then it's night night
probably and we're going to go for full
rotation. Dixie still trying to get back
up to those hundreds. This is
interesting. All right. Now, breakout
trading back down into this support
system. Can it get going here? Big
question mark. Right. We've seen
weakness in Dixie for some time. Can it
get going? VIX. Same kind of story. This
is now flipped.
Trading between these ranges. All right.
You can see between here and here. It
cannot get out of this. It's stuck in
here. If VIX stays stuck in this box, we
will also stay stuck in a box. Right.
Have a look at the mag.
Apple inside of yesterday's range, but
gapping down. So, between PDC and PDL.
So, not very strong there to start the
day on Apple. Amazon has found a bit of
a bid, a bit of a gap up, tagging into
previous days high, pre-market, flushing
back down. So, that's going to be the
trigger there on Amazon. Can it get back
through previous day high and start to
reclaim some of these key levels is
definitely starting to box out here. All
right, but you want to be careful if it
does a failed look. But if it can
sustain, then great. Many of these, I
would imagine, might uh be waiting for
earnings over the next week or two.
Remember, earnings have already started.
We've started to see some of the uh
financial sector names which haven't
been too good to be honest but uh uh
Taiwan Semiconductors was decent
yesterday. All right, Google gap up
previous day low left there. We did not
sweep. So, it's protected this low at
31. You want to be careful if that 31
breaks now because you got lots of buyer
stops there and kind of boxed in as
well. But we are gapping up, right? As
long as it holds a bid over 34, it's
going to try and get back up to those
highs of yesterday of 39. So watching
Google to hold a bid of 34 if it fails
that it's a leave alone buy side. Meta
that's not pretty. It needs to hold a
bid over 19s to get going. Failing of
that bid will be mean that this is like
a two-leg building out liquidity versus
this and failure. So it's got to hold
19s and reclaim 26s really to get going.
If it fails 26 is on a push and then
loses 19s then we're going to make new
lows. So all to play for coming into
earnings. Microsoft that is terrible.
Push yesterday's failed. Rep failed and
can't reclaim. So far not looking so
good. Nvidia, this is where it starts to
get interesting. All right, look at this
move yesterday. Right, this is all off
earnings. Nvidia starting to get going.
Chip starting to look like they're maybe
stronger than imagined. Um, I think we
had some memory names this morning which
also looked pretty good. So, it probably
caught a bit of a bid off there. You're
looking for that 190 break on Nvidia.
190 break and then you'll be targeting
targeting 193s.
Just zoom this out a second.
Yeah, 190 break to get to 193 194 and
then that 196 big big pivot. You can see
this day here 20th of November. Huge
pivot there. We're still boxed in in
Nvidia just like the rest of the market,
but it's uh stronger than the rest of
the mag or at least has been stronger
yesterday than the rest of the mag.
Tesla uh I think they it was a delay on
was it in Germany or some of the
European um lookins to some of their
automatic cars. So
I can't imagine that's necessarily
positive. Maybe just more sideways
action here while it makes its mind up.
And clearly one 440 big level and then
35s. All right, 40 and 35s. Do they hold
bids there? Can they get back above 50s
is going to be really really the level.
45s and 50s. Uh let's have a look at
some of the other chips. Oracle that
does not look good. So it's not catching
a bit. AMD should be okay. Yeah, AMD
looks good. That's a great start to the
day on AMD. So really question, can it
break above the 38s and get going on
AMD? Big question mark, but that's what
they'd be looking to do on an extension.
And let's have just a quick look at some
of these names down here. How long we
got? We've got time right boxed in
NQ
boxed in. That looks a little bit weak
there to be honest. NVTS,
same story. We're just not going
anywhere. RGTI, same story. These are
just messy charts. We're going to have
to wait for hopefully earnings get us
out of some of this.
Yeah.
Okay. So, yeah. No, I would say coming
into the session, there's no uh setup
here, which I'm extremely excited about.
It looks a bit messy.
Not even a bit messy, it looks very
messy, but uh we can watch to see if
we're able to get over the 900s or if
they fade those again. And we can watch
these 800s and 750s to see if they grab
bids or if they fade those again. So
800s and 750s and 900s, 925, 950. Those
are the level.
What data feed do I use for bookmap? Um,
I buy the CM say CME feed.
You don't have to do that. You can try
and use some of the prop feeds, but I
just buy it for the sake of knowing that
it works properly. I'd rather just buy
it.
All right, folks. Make sure you've gone
through your morning routine.
Have you got your levels marked out? Are
you fit, physically, and mentally able
to trade today? If the answer is no, you
got to ask yourself what you're doing
here right now because it's a Friday and
uh you don't want to be giving back all
your earnings from the week.
Market finding a bid here
[clears throat]
just before the open and it's trying to
get up to those 900s we've talked about
many many times
900s 925s they have remained big levels
and that is where it's trying to go.
Just over a minute left.
Can I get the link for the data feed on
Bookmap? Um, it's on their website,
guys. I'm not going to not going to do
that for you. Just go on the website and
buy the CME data package. It's on the
website.
That's all you have to do. Do you
recommend a MacBook for trading?
Absolutely not. Worst thing you can do.
You need a PC for trading.
I know I love MacBooks, but it's you'd
be much better off building a like a uh
decent spec PC and using it for trading.
Most um packages will not work with Mac.
Yeah, we've got uh we do have some news
today. You're right.
Um, we should have gone over that.
That's my bad. Uh,
home builder confidence as well as the
as the orange man as you call him
speaking at 10. So, yeah. And then we've
got Fed Talk 10:50, 11:00, and 3:30. All
right. So, be aware of that.
[snorts] Right. 10 seconds left here,
folks.
Let's see.
Most of the mag starting off green.
Let's see if dips hold here this
morning. Are they interested in holding
dips to get up to the 900s? Are they
going to hold the 800s or uh what are
they looking to do? We're going to find
out shortly.
So far that previous week value area
high and previous day value area low
being held and they're trying to rotate
into these 900s if they can. 5day
holding on the uh ES as well.
900's where it's looking to go if they
can get going.
You can see this gray box. This thick
box is where we have supply all the way
up to sort of 9007s 925s.
So, here it goes. See if they can extend
this through now. There we go. Nice.
We have a little imbalance here into
87s. There's your imbalance. See if they
squeeze through this to previous day
point of control. So, they're trying to
get to the 900s like we talked about.
Watch this New York open. Now, if they
hold a dip into New York open
or that extension into the 900s, they
lose New York open, you'll probably get
a rotation back down to 800 again. So,
here's the New York Open.
They're trying to dip the New York Open.
They're trying to get up to the 900s.
There's a big big seller up there at 84.
If we go through him, we should run him.
Here we go. So, he reloaded there again.
900 almost got tagged. Not too far away.
[snorts] That's where they're trying to
get. That is for sure where they're
trying to get.
Point of control on the day up at 8.85
because there was a massive seller up
there.
So, back to this New York open again.
>> [snorts]
>> So the 800 to 900 rotation like we
talked about pre-market is what we've
seen already off pretty much off the
open
[snorts] just coming shy of it.
Mag all green other than goog by the way
the mag all green other than goog
we're right on that New York open right
now. So this gray box is your supply.
You just came into this previous day
point of control and current week point
of control. And until we get a bid over
that, they're going to keep getting
stuck. If they get a bid over that,
there is potential squeeze potential up
into this not next block. So, we'd be
watching 25s and 50s if they get over
it, which they can't do at the moment.
[snorts]
All right, I'll check the emails after,
guys. It's it's the open. I will check
after. I can't do everything at once. I
have to also be able to trade, folks.
[snorts]
Right, back down to test this previous
day value area low, previous week value
area high. Let's see if they back test
New York and if they stay heavy and try
and look that flush or if they're just
going to resqueeze it over that New York
open.
It's very messy.
Back down to value again. So the 800 the
900 to 800 rotation
and holding value area low from
yesterday. ES is just not moving at all
right now.
Google trying to find a bid here
interestingly. What's Nvidia doing at
the 89s? The 90 break is the big level.
So they're trying to redip in the
previous day value area low. That New
York open still not being able to close
through yet. Here's the push back
towards the New York Open. Like we said,
they need to get through here if they're
going to force the squeeze. They cannot
just come up to here and do nothing.
Big big level here. This New York open.
They get through here, there's a chance
for a squeeze back up to the highs. The
sellers came in very very aggressively
at 85. So
right here, there were some big market
sellers into this 80 to 85. Big big big
players through there. We can probably
get going. Here we go.
Okay, let's see if we can get a push
here. Be careful we in case they reload
these 80s again.
Watching the 900s. Can we get up into
900s? Very very small size long here off
value area low. In fact, I'm going to
move my stop into 50 just to protect
myself in case they do a nasty flush.
[snorts] Let's see. Give it a chance.
This is not very pretty. You going to
take me out 50 here? In the money. That
would be five point in the money. They
rebid again there. Seller got trapped at
the low again there. We just wanted a
close over New York open and then to
push through the 80s. That's where all
the sellers got stuck. Well, they will
get stuck if we get through 80s.
Probably going to get taken out here
because they're bidding under 50 now.
So, I bought 45 stops in at 50. Trying
to see if we can move higher.
Going to attack me. Very close.
Very close.
Save me by a tick or two there.
And very close.
Did I just got filled out there and you
didn't actually hit me? Oh, you did hit
me. Yeah, I'm done. [snorts]
Okay, wait for a reload here if it
offers it.
It literally did me to the tick there.
Cannot believe that. You horrible
bugger.
You horrible, horrible, horrible bugger.
to the tick.
Okay,
I'm not in this now unfortunately.
Probably going to go now. So 80s 80s are
the level where the sellers came in this
morning on that 932 candle. All right,
80s
big player. 250 lot came in at 82. All
right, at 82
and one tick tickle cannot believe it.
They knocked me out by a tick there. It
hit 40. It literally hit me to the tick.
I didn't think it traded through me.
Literally hit me to the tick. Oh, it's
going to go. You
You know what? [snorts]
You You know what?
All right. If you're in this long, okay,
you're looking for a base over this New
York open this blue line and hopefully
you get a drive into the 900s and 925s.
You want to be trimming on the drive up,
right? Cuz this is supply up here. They
might well fade it.
No, I would ne like Why would anyone
ever advise that, Matthew?
Why would anyone ever advise that? What
if a black swan piece of news came out
and you were the wrong side of it?
>> [snorts]
>> You'd lose everything.
Morning. Morning. Fall forward.
Okay. ES is so far holding VW up in New
York open. ENQ is not. Mag starting to
rotate though. Apple, Amazon, and Google
all just closed their gap and gone red
now.
Again, we have strength in the cues
versus the rest of the market. RTY.22%
down. YM 0.02% down. ES 0.21% up. NQ
0.61% up. Chips have been a bit stronger
today.
But Google and Amazon just gone red. We
are just stuck. It might be that we have
to wait for earnings here. I don't know.
Rick, I trade based on what's in front
of me. If there's a trade out the gate
and I can see participants stuck in a
clear level to trade to, I will trade
it. If not, I don't. There's I It's not
for me. It's not a hard rule of like I
have to wait 15 minutes or I have to
wait 30 minutes. Back in the day I used
to have a rule like that. But I don't
need that rule now. I will trade the
liquidity in front of me. If there's a
clear clear sentiment move and I know
one side stuck, I'll trade it. If not,
like today I didn't trade it. So today I
waited for a dip down here looking for
that push and got stopped out.
Right? You're coming back into where
these uh sellers got came in earlier
into 82 and above. All right? So, you
need to clear them and they will start
to stop out. Then, if they stop out,
they become market buyers and you've got
the chance to move higher. So, anyone
who's still holding this dip and 34s,
right? You're trying to get through
these 82s. 82s is a big level. If you
can get through 82s, you can get up
here, right? That's where you're trying
to get.
We keep getting stuck in this node. This
is a big level from yesterday. It's the
big level from the week. You can see it
on this chart here to make it make sense
for you. Right? We keep getting stuck
here and here. Right? So, we're trying
to trade from here to here. The question
is, can we find acceptance over that? If
we keep getting stuck from here to here,
eventually it's possible that they come
for this rotation.
Not a very pretty market this morning.
We have moved uh 56 points so far in the
opening 10 minutes. [snorts]
Nvidia's doing the work. It's through
the 190s, but the rest of the market not
really willing to join in.
No bid on Apple, Amazon, and Google,
but maybe back down to these value area
lows again. If they can't do this move
here and they keep getting stuck,
they'll come for the rotation again. If
we lose this, we've got targets down
below that they might want to wash to.
They come back down to value again.
Let's see if they hold this or if we're
going to wash this out. Come and attack.
8750.
Very possible they lose it.
into the 25s on the cues.
I've seen a lot of people either
skipping this and yesterday's PR getting
chopped up. Would you say it's advisable
to sit to sit this sort of range out to
leave the range alone? I mean, if you
don't like trading range, yes. Um, but
there were opportunities yesterday. We
had three green trades on on stream and
uh those in Discord if they took the
fade. I don't know if they did for the
800 that I called out. There was a nice
move there yesterday as well. It's about
patience and knowing what your trading
style is, right? If you're a range
trader, this should be your bread and
butter. [snorts] If you're not a range
trader, then maybe it's more of a leave
alone. Like, I'm very fussy with stuff
like this, as you well know. [snorts]
Yeah, I can see that on CVD.
You know, we're not breaking lower. So,
sometimes see that as the opposite way.
It means someone's trying to absorb. The
question is, are they able to keep
bidding and bidding and bidding and
bidding endlessly or not? Because if
not, they're going to get broken. But
I'm just not seeing much on the tape
here. Like, we're very, very, very slow
here this morning. Very slow.
We've moved 50 points, right? Back into
24-hour VW up. Back into previous week
low. Back into previous day value low.
We're very slow.
Let's get some volume on here now that
we've been here a minute.
>> [sighs]
>> VIX finding a bit of a bid here on
previous days low. That's not good for
the market.
We're [snorts] at that 24-hour VW up in
those value area lows. question is, do
they rebid this again or are they going
to flush lower? I genuinely don't know
here, folks, because it's so slow. All I
know is there's a shelf here at 46 and
uh we're not able to get above. So,
through 50, maybe they squeeze back up
to 60s, but I mean, you're talking about
10 points. It's pointless, pointless.
All the time they keep rejecting 50s,
maybe there's a flush lower like they're
trying now.
And they've got bids down to 800 here
like we talked about. So, the 900 to 800
rotation. They didn't quite get to 900.
They're 10 points short, and they're
going to try and get down to the 800s
now. It's the same stuff we talked about
pre-market. It's the same levels.
Nothing's changed. Very boring. [snorts]
Maybe there's nothing to be be done here
today. I don't know.
If we do this all day, I certainly won't
be trading it.
Is trading my only source of income?
Well, I mean, no. I'm a landlord
and I still make royalties off my music,
but it is my main source of income, I
would say, but not my only source.
Okay, down to the 800s.
Uh, I really like affordable indicators.
Never had a disconnection issue. I don't
use anything web- based for that reason.
I've always always stated that [snorts]
too risky.
I made music. Yes, I still make music
for people every now and again.
Okay. Yes. Trying to find a bid. Q is a
bit weaker here as we come down into the
800s. Look at this. Tap back in towards
the 8 845 850 we just talked about. This
thing does not know what it wants to do.
It really does not know what it wants to
do. So, 10 points short of the 800
rotation back into this shelf at 850.
Are they going to try and find a squeeze
through this or are they going to reject
it? I have no idea, folks, because the
book is really not moving.
ES back to its New York open and VWAP
already. Are the Q's going to find a bid
here? Here's value area low on the day
that it's trying to drive back through
now. Do they reject this for a drive
lower or not is the big question at this
point.
No. Okay. Jake. Jake, my friend, I
cannot explain how much I've got on my
plate right now. I will listen to the
music when I'm ready to listen to the
music. I have no bandwidth for anything.
I'm really sorry. I appreciate that
you've made some probably some amazing
tunes there, but at the moment, I just
don't have the bandwidth for it. I'm
really sorry, buddy. Give me a week or
two. Yeah, this is my f what? Third day
back trading.
I promise I will listen to it all. Same
with the the stuff that's posted in
Discord. I promise. I promise. I
promise. I just need a bit of time.
[snorts]
ES really pushing now through the New
York open trying to reclaim it to be up.
You'll be watching that 7,000 level on
ES.
You [snorts] think I'll get a laugh?
Okay. Well, I'll make sure I try and
make the effort to get it.
Yes. Cannot get through. It's trying.
Market feels like it's asleep right now.
Apple now quarter% down. Amazon 0.29%
down. Google 0.15% down. Meta 1% up.
Microsoft 0.65% up. Nvidia 1%
up. Back under that 190 though. Tesla
1.6. 61% up.
It's just not moving, folks.
They don't know what they want to do. It
funny. I never knew who you were and so
happened to see your first day back this
week. What do you mean you didn't know
who I was?
Still no movement here.
[snorts]
Are they going to stay heavy versus
this? I just don't want to preempt a
short. But maybe if we do this, there's
this. But I'm also very aware that we
can do this and resqueeze.
[snorts]
It's just feels very iffy. They're still
holding value right now.
Just gross.
Just gross. Previous days point of
control. Previous day value low. If we
let go of this, maybe there's a move
down, but I do not want to preempt it.
Starting to see some heaviness come in
the tape here. Can they rotate this
force break? Maybe
bid at 800. Let's have a look below.
There's not much below right now.
Very strong selling here getting
absorbed.
Look at all this all being absorbed down
here under 820.
They reclaim they will squeeze, but
they're going to have to get through the
50s. So, waiting to see if they want to
do that or not.
Still a buyer at 800. Not been filled
though.
So ugly, man. Barely moving.
Yeah, probably waiting for 10. You've
also got news, not just Trump. You got a
news piece dropping. Still rejecting
previous week value high, previous day
value low. So if they want to trade
outside of it, they want to do it now.
And they got to start getting below
these 20s though. It's all sellside from
20s down to the current New York low of
day. There is a bid at 800.
Still just waiting. I don't feel
confident for a continuation short here
just because it's how it's moving. It's
a good chance they probably do it and
just slam it. I'm okay missing that. I
don't like how we're moving right now.
Yeah, it means momentum is downside
right now, but I'm waiting to have
confirmation of location.
We're trying to move outside of value.
There is a chance that we move down
here,
but what I'm seeing within this at the
moment is not making me full of
confidence that we're going to snap
lower. Every move under 820 is being
absorbed, right? So, everything under
here is being absorbed. So, I'm just
aware of that. Maybe too aware of it,
but it's a Friday. I don't want to go
give him back my week.
If we lose this though, we can really
trade those 750s quickly.
Doesn't look good. Looks like we might
go 750s. Here's the 800 test again.
[snorts]
So 900 to 800 rotation complete
pretty much there [snorts] or
thereabouts. Um 750s is next level below
if they lose this just based on where
nodes are. You see this box down here?
It's basically the next level.
Here's 800.
Someone keeps buying
and they're adding 87 uh 775 now.
That 20 is a big level.
Everything below sellside.
It's starting to really look like it
wants to get going here.
Big seller coming there at 800.
Maybe that was a rotation. I missed it.
I don't know.
I just don't like how we're moving. We
are literally dripping down.
[snorts]
Yes, looking like coming in at a break
now. So 50s are on deck here. If you if
you did take this short versus this, the
next level is down here into this blue
box. It's very possible.
Kind of kicking myself for not taking
this little move here. Might be an error
on my behalf. [snorts]
back to the 800s.
20s is the level that bulls will need to
reclaim. Everything below that is sell
side. Until they reclaim that, there's
absolutely no long. This is just
dripping down lower at the moment.
And we could contemplate a gap fill, I
guess. rule it out
700 if they lose 750. ES is almost at
gap already. It only needs another what
six points or something.
Here comes the drive towards the 50s
that we just talked about. this blue
box.
[snorts]
It is very slow on the tape honestly.
There it comes. So your first TP just
tagged here. This first blue box. So if
you did take the short from here to here
to here and down here next if you get
there. Remember, we haven't had a bid
back up to resell. This is why I'm like
skeptical because this is like literally
being dripped down.
But it doesn't mean they can't keep
doing it. They absolutely can. [snorts]
[cough]
Sellers in control from 80s now. They've
built up like a nice little shelf there
at 80. So all the time they're under
80s, sellers are in control here
into this first box.
Let's see if we can get to the second
one for you guys.
So you can watch this shelf here on the
current week's value. It's uh it really
thickens out into 50s which is why we
have that marked. And then under that
you've got a little bit room into sort
of 720s and then previous week PC 65 uh
7 675 sorry. [snorts]
What a nice trade man. Just didn't see
what I wanted to see there. But there we
go. It is what it is.
It is what it is.
VIX starting to get going. It's about to
close its gap here on the VIX. ES trying
to do the same. It's going for gap fill
here.
[sighs] That is probably trade of the
day. It's going to be 100 point by the
time it gets down there.
Never mind.
Apple, the heavy one, approaching half a
percent down. That thing cannot catch a
bid recently.
So many red days, it's insane.
More heaviness here.
No bid back up yet. They're bidding 25s
at the moment.
Yes, almost gap filled. So probably you
want to watch that gap fill on ES.
Gap on ES will be what? 81
82 8175 82. It's almost there.
Cash gap.
It's about to be tagged by the looks of
it. It's trying. There's a bit of front
running in front of it. Pretty much
there.
missed it by tick fix closes gap es very
very close spy very very close Q's are
what the way to go all the way down into
here into the 700s so you're losing
these 50s now if you lose 50s you're
going to come 20s and 700s
if you reclaim 50s I'd say over 55
you've built some shelf here over 55
they might rel give you some relief to
sort of 80.
I don't think this is finished yet.
Do not think this is finished yet. This
has just been dripped down. Look at this
from here. Just straight drip down. Drip
drip drip [laughter] drip drip drip drip
drip. Not aggressive. Just controlled
selling down so far. It will get
aggressive when they start to pop all
the stops. [snorts]
This is the push to 50 like we just
talked about. This is where sellers will
want to protect around here. So 55 and
resell it if they can. Yes. Now close
the gap. SP now closed the gap. Q's have
not closed the gap. Yellow line is your
gap fill. That's your next target if you
can get down into it.
Here they go. And Apple and Google
selling pulling this market down.
Yep. News in one minute.
actually about 20 20 seconds from now.
Almost at PDC. Make sure you're covering
some into this in front of the news in
case they do something horrible. This is
being dripped down. You just don't know
if they're going to do something
absolutely disgusting with it. And just
[snorts]
push it straight back up to resell it.
So, just make sure you're paying
yourself some money into these
positions. These are the boxes that we
had interest in. Get rid of this now.
[snorts]
Yeah, this is your weekly current week
value area low right here. You're
correct. This blue line and then PDC
underneath and previous week point
control underneath. So, these are some
cover points for you down here.
Oh my gosh, [sighs]
that is a miss and a half there from me.
It's too concerned about them doing
something nasty. And that is just a
straight drip lower.
So Vick's approaching the 16s now. What
was the break? It needs to do 1625 is
where it will get nasty for this market
if the VIX starts breaking through that.
Can't catch them all. Yeah. Onto the
next trade. It's It's okay. It is what
it is. It is what it is.
So, your next TP is down into here,
these blocks here. And then under there,
you've got quite a way to go. Let me
just check.
There's a little shelf at 6. Let's just
call it 650. But you you've got room. If
it starts really letting go here, but
you go into panic mode, you do have
room.
Gap now pretty much filled. Not quite
filled, but pretty much filled.
Google just getting hammered here.
Hardest thing is there's no pop to sell
either. It's just been straight down.
No relief bounce. Not even a bounce back
up to 50 is where we have a little bit
of a shelf up here. Nothing there.
[snorts] Selling everything right now.
And it's pretty controlled.
>> [snorts]
>> Okay, it's the edge of 30s. They're
still selling 30s. If we get relief
through 30s, we probably go 50s.
Let's see how we once we get up there.
Still not quite filled that gap. Very,
very close.
They're still selling 30s. So, we can't
get relief through 30s to 50s. There's
no way I'm selling 30s just to try and
get down to 05s. No chance. [snorts]
Okay, here's 30s again. Can they get
relief through 30s to 50s?
Can they lift up to 50s? Here we go. I
want to see how we act when we get up
into here.
A little bit higher would be nice.
And let's just see now. Want to see if
anyone gets caught up here or if they're
going to go full relief and go all the
way back up because we've been straight
down. The problem is so they need to
defend this now or around here. So I'm
waiting to see if buyers get caught
here. If not, then they'll probably get
a squeeze relief all the way up. So you
can see this 30s lift straight into 50s
like I just talked about. We have
[snorts] to see what happens now.
There's the 50s sell.
So your rotation now is 50s to 30s while
they make up their mind. All right.
So sellers just defended this selling
here back down to here. Want to see if
we cover some here. And if not, we can
get continuation underneath. And if we
get relief, we can go all the way back
up here because this is one straight
move that lacks any structure. All
right. So, you have to be careful if
you're going to sell this. Now, it's not
an ideal position, but it is a location
to sell. Here we go. Nice. Trim some
here. And let's see if we can get down
to PDC.
I got a little piece. Tiny little piece.
If they reclaim 50s, certainly if they
uh reclaim 54s, then a squeeze back up
is going to happen. So, I'm not going to
hold above that. They do a look look
above and fell. I'll cut it. Re-enter on
the way back down. [snorts]
I do want do not want to see this back
above uh sort of 55. We go above 55s,
you're probably going to see squeeze
relief all the way up to the 800s again.
[snorts]
Nice Josh. Great work. Yeah, it was a
big miss on my behalf there. [snorts]
Getting ready to cut the runner here.
So, covered some into the 30s like we
talked about for the rotation. If it
gets squeeze relief, this thing can go.
So, I'm not going to hold on to it
because we're very thin and if it wants
to pump straight up to 800 or 820, it
will.
Yes, reclaiming PDC.
Google catching a little bit of a bid.
No matter what, I'm going to be in the
money here. Doesn't matter what happens
to be in the money. I'm happy to flip
long. If we break above 50s in base, I
would even consider it. I would consider
it. My favorite trade, but I would
consider it.
[snorts] So far, the short still holding
up.
node
824.
Yeah, I just don't want to get caught in
a 70 point squeeze out here.
Cutting here. Always read. Cut the
runner there. Could always read
[sighs] in case they want to come all
the way up.
And we got imbalances all the way up to
97.
This is a question. If this is a look
above and fail, do they rebid this here
at 50s? If they rebid it, then I think
we squeeze. If they don't rebid it, then
that was just a little look above and
fail. Run the stops and then come back
down.
We haven't closed the gap yet.
already failing.
Nice. Okay, let's see. If they don't
hold this little shelf, we're going to
trade the next shelf below. Otherwise,
there's a two leg possible here for
relief up into these 800s.
>> [snorts]
>> Okay, come on market. Make your mind up,
please. These like stops are so
ridiculous how much you slow down.
Pablo, I genuinely don't think I could
explain it anymore if I tried.
I think I've explained everything
about is
as straight up as I could be. [snorts]
If they hold 50s, there's a squeeze up
to here. If they don't hold 50s, then
this is a look above and a fail to close
the gap. All right? If they hold 50s,
then this. And if people say you're
giving us both directions, that's
because the market has the opportunity
to trade both directions at the moment.
What I do know is this is one straight
move down. And if they want to be nasty
and do this above here, they can. So,
I'm going to be very cautious on the
short here. I'd much rather we finish
the short and close the gap. But I also
know ES has already closed it.
We were trading back inside current
day's value now or attempting to.
We're building out volume.
PC shifted down here now and into 50s.
So bulls will want to defend this area.
If they defend this, they know they have
the potential to have a squeeze up. If
they lose this area, we have unfinished
business below for the closing of the
gap and previous week PC.
Yeah, I'm trying to be like make it as
clear as possible before even from here.
I told you 30 to 50 will be the relief.
I'll try and resell that and I'll scalp
some. Scalp some stop me out. Not
holding on to runner in case we go back
upside. If we start losing it again,
I'll re-enter short again and start
trying to get the close.
[snorts]
Probably need to build out a little bit
more liquidity here.
They are adding bids at 700. So maybe we
can come and clean those up if we get
very very lucky here. But just don't
want to front run this because they're
still absorbing these just under 50s
keeps being absorbed. 50 is PC right
now. It's fair value on the session.
Sellers came in hard under 30. So I want
to respect that because we are over
that. So sellers under 30 are trapped.
If we keep holding 50, there is relief
up to 800.
VIX failed that pivot at 16 that we
talked about. Such clear fail.
[snorts]
Definite buyer here. Keep trying to
absorb.
He's trying his best. Like to see him
just piss off so we can get a rotation
lower now.
Still there. He's holding the imbalance
here. Come on. We want to come lower at
this point. There we go. Start digging
in, please.
We can see if we can rotate back down
here. Just want to be careful with this
buyer who keeps coming in here at 40 and
at 25s. Come on. I want to be very, very
careful as we trade into 30s because we
know sellers got stuck. If we can get
back under there, we have more downside.
Here we go. Beautiful. So, it was a
little look above and fail. Just want to
make sure we trade under 28. Really,
that's where the sellers really got
stuck. 28 and under. So, don't want this
dip here to hold. I want to trade under
this. Now, if this dip holds and want to
be very, very careful. Make sure to take
some profit again just like last time.
Here's the 30s test. Really good. Now,
can we make a new low of day? Can we get
under these sellers who were trapped
here from the move down at 10:00 a.m.?
Can we get a new low of day here? Making
sure I'm paying myself in case they want
to hold this level. But holding runners
or the break lower.
[snorts] So 28's got traded there to the
tick. We just talked about the 28s. So
paying myself into 28s. We want 20 uh
40s to stay heavy. Otherwise, I will cut
as this can be a higher low. So I want
to be careful here. Looking for this to
stay heavy and trade under here. Now I
need it under here now. Right. Anything
that does this, I'm out of the short.
Make that very very clear for you guys.
[snorts]
You want to be careful if ES holds its
PDC as well.
Just stuck between these two nodes. 30
to 50.
Market is bearish overall
in this session.
Just can we get outside of this weekly
value area low? Can we expand weekly
value area low here? Can we get a new
low of day? Can we close this gap? Here
we go. Come on, runner. Let's go, baby.
Let's go for gap fill and below. It' be
really nice. Should get a new low of day
here now, guys. This is what we're
looking for. So trading into low of day.
We want to see a snap of low of day. We
want to trade under 705s if possible.
And then we can look for 685.
Let's go.
Let's go. Come on.
Got some limits out here at PDC. If you
protect PDC, I'm going to be very upset
with you.
>> [snorts]
>> Looking for 705s and then looking for
685 here folks. Looking for 705s and
685s. Yellow line and then previous week
point of control. Want to be very
careful. Already trimmed some into here.
We want this to now reject. We don't
want to reclaim with this. All right. If
this comes up here, we want a roll over.
All right. TP TP. If we get really
lucky, we'll come down here. That would
be very lucky.
We do not want a reclaim of 40s now or
37s.
Want this to stay heavy. I'm going to
get a refill. Let me just move my stop
in the money. Make sure these limits are
out. There we go. All right. Be right
back.
Looks good. Buyers just came in there
and got trapped. Looks good. We're going
to get it. We should get it here. We
should get it here.
Come on. We should get it here. They
should flush this now. Take out all this
liquidity all the way down to 90. Come
on, stop faffing.
ES loses PDC and it will really help us.
Very, very close to TP. I can't believe
it's teased so much. Come on. Woo. Thank
you.
All right, let's see if we can get a
runner to really start going here now.
Nice work.
Nice [snorts] work. So TP hit there. And
we'll see if we can get down into this
next box. So gap now filled. This yellow
line. You can see why I had my limit
there. Gap now filled. Cash gap for
those wondering. Cash gap. And then
we're looking for previous week point of
control. And if we get really lucky down
here. So I missed this whole move and I
had two I had to have two attempts at
that attempt one right took some out
here stopped out here just in case we
got relief but once we came back
downside in again TP1 TP2 I did cover a
little bit into 30 again in case and
then we'll see now we will just see can
we get going
be nice if we Good.
Took shorts on the pullback. Yeah,
exactly. That's exactly what to do. Just
hit your TP. Why was stop at 37? Was my
stop at 37?
Uh, I don't know if it was at 37.
I think it was at it was above it was
above 33. Maybe it was at 37. I can't
remember. But it's just this shelf here.
I wanted this shelf being protected once
I left the desk. Right. This shelf here.
This volume [snorts]
25620 should be last resort and defend
zone today. 25620.
Um
640 to
570 is a level.
640 to 570 is a level. Here we go,
folks. All right, next TP now hit.
Lovely. All right. And now it's just a
question. Can we get all the way down
into here? Which would be amazing if we
did. And if we did a measured move, it
would probably work out perfectly with
this leg. If we went leg to leg. There
you go. So, if we're going to get this
same leg again, we might well get this,
which would be really good, which would
be a great day considering I missed all
the top side move down. So, here we go.
Just managing the positions now.
[snorts]
Banks trade got a runner. Good call. I
was uneasy about that small pullback. I
entered small and scaled in it. That's
the way to do it, man. enter small and
scale scale in. I didn't know if we do
it first time or we did exactly what I
talked about. Maybe we do a little look
above and fail. All right, but I have to
be cautious on here because this is such
a big move. [cough] We enter short here.
There's no guarantee that they don't do
that at that point because there's a
lack of structure in here. But once we
rolled over again, right, we got short
again. So, it took two attempts, right?
It took two attempts, but that's
trading. We're not going to get it
perfect every time. We all we can do is
position for the move.
So, it's just a question if can we get
down into here? Now, we know this is a
massive level here.
I'd say shorts want to control 700 now.
They [snorts] want to control 700. This
level here, 713. So, we can make this as
like
let's do it as gray. So, I don't want to
give you guys too much uh sentiment
here, but we can move definitely 700 is
a little spike sort of here really is
more, but I'd be watching 700 whole
level for this here. And then if they
base if if you get a push and they do
this, I'd be very cautious about this
move to fill in this this low volume
node. All right. So shorts will want to
defend this or defend this if they want
continuation early. If you get a base
over this, you want to be careful.
Obviously squeeze back out. [snorts]
[clears throat]
It's a shame. Let's just move that.
So testing towards this 700. 700 is
where a big seller came in. It's more
likely where a buyer just stopped out at
700 on that flush down at 1019. So,
we're coming to test that delta there.
I can show you right here. This right
here, right? We're coming to test this
guy. Hopefully, you guys can see that to
zoom out. Right here, we're coming to
test this guy here and it's imbalance.
And if we squeeze through this, we're
going to come and test this level here
where the buyers came in.
[snorts]
So that refresh seller at 700 still
present. [snorts]
Where do you have your runner stops? Uh
I've just left the the uh up here in
here where it was before. Just at here.
So, I've only got a little micro on now.
So, we either get down here or we don't.
And that's okay. [snorts]
I'm all out. I would have have to wait
for another popup. Yeah. And just
remember, we've hit a lot of low hanging
fruits. Look, we've closed the gap.
We've hit previous week point of
control. There's no reason to be long in
this. We are in trend down. I was
worried that here, right? I'll be This
is the reason I didn't enter this is in
here. I didn't see enough in the tape to
make me think we were going to flush.
And then we kept absorbing uh the 820s
over and over and over again. Everything
under under 820 kept getting absorbed. I
was like, I want to be careful for this
move here. But they just dripped it.
It's not like we snapped. They literally
dripped it down.
So that's why I didn't get short. I just
didn't see. It's actually a really good
setup, but I didn't see
inside the tape what I'd want to see
there. I didn't see it unfortunately
otherwise I would have got short there.
So I had to wait right so I missed all
of this and then we have to wait for
this
and if they start reclaiming here then
we have to consider whether this market
wants to move back for relief over 55s
and 60s. All right so big bounce here
like we talked about through the 700s we
come back into this node. This is value
area low on the day. These are these
sort of 37s, same level as earlier. If
we get through gray box, certainly if we
get through 55, there will be squeeze
relief in this market.
All right? Because you don't want to be
short low of day, right? So, think about
anyone that got short low of day. Where
did all those shorts come in? 700 and
690 was a big level of shorts. We're now
testing the shorts that came in at 10:00
a.m., which is at the sort of 27, let's
just call it the 30 level that we had
before. And if we reclaim that, we're
going to go to point of control, which
is at 50. This is my PC that I'm looking
at. I know up here on Trading View, it's
up here, but for me, it's here. So, this
is sentiment. All right. Do we reade
that or is it relief? Both are
available. I want to make that clear
when I say that because both are
available. When we come into a level, we
need to see what the market wants to do.
Do aggressive buyers come in and get
absorbed? If so, we're going to play
short. Do aggressive sellers come in and
be absorbed? If so, we're probably going
to get long relief. [snorts]
Your analysis are amazing. You're
reading the market is just like a book.
Thank you, Pablo. Green Fridays are
great on a long weekend. Thanks, Alex.
You're welcome, dude. Decent day
considering where it started out, done
for the day on the funded accounts.
Green for the day and the week. Have a
great weekend, Alex. Heading out to the
business that pays the bills. Cheers,
brother. You're welcome, Rob. Pass to
Eva on that move. Thank you, kind sir.
You're welcome.
You're welcome. Flow zone. Would you not
look at the put and call walls to take
the short? Uh, you can look at the put
and call walls. I'd be focusing them on
the ETFs if you're going to do that.
How long do you need before to get
profitable after you started? How long
do I need or how long did you need? Uh,
everyone's different. It dep I would say
on a lot lot of things. depends on how
you absorb information, how much time
you spend on the screens, how good your
mentor is, how disciplined you are. Um,
I had some terrible uh terrible habits
when I started trading because I had an
awful mentor. All right? So, I'd be
picking tops non-stop getting blown up.
All right? So, it's really about
changing that, making sure you start
with a decent mentor. It doesn't have to
be me. Just someone that can teach you
well and someone that teaches h how I
always talk about in a pedagogy that
makes sense to you. If you're a visual
learner, you're going to need someone
that talks that way. If you need
storytelling, you're going to need
someone that talks that way. I can't
listen to someone just talking technical
when I'm a beginner. It doesn't make
sense to me. So, I have to paint the
picture.
Can I use a EMA 200 to see if we go
further down? We're rejecting EMA 200 on
the 1 hour. Yeah, if that works for you,
I I do use that. I use it on a fivem
minute. We broke the 5m minute 200 today
and then started flushing. [snorts]
We're right back down at um the daily
mean right now. One of the things I'm
very aware of at the moment
is this. Okay, look at the contraction
of the Ballinger bands. Right, next week
they're going to be like here.
and here and all the EMAs tight
at some point that it we can't do this
forever guys. I want you to understand
these are going to get tighter and
tighter. This is where squeezes happen.
All right? When we get contraction of
Ballinger bands like here
and then we explode out like here
and then we explode out. All right, we
cannot keep contracting these Ballinger
bands on the daily.
At some point it's going to get painful.
This cannot last forever. It will not
last forever.
We're back into this low volume node on
the daily again now as well.
This gray box.
Okay. So, rejecting. It's a good
rejecting of rejection of 30. So,
hopefully we can still move lower.
Thanks, Spear Fishing. Appreciate that.
You've been my favorite out of everyone
I've watched so far. Got my first payout
watching you. That's awesome. Great
kitty. I'm barely profitable at two
years. Most of the work was mental and
discipline.
So, Shiz, the question would be, were
you taught bad habits? Were you taught a
tool? Have you had to learn on your own?
Like there's lots of things that can
slow down um your ability to become
profitable.
[cough]
I bought the 20our course. It's working
for me. I just need to put in the reps.
That's it. Just put in the reps, man.
Here we go. Let's see if we can get a
break below here now for some
continuation. Ideally, we get a break
below and we hit this TP down here. Be
really nice. Lots I will say lots of
sellers came in at previous week point
of control like very very very heavy
selling came in there. So really we do
need this to stay heavy now um under the
say sort of 86s. Where did this guy
start with his 100 lot? 259
124.
Yeah, we want we want breaks below now.
We look good for it. Here we go. New
lower day.
Let's see if we can get down into this
next block.
I want this to stay heavy versus I'd say
sort of 90s and 700s now. Really good.
Come on, let's come down. Let's pay the
team.
Did I take any trades? Yes, we're short
from here.
I've had three goes today. So I think I
was long
this dip this morning for here
and then
I was short here covered stopped out.
So made sure I made my money and then
reshort again and
cover and then waiting to see if we get
lucky and get down into there.
Initial balance now set folks. Purple
line on your screen, right? to just be
aware of that.
I would like to catch the bottom. Do you
think it's going to fill up at a bottom?
What do you mean fill up?
Um, why do you want to catch a bottom?
If we're breaking away, why do you want
to catch a bottom? It's very risky.
We're in a weak market right now.
Be cautious about trying to do that.
Metal selling off. Yeah, I mean they're
just releasing some of that squeeze.
I mean, silver's still trading at 87s. I
mean, it is absolutely insane.
They're just releasing some of that
squeeze. That's all it is.
Alex is the best. I'm out of this short.
Great guidance. You're welcome, Dave
on Nvidia. Yeah, I mean this is it's not
just Nvidia, it's the whole market, man.
The whole market. The rotation is taking
place in this market. Look at RTY,
right? 0.03% up on the day, right? We
are seeing broadening of the market.
You've got to remember for as long as I
can remember, the market was narrowing.
What do I mean by that? The MAG was up.
The MAG 7 were up and everything else
for two years has been doing bugger. All
right? Been doing absolutely nothing.
So, we're having a rotation out of tech
at the moment, into the mids, into the
small caps, back into healthare, maybe
into finances if they can start posting
good earnings, which they didn't do
yesterday. So, we're seeing a broadening
of the market. Rather than it being
concentrated in seven names, we're
starting to move it into 500 plus names,
which is good for the market, but it
means you're seeing profit taking. What
would the catalyst be? There's two
options here. either the tech earnings
are not what what was anticipated in
they sell off and if we sell those tech
earnings off then I expect a big sell in
this market overall because they're
still worth 60% of the cues or if the
earnings are good if it's like hey we've
got more room with this AI bubble we've
got more room in the chip space we've
got more room in the energy providers
for that nuke etc etc we've got more
room in the data centers to go then
maybe we rebid it up.
Both are possible. Look at the daily
like we just talked about, right? It's
right at the mean. [snorts]
Nice, Alan. Nice. Nice. Nice. All right.
Breaking lower here on ES. Still driving
down. SPY now taking out previous days
low. All right. So on the cash ETF,
previous day low has been taken out on
SPY. Q's by the way have taken out
previous day low on the cash ETF.
Um but on the futures we need to come
down to here to do the same thing on the
ETF. On the cash side of the market we
have taken out the lows. [snorts]
VIX breaking through 16s now. 1620s or
16. Let me just check this pivot I have
marked out. 16 we call it 25 to 30 is
the pivot break on the bits. If we break
through [clears throat] that then market
might get very very very heavy.
Yeah, metals are selling off together
but silver's silver's in 6% down. Gold's
just 1.77% down. You know it's to be
expected folks. It was a giant squeeze,
right? It's a giant squeeze up. It
doesn't mean it's the end. Remember,
gold did this move maybe two months ago.
We did a big squeeze and then we pulled
back for what a good few weeks and then
started to grind back higher and explode
back out in.
It's not necessarily done.
It's definitely It was definitely past
two standard deviation. Silver was
probably past four by now.
Have a look if you want.
No, it wasn't. It was just at two.
That's impressive. All right, so back
down to 5day.
Silver can afford to drift right back
down into this pocket and then rebid if
it wants. Right, mean is all the way
down here. Look, look how big these
Ballinger bands are. It's hugging 5day
top Ballinger. That is a healthy trend.
All it's doing is pulling back to 5day.
It's not taking out any big levels yet.
It's just a pullback until it proves
otherwise on silver.
Okay, looking good here. See if we can
keep drifting lower
into here. Ideally,
you can move your stop down and protect
675. Now, if you want, just keep
managing this position.
Almost at 100 points. Another 10 10
points here would be a 100 point trade.
Yeah, move your runners. Yeah, I would
say like you you'd want to protect sort
of this previous week point of control
now. You don't really want it coming
back over that, right? So you can we can
protect here and see if we can get down
into this.
Really strong selling here, guys. We
could get 600s quick here.
They're bidding at 600 at the moment. So
hopefully we come down into that and
fill these guys.
Here's a 100 pointer off the pullback.
So if you missed that first move, we got
the second move. We got our 100 pointer.
All right. So from 30s to 30s is 100
pointer for you.
But they are bidding now. 620 600 and
then 575. I can see them all. 575 is
where we would want to go. Previous day
open is 590. Previous day low is 560.
Previous week value area low is around
that 575. So ideally we come down there.
It might be that we need relief before
we do it. It very very well might be
that this market does not come down here
in one go. It might be that it squeezes
up before it does it. So just manage
your position. If you if you're not
willing to give back all the way to 76,
then you know make sure it rejects
the [clears throat] IB for example.
sneeze [snorts]
here.
Sorry.
Where's my music? Well, I I don't I
don't really promote my new stuff, but I
used to be in a duo called Tough
[snorts] Love
back in the day.
You can listen anywhere.
All the [snorts] all the usual places.
Spotify
[snorts]
John, great call out again this morning.
These setups are great. Thank you.
You're welcome. You're welcome, buddy.
[snorts]
I feel cold coming on here.
>> [sighs]
>> Apex uh sale just got extended to the
22nd of this month, folks. So, if you
are looking to buy those [snorts] 80%
off
code FCT, we will do a giveaway on
stream later today as always.
>> [snorts]
>> Uh,
I just see Nathan
message you.
Let me get you set up, my friend. Give
me a second.
>> [snorts]
[snorts]
>> Okay, almost there folks. We are almost
there. Looking good.
Looking good here.
So we can see liquidity sat here 615 600
looking good folks
420 is definitely not target that is
asking a huge amount for today. I mean,
if it did it, it'd be insane. It'd be
very, very good. Obviously, that's the
low pivot, but I think we need to
respect these levels, right? We need to
respect where we're coming into. We're
at a node now, right? Let me zoom out
again so you can see what I'm always
looking at. Right, we're into this node
here. The next node down is 580. And the
previous week value area low, all right,
is right here at sort of 560. So, we
know somewhere in here this market is
likely to find a bid, right? If we're
going to trade outside of previous week
value low, then we're going to respect
this level here, 495,
right? Just call it 500. Right? So, if
the market gets weak, 500. If you get
very lucky, you'll get your 420. But
that's asking an awful lot. That's uh we
traded from 900. So it' be, you know,
it's almost a 600 point day down. It's
not unheard of. I've seen a,000 plus
point day, but we want to be careful.
Think about that. At the moment, we're
seeing a twoleg a failed follow through
and finally losing it. We want to be
careful into here. If we start getting
heavy under here, then yes, absolutely.
Sentiment shifts to a big big big sell
for next week.
And there's bid here at 680
or 150 lot really. They're double
stacked and then 95 is trying to scoop.
580 has just left the bid. Move back
down to 570s. All right. So, I'd like to
see 600 taken out, but you like if you
want to take profit into here, you can.
I'm ideally trying to get like a little
bit more, but I know there's a good
chance we will stop around here. So, I
might actually manage my stop and pull
it down to 630s to protect here. In
fact, I will do that.
[snorts] All right. So, stop here now.
630. Technically, you could put your
stop the other side of this shelf, but I
just don't want to give too much back.
It's a really nice trade. So, I'm going
to lock in my runner for 100 points no
matter what. And if we get down to here,
great. [snorts]
[clears throat]
Joined your session for the first time.
Trying to broaden my trading knowledge.
trading small but five profitable days
this week. Thank you for sharing your
knowledge. You are absolutely welcome.
Wild good tune. Glad you like it, mate.
That's with Haley May on. I think um
Trump I may put a tariff on countries
that don't go along with the Greenland.
He may find that everyone
stops working with him altogether.
is as about as much as a dictatorship as
we've seen in the modern era for a
democracy. [snorts]
Did I have a macro to take on lower move
this morning? Uh is in a fundamental?
No, not not not specifically other than
the rotation. It was more just technical
break that we just broke. All right,
under 600 we came finding a bid. Like I
said, I'm not going to let this come
back above 30 here. If it doesn't make
this, it doesn't make it. It's okay.
[snorts]
But we, like we just talked about, we
are going to find a bid anywhere from
now where we are now down into 570. All
right? So, we might find a bid early. In
fact, if we look at what I just showed
you,
look at where we've just found a bid.
This is the importance of understanding
volume. This shelf, look at this little
shelf here that spikes out. Okay? This
shelf here, look at where we've just
found a bid. right on this node. If I
paint this node for you, right on this
little node, we've just found a bid,
right? It doesn't mean that we bounce
from there and and go all the way up. It
just means that this was a cover point.
Everyone else will be looking for this.
If they do want to find relief, right,
then they're going to need to trade
through the 640. So, there's possible
relief if they want to to 640 through
640 back to value through there back to
720s again. All right. So, just
pullbacks can happen here. We've been
strong move lower. We haven't really had
many pullbacks. If we zoom out.
[snorts] All right. We haven't really
had much of a pullback, have we? So, we
got stuck in this gray box, which is
current week and previous day. We failed
underneath. Alex was an idiot and missed
this cell. It's okay. We missed it. We
join in. We fade it. All right. There
hasn't been much of a pullback. These
are not big pullbacks. this market wants
to come back up here and test it, it can
do that. It's absolutely fine to do
that. I'm not going to sit through that
though. If they want to refade it, they
will. If they want to reclaim, they
will. If they want to go back into
balance, they will. Anything is
possible. I need you guys to understand
that when you have mentors saying this
is absolutely what the market has to do,
yada yada yada yada, they are straight
lying to you. Market will do whatever it
wants to do.
typical micro size on a trade. How much
do you scale out there? All depends on
the size of the account I'm I'm trading,
right? So, if you're starting off on a
50k account, start with my starter would
be like one, two, three micros adding
into it as it starts to like confirm up
for me. Willing to add like decent size
all the way into it. And uh I mean I
really haven't got enough size on this
one here, but it's okay. But you know,
one one if you get one micro to do a
runner of 150 points and you lock in
five at 100 points, that's a decent day
still. [snorts]
I'd rather do that and trade to my
levels than have a mini on and look for
eight ticks or whatever people do. I
just think that's mental. That makes no
sense to me. But each to their own.
Who is they when you talk about they?
They are market makers. They are funds.
Right? If we we just view the market as
one single entity. It's the best way to
view the market. It's not actually a
single entity. But if you view the
market that way, you make it much easier
for yourself. That's just Woff theory.
What about 300k account? Um what's the
what's the draw down on a 300k?
How much draw down are you allowed? Like
six sixk or something.
You could pro you could probably put
three minis on if it's if it's six to 9k
draw. You could you could get three
minis on and scale up
depending on the ATR. One to three
minutes I'd say. [snorts]
Okay, if you look at look at the VIX, it
tried to get through that 1630. We
talked about it all morning. If we poke
through 16, we'll go 1630. It's tried to
get through it. It's just had a false
break.
It's just had a false break. So, it
needs to hold a bid now down to 1612s,
maybe even 16s. If it holds a bid there
and it wants to go previous day high
into 1650, then the market will stay
weak. If this is a look above and fail
on the VIX, then we're going to see
relief in this market. So, we have to
see how we go here. But CVD still very,
very heavy in line with the market.
We are starting to build a bit of a
shelf here. If we start breaking above
17s, then you can imagine a pop up to
these soon. Starting to see that move.
So, just be careful here. Manage your
position. It might be that I end up
taking this off here. might it might
need a two leg if they're going to go
for that previous day low. It might need
the two leg to reade. I don't really
want to give back 70 points, right? So,
I might well cut this here if I'm honest
because I don't want to get caught in a
candle coming up here.
Where's this node? 30s. 30s is still the
level for me.
Through 30s I cut. I'm not going to hold
through 30s.
just started following you this week.
Glad to have found a fellow Brit and I
like the way of trading. What indicators
are you using? Um, this is just my
Flowzone Pro. All right. So, a version
of this comes with the course or you can
upgrade or you can buy it on my website
flzzonetrader.com.
Uh other than that, this uh New York
session VWAP, it just saves me having to
anchor it each day. That was built by a
student of mine. It's just private for
guys in the Discord, I believe. And then
just anchored volume profile. That's it.
It's not a lot. It might It might look
like a lot. All I'm looking at is what
is the momentum? Oh,
right. What is the momentum? We move
into a cell. What is the momentum? Where
are the VWAPs? What is the volume?
If I move out of here, what is the
sentiment which comes with the momentum
and then key levels? Horizontal lines on
my chart are just key levels. Previous
day low, they're just open high, lows
and closes on dailies and weeklies.
That's all they are. And then initial
balance, opening range, you see the
opening range trade away from that today
was a fail. All right. So once we left
15 minute, this box here, opening range,
fail and initial balance so far failing.
These are all in one indicator though.
These are all in the flow zone pro,
right? It's just one.
Am I still in the trade? Uh, yes. But
I'm about to cut it because we keep
approaching these 30s
and we're holding dips now into a a blue
level I have on Ninja Trader. So,
I've given this a little bit of room to
35. I probably got to cut this here cuz
we're about to start squeezing. In fact,
I'm going to just take this off here and
not even worry about it. That's me done.
Don't want to sit through this. It might
be that we reflush. We haven't taken out
the previous day low, but uh that's good
enough for me. 100 points on the runner.
Maybe could have locked in an extra 40
points, but it's fine. So, there we go.
I don't want to get caught in whatever
comes now because there's a chance for
this if it really wants to to come and
repric up into here.
Could have taken more off here, I guess.
But, uh, if you're going to be a nasty
bugger and do it, you can still hold for
this.
Trend's still good.
But yeah, I'm now out. I didn't I didn't
want it to come through this node, which
we just did.
[snorts]
Joined your session for the first time
this week. Trying to broaden my trading
knowledge and consistency. Training
small but five days this week. Sorry,
I'm having to like catch up with all the
everything here.
I'm a bit blinded by this big move down.
Took my profits, but help my itchy
finger here. What's the next key level
it might move up from? I mean,
we're into a a node now, Joe, but like
it's very possible it comes to previous
week or a low. It's very possible we
come down here. We have previous week
low. I don't know where it stops. Um, we
haven't broken the weekly low.
We're still just sideways. I know we're
in a cell, but this is just like
yesterday. If we look at a daily,
right, we're just doing the same thing
as yesterday. Nothing's actually
changed.
We're still wedged in.
Wedged in.
Most of the volume's taking place in
here,
right? It's not like we're seeing this
or seeing this. So, we are building so
much liquidity here. It's insane.
I will say this is often what tops start
to look like. If we have a look,
you over here.
If we look at how we often like to top,
they don't happen overnight.
Last year, December
failed to make a new high, lots of
sideways liquidity.
October, fail to make a new high, lots
of sideways liquidity. Once we break,
nasty. Okay, we had catalyst for that,
which was tariffs.
here
sideways build lots of liquidity failed
to make a new high big pullback we can
go back miles as well same story here
same time of year end of year failed to
make a new high sideways for a few
months and then
get hammered co I'm not going to talk
about because it's completely different
situation. Here's the same uh 2018
failed to make a new high.
Q4 into Q1.
Same again here. This one actually makes
a new high. That was the divergence. Go
back to 2016. You can see contracting of
Ballinger bands
sideways for a long time into uh Q4 into
Q1 fade. It seems to always be Q4 into
Q1. We did do it in the summer as well.
Same fade.
Same thing over and over again, guys.
Where's 08?
Q4
failed to make a new high. recession.
It's not like it's uncommon what we're
doing.
And the other thing is we haven't tested
the uh 200 day or the 200 week in
forever.
Right? Here's the 200 day just sat here
waiting to be tested on this pivot.
200 weeks probably down here somewhere,
right? We need to test that. It's a
healthy market when we test it and
absorb it. Trade under, we trade over,
we absorb, we go. We need we actually
need a back test of this. It would be
healthy for the market to do it. So,
it's not unusual is all I'm saying.
Up for the week, gym time. Glad to have
you back. Take care, Scott. Nice one,
dude.
Just scout that bounce. Yeah, we're all
all the way back now, aren't we? This is
what I talked about where I don't want
to hold from 30s. Once we reclaim 30s,
it's we can start getting the squeeze.
Is it 30s
somewhere around here? Yeah, 30s. This
shelf here, we've come right back to the
initial balance. My purple line, a bit
of a shelf here. So like I said, they
might need to do something like this
to offer relief to trap balls to resell.
If they come back inside this though, I
would start being careful. All right, if
we are going to start holding this, I
would start to be careful about thinking
about any more downside. You can see the
importance of this initial balance and
this node. Um, just catching up with
what you guys are saying here.
Yeah, volume volume nodes can be targets
for TPS for sure. Sure. If you think
about what volume is, it's just a place
where lots of people participated. So,
we respect that. Low volume nodes we can
use as like support and resistance, but
we can trade through them very very fast
if no one wants to turn up there. So,
I'd use them as like false breakout
parts of a low volume node and high
volume nodes as like proper support and
resistance.
Please give me a funded account. I have
no funds to trade. What I am experts
trade tell me. Don't know what that
means, but no one can give you a funded
account.
Do I find the volume profiles more
accurate on Ninja Trade and Trading
View? Just find that there's sometimes
discrepancies, but not necessarily more
accurate.
We start grinding up and thinking about
doing one contract long next week expiry
either Tesla or QQQ.
I mean, coming into earnings, I don't
know, mate.
Do what do what you do. Like, if you uh
if that's what a trade that you like,
then do it.
If I'm using Apex Trader funding trader
account, would I need Ninja Trader
version of the flow zone indicator? Uh,
you could have NT or you can have the
one on here. It's up to you. Either or
because you can trade on on uh Trading
View if you really want to. I don't. I
like executing on Ninja Trader.
Can you trade with the indicator? Yes,
you can.
Okay, AA Foster, if you keep talking
nonsense, then you're just going to be
removed. I'm just talking absolute
garbage.
I use Ninja Trader desktop app. I've
been signing into my Apex Trader 8
login. The Ninja orderflow wasn't was
working. Great. Thanks for that video.
Oh, you're welcome, Ero.
You might just need to go back on to um
and turn it back on in the back end.
I've had that a couple weeks ago, so you
might have to regrow through that video
do the same thing again. Sometimes it
turns off. I don't know why.
You're welcome, Cat.
Nice one, mate. See you Monday. See you
Monday.
How do I choose anchor points for VWAP?
Uh 9:30 open and like a news print or a
big peak high or a big peak low is where
I would choose them.
Single prints from 675 to 725 could be
filled. Let's have a look.
Yeah, up here. Yeah,
definitely move down to one minute. See
if we see more. Yeah, I agree.
if they want to. But we know this is
strong, right? This is where strong
selling came in. This is where we broke
down from. Remember, we took it from
7:30.
We took it from here and this was the
follow through. Buyers definitely got
caught here. But yeah, if we get relief,
we've got all these imbalances to fill
if they really want to.
Wondering if there's a benefit over
Ninja Trader over Trading V. Uh well the
ATM strategy for a start, copying for a
start, not being web- based. I think all
those things for me.
Monday's a holiday. Yeah, it's Martin
Luther King Day, isn't it? Yeah.
I don't think we'll get a V-shaped
recovery. I think we might trade into
range, but I don't think we'll go all
the way back up today, but who knows? It
is a Friday.
What is indicator order flow? What do
you mean
for this? I'm going to do a video on it
tomorrow. It's just the footprint
charts, guys. It's just up here. Volume
footprint
previous day low. Yeah, I know. It It
missed it, didn't it? But like I said,
it did take it on the ETFs, right? So
cash cash took it. So if you go to like
QQQ,
right, we took it right here. So we
drifted underneath. We already took it.
If you go to the spiders,
we took it, right? So it's only the
futures that didn't take it. So it's
worth being, you know, being aware of
that. Sometimes cash players got got the
move that they wanted. [snorts]
Hey, nice Kyo. Good work.
New here. Fantastic market analysis
which helped me catch three of the
biggest trades of my career. Hey, that's
great to hear. Congratulations.
Right, back to previous week PC now. So,
if they're going to fade it, they really
should think about doing it anywhere
from like sort of where we are now,
maybe even up to VWOP. They let the
relief happen to VWAP. I would start to
be concerned for this uh for all you
shorts. All right. All right. If we
start to bid above this or do this. All
right. I wouldn't be thinking about
short for the rest of the day. Even
though there's got this target here, if
they start to hold volume and create
volume in here, they will leave these
guys trapped. All right. Shorts at the
low of day have trapped. And there were
shorts at lower day trapped. Okay, we
had big guys come in at low of day. You
can see all this delta under 620 was
sellside. They are caught. All right. So
if they start to hold bids on pullbacks,
I would kind of leave the shorts alone.
All right? If we start to hold inside of
the initial balance, if we start to
reclaim areas, you want to be careful.
[snorts]
Checked out the web video. Could not
find anchored volume profile on NT. You
have to It's not anchored, right? It's
just a normal the normal orderflow
volume profile.
Let me show you guys.
All right. This is the volume profile.
Order flow volume profile. in the
settings. You see how I've got trading
hours set to flow zone trader 9:30 to
4:00. You will need to make your own
trading hours and save it and then load
it. Okay. Um, that's what you will need
to do. That's how you have it anchored
to the 9:30 to 4:00. Like it does it by
itself once you do that.
I'm sure I put it in that video.
Maybe I didn't. Sure I did.
So they are trying now to absorb initial
balance here. ES has just rejected New
York VWOP and PDC.
It's a interesting level. This it is
definitely an interesting level. Shorts
will need to come in soon if they are
going to look to send this back
downside. Buyers will want to defend
this level. This is where the battle is
going to start for sentiment for the
next hour or so, I'd say.
So if they lose this shelf of 5960s,
possibly get a retest of 633s again. All
right. So if sellers come in here, they
will need to send it under this shelf to
here. If buyers keep absorbing, they
will try and trade back inside of value.
So sellers are looking to do this. They
will cover some here and then maybe
they'll get one of these. Buyers,
because we've had like two legs, buyers
are going to try and absorb this to
force this move up. That's what you're
looking at at the moment. It is a
battleground level. It is your initial
balance.
The buyers trying to absorb this here
like we just talked about this IB level
big level and they want to get relief to
sort of 7 700 720 somewhere up there.
That's what the buyers are looking to do
today.
Right now,
I'm going to use the bathroom for a
moment. I will be right back.
>> [snorts]
>> Okay, guys.
How are we doing on the likes here?
All
right, let's get these likes up, guys.
You want to do giveaways? We got to get
400 likes. So many of you come here
every day, [snorts] take the trades for
free, make your money, and don't even
hit the like button. Come on.
Come on now. All right. So, relief now,
like we talked about, they're holding
the IB. I'd be very cautious about any
shorts. Now, if they want to lift this,
they have a low volume node here. They
can trade to sort of 714, 720s, maybe
even the VWAPs. All right, they're
starting to lift this now. [snorts]
ES going for VWOPS as well. Already
through its close already through New
York trying to trade to VWOP. Spy
reclaiming VWOP or having a dig through
VWOP. Huge relative weakness. VIX coming
back down. It failed that 1630 level
that we talked about. It then failed 16.
It's trading right back down to 1562
now.
Just a complete wash out on the VIX as
we trade back into the range again. And
it's just uh back and forth market here.
Going back to PDC here. Big level above.
Try and fill some of these PDC hair key
and get rid of this yellow line. There
we go.
All right. So, any of you took that
long, the reclaim of IB and initial
balance, you'd want to be paying
yourself some into this low volume node
and see if you can get through 700s and
720s. Now, if any of you took the long
from here for the reclaim,
you're in leg two here. So, you want to
be careful in case they resell it. You
never know, you might get lucky, but you
want to position yourself so that you're
trimming into this. You want to be
locking some profits in into the key
levels. You do not want to be
overstaying. You're welcome.
is PDC.
[snorts]
Let's see if they re reclaim this now in
control.
If they hold the next dip in that then
they get offer more relief probably.
back towards these 700s.
Trying to buy this at the moment.
I'm not going to buy it. I'm just saying
what I'm seeing. I don't No way I'm
buying this here. The buy the buy was
the initial balance reclaim. This can be
a second leg which is then sold into
waiting to see. We've just failed
previous day close.
And do we start washing down here or do
they bid at these 85s?
These kind of levels here become key
now. All right. So buyers will want to
hold the bid here
and complete this move. Sellers will
want to get a close under here and
finish this target. But they have to
respect this now because we've now built
liquidity through the session.
Yeah, totally. I've seen the same thing
as you who said the daily. If we look at
this
right here,
current week value area low and 20-day
right here. Totally agree with you. But,
you know, we can we can just get stuck
here because we have everything very
very very tight here. Where's the 50-day
now? Let me have a look. 50 days there
as well. Like at the low of day, it's
just everything is tight at the moment
in this market while it has to make its
decision. All right, we're starting to
lose these levels. So, watching here. If
they start losing this in initial
balance, I'm going to look to size in
for a uh move back lower.
Not before that. They're going to have
to prove to me that they're done with
this. I'm not not seeing a prove yet,
but it's it's a level I'm interested in.
Remember, the main trend is down. We've
just done two legs back up.
We came right into PDC. I would almost
rather it traded into here and failed.
Buyers will want to absorb here.
I will be willing to short if we get
stuck under this or this rotation. And I
will respect this.
[snorts]
Sorry to hear that, Tyson.
At least you got your money out of them,
right? So you're you're net positive.
your net positive on there
the one hours. Yeah,
it's just because we're in a giant
balance. That's all it is. We're in a
giant balance. [sighs] So, previous week
point control buys are trying to absorb
it. They want to complete this move
here. I'm not going to buy this.
I'm going to wait to see if we come back
under this for the day or if we get
stuck here. If we reclaim, then I might
not take the long. The long opportunity
is probably where I stopped out there
and then add there and trim. I'd rather
stay short on this for a protrend short
at the moment.
But we have to be aware of initial
balance. We've had a look below and
fail, but we do have targets below if it
does want to go for it.
does not know what it's doing.
[snorts]
All right. How are we doing for likes?
Because I want to do a giveaway.
Need at least 100 more, guys. There's at
least half of you watching this who have
not hit the like button. It's all you've
got to do. Just hit the like button and
we'll do some giveaways. It's really
simple.
This is the flow zone indicator. Yeah.
So that's part of
this. All right. All right, once we went
protrend
[snorts]
regular time close today. Yeah, midday
close on Monday for Martin Luther King
Day. Midday close on Monday.
It's a battle here. I actually want to
see them lift this to 725 if possible
first.
[snorts]
What's the time as well? Got to watch
these uh
talks.
You got Barkin talking now and Bowman.
So you have got Fed talk taking place at
the moment. Want to be careful of that.
The indicator. Yeah, indicator works
very well.
Um,
we'll see. I'll see about Monday. Maybe
not. If it's a low volume day, I'll see
what the setup looks like on the Sunday
open. If I think there's a decent day to
be had on Monday, I'll trade it. But
volume's likely to be lower.
Um, but we'll see, right? I'm not I'm
not against being here Monday with you,
but only if it's worth everyone's time.
Only if it's worth everyone's time.
Don't want to sit here for three hours
and the market not move.
I want to be aware of it in case they do
some dirty dirty move on a low volume
day, which just would not surprise me
knowing what they're like. It really
would not surprise me at all.
We cannot get through these 700s in this
PDC here. We keep getting stuck on this
top of this node here.
What's TP? Take profit.
All right, Nathan. I hope the hope the
surgery goes well, mate. Hope you're
okay.
[snorts]
I hope all is okay.
Just answer a couple emails here, guys.
>> [snorts]
>> What? What is it? What [clears throat]
is it, mate? Rotator cuff.
What is the graph that's moving up and
down about buyers and sellers? This
right here above me is is your dom is
your ladder. It's your level two. Okay,
here they go. So hopefully they can
squeeze up here. It's not cuz I'm long.
It's cuz I want to see how we act. So
we've reclaimed initial balance. You can
see this now,
right? I want to see what happens when
we get into these
top side of ranges 50s if they really
want to go flying. It's a big ask.
725 still on the tape looking for
outliers here above. Are there any
outliers above right now?
32s was a big sell level. Not many
buyers trapped above.
>> [snorts]
>> Oh, mate, that sounds awful.
That sounds terrible, mate. Hope you're
okay. Woof.
All right. Into this gray box. VWAP
above. So longs are getting paid here
from the initial balance reclaim.
They're trying to push up into VWAP. So
that long IB to VWAP trade is starting
to take place. 25 is a big level. I
would say big big big level. VIX still
dripping downside here. It's lost it's
lost the bid so far. And um we can
consider how this market might want to
act. It's possible that we come all the
way up to 50s here. I would not rule it
out. I absolutely would not rule it out.
Strong buy delta has stepped in the last
5 minutes. Strongest we've seen for a
while. So, do they get trapped or do
they get their way and get the 25s and
50s? We just tagged into 20s.
Certainly 20s being defended there. the
edge.
I think the market will go up now. I
think the market is giving relief. Um I
think sellers will probably want to
defend around here. I can imagine us
doing something like this, right? I can
imagine us doing something like this and
then a trade back down into here. At
this point, it would need to make its
decision if it's doing this or or coming
down into here or if we're just going to
trade in here for the rest of the day.
Very very possible
relief, big relief will come above 57s
and 60s, right? Then then we can get
that sort of Vshape, but I don't think
we're going to get it. But ES is showing
some good strength here.
But if we have a look at the mag, Apple
down 0.68%, 68%. Amazon down 0.19%.
Google down 0.79%.
Meta up 68%. Microsoft up63%. Nvidia
up.39%.
Remember that was up well over 2 and a
half 3% at one point today. Tesla's
basically flat and as a whole the MAG
are only up 0.12%. So they haven't
caught a big bid yet. And the strength
from NQ is gone because we're now
lagging behind ES. We were stronger this
morning in chips. were now lagging
behind.
Look at that. Almost 10% up on the day.
They all caught a bid.
How am I live? Monday to Friday. 9:15
Eastern all the way until lunch. Monday
to Friday.
The buy trade at 25 660
would say it's high risk due to downward
momentum. 660. This is a this is a
better trade because you've got
something to risk off.
You've got this shelf
and you've got no acceptance and you've
got initial balance. You've got
something to risk off but it's counter
trend. So, you need to be locking in
profits because if they when they're
done with this, right, if too many
buyers come in here and they're done
with it and the protrend takes back
over, this can happen very very quickly.
But this is a good level to risk off.
This is a failed break, a reclaim. And
these are the targets from IB to VWAP.
We talk about this almost every day on
stream. IB to VWAP. ES has already done
it. It's already tagged both its VWAPs
from the IB. If we look [clears throat]
at ES
right there's your reclaim clear pivot
held B up one B up two that's your job
done it's done it
[snorts]
So bpock now at 85s.
So still watching 85. Still watching
initial balance [snorts] if we're going
to trade backside.
Is the book map showing orders at 750?
Uh, not really. There's a little bit.
Most of it's at 25 like I've been
talking about.
Look above and fell of 20. Yeah, it's
possible. We're still grinding up at the
moment, right? We're still holding flow
zones. We're still above point of
control. We're still above the nodes.
We're stuck between the gray box and the
node. We're still grinding up.
Waiting to get involved in a sell. I
would like to sell this if we see
weakness.
We do have some buyers trapped at like
15s.
Like we do have a proper auction there.
Above tens, we definitely have people
trapped. But, you know, we're getting
closer and closer to lunch. We've got a
new 30 minute bar coming in 4 minutes.
Just waiting to see if we can see some
weakness come to for me to join in. If
we're going to if we're going to trade
it back downside, we're going to have to
let go of key levels.
Don't want to guess the top. What
happens if you guess this top and they
go, "No, we're going to Vshape." Right?
We're still driving at the moment. I
want to play the backside when it's
done.
If it's finished, I want to see
something like this and leave all of
this trapped and then play lower. I
don't want to be guessing here and get
caught in one of these.
Remember, we've hit most of the targets.
The only thing left is this. So, we're
back inside the initial balance. They
want to lift all the way to even they
want to come and test value on the day,
they can. Look, it lines up with VWAP.
If they want to lift this, if they want
to lift it, they will lift it.
to this seller who was at 14 again.
Still got liquidity above to attack if
they want to go for it. ES now really
looking pretty good.
Guys, lots of you asking like the same
questions over and over and over and
over. Like I'm not going to keep
repeating myself on stream.
Don't be so v. This is real simple. I
ain't got time for someone like you.
Don't be so vague.
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] Another one.
How about you go and do some work and
understand what I mean?
No, we're not going to delete him. He's
gone. Bye.
[\h__\h] can't stand it. Don't be so
vague. I literally talked about it like
30 minutes ago.
Jesus Christ.
Yeah, I'm really vague, mate. Really
vague.
How to know you're a newbie trader and
you've got no chance when you're a
complete dick on stream when someone's
helping you.
Like I'm not being funny. Some of you
are asking the most ridiculous
questions. Do I use Delta? Yes,
absolutely. I use Delta. Like you hear
me talking about it all the time. It's
literally on the screen. You have Delta
here. I keep showing the Delta positions
here. I keep talking about the trap
traders. I'm using bookmap. Like come on
guys, help me out here. I'm exhausted as
it is. Come on, help me out. Help me out
a little bit.
It was only a few minutes ago. I said
it's the strongest buy delta candle
we've had since the open.
Come on guys, help me out.
Okay, back to the 25s which I keep
talking about
into the gray box into VW up.
Here's the big buyers coming in trying
to force the squeeze up. Now, this is
where I'm interested in. Do they get
caught here or do they see follow
through all the way to 50 now?
So, do we see buyers have follow through
to 50 now or not? ES looks very very
strong. VIX looks very very weak. So, I
want to be very very careful. We've
already reclaimed key level. We're
coming right back up to these 50s at the
moment. This is a little peak here as we
peaked through.
New 30 minute bar
level here. 52s looks a big level to me.
I'm just annoyed. You guys just annoy
me. Can tell the traders, not even
traders, the kids that jump from stream
to stream to stream to stream to stream
to stream and then ask stupid questions
because they can't sit and learn. and
they don't want to educate themselves.
They want a gift. It's just infuriating,
man.
And then have the [\h__\h] stupidity to
say I'm being vague.
Okay, let it go, Alex. All right, back
to 25s. Right. Do they rebid 25s or is
this looking above and fail? We hit New
York VW up. We haven't hit 24hour. We
came in low volume node. These are the
levels of interest. Now, do these buyers
up here get trapped? We saw aggressive
buying up here. Do they get trapped? And
do we start to flush or do they need to
get to 50s? Are they looking for a
rotation to 50s? ES looks so flipping
strong right now. VIX is trying to find
a bit of a bid. It is trying.
[snorts]
Just grind back up since that lower day.
I don't mind. Look, I don't mind asking
questions. It's when it's the same
question on repeat, which means
someone's just going from stream to
stream to stream to stream and then has,
you know, I've been live now for what,
two hours and then says I'm being vague.
It's like it's just [\h__\h] that like that
that annoys me. [\h__\h] off into one of the
other channels then which teach you
nothing. I'd much rather you went there
with that attitude.
Nice. Yeah, you got the Tyson trade. I'm
assuming, dude, you just you took the IB
to VW up the Tyson trade.
You're bread and butter, man. You're
absolute killer with that stuff.
Okay, watching these 20s and 25s. See if
they pull the bid here and we start to
flush. Just being very, very careful.
Not in yet. I'm waiting to see how we
act here. Definitely caught some buyers
at the highs. I'm very aware that the
rotation to 50 hasn't been hit, but like
we said, 25s was the big level. Question
is, are we going to start to fade off
the New York VW up? Are we going to lose
these 15s and come down to 90s and then
see some like downside follow through?
That's the question for me right now.
Here we come into the imbalance.
They're bidding 15s.
Point of control now shifted above us
into 30s or 27s. I want to see it start
flushing now. If we're going to get
heavy, I want to see it start doing it
now. Otherwise, they're going to go 50s.
We're running out of time into lunch.
So, if we're going to start rejecting
this node, we want to start doing it
now.
And then the fun and games really start
happening underneath here. So, for me,
PC's just flipped on ninja to here. So,
if we do something like this, it would
be fun. But if we do something like
this, it would be really fun. What I be
want to be very aware of is if they want
to complete this move here, which is
very very possible. So I'm trying to be
patient for them to come here first,
come under, reject, maybe even here for
a bigger ad. Until then, I want to be uh
very very patient.
Yes, still showing strength there.
50 still possible. They're still holding
flow zones. They're still grinding back.
50s and VWAP still possible if they want
to do it.
Cannot rule that move out. Need to be
patient. If we're going to play
backside, I'm going to have to be
patient.
What is the edge of this node?
It's so far away.
Where's it get? 800. Oh my god. Can you
imagine that? They bid back up to 800
today. Be insane. [snorts]
Yeah, Adam. I mean, once you understand
what's going on,
it's a game changer, isn't it? Like,
when you see buyers buying the highs or
sellers selling the lows, you can see
who's trapped very, very quickly.
thing is ES is starting to print over
its pivots from 10:00 a.m. this morning.
And you got to think like if they don't
sell it soon, we're going to be at New
York open and 7,000 on ES and we would
have got gr been grinding back the whole
day.
But QQQ is coming into its VWAP. So, I'm
just flat here just waiting to see what
it wants to do. I have no idea what
these guys want to do with this at the
moment. It's just uh
a bit out of sync.
just stuck. We are stuck again.
Nice. Nice work. 500 on a TPT. Good
work.
This guy here, this these sellers here
that came in at 20 down to sort of
what's this 13s
100 lot 200 about 300 300 of them stuck
between 20 and and the 10ens
and if they remain stuck we can squeeze.
If they if they become in the money then
I think we get a bigger flush. So
between 20s and tens basically between
here in here you have like 300 lot
seller right he got caught in here he's
300 lot size basically he needs this
which is what I'm waiting to see if we
get cuz if he remains stuck and he
starts covering at this point here we're
going to be at 50s real
We're going to go and test where he came
in. This is where he came in. Couple
more points down. Let's see if he gets
out and rebids or if he just adds some
size and tries to force
moment. They're rebidding it. Someone's
just come on the book at 25 again and
he's adding at 15s to absorb
is now considered fair value on the day.
This is the level we've traded the most
at all session. Now, that's how long
we've been stuck here at this at this
level
from 10:00 a.m. And again, now coming
into lunch, same level.
So, all that move and we're just going
to stop at the VWAP into lunch. Are we
just a load of nonsense today basically?
So, we're just going to pause at the
same point.
going to test him again.
Still holding that 25. Remember 25 down
to 15. We have a 300 lot seller who's
currently stuck there. We come under
that then we're going to see weakness.
At the moment he is still stuck. 25 to
15. He remains stuck.
If he gets stuck and we start breaking
here, we will go 50s.
If he starts forcing the his uh stop out
at 35 and above, we'll probably go 50s
real quick if he does.
So, we stop, I'd imagine, is here. And
then we're going to go 50s.
Look above there.
They're trying to rebuild it again. Now
they want to get up to 50s as clear as
day. ES is wants to get up to that New
York open. I cannot believe the strength
of ES. That's insane.
ES is basically like up here right now.
Um, it's called City Cyd
Footprint.
It's a third party app that you have to
pay for.
So, they're trying to get up to these
50s.
Here they go for the push to 50s.
Attempting to get to that 50s and VWAP.
Relentless bid on this. What happens
when they pull it? That's the question.
Still no backside. Still just grinding.
They're adding at 60s now. So they're
adding higher now as well. They're
trying to get filled even higher now.
So 45, 47, 50, 52, 55, and 60 is where
they're adding.
ES is going to go for that New York
open. I'm telling you, the strength in
that thing.
So Tyson, I don't know if you've got any
left for your IB trade, but you might
get your 24-hour view up as your second
tag.
Maybe.
still absorbing.
Still the same target. They want to get
to 50s. Just question if they if they
pull this bid. We've gone up non-stop
grind. It can be like a nasty flush, but
I think 50s is definitely the target
here.
All the way to the other side of value.
Here it goes. There's 50s tagged and
VWOP tagged. And now you have to see, do
they really want to run these stops at
65? But this is your target. So if you
were long from IB, that's your target.
24-hour view up now hit.
ES very close to that New York open that
we talked about.
Amazon's caught a bid now gone flat
and you have to see what next now really
into value area high on the session. If
we find acceptance above value area high
on the session, we have some stops here
to run. But
um You cannot rule out this move. You
just can't cuz we're so thin on where we
lack structure, but you would imagine
they'd want to send it down here at some
point.
But if they hold this, you'd be careful.
But I would be interested in this trade
here down to here and certainly outside
of that.
How we've just shifted value though.
Crazy.
See 50 is a tag. So make sure you're I
don't know 80 90% out of your long.
Nice cat. Good work.
Yeah, tons of trend line liquidity.
Flow zone is just absorb absorb absorb
absorb absorb absorb absorb. Just
non-stop. They're not done with it.
They're trying to come in again here.
It's all for me. This is all about ES.
ES wants to hit its New York open for
whatever reason. They have decided to
turn the buy on to get back to New York
open. Maybe someone was stuck.
We have a look at the breadth. What's
going on right now?
Yeah, finances have caught a bit. So JP
Morgan 1% up. AXP 2.21% up. Um what's
this down here?
SYF 4.20% up. Healthcare doesn't look
great though. Energyy's going all right.
Utilities are going pretty good. Real
estate's going very well. Industrials
are going very well. Tech's just a mixed
bag.
Consumer defensive looks weak today.
Who's the big winner on the day? MU.
Like the chips. It's crazy, man. The
chips are the big winners. Like MU, AMD,
AVGO,
um
other than INTC, everything's up. Nvidia
only like what are we up now on video?
0.48%.
Okay, so 50's tagged.
Um, SLG probably not knowing them.
Just get another positive trade and then
I don't know. You'd have to ask them. I
I wouldn't know but technically no.
I was down 100 earlier. Now I'm up 300
because of the trapped seller at the
50s. Thank you. You're welcome.
>> You're welcome, Willhouse. No worries.
Okay. So, back to test PC in this node.
All right. So, buyers will want to
absorb this kind of node here. The
weakness will come. All right. Once we
start losing this, I'm interested if we
start losing this for a rotation here
and here and then run us back down to
here. If we get lucky, if we keep
holding bids, there's just really
nothing else to do with this. We can't
force our way into a market. I'm
certainly not going to bid up here.
Should I bid initial balance? Possibly.
It felt risky, but possibly.
All right, use the bathroom, get a glass
of water, come back. We've got 10
minutes, and then I want to give away an
Apex account.
big sellers come in here. Still being
absorbed.
I have lost interest in this account.
No interest in this now. Too late in the
day. too close to uh
coming into lunch now. So, let's do some
giveaways.
Huge ask 92 to 95 on ES. Yeah, they're
trying like they're trying to protect
New York open is 90 650 or 97.
I'm seeing that being protected at the
moment,
but I just don't like what I'm seeing
now. Right, I'll show you on bit map.
Where are you guys?
Okay, this guy got stuck. Remember I
said like there's 300 lot stuck is this
guy here.
All right, he tried to sell the low for
this breakdown underneath the 25. So he
was looking for the look above and
failed. He came in aggressive. He got
caught. They re they absorbed the
absorption happened here. They rebid up.
They've never let him out. He then
stopped out. All right, if you think
about this,
his stop was here. Look what happened
once we got through that 310 lot. All
right, so he stops out. You get breakout
buyers. We know he was 300 lot or just
under 300 lot short at the low. Guess
what? 300 lot long there. That's his
stop. All right, we squeeze up and we're
holding this now. Maybe we get look
below finally come, but it's too close
to lunch now. They've had they've had
the time to do it. All right, they've
had the time to do it.
That's why I kept saying someone's stuck
there. You can see him. I told you
exactly where and how much size he had.
All right.
[cough]
I still don't get how you're seeing what
you're seeing on this chart, but no
longer looks like Picasso rainbow to me.
It's just time, brother. It's just time.
like over time you'll start to see the
the patterns and the traits and
everything else. Sorry guys, I haven't
even said it live yet. It's my bad. Give
me a second. I tell you what we're going
to do because I don't want you guys to
get banned who you've just put it in.
Let me do
different word first. We'd give away
We give away the course first, right? So
just type course in in chat once
and give away the course first. We do
the Apex account after. So, just type
course chat in chat once only cuz loads
of you put the code already and then it
would ban you. So, I just want to make
sure you you're all entered into it.
Give you guys a couple minutes.
back to this same level where that guy
was just stuck. Literally exactly the
same level he was stuck at. So if they
let him out, we might get a flush. If
they don't let him out, we're going to
rebid up to 50s again.
He's still caught there. Exactly the
same level.
Exactly the same level we just went over
on bookmap. Right. Give you guys 30
seconds more.
So tempted, but it's so close to lunch,
man. It's so tempting. It is so close to
lunch.
It's time to sell this now.
Well, we can watch 15s to see if it
rejects, I guess.
Soon as I do the giveaway, I miss it.
[laughter]
Wait the whole time for backside and
they just [\h__\h] dunk it. All right,
we're coming down into the 97s and 700s.
I want to see if it offers me an
opportunity to sell this. Oh my god.
Like, talk about sods law. All right,
let's let's choose this winner. 72 off
sweet. Cannot believe this. The moment I
do the giveaway, it does it. It's
hilarious.
Oh, they're playing with me.
[snorts]
Oh well, whatever. That's a bit of fun.
At least you can see [snorts] that's
what I was looking for. [sighs]
The 50s, the leave of this volume, the
trade down to here. All right. Maybe now
you get something like this. And if we
lose this down here for the day anyway,
I'm done with it. Whatever. [\h__\h] it.
It's a bit of a laugh. But you can see
like the the market moves in certain
ways. This is why. So you'd be looking
to resell 15 here if they stay heavy.
That's what I'd be looking at. Or 15 all
the way up to this level here. 30. So 15
to 30. You'd want to see buyers get
trapped in here. 72 off suite. Are you
here, my friend?
72 off suite. Are you here?
Spy is holding PDC. It's very very
strong that from spy.
You would need to see buyers get caught
here. You don't want to just sell it.
You need to see buyers get caught here.
72 off suite. Are you here? I'm going to
give you 30 more seconds to let me know
you're here.
Otherwise, we're going to roll it.
So, they're coming right back up to VWAP
again. If they don't reject here, then
there's no downside to play. You need to
see sellers step in versus that point of
control and VWOP.
All right, we're going to reroll this 72
not turning up.
So reroll in five 4
2 1.
Teresa Teresa won yesterday.
There's one very lucky person. Teresa,
are you here?
Are you here? Teresa
bedtime.
Let me know you're here.
There you go. Same as yesterday, Teresa.
Um, just email me. I'll send you a link
for the course. I'm going to make a note
of that now.
So, info@flowzone trader. Send me a
picture of you logged in.
[sighs]
Okay, let me set this up.
Okay, just type FCT once in chat. We'll
give away an Apex account. Give you guys
a couple minutes.
>> [snorts]
>> Please don't spam it, guys. Please don't
spam it. It will automatically pull you
out if you spam it. You only need to
type it once.
Most of you are being very good here. A
couple of you have spammed. Just don't
spam it because it it automatically
pulls you out and then you won't win it.
So, you're not doing yourself any
favors.
>> [laughter]
>> We won't let Teresa win this one. She
won yesterday. She just won again. She's
not allowed to win this one. Okay. If
she wins, we reroll it.
Okay, let's pull this winner. Five,
four, three, two, and one.
Spearhead Media Group.
Are you here? Spearhead Media Group,
let me know you're here in chat.
There you Yes, you are. Nice. Okay,
Spearhead, just shoot me an email, okay?
info@flzonetrader.com.
Send me a screenshot of you logged into
your YouTube so I know it's you. I'm
going to make a note of your name and
you can have a free Apex account.
uh any size account you want
and I will sort you out with that
straight after the stream.
All right guys, happy Friday.
I hope you all have a good weekend.
Um look out for the newsletter. I will
do it after the close today. It will be
in your inboxes for tomorrow morning for
those of you in America, tomorrow
afternoon for those of you in Europe.
All right, make sure you go through
those key levels and everything I talk
about in there. It will help you with
your sentiment for next week. I will be
back here next week trading with you. I
will do a uh try and get an educational
video up this weekend for you on using
footprint on Trading View because I know
lots of you have been asking about that.
All right, so we'll try and get it up
for you guys. And have a good weekend.
Make sure to get off the charts.
Remember, this is just a job. It's only
trading. There's a whole world out
there. Try and be nice to people,
especially you
people on stream which give me a hard
time. I'm having a hard time enough as
it is at the moment. I don't need extra
pressure when I'm here trying to deliver
you the goods to make some money and
help you for free. All right? So, try
and be nice to people. Karma will come
back your way. You're nice to people,
people be nice back to you. You'll see
your life will be a lot better. All
right. Peace and love everyone. Have a
great weekend. Love you all. And uh
don't forget also those of you in
Discord, there is uh a competition right
now for a free funded next account.
Those of you on YouTube, go over to the
community page. There is also a free
competition. All you've got to do is
answer one question and uh at the end of
this month, we will pick a winner. All
right, take care.