Morning
team. Welcome back. Welcome back to the
show. Hope you're good. Wild moves. Wild
moves happening in the market right now.
All right. As the rotation continues,
you can see if we uh just move to the
daily here. Here we go. Okay. And we're
still and we remain still inside the
weekly range. Right? So if we think
about the Monday count, Monday, Tuesday
set the high low of the week. We had
continuation yesterday uh which is what
we played to the downside. Right? The
break of the low volume node which is
some reason gone missing. Where is our
volume? Oh, we're going to have to put
this back on apparently. So let's see if
we can uh get the anchor to go back on
from January
last year.
Let that develop. Okay, so we found a
bid.
All right, false break underneath. Came
back to the EMAs, closing right back at
this bundle of EMAs, 50 and 20. And this
gray box is a low volume note. Don't
know why the volume isn't showing, but
for whatever reason, it isn't right now.
It's struggling to show it. Then we
start to drive higher, okay,
in this GlobeEx session and we're coming
right up to where we started all of this
move yesterday. All right, so right back
into the Wednesday open, Wednesday high.
If we can find a bid above that and we
base, all right, there's a chance to
come and take this out. You can see the
Ballinger band is trying is desperately
trying to start turning
and we have all these stops up here at
26 or 125. That's kind of the area that
we're looking at. The easiest thing or
the nicest play today will be if they
stop rotating and they just offer a dip
somewhere into sort of this 830s would
be good. All right, something like this
for a continuation trade higher, but we
will just have to see what these guys
offer us today. This is a big move off
the lows. All right, so 300 point rally.
Why? Well, we've had earnings this
morning. SMCI had good earnings. So
because of that offer Taiwan
semiconductors you're starting to see a
rotation back into the chip name. So
they're starting to get some relief. So
the likes of Nvidia etc etc are starting
to get a bit of a bid. So we will go
over that as we go through the
individual names. Once we look at the
profile on the hourly we can see what
we've done here. So this is your
developing weekly profile. You can see
yesterday right we failed outside the
previous twoe range right here. Right.
We were short yesterday morning from
here for this move down. We've come all
the way down almost tested this old
naked point of control which we have
back tested already. So, it's no longer
naked and we found a bid and we closed
back inside. All right, back inside to
the current weekly value area low and
the previous week point of control.
GlobeEx has reclaimed it all and we're
back up to the current weak point of
control. I mean, it's a mess, folks.
Like if you don't think it this is a
mess, this is a mess. All right, this is
a mess. This is a massive liquidity
build out. All right, we need a break
either side for a continuation.
Otherwise, we're going to keep doing
this rotation. So, we have to be
careful. I would say it's a pretty
bullish move overnight. The key part
coming into this big huge PC here, right
here. So, we're getting stuck. You can
just call it sort of 900s and just
above. The easiest move in my mind will
be a dip. Now I am watching the edge of
this shelf into 860s. Interested if they
held the shelf if not down into previous
week value area low. And do we catch a
bid around there? 850 to 800. Let's call
it. Do we catch a bid around there and
start to do this for an upside move? If
this is just all too thin and too much
of a reaction and we instantly lose. All
right. If we instantly lose previous
week value area high and we stay heavy,
then we're going to get this again and
we're going to rotate all the way back
down into the 700s. All right. So, those
are the two things I'm looking at. Do we
catch a bid between sort of 850? Let's
call it Yeah. 860, 870, and 800s or
820s. Let's just call it 8. Let's
measure this out. 870
to 830s. Do we catch a bid in there on a
pullback or do we stay heavy? The other
option is if we keep driving, then we're
going to have to look for a pull back to
hold point of control and don't really
love that trade. I'm going to be honest,
not leaving ourselves much room. But
there we go. That's what we're looking
at. So either this move here, maybe a
little false break and something like
this. Maybe a shove this morning that's
absorbed. If we just keep shoving, you
want to be very careful buying into this
because at some point they run the stops
and then they collapse the whole thing.
If we lose previous week value area high
and back test it and stay heavy then
this move back down into previous week
point of control previous day value area
high etc etc for the rotation you can
see flow zones on the hourly are trying
to turn positive or they have turned
positive but we are extended away from
them overnight what did we get well Asia
went sideways
and then we got into London which
started to rally and we've pushed that
rally higher now based off earnings.
Okay, let's have a look at some of the
broader market and what we're seeing.
You can see this strong trend here
developing. Even if you just wanted to
put a trend line on. All right, we are
very very strong upside right now. Do
not be fighting that trend right now.
All right, yes, we're coming into a key
area. I agree. Previous day high,
previous week high above into previous
point of control. Yes, lots of
resistance, but we're very bullish.
You're not seeing this market roll over.
And you're seeing the same
in the ES. So here's the ES and
obviously this has a relative strength
overall. All right, if we compare where
we are on a daily ES looking to break
out every time it comes up into these
kind of levels, it's being sold off. The
question is, will it do it again? This
is one, two, this is the third time
visiting up here. All right, dips have
been absorbed. We talked about it
yesterday. There was a buyer on the tape
all day yesterday. Even when we moved
lower, there was someone trying to
absorb the tape. Well, if he's held on
to his position, if that was
institutional buying, then he's very
comfortable right now looking for a
breakout, isn't he? So, we need to be
aware of that
all those moves higher. But yeah, it
looks comfortable here. Let's have a
look quick look at the ETFs. Think about
the levels. I would imagine there's some
gamma exposure at 695 on the spiders.
And we can mark our gap fill underneath.
Where's that at 90? So, gap fill at 90s
will be nice if it offered that. I very
much doubt it wanted to do that today,
but we will see. Same on the cues,
right? Coming into some big levels.
reclaimed the 25s and that gap filled
basically down to 1950s. I I just can't
see this market wanting to do that. I
mean, it's possible. We've done it
before. Um we did it a lot last week.
This will be an instant buy opportunity
if we even dare to come that low, but I
find it somewhat hard to believe.
Dixie rallying as well this morning. Um
that's a strong move off the Dixie
trying to get back to that 100 spot. If
we have a look at the VIX, all right,
got crushed that false break of 18. we
talked about it got crushed back down
into some old support here. And he's
moved all these again.
Okay. So, if we start losing a bid on
Dixie, expect this market to continue to
move higher. Let's have a look at MAG
because that's the interesting part this
morning. All right. You can see this
dip,
this undercut here. This dip got
absorbed yesterday. We are potentially
building this liquidity to try and
break. Apple has been one of the weaker
names. Um, but we'll see. We'll see.
We're still just stuck inside this,
right? But if we can get back over the
60s, maybe Apple's got a shot of like
starting to catch a bid. It's been weak
for a little while here. You can see the
turnaround starting to happen. Amazon
the same. Right. There's your box. We
break, we retest, we break, we retest,
we stay heavy. We flush yesterday. We go
sideways. Here's your twoleg. Can it get
back inside this box? That's the big
question mark right now. Can we find
acceptance back inside some of these
ranges that we've broken out from?
Google looks good. That is a strong
look. This is the kind of thing that I
would like to see. All right, that's a
strong look from Google. All right,
false break. Came back, retested this
old box right here. All right, found a
bid. That looks pretty good to me.
Google showing some strength.
Meta a little bit weaker here. Still
boxed in down here. All right. So, the
rest of the market, remember, has
already started to do this. So, Meta is
still weak. Still relative weakness on
Meta for those of you trading it, but we
are gapping up, but we have a little bit
more weakness there. Microsoft trying to
do the move. This is what we've just
talked about. It's failed from here. And
that was from a bigger failure point in
a downtrend. Can it now start to hold
bids and try and break out? Big question
mark over that. And Nvidia, these are
going to be the important ones. Catching
a bid of SMCI like I talked about. All
right. 180 big level. All right. False
break so far. And that's a decent gap
up. Two $3 gap up. So, we'll be watching
for a break of right here.
All right. 88s
will be a decent break even where we are
right now. Really, 86s and 88s. But we
get through 88s or if we hold a bid
through 87s and 88s, then we're back
into that old range, which will be
important even if even if it just closes
up there. The important part is what
happens when we get up there. But yes,
catching a bid, like I said, off SMCI,
the earnings coming through this
morning. Tesla, same story. So much of
these having the same story. There's the
box, there's the failure, there's the
undercut, there's the pivot, there's the
hold. Can we get back inside? That is
the question. If we fail that and
retest, market will might maybe roll
over this squeeze this morning. So,
that's what we're watching for this
morning. All right, that's what we're
looking at this morning. We can have a
look at some of the broader names that
probably caught a bid as well. There you
go. Oracle filing a bid off that SMCI.
I'd imagine AMD as well. Yes, AMD
catching a bid. So, all the
semiconductors catching bids here this
morning, which is going to help tech.
I'd say the broader market. I think uh
did JP Morgan have earnings this
morning? I'm pretty sure they did. Let's
have a quick look there.
Pretty sure they had earnings. Yeah,
they did. I think they beat as well or
they've got them coming. This
Yeah, 5% rise. Yeah, they beat as well.
So, slight gap up there. So, you might
get some breadth moving with it as well,
given that um if the banks start to go,
then ES will look good with the broader
moves in the market. All right, let's
zoom this back in.
Let's get us set up here. All right,
already breaking out.
Wow, look at this. Even since I've been
talking. Jeez, man. Market does not want
to slow down. I would not want to be
buying the top up here today. Um, it's
just one of those. If it goes without
me, it goes without me.
That will be it. All right, folks. So,
that's kind of the setup. Um, I would
love a retest of this area here. All
right, this is uh areas of interest for
me to bid off. It very well might not
offer it. All right, we're coming to a
bump in the road here. I'd love to be a
buyer down here. I'd even consider some
of these areas here. Otherwise, we've
got to I've got to wait for it to break,
hold, and go.
Those are the opportunities today. Um
you know, it's unfortunate, folks, but
we are driving. You know, we are
400 points higher than where we closed
yesterday. I don't really want to buy an
extension like this without good reason.
So, that's what I'm thinking about and
looking at. Hopey that helps you guys.
This is in a squeeze. This is definitely
a giant squeeze. All right, 2 minutes
here before the open. Go through your
prep work. If you've got any uh
visualization you need to do, breath
work, anything like that. Make sure
you're sized properly. Make sure you're
not chasing this market. Make sure
you're feeling mentally and physically
fit and able to trade. If not, back off
and just watch, right? The market will
be here tomorrow. Don't be forcing
anything.
Yeah, I don't trade with music in the
background because I think it's probably
annoying for you lot. That's the main
thing.
Definitely wouldn't be trading with any
music that I used to play in the
background. That would be uh very
offputting.
Okay, let's just give this market 90
seconds or so, whatever it needs.
Morning all. Not going to be able to go
through the uh all the good morning
calls. Too many of you in here. Morning,
Bella. Hope you're doing well, Bella.
Hope the trip's going good. Um, smash
that like button nice and early, please,
folks. We will be doing some Apex
giveaways as always. So, let's smash
that like button nice and early. Codes
are down below. FCT for all the prop
firms other than take profit trader. You
can just use code plone there for 40%
off.
All right, open coming up here, folks.
Just over 30 seconds.
Lucky we get that pull back. I'm looking
for
would be nice.
I'd like that pull back before we get up
to those 26ks
ideally
starting now which is good. Hopefully we
can get a nice blush involved in this
level here. 835. Make sure I've got
everything marked out.
All right. Three, two, one. Here comes
the open, folks. Here comes the open.
Let's see. Are they going to keep
squeezing or are they going to be kind
and give me a pullback to get involved
in? Here comes the squeeze. Straight
upside missing taking out those highs in
that first drive.
Here we go. Come on, baby. Down you come
for me. Be kind. Be kind.
Instantly absorbed here. We want lower.
Watching ES into PDH here.
There's PDH on ES. Let's see if we can
come a little bit lower still. First,
please market.
If they reclaim New York, I'm going to
have to think about taking a long.
There's the push into New York. No
reclaim yet. Just to shove in. Yes.
Bouncing off PDH like we just talked
about.
No rush here. Just waiting to see if we
either drift lower or if we do reclaim
New York. I might be forced to buy high.
It's not what I want to do, but
definitely don't want to be left behind
today, but hopefully we can drift lower
first.
Look at the mag.
All the mag gapping up. So, I keep
getting stuck at this uh New York open
so far. This red block, right? We keep
getting stuck there. Not finding
acceptance over it yet. I'm not looking
to play the short down into here. I want
to wait to see if it can offer me the
long.
You guys do what you feels right for
you. I'm not looking to play the short.
I would much rather look to absorb a
long.
Still not through that New York open.
If they get through that New York open
and they base above, there's a chance
that they squeeze and take out the
highs. But I'd much rather it came
lower. going to offer a much better
riskreward.
Morning, Tyson.
All right, watching here. Here's the New
York open test again.
Still stuck there. So, definitely some
passive selling up here so far. I think
we will probably squeeze through it once
we go.
Watching for a trigger. Still stuck
there. Still no base above. Still
getting sold into it. Still a passive
seller.
Google flat miss out the rest of the
market. Nvidia the big winner this
morning over 2% up. Here's the New York
open again. Still can't get through it.
Still testing trying to get through
those 20s.
Break above there and we can potentially
squeeze if we can break above and hold.
Here it goes. Here we go. Here we go.
All right. Are we going to get some
movement through here now?
Can we base and absorb? Lots of buyers
coming in here, but not seeing a base
yet. So, still waiting. Outlier delta at
21s. Still no base above. Don't want to
force my way in. Just waiting patiently
here.
See the importance of that blue line.
That is your New York open. That's where
they keep getting stuck. Buyers keep
coming up at here and trying to force
the way higher and they can't base
above. If they based above, I'd be
willing to potentially look for the
move, but really I want to be a buyer
down here. It's the best opportunity
possible.
They're having another go up here in
these 20s again.
Google gone red now. Oracle gone red.
I just look around at the ETS. Vic still
dying.
nice and patient. I want to wait and see
if we come down here. Maybe some of you
are looking to play this short down to
there. It's uh it's a possible move.
It's not what I'm looking for. I want to
be a buyer in the market if we can
rotate down
because we're gapping up over the
previous day's value. So, I want to try
and be a buyer. Sellers just got caught
at those lows at 88. I'll tell you that
right now. 197 lot just got caught at
the low of day there or current lows of
88 in the New York session. So if they
don't break below that there is a
squeeze potential.
He's right at 88 that big seller. They
need to get under that for him to feel
comfortable. They're going to have
another attempt down here. Are they?
Well hopefully we can get down into
here. It' be very nice if we could.
What is the edge of this that we talked
about earlier? 60 60 or 70, wasn't it?
870s
down into 830s is a sort of level. So,
here's the 870. This is the edge of the
big point of control node. And if we
lose this, then hopefully we come down
into 830s, maybe even deeper if we get
very lucky. Right, Google starting to
sell now. So, Google starting to sell
off 3/4 of a percent down. Rest of the
market still looks okay. Here's the 70s
test. Can we come down into the 30s and
below?
Yes, still holding up against the
previous day high. I think it is. No,
must be previous week gap.
So, 70 is finding a bid so far. Like we
talked about pre-market.
If we lose 70s, there's a chance for it
to move to 30s.
There are some bids at 50s and 45s,
but this 70s just based on current the
current weekly profile, the developing
profile is important. I'm going to get
rid of this trend line because it's just
in my way. Can't see what I need to see.
And I think if we get back over 90s,
there's chance to move higher.
Watching this carefully. That's where
that big seller came in. Remember,
there's the move to 90s. All right. Can
we base above and squeeze?
So, there's the attempt to go through
90s. Still trapping buyers up there.
Still a passive seller here at 900s.
No base above still. So, same as
earlier. Buyers are attempting, but not
getting a base.
Not going to force my way into this. I'm
going to be very, very patient.
that was the London high 30s. All right.
The edge of this
830. Yeah, I really like that area. I
like where we are now and I like 830s.
Both of those have opportunities.
They're trying for the 90s again and
they're going to try and push 900s if
they can basic up above 90s which they
still are unable to do. So sellers still
dragging this market down. How we
looking on the mag oracle trying to find
a bid. Google trying to find a bid.
Here's the drive back down towards
the 70s again. Still waiting here. Just
patiently waiting here.
Spying to its VWAP. By the way,
cues are under the VWAP. Coming to the
5day now
almost into this level of interest.
If we lose this level of interest is a
long way down. So we we really if we're
going to be uber bullish today, I'd want
to see them absorb between where we are
now and there. Really
feel slow, man. Maybe it's just me
slower today.
Where's that delta? 90 is big level.
Still a big level for a break above and
hold. Still not been able to do it. Yes.
is trying to absorb its 5minute flow
zones at that previous week high
level of interest
60s now we got on the tape we got anyone
hanging 30s, 800s, and 845 so far. Not
much at 30s. Not a little bit of action,
but not much.
Spy still holding B up for now.
Some volume on here
right watching these 90s 80s and 90s
this block here we start to drive
through 90s that's the level where the
delta keeps uh building up
here's the attempt back to 80s. Can it
get through 90s? I'm watching 90s as a
trigger. If we're going to base above
and hold, I'm interested. Here's the 90s
release. Okay. In looking for the tap of
value area high at 10s. Can we get
acceptance through this now? I'm
watching New York open. So, just
scalping my way through this.
I'd want all dips to hold 90s now if I'm
going to scalp through this.
And let's see. We're at value higher on
the session. 08s. I want to see if we
can get acceptance through that. I know
it looks different to you on here. I'm
just judging it off my Ninja Trader
right now. Uh value area high on Ninja
Trader is 908s. I need to find
acceptance above that for a squeeze out
back towards the 960s.
Really, we've got to get through those
920s again. So, this dip here needs to
hold otherwise I'm out and it would just
be a scalp.
That 20s was the trigger. Sorry, the 80s
was the trigger like we talked about.
Okay, cutting this now. It's just a
scalp to start the day. What did we get
there? 30 points or something. Let this
build out more.
Back to PC on the day. Market doesn't
know what it wants to do right now.
Microsoft's gone flat. So, this is the
problem. You got chips going okay. The
rest of the market does not look good.
Apple's gone red on the day. Google's a
quarter% down on the day. Microsoft's
flat on the day. I'll give you a
readout. Tesla 0.71% up. Nvidia still
pushing 2.24% up. Remember 88 break is
the key. It's almost there. It's not too
far away. Microsoft 0.07% up. Meta 0.44%
up. Google 0.20% down. Amazon 0.60% up.
Apple 0.02% down. Flat flat to red on
the day. This is the problem. It's the
rotation right now.
SPY still at its VWAP. Still at 5minute
flow zones. still has 5day underneath
for protection.
Sellers failed to break lower there.
Worth noting. So, it's definitely failed
to break lower there.
Okay, 30s again possible here if they
can base above 80s and 90s. This is the
edge. You can see this outlier delta
keeps stepping in at 90s. We're not
getting follow through over it.
You have to be patient today. If you're
going to be a buyer, you've either got
to join when the Momo's there or wait
for it to drift lower into the zone.
What I don't want to do is be buying the
high of day, but I don't want to miss
the move either. So, it's a tricky one.
You can see value area low keeps
developing here and we're not finding
acceptance lower right now. Remember, we
are moving value higher from yesterday.
We're back inside the current week's
value and we talked about there's 70s
pre-market
or 70s down to 30s as a key level based
on current weekly developing value.
They're going to have another go here by
the looks of it. Value area high on the
session is 900. So the question is can
they get back above that?
Yeah, New York view up is set to 930.
Set to the 930 open. We're right at this
level at 90s. Can we find acceptance
through here now and start driving?
Look, I'm interested in this, but need
to be very careful. We cannot get
through these 900s yet. If we start
getting through 900s, we can look at the
New York Open 920s. And if we get
through that, we can look at a really
nice squeeze out.
So, we are now basing above that 80s,
sorry, the 90s, which is good. We need
to get back through the 900s through
value area high which is 9006 and find
acceptance over 24. So looking long here
to see if we can get a continuation
squeeze higher here. You need to be
aggressive with stops today because this
market is not showing momentum yet.
Here we go. Beautiful. There's the New
York open. Let's see if we can really
start squeezing now.
Lovely.
So through value into the New York open
this level here we need to find
acceptance above this now we find
acceptance above this New York open it
means all the cash players will be
positive and we can look for this drive
all right so we're long from here we're
looking for this now for ads
so the dip today was 70s to 30s we
talked about pre-market really good his
previous week close so you can trim some
into here you can reload if this next
dip holds
Market catching a big mad mag starting
to go green which is good. We can hold
above New York open it would be good but
definitely above 910s would be ideal.
Above 910s would be ideal here.
Really nice. All right let's see if we
can start squeezing out here. Really
good. Come on market. Let's do it. Let's
be nasty. Let's trap all these shorts.
Really good. Let's go, baby. All right.
Looking for a squeeze out through high
of day. And let's see if we can hold on
to this now. Get through this gray box
and see if we can get all the way up
into here. That would be the best
scenario. But we're going to trim on the
way and pay ourselves.
So, if you go back to earlier this
morning, I was talking about the 70s
to30s dip. The 70s to30s dip. That was
all because of the current week value.
All right, current week value. We had a
big node here and we're holding. So,
trimming some into this. Please do not
be greedy because if they want to fail
this, they will
beautiful.
That delta at 90 was key, right? Once we
got back above the 90s, we I needed two
attempts there, but we got it. And
that's where we've now moved uh point of
control now is sort of 87 90s and 87 on
the day. So, nice decent move there. Not
too bad.
50 60 points. We'll take it. And we're
only what 15 minutes into the day.
If we can't hold PC, I'm not willing to
uh rebid on it.
So, my PC is different to this what
you're looking right here. Uh this level
here. We need to hold this. We need to
hold this low volume node and this. If
it can't hold this, I'm not interested
in longs. I'll let it come back down to
here. If we can hold that, I'll consider
rebidding here. Looking for this.
Just be careful because we're in the
middle of that 15minute orb.
Yeah, lots of you grabbing it with me.
Nice work, folks. W's in chat if you got
a piece of that. Not bad. I can show you
my scorecard start date. All right, just
two two uh accounts.
right? Starting to build on that PC,
the 10. Would like to see us get back
above that New York open.
No worries, guys. Yeah, nice work. Nice
work. That all came from planning at
pre-market, right? That came from the
plan of pre-market understanding that
this was potentially an area to buy in
if we're going to be very aggressive.
All right. So, there's the leg down.
There's the pullback. There's the
squeeze. Can this pull back and hold now
for acceptance higher? We don't know,
but we positioned long for it. We don't
know what the market's going to do. In
truth, we can position for it. We don't
know what it's going to do. We have to
put risk on if we're going to make
money.
If we lose this though,
let me do it. If we lose this though,
then I'm re re-entering down here or I'm
interested in re-entering down there, I
should say.
Mad really doesn't know what it wants to
do. It's the one thing. Nvidia now
through the 88, 3% up on the day. So,
Nvidia having a really good drive. Chips
look good. AMD 5% up on the day. Oracle
lagging behind. That has been the cheap
the weakest one of the bunch for a
while. people worried about debt issues
there.
Be nice if this market could just make a
decision. When I look at that daily, I
just think it looks
absolutely awful, doesn't it? Not
necessarily today's chart, but just the
last I mean, I'd say even say all the
way back to the early December, the last
two months look terrible. They look
terrible.
Okay, back to this New York open. Can
they base above New York open, above
value high, resqueeze out, and really
start to go for the day? Can we get
above all this and start to go for the
day
moment? It's struggling.
I would not be holding on to longs if we
lose 90s here. 890 is that sort of delta
area. You do not want to lose that area.
You lose that area probably means we're
going to take out low day.
Here's the 90s test.
QQQ back to V1. Yes. Above it V1.
these 900s
apes asleep here this morning.
PC just above at 10. It's protecting
that now. We can't get back above that.
So, not really interested in this dip
there at the moment.
It's that sort of 90s test again.
That doesn't look good. I don't think
I'm going to touch this for a bit and
just let this do whatever it is it wants
to do. Looks nasty.
Looks nasty right now.
Maybe they come down for these 830s,
870s.
Opening range low is 50s 30s as an area
of interest. 24-hour VWAP is all the way
down at 800s.
What do you want to do market makers
trying to find a bid at 1560s.
Here we go. So, moving lower. So,
leaving this alone like we talked about
once it lost 90s. I was not interested
in holding a a thing in in this. No
interest. We can have a think about how
we act down here now into previous week
value area high.
But we wouldn't want to lose that. If we
lose that, I'd say there's a good chance
we trade 740s.
So, if we lose that, we're probably
going to trade 740s. So, don't want to
just bid against this, especially if the
market's going to go back into a
rotation again like it has. I don't know
the last week or so that you guys have
been trading it.
Mag starting to not look so pretty here.
Apple just about holding on. Amazon just
about holding on. Google now 0.62% down.
Meta 0.07% down. Microsoft 0.30% down.
They cannot make up what they want to do
with this market as the rotation just
continues day after day after day.
The truth is we have not been able to
print above a key level since
November 5th
and we haven't been able to duck under a
key level since
well December 17th. We've been stuck
really since then. Just stuck sideways.
I'd argue even the way all the way back
to sort of November 25th.
Just stuck sideways.
Will be a range trader paradise right
now.
There's no bookmap settings, guys. I
don't understand this. I say it every
day. Just use Why do you need a setting
on bookmap? Bookmap's showing you what's
happening inside the candles. You don't
need to change anything really. You
really don't. Only thing I change on
bookmap is my DOM.
Big buyer keeps stepping in here and if
he doesn't get his way, he's going to
become the liquidity to move lower. So,
let's see. Back inside point of control
now. Back inside value. I'm going to
test these 890s again. 880s, 890s maybe.
That was the pivot. Remember where I
said I don't want to be long if we start
breaking that. They've held this dip in
front of pre previous week value area
high right now. It's it just looks a bit
ugly to me if I'm honest with you.
Testing this 80 and 90 we talked about.
That's where we broke down from.
We're midpoint of the range. It's not
very pretty. So, here's the ' 90s test.
This is where we broke down from. Do
they resell this again?
If not, if they cause a squeeze, we're
going to test 900s, 915s, and New York
open. They're still trying to sell these
uh 90s like we talked about.
Testing these 90s.
I don't really fancy the long in this
now. Second attempt at this. This is the
same trade we took earlier. I think I'm
actually going to wait.
Do not want to get caught in this. So,
we've just hit that next shelf, the
900s.
Next stop is 25s again. They're trying.
They're trying to lift it again. Max's
trying to rotate again. And Apple's
trying to go red to green. Oh my god.
What are you doing, market makers?
Let's see.
I actually want to join if we squeeze in
base. I don't want to play midpoint of
range. Let's see if we can squeeze in
base. I'm really interested.
Big buyer stepping in here. Back to this
New York open now.
25's next level. That's the New York
open. Can we get over that and value
area higher? And can we push value on
the day higher?
I don't know, folks. All I know is that
this is messy.
This is messy.
Hands off mouse for me. You can see how
the profile's developing now.
Going to remove this. I know this is
here, but it's just taking clogging up a
bit too much. So, getting stuck at this
node again.
So, these 90s to 900s, 910s is the
rotation right now. Buyers really, they
want to hold this dip. They should have
held it last time. This is what I was
talking about. They have to hold this
level here. Why can't you draw it on me?
You have to hold this here, right? For
this. If they lose this, we come lower
again. Right. This is what we're
building. You're looking to do to grab
that. If if they can find acceptance and
hold this and this, then everyone in
here will get caught. If we lose this
and we keep digging down, this is where
they're going to want to test. So, it's
you got to be like, see money, take
money. Look at the EMAs. Look at VWAP.
Everything's flattening out. It's not a
very pretty day right now. We've had
some nice trades this morning. I think
two two attempts it took. Made some good
money. Don't be forcing it. We're still
very early in the day. New hour coming
up in five minutes time. New hour, new 4
hour. And we can think about what
happens next once we get that maybe
back to the 90s. Back to this node
83ish.
So 90 down to 80s is where bulls need to
step in. And if they fail to step in in
here, then I think they're going to be
in trouble again
right onto that node again we just
talked about. This is where they have to
step in. They don't do that. I think
there's more of flashing them up.
Grabbing a coffee. Yeah, I don't blame
you.
3 minutes until the new H4.
Actually more like two minutes now.
So they're trying to bid here like we
just talked about. Point of control now
here though. So it's fair value on the
session. We've got a tight range right
now guys. We've got 109 point range this
morning in the New York session and I'd
say most of that range has been
happening around where we are. So, we're
not finding
too much acceptance
uh lower and we're not driving higher.
We're just building out volume right
now.
If we think about the New York session,
it's just it's just standard Dshape,
right? D-shaped profile range. So far,
until we find acceptance below or above,
we are just rotating. Most of the volume
is taking place from 25 I mean
technically down to 72 but I'd include
it down to there. So you know you got
like 50 to 75 points range. That's all
we're looking at right now in this
session. There's not much to play with.
Let it develop
again.
Just over 30 seconds to this new H4.
Your VP looks different. Um, I didn't
change anything either, bud. I don't
know. Maybe just a bug. Maybe just need
to hit reset on it.
Have a look at the breed out of it.
Healthcare getting hit this morning. Eli
and Lily big loser. It's probably might
be the weakest one in the market right
now.
Um, BSX, Eli, Lily, the whole healthcare
sector is red. So that's dragging ES
down.
Yep. Lost that same level again. Now,
here's the new H1 H4,
I'd say. Uh, yeah, those 900s are a big
level.
the H1 transition
95 8.95 is a big big level.
So, back to point of control again. I
know it doesn't look like it for you,
but my PC is here on Ninja Trader. All
right, so I'm just reading Ninja Trader
right now. We cannot get through that
890. It's been the level all day. That
has been an over under level all morning
so far.
How do I know to enter a trade? Well, it
needs to fit my system. At the moment,
we've got flat EMAs. We're inside a
D-shaped profile. We're not seeing
momentum. We're seeing sideways action.
So, it's not what I like to trade. If
you're a range trader, maybe it's what
you like, but for me, it's not what I
like. I like a continuation or a big
failure. I don't like sideways.
So, my EMAs are flat.
It's possible if we start to lose this,
they come back down here and look to tag
into here.
Remember the trade today was this to
here, I think. I think that was it. And
that's all we all we've taken. Two
attempts at it. Maybe this attempt and
this attempt.
Leaving this alone now. We're starting
to potentially break down into here. And
then I'll see how we respond if we get
down there.
Mag cannot make its mind up. Honestly,
it's one of the big problems right now.
We've been rotating out the mag for a
couple weeks and in back into like small
caps and stuff, which is why you're
seeing bids on RTY,
but you know, we were short yesterday on
the Q's because we were the weaker
asset. We're long today on the Q's
because we're the stronger asset. Q's
almost 1% up. The rest of the market,
you know, ES half a percent up. YM 0.42%
up. RTY 0.73% up. But we can't get
going. The gap's just too big to sustain
right now by the looks of it.
You think we come to 800s? Um, I mean,
yeah, that's the box we've got lined
out. It's very, very possible.
It's very, very possible.
He's
gone to sleep.
We're going to have to play a game or
something, guys. If we If we're going to
stay inside this opening range, we're
going to have to do something else. Oh
my gosh. There's your opening range.
There's your Dshape. We are just stuck.
Did anyone play long overnight? What a
squeeze that was. What a squeeze that
was. You got that?
Are we heading towards VWAP? Well, we're
stuck between the two VWOPs, aren't we?
There's your 24hour VWAP. There's the
New York VWAP.
Point control shifted lower again now.
So 70 now. PC trying to test those 90s
again. Can it find acceptance over 90s?
Can we push value area high up today?
Nvidia starting to squeeze. Just got
another alert here. So, it's back
through the 88s again.
Question is, can it hold up here on
Nvidia and find acceptance? We cannot
get over these 90s. It's the same level
I've been talking about all day. this
level right here, right? We've held no
dip into it, right? We've squeezed
through it, flush through it, squeeze
back through it. We cannot base above
it. Market, right, to get going has to
get back above this and find acceptance.
At the moment, every push into here is
being sold, right? So, it's possible
they're going to do this with it. I'm
not going to trade that because you're
trading at not a great location in my
mind.
There's a seller trying to walk this
down now. He's just moved from 80 to 75.
He just got absolutely wrecked there.
Filled now. There we go. Let's see what
he does. Does he step back on the tape
again? Get squeezed out.
See all this volume building up. Just
I'm just leaving this alone until we
leave this volume and we see what we do.
Maybe we come down to this blue box and
the value area high from yesterday from
previous week. Maybe we stay heavy under
that and we start rotating in previous
week's value again. I'd rather we didn't
do that. That would be an awful move
right now. I'm not interested in doing
anything.
Sam, I'm ready to go with your course
and start my journey. Yeah, I look
forward to working with you then, my
friend.
Honestly guys, for me, this is just a
leave alone part right now. It's good to
just sit still.
Let it make up its mind. Let it either
come lower or break higher in base. But
I don't want to bid against it, that's
for sure. Not when we're going sideways.
And there's a good chance they want to
wash these guys out because they can't
get back back above these 90s which we
keep talking about.
Is it a must to work with the bookmap?
No, it's not a must.
It's not a must. Plenty of people trade
without it.
I feel like I'm trading blind without
it. There we go. Here's the wash. Let's
see if they come down into here now and
how they respond. If we don't hold
previous week value area high, I would
have some concerns here.
Like in this, we call it like a block, a
level, right? If we don't hold this
area, I'd have some concerns because I
think then possibly, you know, a trade
back down to 755, 750s is possible,
right? All the way down here. It's not
ideal. So, they really bulls what we
want to hold dips here. Otherwise, we're
going to go back inside the previous
week's value area range, which is like
it's just not ideal. If we're going to
do that,
there would be a node. Yeah. 770
770 750
674 It's less than ideal if they let go
of it. We go back in rotation of
previous week's value.
Alex, how do we get better at planning
and building an overall narrative? I
tend to struggle with that. Is that one
of the hardest things to develop? Um,
it's a good question. Uh, I think it
just comes from time, understanding how
the market likes to move, understanding
what your playbook is, and being more
focused on the higher time frames,
understand like, are we attempting to
move the market higher? If we're in an
auction, remember the market's either
looking to find value or it's in value.
It's either looking to find new value or
it's already in value currently. All
right, you could argue we have been
looking to find new value because we are
leaving previous day's value. If value
yesterday was in here, right, we left
that value, which means we've decided
that's too cheap. Now, we're trying to
see, okay, are we finding value here? If
the answer's yes, we're going to go in a
rotation here. If we're saying, hey,
this isn't good value, then we're going
to come down, right, and we're going to
look for value somewhere else again,
maybe where it was before. It's
understanding that process and using,
you know, SNR off hourly levels, daily
levels, things like that to understand
what the market's doing. I mean, all you
have to do right now, if you zoom out on
a daily, what are we actually doing?
We're not doing a lot, are we? All
right, we're not doing a lot. This is
what we've done on the daily for a
while. You can see we have failed to
break about above this since early
November. We're in one of these, but
we're tight. All right, so we are
creating liquidity. At some point, we
will use that liquidity, but right now,
we're in liquidity creation by going
sideways.
Okay, back up to these 90s again. So,
that last dip was a little wick below.
Back to these 90s again. If they get
through these 90s, they have the
potential to squeeze. They've got to get
through and base. Otherwise, we're going
to continue this rotation. So far, we're
not finding every time we come down
here, we're not really finding
acceptance. Yes, there's a lower low,
but this uh for me is probably a bullish
liquidity build right now. Right.
At some point I expect to see something
like this happen and then we can join.
Yeah. Uh my fillet ITM. Yeah. If you
just like go down towards the end of the
course, there's like a module on Discord
that will tell you what to do.
Blew an account this morning. LOL. The
market is moving awful. Well, it I'm
going to give you some tough love there.
It means you've oversized or you played
something that isn't there because the
market hasn't moved that much. Market's
moved 111 points and most of that's in
the 70 point range. So, if you've blown
an account, you've tried to take too
many trades or you've oversized.
Yeah, I see that JD. I mean, we're
actually in the stronger asset. Well,
RTY now this what I was talking about.
The rotation the last few weeks has been
out of tech back into small caps and uh
like bio and stuff like that position
positioning for increased market breath.
Last year the breadth was awful right it
was mag well I'd say in the last two
years was awful mag 7 doing all of the
work all of the work came from the mag
7. So we're trimming mag 7 at the moment
and we're rotating into everything else
and at some point they will come back
into mag 7 when they deem the market's
ready. Okay, back up to 80s. So, we're
going to test 90s again.
Waiting to see if we trigger a squeeze
and a base up. Yes, back into its VWAP.
Uh, daily and hourly are my go-tos.
Hourly I I call like God, right? God
hourly is very very key for me. Even a
30 minutes can be very very useful.
Like right now, if you look at the
hourly,
we're just stuck, right? This is this
week's developing profile. We're stuck
in here,
right? We can't find acceptance above.
We're not finding acceptance below.
We're in this huge pocket of volume
from this week.
It's why the 23s are key. 90s in this in
current days
uh levels are key and then 23s which is
up here. This is the edge of that when
we talked about that rotation. It was
840s,
right? This is that huge current week
volume node. This is what we're trading
between right now. If we can find
acceptance above this, we can go for it
right now. That's all we've got.
Alex, how long does key levels stay
relevant for you? For example, price has
moved through last week's value area
high multiple times this week already.
Still key though. Still key because if
you look, it's moved through it, but
once we moved through it, what did we do
overnight? We This became key, right?
You can see as an area. Don't use it as
a direct area as an area. This is where
we held found bids and and went over,
right? Still key. It's best way of
putting that is it's key until it's not.
It's still it's still a big level. If we
lose it, then we just look for the next
level down
back into this shelf here again. These
90s again. I'm just saying the same
thing over and over again because the
market is doing the same thing over and
over again. Here's the test of 90s. And
the question is now, do they squeeze and
base above or do buyers come
aggressively in here and get trapped?
Here's the squeeze. Can they base above
though? Answer so far is no, but
aggressive buyers came in and got
trapped again above 90s. So, we've got
passive selling up here between 90s and
900s. It's absolutely clear they cannot
get through that level.
Am I looking for shorts? No.
New to the channel? Morning Rob Miller.
I'm going to get a refill on my tea
while this is doing absolutely nothing.
All right, be right back.
There we go.
Holding there.
Okay. Same stuff. Still true.
Still in this shelf.
This probably the hardest part of the
game, especially for you guys who are
new, is just sitting still. Just sitting
still. Not wanting to click. Nothing's
going on here, folks. So until we get
that break above and a base or that dip
below and a hold, I don't really want to
do anything.
Interesting. Let's now see our acts back
into the same level.
New York right there.
So key, man. So key this level up here
with sentiment.
When it passes the first 15 minute
range, low and high, are we looking for
a fair value gap? And when will we know
whether to take long or high? I don't
know. Go and ask your crazy mentor cuz I
don't know what uh what type of setup
that is.
I'm assuming you mean an opening range
break with some momentum,
but that's not my setup.
That's awesome. Great work, man. Passing
those lucid accounts. Fantastic work.
They are trying to hold bids here at the
moment. This is where we're stuck.
Right. Here's your node. This is where
we're stuck. All right. This is the
volume build. I would love to see it do
this. And really, I'd love it. Above
here, we really get going. Right. This
is This is a bigger node on a weekly.
Above here, we really get going.
Can also be a trap level.
spy right at its view up right now. Can
it find acceptance back through it? Can
we get going today?
Possible that we've seen some
accumulation at these lows.
Here's the drive-thru. Buyers caught
there again. Still a passive seller up
there into 900. 90 to 900. still passive
selling up there that every pop through
they are just passively selling. So
we're seeing big buyers step in and
they're just getting the door shut on
their face over and over and over again.
And that is the story so far today.
How do I do my entries? I it depends on
the setup, but I normally limit in
and I'm waiting for the market to show
me it wants to do something. At the
moment, there's there's quite literally
nothing to do, guys. There's there's no
entry, right? I'm just flat. I'm just
waiting. There's nothing going on right
now. If we can find acceptance above the
here, then I'm interested. But it's
going to be a scalp to start because I
don't know if this door gets shut on my
face here. All right. So, if we are able
to hold here, I'm interested.
I'm also interested down here. I'm
focused on the longs today, even though
we're sort of sideways and melting, but
I'm not going to like force my way in.
It either shows me exactly what I want
to see or I just have those first two
trades for the day, and that that's also
okay. Like, you can't
you cannot sit here and be like, I want
to buy it, so I'm buying it. That it's
just [\h__\h] stupid. Um, pardon my
French, but like if you're clicking
buttons for no reason, it means you
don't have a setup.
Those in Discord will know. I've just
done a competition. I said, I want to
know your setup. Tell me your A+ setup.
Because if you can't describe your
setup, what you're looking for, you've
got no business trading to be quite
honest with you.
What do you mean? How do I choose my
Maybe I'm not understanding, Eddie. Can
you explain a bit more? How do I choose
my entry?
But all I want the key level one side
trapped and then I'll play their pain.
That that's that's basically what I do.
Whatever time frame I'm looking at.
So like if this is a key level, right?
We talked about I think we talked about
70s to 30s, right? If this is a key
level, what do I want to see? I want to
see in here aggressive sellers, right?
Market sellers in here. And I want to
see limit buyers absorbing the tape. I
want sellers to get trapped, right?
Ideally under this level here because
we've got a node and I want to use their
pain for them to stop out to go higher.
And then I'm going to take profit on the
way up because I know right now we've
got buyers trapped above this level
here. That is the same level if we go to
an H1 that I'm looking at. Right? So
I've got confluence of this node right
here. Right? So I have to trim here. If
we find acceptance above that, we can
get going. But at the moment, we can't.
The moment is just a rotation. So, that
is pretty much the same setup I'm always
looking for. Pretty much the same thing.
Whether it's a reversal, whether it's a
continuation, it doesn't matter what it
what it is. I'm looking to play people's
pain.
Back to these same levels. 90s again.
That's great. Green otter. That's great.
like one one losing day in 3 weeks is
amazing. That's not just great, it's
fantastic
and you're only negative 135. That's
very good discipline. Like that is good
trade. I'm telling you that is good
trading. Too many people think a
negative day is bad trading. If you've
stuck to your rules and you've lost on
the day, that's good trading. What's bad
trading is if you haven't stuck to your
rules and you've won on the day or you
haven't stuck to your rules and you've
lost loads on the day, that's bad
trading. sticking to your you're
sticking to your discipline. You're
you're telling me that you've won pretty
much straight for 3 weeks by sticking to
your rules and you've lost one day.
Well, that is going to equate to a very
very good profit factor as as long as
your RR is decent and you're going to be
fine.
Paul, I use it on an M5 and an M1.
That's what I use it on.
Oh, man. That's very kind of you to make
that donation. Thank you. I'm so glad
you're back. I started following you not
long ago, but I found you to be a very
good valuable person. Here's the '90s
test, guys. Although we can say that our
community relatively small, I can assure
you that we have been thinking about you
a lot in the past period. God bless you.
Thank you so much. Okay, here's the
squeeze up to the next level.
Let's see. Do they fade this? Now, we're
looking for dips to hold and otherwise
we're looking for the 25s if there's a
way of getting involved in this.
So this was the move we were looking
for. Is there a way of getting involved
in it now? Is the market going to be
crawled and go without us? ES
approaching high of day already. I want
to be involved in this now. This is what
I was looking for. We've left 20s now.
Sorry, we've left 90s. We're approaching
trying to get to those 20s. Remember the
20s is the edge of the current weekly
developing profile. Right? So this is
exactly what I just talked about. We
leave here, we will try and trade to
this node. If we get through this node,
we will trade up towards here. This is
the edge of the current week. If we get
through this, there is expansion
possible. The question is, is it going
to offer us an opportunity to get
involved? Sometimes we can see the
levels and it will not offer us an
opportunity to get involved. That is
very, very possible. If dips start to
hold here into 90s, I'm interested. If
they don't hold 90s, I'm simply not
interested in playing. It just means
it's another false break and we come
right back down to what we're starting
to see. So, no trade here for me. It's
unfortunate. Like so we missed this
light drive up, but there's like I said,
I would have wanted to see it do this
and it would have been TP1 and then hold
for TP2 and we would have got stopped
back out
and needs to give above the open. Yeah,
the opening print. That's literally it.
That's the edge of that open print is
the edge of the current week's
developing node. It's a massive level.
All right. So, this is another good
example for you where it hits the
levels, but where's the entry? For me,
there's no entry there. I mean, maybe
some of you like buying breakouts.
There's certainly no way I'm buying a
breakout here for that move.
So, we're just flat,
you know, and there's clearly passive
selling on the tape. Like, how many guys
got stuck in there? 267 lot, 243 lot, 24
lot, 12 lot. They all joined from that
90 break.
It's just messy, folks. Like, this is
barcoding,
right? This is barcoding, really.
Oh my gosh.
All right. Oh my gosh. Can't do it. Here
we go. All right, we're barcoding here.
Most most of what's happening is
happening here. Right. Right in here.
It's okay not to trade, guys. I know you
might be frustrated. You're probably
leaving this channel and you're jumping
around to other guys who rip their
shirts off. Oh, we're going higher. No,
we're not. We're going nowhere right
now. All right. So, just learn the
discipline to sit still.
Learn the discipline to sit still. It
will be obvious, right? It's going to be
really obvious when it wants to do
something. It's gonna scream at you to
get involved in it.
So, you got the So, sorry, Alex Damian,
I hope I've said your name right. Right.
You have a bearish sentiment and that's
that you want to go to the new week
opening gap and rejected it. So,
shorting retesting it again.
Okay. Like if that's your system, then
that's exactly what you should be doing,
my friend. There's nothing wrong with
that. If that's what you're looking for
and that's the system that pays you, do
what the system pays you, right? Like I
said, this is just how I trade. This is
uh there's no um set rule. There's no
one way to trade
the moment. If you just think about
value, if you're buying all dips here
and selling all pops here, you're pretty
good today, aren't you? Buy that, sell
that, sell that, buy it back. Buy that,
sell that, sell that, buy it back. All
right, there's your range. Remember
earlier D-shaped profile
once we leave it
might be more.
I am going to um
just mark another little node out which
is right here.
Watch the previous week
here. Same node.
Okay,
so another attempt to get back down into
here now.
Thanks, Alex. Still down trend. Uh,
yeah, so far on the day, but like zoom
out.
Right. I don't think we're backside yet.
I think this is a big drive.
All right. And we can absorb here to
rotate here. Where would I consider it
backside? Well, probably if we lose
this, right? That's where more weakness
comes in is under here. That's why I'm
being cautious. Everyone looking for the
short. That's why I'm being very, very
careful because this can be a big
buildout to go higher. All right.
What's the main move here? It's been
leaving previous day's value, isn't it?
Leaving previous days value. In fact,
it's also left previous week's value.
Previous day value area low. We found a
bid. We reclaim previous week value area
low. We take out previous day value area
high. We take out previous week point of
control. We take out previous week value
area high. We drive up. It can find a
bid here. This is a strong move which
might have still have continuation. And
yes, maybe we drift down into here, but
I would need to see that first, right?
That's why I'm being very careful about
thinking about a short. I'm not uh not
too interested in the short right now.
I'm going to be very honest with you.
All right, initial balance now set 111
points. might be this purple line on the
bottom of your chart.
Felix. Um, depends on the type of
account, but I would just scale right
back to micros. Two to three micros
gives yourself plenty of room on a 50k
account.
Plenty of room.
If you go to minis, unless you're like a
good trader and you're looking to like
aggressively pass them,
which is, yeah, I'll be honest, I often
do that. I can be aggressive with minis
on evals, just get them past um because
I don't want what I would call time
decay sitting in them too long, but I
wouldn't advise that unless you know you
can you've got a good shot at pass them
if you're a newer trader. And definitely
if they're PA down to micros. Okay,
here's the rotation again. So another
failed look below underneath value area
low still being absorbed. We have
negative delta. So sellside delta came
in there at 860s. So 860s we had when is
this guy
190 lot at 860
sellside and we've got 194 lot buyer sat
there now. So that's a level right now
that I'm watching carefully to see if we
interact back down there.
Is there a trading system that isn't
yours that you're envious of? I don't
have envy for systems. It doesn't matter
what a system is. All you got to do your
job is to make money. Job is not to
gloat, not to to shout on social media.
Your job as a trader is just to make
money and get off the charts, right? So
that's it. I'm quite happy doing that
and I love teaching my system to other
people and developing it and refining it
and that never stops. Like the moment
you think you're smarter than the market
is the moment you will lose it all.
Okay, guess what? We're back in these
90s again.
to be this is so tight.
Boring, isn't it? When it's like this.
It's how the market used to be all the
time. So slow like this. Big seller
coming in here being absorbed.
90s is such a big level, man.
Is the blue and red chart bookm? Bookmap
is this uh what is above me right now.
All but map is is a is a visualization
of level two, right? That's all it is,
right? 90s testing again here.
Passive sell is S sat up at 900.
Every time it feels like it wants to go,
it doesn't though. It's so weird. Yes,
looks pretty good. Still not through its
New York open. Mag looks all right.
Other than Google. Google the only one
red now. 0.85% down. The rest of the mag
comfortably in the green now. Is their
follow through through the 90s? And can
it get over the 20s? That's the bigger
question. Can it get over 20s? No.
Follow through over the 90s again.
VIX just basing down at low of day. Here
we go.
Right. Let's see where we go at 900s. Do
they squeeze now? It's looking a little
bit better
through the 900s. 915's lifting up here.
They're bidding 900s now. Can they get
follow through and hold those 900s for
the whole number?
They're bidding 8580s. I want to see
them walk up through 900s if I'm going
to join here.
They're still bidding 90s and 80s. I
want them to see them. I want to see
them walk up. I don't want to see them
sat down there. Come and join this tape.
Here they come coming to try and join
the tape.
Move up, please, Mr. 90. Move up,
please. Okay, here comes the 10ens.
Looking for this now for expansion over
value high. Here we go. Right, I'm
scalping some out here straight away.
Let's see if we can get to the 25s. I'm
going to trim more at 25s, right? Or
into 20s and then I'll see if we can get
a runner to go. So, if we get over that
New York open, we know that's the edge
of the current week profile.
And if we get through that, we're going
to search for value higher. Come on,
baby.
Trimming some here. Come on, baby. Get
through it. Get through it. Trimming
some here into this. Come on. One left.
I'll read add if we base above previous
day highs here. New York opens here.
We've got to get through it. If we don't
get through it, I'm just going to cut.
They are offering 30s and 50s now. I
just don't want to see this dip back
down underneath value area high which is
903s.
I really don't want to go back into that
mess that we've created for the last few
hours. I want to see expansion now up.
ES almost taking out is that pre-market
high or is that open high?
Okay, it's just got pre-market high
left. So ES making a new high in New
York. Not taking out pre-market high
yet.
We look good. This is better. Just make
sure you're paying yourself. Jeez, we
had to wait ages for this.
Do not want it under value.
Come on. You've got a node there to bid
off. Come on,
please. Someone big step on the tape.
Come on. It's so slow.
All right, ES taking out pre-market
high. Just be careful here if it's a
force break on the S because we'll dip
back inside if they do that.
The S already at its initial balance
high. Come on. You're so slow, dude.
You're so slow. Right. It needs to bid
here now. Otherwise, I'm cutting. Needs
to bid right here on value area high.
This node here that you're looking at, I
need I need to see it bid here. I don't
want to risk all the way back down into
this. needs to bid here or I'm going to
cut.
Nice.
I want the next push to take out New
York open. The blue line on your chart
and previous day high, the red line on
your chart. Need to see it take out that
on the next push. I'm not going to sit
through a two-leg pullback in this
current position. I'll cut it and read
if I have to do that.
Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go.
Turn it on. 50s coming up. Put the
boosters on through 20s to 50s. Let's
go, baby.
Come on.
Oh my god. They got no juice over these
20s. Okay. So, remember, we have to be
aware. The reason I've trimmed some here
is we have to be aware the current week
developing profile. This is a huge
level, right? Once we get over this, all
right, once we get over this, we're
looking for up here. If we get really
lucky, 20s is a big level. 25 is this
edge right here. Yeah, 25 is big, big,
big level. If we can base over that, we
have a shot. All right, if we can base
over that, we have a shot. But we've
trimmed. All right, for this move up
into this, it's not a huge move. What
have we got? 40 point. It's not bad
considering, is it?
Just be careful because ES has taken out
its high day.
VIX trading at lows 1550 out. I'm done.
I'm done. Not holding through that. All
right. Not bad though. Not bad. I can
always read if we start to prove. I just
don't really want it to come all the way
back down into this node here. This is
why I was wanted it to hold this right
here.
So that edge at 25s is a huge level.
The discipline to cut here can always
get back in. That's the other thing
folks like you can always get back into
the trade.
That next shelf is key down here. Buyers
stepped in at 8.87. 87 earlier on this
drive up and a seller got caught there
at 60 65 lot. He got caught at 86 and
100 lot got caught at 78. We're still
bidding off it.
Did I not give that enough room to
breathe? Possibly.
Possibly.
That's my indicator telling you to buy
there. That's That's the flow zone pro.
is actually where I bought. I didn't use
the indicator for it, but it is where I
bought because we'd reclaim flow zones
and we broke through 90s and we trapped
sellers. So, the key for me was we
trapped sellers right here. Someone
asked me earlier about it. We trapped
sellers into 90s. So, once they were out
of position, we got this squeeze up. We
need to break back above 25s now to get
up to those 50s. It's it's doable. If we
rebase here, it's doable. What you want
to see here is a new buildout of
liquidity in this range, right? Low
volume nodes held as support. That's
good. We've reclaimed this. You want to
see this. You want to see this move
here. Now,
you do not want it to come back down
into here. It's got no reason to come
back down into there. We've already
trapped. It should not be coming back
down into there again. It's tapped it
once. It doesn't need to do it. It's
already filled. There's a buy side
imbalance in here. It's already filled
it. It doesn't need to to do it again.
There is actually a sellside balance up
at 15s that you need to be aware of
right here.
I enjoy your show. I did well today.
Awesome. Nice work, man.
That chart. No, that's Ninja Trader. the
chart you just saw.
Oh my gosh, it's so slow.
Painfully slow.
It's both. This is New York view.
Daily VW's down here. So why New York VW
up? There's a whole video on New York
View up and the importance of cash. But
if you think about where does most the
volume come in,
where's the volume coming in from 9:30,
right? So where am I interested in? I'm
interested in the average
participation of buyers and sellers
based on where volume comes in, which is
why New York view is important.
chop best. Yeah, is a little bit. Do I
have a video on YouTube chart setup? Uh,
there's one for Ninja Trader. I'm not
sure if there is one for Trading View.
Maybe there is. I'm not sure. Can't
remember. It's been a while. There's
definitely one for Ninja Trader.
Don't think I want to rebid down here.
I don't think I want to rebid it. It's
very possible they hold and rip it, but
I'm not too keen on the rebid. They
should have done the move. The fact that
they rejected 25 says to me that we're
staying inside this uh Vshape. And uh we
all know Alex doesn't like trading
rotations.
Is that a separate VWOP? Yes, it is a
separate VWOP. And you can just anchor
it. You can just use an anchor volume um
anchored VW to the 930 open. I'm very
fortunate. Someone in my community made
us a uh a New York view up for the flow
zone community for free, which is very
kind of them.
I'm either too conservative or too
aggressive. Hence the question, what
your regular position size is on a 50k.
Um, okay. The the problem with that
question, Felix, is you're not taking
into account the potential of the move
in front of you and the ATR. So, if
you're sizing the same for every single
trade, but the volatility is different
and your ATR is different, then you're
going to get caught because if you have,
let's say, a 20 point stop loss every
day, and we're in a day where we're in,
you know, high volatility, maybe VIX is
at 18, 19, 20s, your 20 point stop loss
isn't going to mean diddly squat, right?
So, you have to understand that you
should be positioning based on where
you're trying to get the market to move
from. Now, if you're going to start, if
you're newer and you want to start with
a fixed position sizing, then just size
down and try and understand where the
market's trying to go to. Or if you're
going to be a scalper, maybe you're
you're risking 30 to make 30. I don't
know.
But if you don't understand position
sizing versus ATR and volatility or
where liquidity sat, you're going to
find it hard. I see other traders,
big big streamers put on like one mini
to scalp
10, 20, 30 points or maybe even less,
probably more like eight points at the
start of the day, but they're not
understanding the volatility of that
market and then we'll get wicked out
very quick. So,
thank you. I've been watching for three
weeks to learn futures. I've been a
swing trader and passed two Apex
accounts with your code of your
knowledge and discipline. Nice, Chris.
Congratulations.
In a lucid end of day draw down, if
during your day your account goes below
the minimum, do you automatically fail?
Uh, yeah, I think so. So if you go over
the the hard stop, yes, my understanding
is yes. I think I asked this before, but
is there a setting or indicator that
automatically sets the open
and close for the day? Um,
there probably is. My flow zone
indicator would do it for you, but if
not, you could probably just do it in
the settings, I would imagine.
Um, there's probably a way of just doing
it in here. Status line. I'm sure
there'll be a way of of doing it, but
but uh yeah, there they will without no
question of a doubt there will be a
setting for it. Um
which you could automatically put on you
just just search for it and indicate.
Just Google it and you'll probably find
it. This is why I didn't want to rebid
because they failed that up here again
the 25s. So we come back down to value
area high. If they lose this kind of
area here, there's probably a deeper
rotation. All right, because we've now
had a failed break. And if we lose this
area now, there'll probably be a deeper
rotation.
Vic starting to find a bit of a bid
here. Now
the next pivot for VIX is really 1611.
It's got room. It has got room.
All right. Right. So, previous week
value area high tagged this little node
here tagged. If we fail this then you
know maybe 775 750s.
This is the previous week value area
high. The question is do they bid down
here? I don't know folks. I don't know
if they do. We can just sit and watch
now for a minute. But momentum
definitely came strong off this rotation
of 25s. All right. So, we're 100 points
down already back into this area.
And if we lose this, we've got other
blocks and nodes down below that we can
look at. But question is, are we going
to base above previous week's value or
not? If we're not, it means there's no
acceptance above previous week's value.
Previous week's value comes all the way
down to here, right? And previous days
value area high is here. And this right
here is your gap,
right? So if they lose this, they might
check this. Maybe they reclaim this and
squeeze. If they lose this, then they
probably go gap fill and test these
areas.
because we're in a rotation
right now. We're going to come back
probably test these sort of 60s initial
balance. This is a look below so far of
IB, but it's only been for a minute. And
give it a bit of time to develop here, I
think.
Apple now gone red. Google now 1% down.
Microsoft 0.27% down. Nvidia losing
about a percent off its peak today now.
So, you're starting to see this market
pull back a bit.
Hey Joe, no nothing. No external
indicator works with top step I'm afraid
mate. If you're using top step X which
is I assume what you mean you can't use
a third party indicator. You can only
use what they provide.
Jason just nuked a funded account on my
first trade. Ouch, that sucks. I should
have taken a loss sooner. Well, yeah,
you should have either taken a loss
sooner or under or size down. Sounds
like you're using way too much size.
All right, ES back into its 24hour VW
up. We're around the same point here.
They're not bidding on this. It's an
area of interest,
but I'm not bidding on this right now.
I think this market knows what wants to
do. I can show you my scorecard for the
day. Again, not linking anything yet.
Only my second day back. Nice and slow.
Yeah, Felix. Two to three micros. Just
just two to three micros are all you
need. All right. If you're getting a 100
point move on two micros, it's $400.
That's all you need. You don't need to
be People try and make all the money in
one trade. It's where they go wrong.
It's just like psychopath moves, you
know.
Yeah, I'm I definitely am checking order
flow here. I'm watching everything right
now. I mean, I know there's sellers at
the lower day at 820. I know we've
reclaimed previous week value area high
now. I know there's an imbalance we just
tapped into into uh 40 all the way up to
44. We have a sellside imbalance there.
And I know there's big sellers that came
in at 45. So, that's where their pain
point is,
but we're rejecting initial balance
right now.
So, I really don't want to be counter
trend long at the moment.
They're bidding right now down at 800 is
much below.
Not really.
So, we're back into the GlobeEx session.
The GlobeEx pivot is really 800 or just
underneath. Yeah, 800.
We really lack structure from that 5
a.m. candle. That's the bigger problem.
That could take us down to 760
if we lose the bid.
Still planning to shed the mountain. I
mean, I wanted to go. Um, obviously I've
had to deal with some personal matters
and also
it wasn't we had some landslides here,
so all the roads were blocked, so you
couldn't actually get up to the mountain
and it's been like 80 here since. So,
probably probably all the snow's gone
already. I would like to get up to Mount
High at least for a day or something.
Yeah,
you and every coach out there say not to
copy trade, but the last four weeks or
so whenever I try my own thing, I get
cooked. When I copy coaches, I win.
Maybe the nuance to copy trade strategy.
I'm not sure what you mean there, Joe.
As in not copy trade, copy me. I mean,
it's important that you don't copy
people because you have to be in charge
of your own money and you're going to
have to learn to stand up. Like there's
nothing wrong with being in a group and
like saying this is what I'm looking at
and understanding and learning,
but I think uh you've got to understand
the markets because at some point you
might want to travel the world and be
able to trade on your own instead of
watching some 40-year-old with long hair
on YouTube. Okay, so here's the drift.
Potentially, if they don't hold a bid
here, potentially they come down here
into the 760s.
still going. So 18 sorry 1586
would be the next drive and then that
would take it to 16s.
Question here is do we reject previous
week value area high now? And if we do
that means we're going back inside
previous week's value which means this
there's no acceptance above value. If we
reclaim previous week value area high
it's just a dip below that's like a sign
of strength. But how we act here becomes
I'd say pretty important now for
sentiment. Are we looking to move value
area high higher or are we saying hey no
this is no acceptance. So this level
here is very very very important now.
Yeah you're right. CVD is showing
divergence. It's showing stronger
aggressive buyers but we're moving lower
which means there's more passive sellers
taking control of the market. So it's
negative divergence right now.
since 9:30.
The buyers are being aggressive and
losing.
Price is moving lower. Delta is not.
I'd say this value area high is a
massive, massive, massive level. Do we
reclaim and squeeze or do they just keep
rejecting it?
Here's the reclaim. Now, did they base
or not? Just tapped into that imbalance
that I talked about maybe five minutes
ago, the 40 to 44 imbalance. You won't
see it if you use fair value gaps
because it's not there, but it is a
legit imbalance which just got tapped
into.
Nice, Jason. Great work, man. Awesome
work.
If they catch a bid here, it's very very
thin for the drive up. That's the one
thing I would say. If they catch a bid
here, it's very very thin. We're
starting to try and base over previous
week. Value area high. Value area low on
the day is 56es. Um, don't want to be
early to this. So,
if we base, I am interested. They've got
to start basing, building out, trapping.
There is shorts caught down here for
sure underneath 20. There are shorts
caught underneath 20 which is what right
here underneath 20 there's sellside
caught in this c in these candles here.
This one right here
but otherwise
not convinced.
So we can't even get through that
imbalance of 40 I keep talking about.
It's got to get through that to uh have
a chance of doing anything at all.
That initial balance big level 40s. It's
the IB. Remember? Whoa. Someone sold
that IB.
Someone tried to aggressively sell that
IB and sellers got caught at the lows
there. This could be interesting. Now,
if enough sellers just got caught in
that flush trying to play the follow
through, we might start squeezing. It's
got to get back through the IB now. 40s
to 45s big level. There's an imbalance
there. We have the initial balance
there. They just tried to reflush that.
Sellers just got caught again under 20s
on this long wick under 20s. They came
aggressive and got caught again. So,
we've got like three lots of sellers
down there now. Caught under 20. So,
bids need to hold over 20 and start to
accelerate upside for a squeeze.
Otherwise, we're not going to see
anything happen.
Here we go. Here we go. All right. Can
we get going here now? Looking long
here, trying to accelerate higher.
Want to get a uh move back through value
area low minimum. Really want to see us
bid through 50s. Uh delta there was at
60s. We had a big seller at 60s. Once we
get through that, we're going to start
squeezing and we're going to have to
hold bids. Can't hold bids yet.
Feathering into this very small size.
Stops very, very, very tight here.
I do not want to see a flush below 20.
Like, we cannot go down to 20. It's as
simple as that.
There's IB. Come on. Print through 45s,
please. Come on, market.
Come on, baby. Come on, baby. Get
through these 45s.
Through 40 through 45.
Suck a nut.
Ah,
let's go.
All right. Straight straight into target
one.
Beauty. What a beauty.
All right, let's see if we can trail
now. I want to see it hold a bid over
56s. We just took out all those stops
just got wrecked like I talked about
through the 45s. Damage is done. We're
locking in no matter what.
And let's see. We've repriced this big
kill candle. We've gone straight back.
Look at the same level. What do we talk
about earlier? The ' 90s. All day. These
90s. These flipping 90s. So, we've got
to see a bid over that if we're going to
see acceleration. So, we were long from
here. Trim some here. If we get
acceleration now, it's going to be
really fun. But like, pay yourself like
don't expect it, right? Pay yourself as
if it's not going to happen.
What the hell happened? I'll tell you
what happened in here. A big seller
stepped in under 20. He readded on this
flush, right? So, he now had a huge sell
position here and once we broke the 45s,
he was offside. So, he stopped out and
that increased
the push higher. As simple as that. So,
we had a look below initial balance into
our key level, the blue box that we've
had. We reclaimed and now we start to
squeeze. Now, can we find acceptance
over 90s now and go all the way up?
That's the big question. Now
that's the big question.
Back up to these N. Just trying to see
if I can get a runner to go here. Trying
to see if I can get a runner to go here.
point control now sat at 73. Value area
low down at 56es. So you want dips to
hold that this node. I don't really want
to add in this node. It's not the best.
This rotational node again.
What was the blue box level? It was uh a
big node from the previous week.
I'll show you.
It was this guy right here.
Yeah. So, I was trading against that.
Can that hold? That's a dip down against
it. And we went wick to wick. So, it
lined up with confluence node here. Wick
to wick for pivot, right? Resistance
becomes support. And we look to
accelerate if we can. So, we might look
for a giant inverted head and shoulders
here if we can really get going. All the
stops are still up here. doesn't have to
do that move today, but that's what
would be nice if we can find acceptance
higher. Really good through the 90s.
Come on. Through the 90s. We'd like to
go through the 90s. Continue this
squeeze. Can we get up to 25s? Can we
get up to the 25s? If we get through
25s, I'd love to see acceleration.
When I speak, I'm mostly 50/50.
Definitely not.
Go to the I'm I'm not even going to
bother. I'm not even going to answer
that.
You, my friend, need to learn to trade.
There's always two options. I'm telling
you, if we do this, it does this. If it
does this, it does that. That's how the
market moves.
[\h__\h] me. I've been very clear on what
I've been looking for today. I've been
looking for longs off the blue area
because we've pushed value higher. I've
literally gone over it since 9:15 this
morning. You [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] me. I give you gifts and that's the
type of [\h__\h] I get.
Oh my god. I don't have the patience for
it. All
right. Looking to see if we hold 90s
now. All right. This node looking to see
if we hold 90s now. Here's your if
button. Maybe if we hold that, I'm
looking to do that. If we lose that, we
will rotate cuz that's the rule of the
market.
[\h__\h] me and [\h__\h] off to someone else
then.
Piss me off, man. No thank you. Just
like yap.
All right,
let's see. I have no patience, chat. I'm
going through a lot right now. You piss
me off, I [\h__\h] You get banned or I
leave. It's really simple.
Yeah, I think we're going to go 50s.
We've got we've got loads of bid of
offers up there. We want to come and get
up there.
Trying to just manage this last guy now.
Let's see if we can get through the 25s
and then we're going to accelerate
through 50s if we can get to 25s. So, if
you haven't trimmed some, you might want
to trim some into this node up here.
Come on. Through the 25s. Let's go. Turn
the boosters on.
I'll consider an add- on a dip down to
90s.
If it holds, if they trap sellers down
there,
we're trading right value area high for
the day. So, if we're going to go in a
rotation, that's going to be annoying.
Sellers just got caught in that last
little flush to 900s. Someone's
absorbing, trying to step in to be
aggressive. They're trying to step in to
be aggressive. I just want to see a dry
325s. I think we'll get a really nice
squeeze if we can drive 325s.
So interested if they hold dips into
8.90. Not interested really underneath
that.
And I'd like to see an acceleration
325s. We haven't pulled back yet since
this drive up. So, I'm expecting that
they might well pull back.
Yes, right at that IB high.
See if it bases and squeezes New York
open and IB high here on ES. That will
help us if we get breath to the market
increasing. Sellers keep adding at the
lows of each M1 right now, which is a
good sign. They're being absorbed,
stagnating here a little bit. Might be
that they flush this down to the 90s.
still being absorbed. Still passive
buying there.
So everything under 9 or around 900 is
being gobbled up. I'm not adding up
here. I want to see if we come back down
to the 90s. I'll consider it. But I want
to be careful now because we've been
trading between two nodes. So I don't
want to leave one node and get trapped
between these two and rotate between
these.
So I don't want to add up here. I'll
consider an ad down here. It's not
ideal, but I will consider it. Um
because maybe we can do this.
Alternatively, and I'm not going to add
up here, but alternatively, if we just
squeeze through this and come through
higher day, that would be ideal. That'd
be the most ideal scenario. Not even
offering me an ad and just keep
squeezing
Yeah, the bidding 900 95s and 890s and
880s. Don't really want it into 880s.
It's right back down into the midpoint.
I'd like to see these passive buyers
walk up. Not seeing that right now.
Really nice if went back through 88s as
well. Here we go.
Come on. Retake IB, please.
Yes.
Want to be careful because we're
straight up, but I want a straight down.
So, here's a move to 90s. This is what
I'm aware of.
For me, it must hold 90s. Don't want it
into this thick of this node. And it's
got to protect in front of 90s. I don't
want to be in the thick of that node
because we were straight up.
Big starting trying to find a bit of a
bid. So, I want to be a little bit
cautious here. Not adding yet. Just
waiting to see. Remember, we're
positioned all the way from down here.
So, can give this a little bit of room
on the runner.
Good absorption there again.
Great absorption there again. Sellers
came flying in there at 900s and haven't
won. So, I want to see this accelerate
higher now because we just trapped all
the sellers. Here we go. Go, go, go, go,
go. You just trapped them all. Let's do
it.
Push. Break 25 and start squeezing.
Let's go. You just trapped them all.
Let's go. Let's go. You've done your
job. I don't want you to redip back in.
Not looking at a red dip back in. I want
this to accelerate now. It's just done
the job of trapping them all. They just
all got caught under 900 there. They
tried to play the break, the 900 break
lower and they got caught. Now we're
holding value area high. I want to see
this break higher through 25s. Please
just go through 25s to 50s. Make my life
easy.
Seller here at 14 getting filled. Come
on. Go 15s and then go 25s. Come on. No
more dips. Go go go go go go. They're
still rebidding 900. I really don't want
it back down there. Don't want them to
test these guys.
starting to lose faith in this.
If they don't hold this now, I'm going
to cut. This is the pain point for them
right here, right now.
Can show you what I'm looking at map.
All right, I'm probably going to cut
this here. All right, so these sellers
here are the guys that got caught,
right? They just tried to take the break
underneath. We used their stops to drive
higher. We are now retesting their
stops. It must hold this and accelerate
higher. Otherwise, I'm out. I'm out now.
I don't care even if they send it
higher. I'm not willing to sit through
this. We had They had the chance to do
it. They just trapped everyone. Maybe
they retrap again on a second leg, but
I'm I'm good with that. I can always
read in back over 25s. Need to uh stick
to my rules, manage my positions
effectively.
All
right, I'm going to take a bathroom
break. I'll be back.
Okay,
as you notice guys, I have zero patience
right now. And when you go through what
I'm going through, neither would you.
So, I would advise you not to test me on
stream because I'm doing my best to be
here. If you test me, I'm likely to
blow.
just joined and subscribed. What stocks
you trading? We're trading futures. This
is the NQ
level. Holding well. Yes, holding very
well actually. Maybe I was a bit uh can
give it enough room. But for me, the dip
I think was it this one. Whichever dip
that was, one of those dips, it trapped
enough in. It shouldn't it shouldn't
need to do it again.
Shouldn't need to do it again. So, you
got to be careful if we go in rotation,
right? If we're going to stay in
rotation, it's going to be a pain.
Make sure this lines up. 56 is Yeah,
it's pretty much there. So, that's what
I'm aware of.
It can still absorb, right? The problem
you've got now is if you've developed a
node here,
right, and buyers get stuck here and you
drift down here and buyers bid this,
your rotation takes place in here until
you find acceptance or unfortunately for
a person who got very upset or we will
do that because those are the rules,
right? There's never one trade.
You believe that market can only do one
thing, then why doesn't it always go up
or always go down? It's just nonsense.
could be trapping more for the run to
26116. Yeah, I I would agree with you.
It's very possible. Um but the first
problem is
it could be trapping. It's got to get
through. You've got a big node which we
tapped into this morning 950 to 970 and
that's before you've even got to 26 uh
042, right? I see what you're looking
looking at. I agree with you. From a
swing point of view, it makes sense.
Absolutely it makes sense. From a swing
point of view,
still hasn't broken the orb. Yeah, I
mean failed look below. Hasn't traded
through the top side. Yeah, same as the
initial balance. Still trading midpoint
of IB.
Absolutely. Absolutely agree with you
all saying that
Luna the Luna
Google the lagger today as I was
thinking of Luna because he's looking at
me. Google the lagger today. Here's the
900s again. So they're going to try and
do that move. They are trying to hold
the 90s. They are trying to get that
squeeze up. They're trying to develop
this inverse head and shoulders we
talked about. The problem is you've got
this little node here, right? Get
through that and you've got a shot. Get
through that and you've got a shot. But
you must get through this right here. So
these are the nodes that you're looking
at right now. We can just do them as
gray. Right? One there
and a big fat one here.
Right? These are the nodes. That's the
rotation.
The best day for me. I made 13K. That's
awesome work.
Let's see if they rebid above that or
not.
Here
we go. All right. Rebidding above this.
Let's see if we can go now then. See if
there's a way of getting involved here.
Value area high on the day 12s. I want
to see acceleration through 25s.
want dips to hold now and I want
acceleration through 25s
if we're going to build this inverse
right shoulder and come up to this IB
high maybe accelerate through it.
There we go.
Lots of liquidity at 25. Should go and
take that out. There we go. Come on. So,
imbalance here. We just tapped into old
imbalance from uh 1040 this morning.
That's up to 17. Yeah, 17.25.
We need to trade through that imbalance.
Feeling an old sellside imbalance there.
Once we trade through that, I think we
can really start accelerating. We will
see if it's able to do it.
the top of value there as well. I'll be
careful of that.
16s there. What if I got it on mine?
12elves. Not matching up quite right.
So, this gray box needs to hold now for
the longs.
How long we got left? Ages left. 40
minutes left. I was hoping it was
lunchtime already.
Hey, amigo. Did you was clicking
something already for me? Yeah, I can
tell you what we played this morning. We
played this long here
and this long here and this long here.
Those are the longs.
We left everything in here alone.
And some people have probably added into
this 90s here. So maybe some of you are
still long. You'll tell me in chat.
long for this squeeze.
Maybe they added here and looking to see
if we can do that now. Needs to push
value higher. Need to accelerate.
What indicate so is there on Ninja
Trader that plots previous week value
area high value area low? Um I don't
know if there's something that does it
automatically. You have to I do it all
by hand.
All right.
Still holding well here so far.
Uh, if you haven't checked it out, by
the way, on my community page on
YouTube, there is a competition right
now to the end of the month to win a
free funded next account. Worth checking
that out. Doesn't cost you anything.
Let's get these likes up, guys. There's
over 600 of you watching and there's 200
likes. I am not doing a giveaway unless
we get to 400 likes today. So, smash
that like button. and it cost you
nothing. We're three for three today on
longs. Some of you are still probably
holding longs. I don't think I'm asking
too much to say just click the like
button for me. It's all you've got to
do.
Can't find an volume profile on NT. Um
you have to manually
I think it's in data series. You will
need to create a condition. I can't
remember how to do it off the top of my
head. My head is fried. But uh you
basically need to create a setting. You
can call it whatever your name is, which
starts the volume profile at 9:30 each
day. There is definitely a way to do it
cuz I've done it.
So failing again to break through here.
I think it will come sooner rather than
later. Let's see if I can find the um
setting for you. Hang on.
Come on in.
All right. Order flow volume profile and
then trading hours. In trading hours, I
have it set from 9:30 to 4:00. You will
need to create your own trading hour to
do that. All right? Your own one to do
that. I'm pretty sure I did a video for
it on YouTube. In fact, I know I did.
Um, if you go to my orderflow video on
YouTube, it will show you how to do it.
All right. I I definitely put that in
that video so that you can see how to do
it. Go to my order free orderflow video
on YouTube.
Let me try and find it. I'll post it for
you. And it's in there. I know it's in
there.
Um this one here,
right? If you go on this video, it will
show you how to do the volume profile.
Here we go, folks. All right. Can we get
through these 25s now? I'm looking for a
squeeze through 25s and ideally up to
50s and beyond. Here
we go. Lovely. Lovely. Through the 25s
now.
Lovely. Can we get up to previous week
close which be in the 940s? I'd really
like acceleration through that as well.
So, if you haven't paid yourself yet,
make sure you're paying yourself.
I really want to get through the 50s.
Yes. Doing the job as well.
Just want to see a big buyer step on the
tape here at 25.
I've just wicked everyone out. They have
got a chance to move higher at this
point.
And you'd want dips to hold really this
edge at 14s if you're going to look for
continuation. I'm not going to add any
more here. It's my second attempt.
Uh, Brian, where can you sign up for the
newsletter? If you just click the link
down below or just look in the um either
just scroll through chat and look for
the comments from Nightbot or just go
into the info section of this video,
there will be a link for the newsletter
there. It's completely free. All right,
seller now on the tape at these 22s
taking him out.
They're faffing around here a lot.
There's a lot of aggressive buying
taking place here, which concerns me
because we're not moving higher. We just
had like a 286 lot, 101 lot, and we've
faded back away from that. Don't like
it. I do not like that we haven't
accelerated away from that now. So,
buyers starting to get trapped there at
25s.
I might be done with this now. Locked
that last one in.
I did, but you used a downloaded
anchored profile. I didn't use a
downloaded anchored profile. That's not
what I used at all.
I used the orderflow volume profile and
I create
my own 9:30 to 4:00 which I show you how
to do in there. There's nothing
downloaded for it.
all right definitely seeing those buyers
get trapped up there under 25s now
back to this gray box we just talked
about P
for the day it's also P for the current
week so this is fair value for the week
so it's becoming less and less
interesting to trade around here now.
Still need to get these likes up to 400
on stream if we're going to do a
giveaway.
Would like to give away an Apex account
at the minimum.
low volume node underneath. If they lose
the bid here, we'll flash back down to
the 880s again. That's why I'm not
interested at the moment.
Do I trade inverse val?
No.
go in and out very quick. I mean, I
don't feel like this was a quick trade.
All right, I stopped out here. What was
that like?
I don't know, like 15 minutes. We are
day trading after all. and I hit TP. So
if I hit T, I'll hold all day. If it
wants to play bull, but you know, I'll
cut the moment the trade is not making
sense, I will cut,
right? If this took an hour to take
place and we were doing this,
then I would have waited an hour for it
to hit TP. But we did it very quickly,
didn't we? What's been the level all
day? this here 90s and the 25s
and this was the buy opportunity here
once we trapped that was the long TP1
TP2 into here stopped out didn't like
how it's acting I'm not going to hold a
trade if it's not if it's hit TPS and
it's not doing what I want to see I'm
not going to hold a trade right it can
be a day it can be a week it can be a
year it can be a minute it can be a
second it's all depends what price is
doing in front of me.
Just found you. I heard some terminology
at Convergent Trading. Did you study
their program? I have no idea what
you're talking about, Dustin. Sorry, but
if you're hearing me talk, this is it's
not someone's program. This is just
market auction theory. This is it's just
basics of how the market moves. It's
not. It's No one owns this.
Well, not a program owns this anyway. I
don't own this certainly.
Okay, retesting this node and value high
on the session. Running out of time
here. 30 minutes left. New 30 minute bar
coming
in 5 seconds.
Yes, holding above IB nicely. VIX still
trading around the lower days. Not
breaking lower, but just stuck.
Still need some more likes here, guys,
to do the giveaway. I'd love to give you
guys an Apex account.
just stuck here. Those red lines on your
screen. current week's PC,
current days PC. We're absolutely stuck
at value. This is fair value. This is
where the most volume has been traded
since the Sunday open and the most
volume has been traded today.
Exactly. TJ
feels like it wants to go. Definitely
feels like it wants to go through the
25s. I'm not I'm no longer in it. I give
it the opportunity.
We're running out of time.
probably done. What we going to call it?
Yeah, it's just because we're pack we're
packed in, guys. If if you just zoom
out, look,
doesn't mean it won't break. It's just
like look, let's just start from top
down analysis like we start every day,
right? Daily,
here's our range.
No acceptance above this.
No acceptance below this. Dips yesterday
held this. Okay, here's all the range.
No acceptance below. No acceptance
above. No acceptance below. No
acceptance above. It's the same back
here, right? I know this is bigger, but
this is why we are so packed in here. If
we break and the bowls start to expand
and the market decides, hey, you know
what? We're going to go risk back on in
tech. Then we'll do this move. The
question is here, right? Is this a big
old bull trap which is instantly sold
back down or do we base and start to do
the next leg up? Is this accumulation
for the next leg up or is it a bull trap
that sells? That's why we're stuck. If
we move down to from a daily
into an hourly,
right, you can see
this is in the old contract. This is a
two weeks balance range that we left.
Remember, the nicest trade we had here
at the end of last year was this here.
We left a two weeks balance range and we
faded away from it. Ever since then,
since I don't know, mid December, we've
just been trading between this range
here and this range here and building
out. Look at this. 1 2 3 4 weeks going
nowhere. We are quite literally going
nowhere in the market. All right. while
we build out liquidity.
What does it say about me that my best
trading comes when I'm trying to lose
money?
Oh man, that's the worst. E, so you've
made too much. You're trying to lose
more. You're trying to lose some and
you're making more. The best thing to
do, mate, is not worry about um the
trade. Run your costs up, right? If you
want to do that, run your costs up. Buy,
sell, buy, sell, buy, sell, buy, sell.
Just non-stop run your costs up. That's
the best way to do it.
Have I been naughty today?
That's a weird question.
Like I said, if we lose this, we'll come
back down to this gray box. Here's the
90s again. And the dip in the 90s again.
Right.
We're running out of range to play with.
Yeah, that's a that's a good idea,
Ransom. That's a good idea. Something
with a bigger spread and flip them.
That's a great idea. And hit the market
each side. Buy the market, sell the
market. So you you get filled the spread
and you get filled the cost of it. It's
a good idea. What would be a good one
for that? Like cattle or something? Is
it something that lacks liquidity with a
bigger spread?
Soybeans, maybe
coffee,
something like that.
All right, market's not moving. If we've
got enough likes, I'll do a giveaway
now. We'll do it a little bit earlier.
We need 12 likes.
12 more likes and we'll give away an
Apex account.
You had some. Yeah, I see that, Steve.
Well, it was the it was the reflush on
silver, wasn't it?
After that giant squeeze out.
There was the flush last night on silver
taking out the squeeze rebid. I don't I
really don't think this thing's done
yet. From a macro perspective, it's got
more juice in it. I mean, maybe they
offer a reshort and then accumulate. Um,
bit like gold did
uh a while ago when it had its flush
moment
down here.
Right, there's the flush off the squeeze
reaccumulation. It takes a while and now
we're basing above the old high on gold.
They've they've got room in them.
They've got room in them. Honestly,
they were just trailing from box to box
right now. All right, we got enough
likes. That's awesome.
Um,
hey, that's awesome, Ransom. So, Ransom
just said, "The first thing I've ever
won in the trading world was an Apex
account from me, and they've a week ago
or so, probably a couple weeks ago
because I wasn't here last week, and
you've now passed it, and you're trading
the PA. Congratulations, man.
Congratulations. That's That's awesome.
All right. Don't type anything yet,
guys. I haven't set it up. Let me just
set this up. You all
feels like it wants to move higher still
to me. But that 25 level is a huge
level.
Huge. Huge. Don't type it yet, guys,
because if you type it now and when I
set it live, you won't be entered. And
just give me a second to set it up for
you. Hold on.
Okay, FCT, type it once in chat. I'll
give you guys a couple minutes to do
that
and we'll give away a free Apex account.
Guys, a couple minutes to do that.
30 more seconds, guys.
Don't worry. Any anyone that's spamming
just gets pulled out. Like, Nightbot
just pulls them out. Like,
it automatically pulls them out.
Everyone that spammed, you get removed.
market trying to have another go here
towards the 25. Yes, looks better. Okay,
put in the winner. Five, four, three,
two, one.
Teresa, hopefully I've said that right.
Teresa 19 or 9481.
Are you here, Teresa? Here's the market
having another go at those 25s.
Teresa 1 19481, let me know you're here.
and give you another 30 seconds. If you
don't let me know you're here, we're
going to reroll it.
Yeah, there you go.
Awesome. So, you know the deal. Yeah.
Email me screenshot
info@flzontenttrader.com.
Just screenshot of you logged in. That's
all I need. Nice one, Teresa.
Congratulations.
Set this up.
All right, let's give away a free intro
course as well.
Give me a second to do that, guys.
Okay, if you're a complete beginner,
you've never traded before, this is a
good course for you to start on. All
right, it's a 2hour course, introduction
course. If you win it and you already
know how to trade and don't want to do
it, you can give it to a friend. It's
only worth $99, but it's a nice place
for you guys to start. So, I'll give
away one of those. Just type course once
now in chat.
You need to try type course in chat if
you want to win that.
Give you guys 30 more seconds here.
Sorry to hear that, human craft. Hope
hopefully tomorrow you have a better
day. There hasn't been too much follow
through today. We're still inside
profile trying to expand it higher, but
we can't get outside the weekly weekly
profile range at the moment.
Okay, let's pull this winner.
Three, two, one.
Crocco 618. Great one. Great name.
Crocco 618. Are you here? Crocco.
Nice. Awesome. Congrats, man. All right.
Just shoot me an email
info@flowzonerader.com.
I just need to see a screenshot of your
YouTube with you logged in just so I
know it's you.
and we get you uh all set up.
Yeah, no worries. You're welcome. You're
very welcome.
Awesome.
All right, 15 minutes into lunch. I'll
sit here with you just for a moment. See
if we get something. But, uh, Marcus's
kind of gone to sleep here.
I'll do a video this weekend on uh how
to set up autoflow, how I have it on
on here, right? So, you can have it the
same way. I'll do a video for you guys
this weekend on YouTube because I know
lots of you have asked. I just have not
had the time to do it. Haven't had the
time to do it.
You can see we've at the moment we've
got trapped buyers on this breakout up
here.
We need to see follow through above that
and we're not seeing that base above 25.
Right, we had a a push up, right?
Sellers trapped at these lows here.
There's the squeeze, retrapped here.
They had the opportunity to do it there,
failed, and we've just been going
sideways ever since.
But I will uh yeah, I'll do a free video
for you guys at the weekend for that if
I can get a moment to think.
Yeah, I'd agree. I'd I'd agree with
that, Ray. That's uh I would agree with
you there. It wants to move upside. It's
just there's no momentum or follow
through. But it might come, you know,
you might get it in the afternoon
session. It's it's possible. Maybe they
just build liquidity and save it for
tomorrow.
We don't know. They're trying again now
like into these 20 20s and 25s again.
Yes, new high of day, but you know,
there's just been no follow through
through these areas. Once you get
through these areas, there's a good
chance for it to try and like lift up to
50. It's just really struggled to get
through these areas.
Here it goes. There's 25. So, did you
get acceptance above this all the way up
here? Now, for those of you who are
still holding your longs is the
question.
Still stuck there for now. I'm not going
to take another trade this morning. I
had I had a go at this to try and get it
higher. It's probably going to go
without me now into lunch. Probably see
a lift, but uh
beyond my appetite now.
Beyond my appetite. Uh let's see what
you guys are saying.
Order trader flow on in trader is free I
think. Yeah, it is just hard to read. I
had to change it. Yeah, I mean I don't
use the orderflow the free one from NT
but um there is it is available.
Exactly Joe. Exactly.
If ENQ is dead, why not look at other
markets? Well, I've made my money. I
wouldn't say it's dead. Um, and I like
the personality of ENQ. I've learned the
pal personality of ENQ. I'm very
comfortable trading it. And half the
reason I trade futures and not trade
lots of small caps and large caps is I
don't want to keep having to change my
screens and looking around and losing
focus and understanding the different
lot size and different reward per lot
size per tick, etc., etc. So, I feel
comfortable here. So, I stay here. It's
what I'm good at. Here
it goes. So there's the 30s. Here's
previous week closed tap into 38. This
gray line here. And once you get through
that, you got IB high. There's a big
node up here, which is where I was
trying to lift through. So we were
trying to trade from here to there. Uh I
failed you doing that. We got this and
this and we went sideways so long I'd
lost interest. But this dip here into
this node held and we reclaimed this
node and we should now come up into
this. And if we get acceptance above
that, you got previous week high and an
old value area way up higher. But if
you're still long in this, I would trim
a little bit into 50s if you can get
there and then see if you can get
acceptance above.
If you're very very very very lucky
today, you'll get 26,044s
up here.
There's a probability that if it makes a
new high of day, the probability is 67%
that it will search for low of day on
the same day. I very very very much
would doubt that today. Um unless you
make mean low of day in the New York
session. I
absolutely have
I can almost guarantee you it's not
coming back down to here. It's just not
happening. So I don't know why they said
that. Maybe you mean of the New York
session. If you make a new high of day,
comes back down to a low of day of New
York session. Even that I find hard to
believe. We've had no acceptance outside
of initial balance high. I find it
highly improbable that we come down to
here again. Maybe we do a false break
and we trade inside of range, but I'd
find it very unlikely that we trade down
to here. And I'd find it I'd say almost
99.9%
chance we will not come down to here
today and close this gap. Why would it
why would it suddenly want to do a 400
point trade downside after a squeeze
out? I just But maybe maybe they're
referring to something different.
Maybe they mean the New York session.
New York. Okay, there we go, Dean. Okay,
New York sess New York session makes
sense to me. That that that's possible
because we're not talking we're talking
only about 100 points, right? That makes
sense to me. That makes sense to me.
That's possible.
All right, seven minutes left, folks. I
can't see this going anywhere. I might
get off early here unless you guys have
got any more questions for me. There's
not another trade setup I'm looking at
here.
We're inside of balance. We're inside of
initial balance.
We're drifting higher. Um we've had
we've had the trades today out of the
locations. Remember these are the
locations we had on before the market
opened. We were looking for what was it?
70 to 30 was the first level and then
down here if not. All right. So, we
would we would dip long here. We would
dip long here. And then we were waiting
for the trap and long here. Those are
the three plays. They were planned out
pre-market. You can go back 9:15 to 9:30
this morning. Look at what I was looking
at. Made that very clear.
What's the purple line? That's the
initial balance, right? That's your high
of day basically,
right? That's 9:30 to 10:30.
10 30. That's the IB. So, it's the first
hours of trading.
All right, guys. I'm going to take a
break. I need a mental break here as
well. It's I find this quite exhausting
at the moment. And um those in Discord,
I will try and pop in later.
I'm going to go and uh walk my dog and
get a coffee and have a rest from the
screens. Right. I've got to build up my
resilience to doing this again.
It's a hard job.
Some sometimes my
mental health is not always in the right
place to do this job, but I want to turn
up for you either way. All right, so big
love everyone. Um, it's the initial
balancing indicator is I'm sure you can
get a free indicator for it. You can
plot it manually. It's it's your high
and low 930 to 10:30, but it comes for
free in the flow zone. Everything you're
looking at here outside of volume is one
indicator. It's my flowzone pro. Okay.
You can check it out on the website
flowzonerader.com.
Yeah, it's exactly what I'm actually I'm
really enjoying. I'm listening to the
Ricky old Ricky Devase podcasts from
like 20 years ago at the moment from his
XFM days. All right. Peace and love
everyone. Be kind to each other. All
right. Look after each other. Use hard
stops. Remember your first stop's your
best stop. Take care.