All right, guys. Morning. Morning all.
Sorry I've been away so long. Um I'm not
going to get into it today, but um yeah,
been going through some stuff. Let's
just say let's leave it at that and
focus on the charts, but I've missed you
all and I've really been looking forward
to coming back and trading with you
guys. I did actually take my first trade
in about 10 days yesterday.
trying to get a feel for this market.
So, let's go over where we are and have
a look at what kind of models we're in.
Starting off in the daily as always. You
can see so far we're on a Wednesday,
right? The weekly high and low so far
has been set by the Monday and Tuesday.
Those who have done the course will
understand that is our weekly range.
That is equivalent of a initial balance
for this week. So, we're waiting to see
if the market wants to find a
continuation outside of those first
Monday and Tuesday high and lows.
within that we have some clear
resistance. Now you can see every time
we're popping up into 26,000 and above.
All right. 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 and even
yesterday 8 we are unloading. All right.
Someone keeps passively selling up into
pushes in there. All right. The
Ballingers have been contracting. We
have all the EMAs very very tight down
here. So far, we keep finding bids in
this low volume node down here that we
talked about a few weeks ago. All right,
so really the levels are 600 to 26,000
rotation, 400 point rotation. We can see
we have a node right here into the 800s
as well. Worth paying attention to.
Okay, so can the market find acceptance
over this? If it can, can it get
acceptance over this and start to drive
up with the bolds? Or does the market
find acceptance below this and come down
and open this out? We don't know. It's
really that simple. We don't know. So,
we are stuck in here in rotation while
it builds and we can get some more clues
as we move down into the hourly charts,
which we will do now.
Okay, hourly. Make sure you can see all
this. Make this a bit bigger for you.
All right, you can see we have this old
balance range down here. We're basically
stuck between two balance ranges, right?
This was a twoe balance basically in
here on the old contract, right? And
this was a two twoe balance dating back
to what the 29th of December. Okay.
And we keep attempting to find new
balance to move point of control and
value higher, but we keep failing. So we
came in here for a few days and now
we're opening up underneath back inside
this old balance. All right. So this is
the problem right now. We are not seeing
continuation. Tech continues to be a
little bit weaker as the market starts
to broaden. We are not seeing this kind
of move here. Moving balance higher,
taking out stops. What we're seeing is
balance created. Everyone says, "No,
that's too expensive. Let's come back
down." And we're back into this old
weekly point of control. So, it's worth
noting the previous week and the
developing week. We are under the
developing week's value right now. So,
if we find all right, if we come into
sort of the 830s anywhere up here, and
we keep selling into it, then we're
probably going to rotate down to this
point of control. This is where they
keep finding bids. It's a big level.
One, two, three works week weeks worth
of PC down here. If we lose sort of 680,
700s and we back test it and we stay
heavy, then I'm expecting a rotation
down to 55s. All right, 550s. If we come
underneath, find a bid, reclaim, rehold,
then what we're going to do, we're going
to come right back to 850s. If we go
over 850s, base and hold, then I'm
thinking we're going to go to 900. So,
there's lots of levels here that we need
to be aware of. We are in a rotational
market. I would say this current week
potentially is seeing some weakness now
if we stay heavy versus these eights.
Okay, if we stay heavy versus eights and
definitely if we stay heavy under 680s.
All right,
we can see if we move up here what we've
done overnight. All right, Asia goes
sideways, we lose the bid, we come down,
we come into uh London, we lose it, and
so far you're starting to see the sale.
Yeah, I'm going to go through the news
shortly, guys. I know some of you are
talking about the news at 10. I know
that the tariff news is potentially
coming at 10. We don't have that for
certain. [sighs] Okay, so that's what
we're looking at
when we move up into here. So, you can
see my key levels. I'm interested in
pushes that fail into here, which is
what we had on that 830 PPI print. All
right, pushes that fail anywhere up
here. Do we see the sell bids that hold
here? All right, dip and reclaim. Do we
see the buy if we flip this? And I'm
expecting to sell this back down to the
next lot of levels. All right. I don't
really want to get caught just trading
between this. This is your range
potentially building out though, so it
is worth noting. Right. We can have a
quick look at the ES and the spiders.
Same kind of thing here. We're seeing a
rejection here of 680s. Sorry, 980s.
Right. Keep rejecting here. If we keep
doing that on the ES, we can have a
little zoom out here and maybe we dig in
for some of these stops. We'll have to
see. Let's have a look at uh some of the
ETFs quickly. Just make sure they're in
alignment. Yeah, same thing here on the
Q's. Looking good.
Rejecting this. So, you've had one, two,
three drives coming underneath. Do we
stay heavy here for this rotation?
That's the question for me.
Spiders the same thing. Yeah, exactly
the same thing. All right. 1 2 3
starting to get stuck here. Do we see a
retest of 87s, 88 somewhere down there?
If we have a look at the VIX, you'll
notice it's started to find a bid. We've
talked about this for a while. This kind
of thing here is always dangerous,
right? There's the bid, the reclaim. I
can mark that out
as we start to see uh then price in some
risk. Now,
same pivots, same levels up into this
same pivot. And you can see this 18
break is where the market can start to
move. 18 and 1860s is where we're
starting to get more violent. We start
moving outside of that on the VIX. We'll
see downside pressure in this market.
Let's have a quick look at the MAG. Just
see where we're opening up.
All right, gap down there in Apple
inside its weekly range. Amazon
gap down starting to lose some of its
weekly range. Goo
gap down. It's not as bad as the rest of
the market. That looks a little bit
better to be honest. That is awful. Meta
getting absolutely slammed there. Losing
a bid. Starting to expand lower. So
that's very, very weak.
Microsoft, same story as Meta, starting
to lose a bid here. So weak in tech.
Nvidia,
well, let's just zoom out a little bit
here. Yeah, it's starting to lose this.
Every attempt to reclaim it this week.
One, two, three, rejection. If it keeps
staying heavy at 86es, it's going to
start losing bids.
And Tesla, what are you doing, my
friend? Same kind of story. That's a
little bit stronger. It's not too bad
versus Monday. All right. So, you've got
that pivot versus Monday, which it can
still protect. And the broader market
has started to sell.
Okay.
I'll tell you now, guys. I'm likely to
take it very very slow. It's my first
day back. I've got to ease in, find a
feel for the market. Probably not going
to be big risk on out the gate. Just a
bit of a heads up there. Just my
developing profile. It is good.
Um newswise, yeah, some of you talking
about this 10 a.m. news, which is
possible we get the tariff news today.
Um not guaranteed, but definitely
possible. We had uh PPI that come out
already. See if I can reload this. Uh,
came out retail sales came in better
than expected. Um,
retail sales minus autos came in better
than expected. If you believe any of
this, these are all delayed reports.
And, uh, consumer price index came in
cooler.
Let's have a look what we got here.
Business inventory is coming at 10. And
then we, yeah, we are expecting,
um, the tariff news from the Supreme
Court. So, we will see. Uh, I'm not
making guarantees there. would not be
surprised me if they don't make a
decision yet again and bump it to
another day. But we will see and we will
see if that's priced in already. Um big
pivots here that I'm watching. Uh
spiders 690 you can see keeps finding a
bid down at 690
and the cues really are watching those
sort of 620 um 621s up to 623s. That's
the kind of rotation right now. All
right. Good morning everyone. I'm not
going to get a chance to go through
everything,
but hopefully some of you have traded
well while I've been away. There have
been some really nice setups while I've
been away. Really, really nice.
Hopefully lot lots of you locking in
some good profits as this market. It's
given you some uh pretty big rotations
for you to play.
Thanks, guys. Thanks, guys. Yeah, it's
good to be back. Hopefully, this is uh
back to normal. I'm expecting a few
bumps in the road for me, so it's
possible I won't be streaming every day
next week, but let's see. Hopefully
hopefully we can get back to normal. All
right, I just want to check my levels
here. Make sure everything is looking
good.
Where is that P?
All right. So, I want to see if I can if
we can get a drive out this morning to
the upside to fade or see if a dip holds
here or even if they flip it would be
really nice. Market feels a little bit
weak to me today. So, let's just see how
we go.
Couple minutes left here. Well, we get
prepped. It's been a [snorts] good week.
Yeah, lots of you done well. That's good
to hear.
That is good to hear.
There's been some nice opportunities.
Definitely been some nice opportunities.
You can see like we're just at the
midpoint of the range. If you look at
the daily, like we're right on the
20-day right now. So, you know, the edge
will come if we start to lose the bid.
And we can think about the rotation to
come and take out some of these stops
maybe down into the sort of the fives,
the fours, and even the lower Ballinger
band down at 120. Well, that doesn't
have to happen all in one session or
even this week. But if we lose the bid,
we'll get some edge in the market. If
the bid starts to uh hold up and look to
expand over those stops at 26125, then
we can think about alltime highs. But at
the moment, the market's showing that it
is really struggling every time it wants
to look up there.
I agree, Carla. Yeah, I agree. I agree.
It would be a nice area to
to be short versus or even to be long
over if we start to reclaim.
Put these levels in above.
Okay, here we go folks.
15 seconds.
Like I said, I'm likely to take it a
little bit easy today. Not even going to
guarantee that I'm going to trade. Just
want to get a feel for this market.
See how I feel.
All right. Fast moving tape here this
morning. Let's see what they do. Can
they pull it upside off us that fade?
All of the mag opening up very very very
heavy to start the day. All gapping
down, all in the red. So, can this
market move upside and offer us a fade
to start the day or are we just going to
stay heavy and lose this previous week
point of control? It's actually a twoe
balance down there. Let's see. Time will
tell.
Feels heavy to me. Feels like we're
going downside here
into some of these old imbalances.
Get this five minute. Looking better.
There we go.
All right. Give this a chance to see if
we flip this blue box or we drive into
the red box. Don't really want to trade
in the middle of this. I feel like we're
going to come down into this. Most ideal
thing would be if we drive higher first
and then lose a bid. That would be
really ideal.
They keep bidding around these 720s for
now. I think we'll probably lose this
and trade down to these 685s at some
point as the mag looks very very heavy.
Big sellers coming in here on the market
trying to force us lower now. So into
these 700s once we lose these. I'm
looking for 685s. Here we go. Bang.
Straight into it. So a little scalp
trade into that from 700s down. And
let's see if we lose a bid here in this
blue box now and we start to flip this.
So previous
is this right? Just make sure I've got
this right.
Yeah, we can trade all the way down into
565s here if we lose this point of
control. Really nice.
So into the 80s. This is the previous
week PC.
And if we lose this, very possible we
come into sort of 570 kind of area.
This blue box, we need to flip this blue
box now if we're going to get
continuation. All right, this is the
choice. Market comes back up here or
market builds some liquidity and comes
down for this. Just letting it build
out. I did take a little snap trade from
the 700 break down into this previous
week point of control just for a little
scalp. Trying to feel my way back into
this market at the moment. Big selling
came in this morning at 720s. So that
you know that's a level.
Vick starting to break out upside.
Looks good for more downside pressure
here.
As long as they stay heavy. Would like
to see us come under this retest this
and stay heavy. That would be the best
move. I see how we work our way back to
be up here if they stay heavy. But I'm
not going to reshort until we come under
all of this. Now I want to see buyers
push us up and get trapped basically.
Otherwise, if they're going to hold this
blue box, then we can think about if
we're going to go in full range rotation
all the way back up to here. Right? Make
sure you're zoomed out on the hourly.
Remember, we went over this level.
There's a reason there's a blue box
here. [snorts]
So, they're finding bids here for now.
Question is,
is this met with some passive selling or
are they actually going to look to hold
previous week point control and come all
the way back up all the way up into
here? So, at the moment, they're trying
to hold. Here comes the squeeze. It's
good to get a feel for this market right
now. Back to the New York Open. If they
squeeze through this, then technically
they should come back up for these 820s.
If they really want to gun for it,
[snorts]
there's a New York open. They're getting
trapped there to buyers on that New York
open. So far,
720 has been the level that they keep
selling at. Buyers just came in
aggressively at 740. Can they hold a bid
over that 740, that New York open print?
If they can, then maybe we're going to
go back into these 820s, which would be
an area I'm very interested in uh seeing
if buyers get stuck into fade against.
So, here's the squeeze. So, they're
still protecting this area. Amazing. How
many times is that now? Quite a few.
All right, this is where we're going to
get interesting. into lower time frame
algo into the VWAP into previous day low
into previous day value area low
previous week value area high previous
day point of control. So I'm looking for
this to lift into here. I'm not playing
this long. I don't like that setup down
there. I'm not playing this long. Let's
see how we act in here. If we are able
to fade this or if we pivot above base
and hold for a resqueeze up to 900s. I'm
not ruling anything out. [snorts]
Took the long from previous week point
control. Yeah, I mean it made sense. I
would have liked to have seen it dip
under this. I guess it did dip and rip.
But I mean, your only long trigger
really was, I guess, 700 reclaim, but
you're already almost 100 points up.
It's a good long. Some strong selling
coming in here. And we're still bidding
up. So, just be careful. They look like
they're trying to force a squeeze here.
That is a big outlying delta there at
780.
They are really trying to force this now
into that 24-hour VWAP. If we get
through this, we're going to go 820.
Really, previous day lowered. Watch 800s
to 820s maybe all the way up to 840s.
Let's see if some buyers get stuck up
there.
If not, then 900s.
A look around here. Build for it.
Okay, some buyers caught on that big
outlying delta I just talked about at
the 80s.
>> [snorts]
>> 24-hour view up over this New York open
print bids. They will buyers now we want
to try and hold this bid here and
complete this. I actually want to see us
come into here to see if we can do
something like this for that fade all
the way back down. Don't really want to
trade the midpoint between this block
and this block. Not especially on my
first day back when I'm probably not
that sharp.
You're not seeing profit or loss so far.
It's just one trade, mate. That's all
I've got, right?
One trade. There's nothing to show.
Already people in here looking for
signals. It's incredible. [snorts]
Okay, back down to that previous week
point of control. Buyers losing that bid
there. Not able to hold that New York
open. We're going to come all the way
back down now to these 700s. If we start
to stay weak under this, then all that
buying pressure and that squeeze
pressure just came in will get stuck.
So, we will see here. It's a bit of a
messy tape here this morning.
Mag still very heavy.
Spider's holding those 90s. We talked
about those 90s on the spy probably
gamma exposure there. Here's comes the
fade back into that volume point of
control kind of level.
from previous week. It's also current
day
right back into this blue box. So, I'd
say now sellers will try and fade every
single pop here. They will try to fade
and force a new low, leaving the buyers
stuck. Buyers will want to reclaim New
York open.
This is what I'm saying. Bit of a messy
tape here. Probably to be expected
before 10:00 a.m. Right
back to these sevens [snorts] again.
They're trying to bid off sevens.
Feel like they want to wash this.
Honestly, we'll see.
They've got to come under there and stay
heavy. In my mind,
we're right at point of control for the
session right now.
[snorts]
Let's get a bit of volume on here.
There's my guy.
So big selling came in at 15s for today.
So they keep trying to drive up there.
That's where we keep seeing big selling
stepping in. If they get back above 15s,
there's a squeeze out to 40s. There's
above 15s now. So can they squeeze out
to 40s now is the question
and cannot get a close above 15s. So
there's passive selling still there
around 15s. Aggressive buying, passive
selling. So there is a passive seller
around 15s. If he gets squeezed out,
then we probably trade 40s. If he keeps
stepping in there, then we're probably
going to see downside pressure for low
of day. It's very messy because we're on
this big blue box. We know this is a
huge level from two previous weeks. All
right, this isn't just a daily level.
This is a weekly level from at least two
weeks, possibly even three to be honest.
Dates back to Sunday the 21st of
December. So, we got P from that week
and from what's this? The 4th of Jan.
That 15 is still a level. Still a battle
here at 15. [snorts]
Yeah, supposed to be at 10:00 today,
Adam. Supposed to be. No guarantees
though. They've kicked it two or three
times already down the road. [snorts]
Back to the 700s. Huge seller coming in
here. Let's see if we get some follow
through now versus point of control. Are
they going to absorb here or are we
finally going to see some follow through
on the market today?
Still absorbing that previous week point
of control. They've got to get under
85s. If sellers get under 85, we're
going to see new low dates. I'm just I'm
interested this we're underneath point
control on the day the 700s. A big
sellers just stepped in here. We can't
reclaim 15. Sellers have got the
opportunity to wash this but they need
to get closed under 85s and then we're
going to see lower day. Here we go. 85s.
Can we get closure under here? And are
we going to start a break lower? So
trying to position for a snap here.
No closing under 85s yet. It keeps being
absorbed there.
Just a little scalp there for me again.
Back to point of control on the day
which is 700. So sellers have the chance
to take control of this but we are in a
demand area. All right. So sellers have
the chance to take control of this
market right now. We're hovering at
demand area. What sellers need to do is
very simple. They need to fade versus 7
or 715 close under here and reject to go
lower. They want to be very careful
adding short down here. They will get
caught just like they did here. So,
we're looking for this to fade, to stay
heavy, to cause a rotation down to here.
That's what sellers need. Buyers, they
want to reclaim this. Leave all this
sellside delta trapped.
Have a little look at the Mac. Tesla
1.35% down. Nvidia 1.75% down. Microsoft
1.03% down. Meta 1% down. Google 0.90%
down. Amazon 1.24% down. Apple pretty
much flat on the day. Still red but flat
on the day. Let's have a look at the
broader indexes. ES just under half%
down. Uh YM holding up almost flat 0.07%
down. RTY 0.19% down. So those indexes
which we've seen rotation in doing a
little bit better. We are in the weaker
asset in here here in ENQ, which is why
really if we're going to be short, this
is the best asset to be short on because
tech has been weak. [snorts]
Here we go. Thank goodness for that.
Okay, here we go. So, the rotation, as I
said, trying to position 715 700. See if
we can get a rotation. Right, let's see
if we stay heavy now for potential ads.
And we'll look for this move here. All
right, we do not want to see this. We
want to see heaviness stay in the market
down into here now.
>> [snorts]
>> Really good. Beautiful. All right. Have
we got any bids lower? Hopefully we
have. We got bids stacking up lower.
Yeah, we got sixes stacking up, which is
good. Well, I want to get to 570s.
[snorts]
No, let's not go buyers. We don't care
about the buyers today.
[snorts]
Beautiful. Beautiful.
I would be paying yourself on the way
down to here. This is where we want to
get to, though. We want to get down into
here. And if we start losing that, I'm
telling you, this market can get very,
very weak down into the 300s. If we
start losing that blue line, [snorts]
paying myself into this, waiting to see
if a if we get a pop that starts to
reject now. All right. Do we get a pop
that starts to reject this now? Or do we
get a reclaim? I'm going to get more
size on. That's what I'm looking for.
>> [snorts]
>> We have an imbalance here. 662 to 679.
And another one 682 to 687. Really good.
Oh, come on. I want to get more size on.
Not like fully sizing cuz I'm I know I'm
probably not that sharp. Here goes
Vicks. Looking for that 1750s on the
VIX. [snorts]
Beautiful. Beautiful. Beautiful.
What I don't want to do is see us trade
down to here and then come back up and
look for an ad. I want to get an add-on
before we see weakness down into this.
All right? Because this is like a low
hanging fruit.
And I'd say it's a range cuz last week's
one is
sort of 560s and the week before is just
below at 540s. So it's a range down
here. So it's probably a 20 point range
that we can think about a cover point
in.
Come on, get your ass up so I can get
some size on here, please. [snorts]
Where's my volume gone? Didn't I just
put that on?
Nice development here as well. This is
going to support thesis of shorts from
sort of 70s to 90s. Oh, just going to
use my runner only. Am I? You mother
clucker,
man.
All right, coming into the 20-day on the
cues.
Spy with a little bit further to go.
Oh well, almost 100 pointer, but not
enough size.
All right, opening range now set here,
folks. Your first 15 minutes. So, just
be aware of that. This white line, your
opening range. I want to see if we
return into here and stay heavy. All
right, so trimmed most off now. Going to
make sure I lock in $800 no matter what.
No. What is it a bad time to ask? No
worries. But were you inspired by all
the turtle trading strategy? Always
minimizing losses and and never
minimizing profits. I mean, I don't
think that's like a turtle trader
strategy. I think that's just the key to
trading the end.
Big buyer down here at the lows. Big big
buy down here at the lows. So, I don't
think we finished the auction lower. I
think we're going to move lower. There's
a big buyer down here. 190 lot right at
the low of day. I don't think that we
finish this auction based on that.
I think we will move lower. We might
have to pop up first, but I would not
say this will be low of day just because
of what I seen there.
Yes, remaining weak.
Where's this guy stacking? 50s 600's
below us. I think we're going to wash
600s, honestly.
Let's see if we can pop first. Will they
let me get some more size on? There's a
little shelf here. 43s and 55s. Here we
go for the drive into it, which is good.
43 and 55s.
Sell it here at 650. If we reclaim this,
we squeeze right back up into this
block. We've got a little node which has
barely been traded through here. It's a
little bit of a gap here into 70s if
they do really want to get up for that.
I don't think I'm not convinced lower
days in just cuz of this guy here. But
maybe we did flip that delta. But we'll
see. We will see in time. It's good for
me to just get feeling of what this
feels like.
So up to the 55s like we said into this
sort of node. You can see this sort of
shelf here develop
acting as resistance so far
and they're finding dips now versus 30s.
come up here. So, we're reclaiming this.
I'll make this gray.
I want to see how we act into this. This
is what I really want to see. Little low
volume node. Do we push and fail here
into this imbalance
messy tape? I don't think low of day is
in. I'm going to be honest. I know we've
got some delta down there, but that big
buyer that came in here, 167 lot at low
of day, I doubt they let him stay
comfortable. I very much doubt they let
him stay comfortable. Losing this shelf
again then see how we react here. Get
into this low volume node almost.
[snorts]
So bid here 170 lot at 630 once we wash
that potentially lower day. If they keep
bidding off this then maybe they go for
a two leg higher into that block that we
talked about before into the 80s. If
they lose it, maybe lower date.
Yeah, thanks Mike. We've uh we've talked
about that quite a few times. Use it
then.
I mean, I don't know. If they say the
tariffs illegal, how the hell are you
going to give all the money back that
you've pulled in? How do you keep record
of that? Be interesting. That will be
interesting.
They're
looking to trade this 630 is a big shelf
now. This will be the third time
attempting this shelf in the last 2
minutes or something. Just looking at
bookm
[snorts]
trying to do a two leg here.
Thanks, Bella. Hope you're good. Hope
you're good.
Bella, could I ask a favor? Could you
send me some more codes, please, so I
can do some giveaways now? back. That'
be amazing.
This 630 is a big level. You can see it
on bookmap, right? We've got 175 lot
stacked there. We've come down to it
twice. I want to see if we trade under
it and lose it or if they uh bid off
this. I'm just waiting at the moment. I
think if we lose it, I think I'm not
guaranteeing that lower day is set
because I don't like the look of that
lower day. I think there's too many
buyers down there and they will probably
want to wash them. But
my first day back in the market, so
don't take what I say as gospel. All
right, coming back down to this 630
again. So 176 lot is. Let's see if they
fill him.
Does he get absorbed here? He's just sat
on the tape. Everyone's front running
him. I think we're going to snap him. I
just think that this is going to get
nasty.
Here
he comes. 630. Let's see if we wash
through him. And if we do, do we go
lower of date?
Still absorbing off him so far. They've
added size into there as well.
Everyone's front running him. Haven't
quite touched him yet. 180 lot there
now. 630. Still haven't traded through
him. Just hasn't used him to be absorbed
yet.
Yes, we don't.
I'm not going to get into tip tap.
630 still holding. Still not traded
through him yet.
Still inside our opening range. 15
minute opening range as well.
Can't get above this gray shelf. All
right, 630s. Here we go. There he goes.
Night night. Big seller coming in here.
Now, can they get follow through?
153 lot sellside come through here. Do
we get follow through for low of day or
not? That is the question. So, we've
absorbed him into 630. We're back above
that 630. That's your pivot. The big
seller came in there, got absorbed by
the buyer. They're starting to stack
now. 610, 605, 600, 590. These buyers,
sellers keep attacking this point of
control which is slowly drifting
downside. This red line on your chart,
that gray box is your over under right
now. Sellers are trying to What sellers
want is for this to fail
and to use these stops. There's 190 lot
buy side here who came in at the bid
market buying here. They're looking to
trade him down to here. That's what
sellers want to do. Buyers will want to
reclaim this and get up to here and then
make a decision at this point.
It's good for me to be back just to get
a feel of what this market feels like.
Let's go and get another tea here in a
minute. What indicators do I use? These
are my flow zone pros.
[snorts]
Gray box still holding heavy.
There's so many buyers stacked from 15
to 90s. Honestly, I'd be very surprised
if we don't go and clean them up. Here
we go.
I think low day, a new low day here,
guys, because the one the 190 lot that
lows is just standing out like a sore
thumb. Gray box rejecting. Here we go.
Yes, Alex was right. Okay, he's still
got a feel for the market after even all
that time off.
[snorts] Okay, going to come and fill
all these guys up. They're starting to
add size now all the way down to 75s
which will take us sort of into previous
week value area low. Remember this is
the target. This is what we talked about
this morning. Pops to fail rotation lose
gray box lose point of control. They
want to come down into here. We're
starting to see it happen now.
That's a better low of day auction. I
will say we actually have some sellside
delta at that low unlike before where it
was all buy side. All right, we've got
how long? We've got four or five minutes
until the news. I'm just going to get a
refill of my tea and come back. Okay.
Where have you been? If that's not too
personal. It is too personal. I needed
some time off. I've had the worst 10
days of my life, and it will always be
the worst 10 days of my life for the
rest of my life. So, I can't get into
it, guys. I will choke up. I will start
becoming a puddle of tears on stream. I
can't I just can't get into it with you
guys. All right? But just know I don't
leave you guys. I don't not stream
because I can't be bothered or anything
like that. If I'm not on stream, it's
because something serious has happened
unless I'm on vacation. That's what's
happened. something very very serious
started to occur last week and I've been
dealing with it ever since. All right,
so it's been a very very tough time for
me. It continues to be a tough time for
me, but it's important that I have my
own sanity and try and get in some
routine and I genuinely miss trading
with you guys. So, it's it's healthy for
me to come back. All right, we have some
buy side delta here at 16s. If we get
under 16s, that big buy will get caught
again and we get a reflush. There's
under 16s. Let's see if they expand it.
There we go. So, you can see him on the
tape. He keeps getting himself caught.
He keeps aggressively buying down there
for some odd reason. He's got himself
caught again.
So, I think you're going to get rotation
to previous week value area low now.
Thanks, guys. I appreciate it. I I do
appreciate you
guys. I can't like even to say thank you
for you guys makes me like choke up. But
I really appreciated you all, those who
took the time to write me a message,
whether it was in Discord or in YouTube.
Some of you even sent me a private
email. It didn't go unnoticed. I know I
didn't reply to a lot of you. I've just
been dealing with too much. But I am
genuinely very grateful for the prayers
and the love that you give me. It it
gave me strength in a very tough time
and I appreciate you all. All right.
Okay, I can show you my scorecard. I'm
only trading one account today because I
just want to ease my way back in. So,
just 900. I said to you, I'm going to
make sure I lock in at least 800. So,
900 on that one.
When I'm feeling comfortable, maybe by
next week I'll start trading all of
these together again.
[snorts]
And we got four minutes.
Three minutes until the news if we get
it.
Building out lots of liquidity here. I
still think we can rotate lover. So
those of you who are in shorts, as long
as you're managing your your stop,
protecting your profits.
You look good. Remember, we were short
this morning.
I think it was this drive here. Trying
to remember. It was either here or here.
Somewhere around here. We were looking
for shorts. And this is where we're
looking to try and get down into. All
right. So, we're looking at this whole
number 600s here. If we lose that, I
think we trade into this. This is like a
20 point block. All right, I'll tell you
why it's a 20 point block. Cuz it's a
twoe range that we're looking at down
there. The edge of a twoe range. We went
over this pre-market. All right, this
right here. All right, bang, bang. All
right, this is what we're looking at.
This kind of level. If we lose that and
stay heavy, then you can see this old
pivot. Don't have to do it today, but
it's possible. All right, maybe if they
if we have some bad news like the
tariffs were illegal, blah blah blah.
Got to give all the money back. Don't
know how that looks. Maybe we come down
into that. We have a huge amount of
liquidity. Then think about all the
liquidity we have then built built out
in here. And if we start to lose it and
these are all buyers, all right, we will
see major heaviness in the market that
might start to form a crack in the
market because that is one, two, three,
four weeks trapped and before that we
had another few weeks trapped up here,
right? So, if we start to lose all of
this,
we can talk about this was the old naked
point of control, wasn't it? Let's move
this up. Remember that we bought those
dips last month into that. So, again, a
level to be aware of.
No longer naked, but we uh we traded
into that a while ago. Let's move this
up so you can see the days. There we go.
Okay. Almost there, folks. Almost into
this previous week value low.
So, that's your low hanging fruit. I
would be taking a good chunk of your
money off into that and you can hold
runners for beyond that.
What is the news at 10? Uh well,
allegedly we're going to get a uh
decision from the Supreme Court on
whether tariffs are legal or not.
Um, we also have existing home sales.
And then we don't have anything until
midday where we've got, you know, I'd
say 12:00 all the way into like 2:00.
You have Fed Fed speakers. You got the
beige book at two as well. So, you might
get a little volatility at two. I won't
be here for that today. I've got to ease
my way back in.
[snorts]
Almost there, folks. So, make sure
you're paying yourself. You can uh think
about this shelf even down here now.
Make sure you're paying yourself on the
way down. Okay,
here we go.
There's your TP.
And there's the weakness. All right. So,
you should be done. You can hold
runners. That is an absolutely gift. All
right. Beautiful session this morning.
That's exactly what we were looking for.
All right. All the way from 740s really
down into here. So almost 200 points.
Make sure you're paying yourself into
that. Like I talked about, this is a
twoe balance range down here. We do not
know how we're going to act down here.
[snorts]
Opinion on bookmap and footprint charts.
Uh opinion is they are fantastic. I use
both. As you can see above me right now,
I have bookmap on my Ninja Trader. I am
using footprint, but you can use it over
here. You can see I have footprint on
here for you guys.
All right, I use both. They are
fantastic.
It's where I get my edge from
[snorts]
really good. All right, so the question
now will be very very simple. Can we
build out new liquidity
right somewhere in here
to come down into these?
That's the question. That is the only
question I'm now asking. All right. So,
really, really solid trade. W's in chat
if you got any of that.
W's in chat if you got any of that with
me. Hopefully some of you locked. You
don't have to have got it all, but
hopefully you got some of it with me.
Vick's really starting to break. Look,
I've just got a notification. Vick's
coming into the 18s we just talked
about, right? It just got stuck in front
of 18. So, be aware of that.
Existing home sales came in good, better
than expected. 4.35 million versus 4.13
previous 4.22. So, more home sales,
which is good. And nothing on the
tariffs yet. Like I said, that that's
the uh outlier. That's the
that's the big outlier today. If we get
that tariff news. Yeah, lots of you
getting it. Nice work.
Oh, sorry. bookmaps footprint feature
instead of trading views. Uh I don't use
footprints on bookmap. I I just struggle
to read it that well. I don't like the
layout of it. Um I use it on Ninja. All
right. So I have it on my Ninja Trader.
I use it on here
so you can see. But it's horses for
courses. You got to do whatever suits
you. [snorts] Whatever suits you.
took the short from 690 uh from up here.
Really good. Look at that. All the way
down. So, well over 100 points, 130 odd
points for you. And we see now this is
we see if we build liquidity here like
we talked about. I mean, potentially
there's a continuation. But remember,
we're on discount now versus the
previous week. But if we lose a bid, we
can't rule this out. This is not the
best location to be short now, which is
under previous week value area low
because we are very, very cheap. We're
in discount. But if we lose a bid here,
we can't rule out that this market, it
may very well want to continue to rotate
lower. We cannot rule that out. It's
very very possible.
But lots of people been trying will be
trying to buy here thinking that this is
cheap on a twoe discount. So uh we will
just see.
I say you need to pay attention to these
shelves. Look at liquidity built here.
low volume above up into 14s. So if they
get a squeeze out, they'll come to 14s.
I would be sort of risk off if we start
to where I'd be cautious, right, is if
we start to reclaim this is where we can
get a little bit squeezy. Otherwise, we
can squeeze up into here and it can be a
failure at that point. Again, it's
possible. Look at the liquidity built.
Look at the value area low. But uh new
money short location is not good down
here.
If we're going to go into trend day,
then uh your runners might work really
well. I'll just let it build out a bit
more liquidity before you add on. Do I
live stream every day? Yeah, normally
I'm here every day. I' I've had some
time off recently, but yes, I'm hoping
to be back here every day. 9:15 Eastern
time all the way until lunch.
So, smash subscribe, smash that like
button. I do want to do some giveaways.
We can do a few giveaways today because
I've been away a while. Maybe I'll give
a couple Apex accounts away today.
Okay, SPY coming into its 20-day. So,
we're, you know, that mean reversion
trade into the midpoint on the daily has
happened.
Q's already under it.
18's a big level on the VIX. Remember,
we went over this level earlier
on the VIX. You can see my alert. It's
been there for weeks. All right. I know
the break over there is a problem for
the market. All right, so
we got very very very close. There were
some huge Anyone watching the the option
chain on VIX, there was some huge calls
taking place yesterday on VIX. All
right.
[snorts]
Yeah, I yeah, I see that as well. The
gap still there.
Okay, into this low volume node.
Watching this gray box above. They can
protect this node. It can act as
resistance. Flow zone also there as
resistance.
I would like to see a twoleg if I'm
going to think about reading this. I
want to see lots of participants trapped
in this. If I'm thinking about actually
reading it,
be very careful here because we've hit
the lowhanging fruit. Remember, our
target was this blue line, right? So,
we've hit that low hanging fruit. I'm
willing to play long if we start basing
above everything and leaving sellers
trapped at the lows. If we're going to
go rotation here, I'm I'm willing to
play it if we start reclaiming and
leaving everyone caught, but not until
that point. Right. Trend right now
currently is lower. We're outside of the
opening range. We are outside of
previous day's value. We've come down
into the low of previous weeks week's
value. We want to see if pops get sold
into. That's going to be the easiest
um way to position in this market
currently.
And I'll only consider longs if we leave
lots of shorts trapped and we start to
reclaim big levels or squeezes back up.
I'll give you a readout on the mag.
Tesla 1.59% down. Nvidia 2 and a half%
down. Microsoft 1.41% down. Meta 1.66%
down. Google 1.03% down. Amazon 1.64%
down. Apple 0.51% down. As an index, we
are 1.23% down. We have relative
weakness. ES only 0.72% down. YM 0.35%
down. RTY trying to go red to green.
Okay. So, we have relative weakness in
tech. We've talked about that.
Definitely talked about it in Discord
this morning.
How do I set up my profile? This is just
anchored to 930. It's anchored volume
profile to 930. I've got it set at two
ticks. You can have it at um a th00and
per row. Here we go. So, pops failing
again. I would like to see a second leg
here develop to really get short into
this
but into this low volume node into this
like little bit of an edge.
I really want to see a second leg
develop here to short. What if I'm
saying a second leg? What I'm talking
about? I love to see something like
this.
This would be really nice. And we can
look for the trade down into here and
here. So, I want to stay short on this.
Please don't just be a single leg.
Please.
Right. I tell you what, 550 to the low
of day is well where sellers got
trapped. So, if they're going to force a
second leg up, they're going to want to
protect 550. If they can't, then we're
probably going to go lower day.
Which tool is this? It's anchored volume
profile, guys.
All right. It's right here. See this?
Anchored volume profile. All right. And
these are the settings
right here. Two ticks and have it set to
right.
Okay. So, they're holding that 550,
which is good. So, hopefully we can get
that second leg higher here. And then if
buyers get stuck, we can think about
that reshaw. Alex, I passed 50K. take
profit trader evaluation. I just wanted
to say thank you for taking your time
trading with us. I've learned so much.
You're a great mentor and teacher. Thank
you. You're welcome, Eric. Thanks for
joining. Thanks for [snorts] joining
everyone. Make sure you smash that like
button for me.
I got to get this algorithm remembering
that I still exist. You know after the
time off,
let's get these uh likes up. I want to
do giveaways. I want to look after you
guys. Guys, want to thank you guys for
coming back to me on stream.
[snorts]
Nice hold of 550 there we just talked
about. So those sellers are trapped
under 550. If you're wondering how I can
see them, I'm can see them using
orderflow. All right, could see that the
sellers were caught under 550. That was
a big level. Question is, how high can
buyers push this? Can we get this second
leg up to sell into? Can SPY or ES get
back into that New York VWAP?
Is there a way to fade up there?
Is that the 50-day on the cues? It is,
isn't it? So, stack between 20-day and
50-day on the cues now as well. So,
coming into huge big big levels
on these cues. Maybe we can start to get
some crosses over the next few sessions.
We will see. All right, here's the 50
hold. Let's see if we can get up to one
of these gray boxes. This would be
really nice if we can get all the way up
into here. It' be really nice because we
have buyers stuck up there already. We
already know it somewhere up here.
Back down to these 70s. Do they test
these 50s again? Hopefully not. We want
this higher, please. What we looking
like on the hourly here?
If you hear me talking to myself a lot
folks, I've got to get myself back in
gear here. Right. So, the hourly trans
transition was 86s.
There is a big imbalance on that hourly
if we do want to drive back up and test
some of those levels. So, I am aware of
that.
So, I want to stay short, but I want
this market to move up first, trap
buyers to allow me to think about the
short. I do not want to be short at the
low of day.
I haven't been here this week, but it's
looked to me like we've rotated quite a
lot on numerous 200 point rotations.
Yeah, I see that Adam. Yes, like that 17
has that big buy delta spike and then
above that we have sell delta at uh 29s
and then point of control into sort of
44s. Yeah, I see exactly what you're
looking at. right into here really into
this gray box right this is where if you
think about where they kept bidding off
do you remember why I said I don't think
the low of day is in yet because we had
a huge buyer here it was 190 lot buying
here on the market I said if we if he
loses we wash and I said this is not low
of day because it was buy side delta or
that was the wash so we want to see if
we retest it and if he sells on the
retest right if he didn't stop out and
he sells on the retest we'll see some
heaviness come back in if he's just been
relentlessly buying this and he gets
back above. He'll take control of the
market. There we go. Maybe we've just
had some news there. That feels a bit
newsy. Let's have a look.
Maybe that's the decision from the
Supreme Court. Let's see.
I can't see anything yet.
Nothing on Squawk.
No ruling today. Is that what they just
said? What a surprise. Is that right,
Gigi? Has that actually been announced?
Looking for that on juice.
Financial juice. Okay. Yeah. Well, then
that's the case then. So no reason for
this market to necessarily fade lower
other than like technicals now. We said
it, didn't we? We said it.
Will they kick it down the road again?
Apparently the answer is yes. So we're
coming into that block. Like I said, if
we reclaim this now, this is the danger,
right? [snorts] If we reclaim this now,
we talked about this earlier. We built
liquidity here
and here. And if they start reclaiming
this, this drive out can can take place.
Doesn't have to take place. Can take
place. This is the big level.
It's why you don't get short at low of
day.
Back to point control.
You're welcome, April.
All right, so spiders coming back up.
They're through that New York VWAP. ES
doing the same through New York VW up
coming up to 24-hour VWAP. We're through
New York VW up. 24-hour VWAP is up here.
All right, we've left sellside delta up
here. All right, if buyers start taking
control of this market, they can try and
complete a full rotation back into
value. All right, previous week point of
control here is key. Do we reject this
and come for a retest or are we just
going to go straight squeeze and start
reclaiming every key level and come back
back up to these value areas?
[snorts]
I execute on one min. I don't uh like
I'm looking for trap participants and
execute on one minute. But my analysis
does not come from a one minute chart.
Not at all.
Big big buyside delta in this 5minute
candle. Huge buy side delta. Biggest
biggest buyside delta we've had of the
day. So big old squeeze
popping lots of stops I'd say.
Where was that big seller this morning?
He was at 700. All right, 700.
Yeah, exactly. Couldn't get through the
18s, could we, Peter? It came right up
1799. I had my alert there at 18s.
Straight back down. [snorts] Gross.
Absolutely gross.
[clears throat]
Just waiting.
back to this previous week point of
control. Here comes the move towards
that 700. Remember that 700 was the big
seller this morning, right? So, expect
some selling up here. This is where that
big seller was this morning. If we're
going to go on a gigantic squeeze here,
we have all these levels up here to aim
for. All right, but they're going to
need to pull back at some point. Depends
how big a squeeze. We've just popped a
ton of stops. They're reselling in front
of those 700s. We talked about those
700s, right? 7. Yeah, 700 on the money
is where that huge seller was this
morning. You can see him on Delta. He
stands out loads. 158 lot this morning.
Came in there and then a bit a little
bit above him into sort of the 20s.
Waiting to see how we act now. Am I in
the US? Yeah, I'm in Los Angeles.
Here comes the rebbit. They're trying to
get to the sevens. Is this the old line
from ages ago? I can't believe that's
still on here. Delete that.
Trying to
>> [snorts]
>> The outliers 75 is big buy side delta 78
is big buy side delta 83s and then 700s
is the sell side. [snorts]
So buyers will want to hold this shelf,
right? Buyers will want to do this. They
want to hold this shelf
and reclaim this. Sellers will want to
fade this, get under this, and force
this rotation back down.
How we acting this shelf is going to be
key. Remember, we squeezed up. There is
not a whole lot of structure in this. Is
a big squeeze up. They're trying to hold
this shelf. The buyers doing pretty good
job. They're trying to get to sevens.
Remember [snorts] they are trying to get
to sevens right now. Right? The reason
they're trying to get sevens
is in here. Right? This is where we
cracked and where a huge player came in.
Right? A huge player came in here to
force this market. So, we're repricing.
What a push. Yeah, good push, wasn't it?
Good push. Why you don't short the lows?
Why I said down here, this is not a good
position to be short on. I was willing
to play short if we did something like
this I talked about. I was willing to
play short. We haven't done that. All
we've done is this, right? We're
starting to clean up all of these now.
We have to wait if they want to full
send it up here today. They might have
enough C to do it. We will see. This
gray box now becomes keys, point of
control. This little shelf and this node
down here can do another one. Let's do
one down here. This edge
[snorts]
for Trading View. Um, you'll have to pay
for Pro and uh if you just come up to
here to candles and just change it to
volume footprint. I'll do a video on
that this weekend if I get time because
lots of people ask me that.
Okay, so watching to see if they can get
up into 700s. We got VWAP just above
that. You've got the New York open up at
740s. Value area high on the day up at
740s. 745s
and then previous day value all the way
up here. So they're starting to hold
this. This is the bullish move now.
They're starting to try and squeeze.
Here comes the sevens. They're trying to
get to that sevens [snorts]
into its New York open already. So far
rejecting that. We're not quite there
yet on the ENQ.
like one more squeeze
rotational market. We're inside value
now on the day, right? I'd love a
squeeze up here and see if we get stuck
down into this gray box again. Do they
rebid off this and be up again or are
they going to let this go?
VIX has found a little bit of a bid here
towards the 20s on the VIX. Back into
this gray box, back into point control.
This is the question. Bulls must defend
this now. If they fail to defend this,
they will get themselves caught. There's
a lot of aggressive selling coming in
here and so far it's being absorbed into
point of control. Lots of aggressive
selling coming in here. So far being
absorbed into point of control. We do
have bids down at 640, 630, 625.
So sellers are getting a little bit
angry here. There is definitely some
passive buying absorbing this on the
tape at the moment because sellers are
not getting the flush and they came
through pretty heavy there.
It's really strong from buyers to absorb
that. That was heavy sell pressure. We
had 84 lot, 36 lot, six lot, 43 lot, 55
lot. Everything absorbed, 30 lot. Just
everything absorbed. And now they're
trying to get aggressive back to the
upside. There's a big battle in this
area of this gray box point of control.
This area here is huge for sentiment on
the rest of the day. [snorts]
Hey Scotty, thanks man. Thanks for that
video the other day. Sorry I didn't
reply. I was right in the middle of
something. Um meant meant a lot dude
that you uh text and reached out.
Appreciate it. [snorts]
Bit choppy here while we make up
decision of what's next.
I haven't, Jake. I'm going to be honest
with you. I haven't had the chance to do
much. I'm [snorts] sorry. I'm sorry, my
friend.
It's not cuz I don't want to, bud. It's
just uh my brain has not been
functioning
on all cylinders right now.
Could we rotate inside prior week's
value? Um prior weekly
uh we I mean we are already rotating
inside prior week's value. This is what
we're doing currently.
We are already doing that.
Current week's value.
All right. Developing week's value. 8:30
is your level. That's your value area
low. 8:30. We have a node at sort of
740s.
That's the level of current week. All
right. To get inside current week's
developing value, we will need to get
back inside 830s. All right. There's a
big level at 740s.
So, that would be your first bet. We're
already rotating inside previous week's
value.
Guess what? Uh,
you made money. I hope. Tyson,
you got a payout? Another payout. That
would make me happy. Another payout.
They keep getting stuck here in front of
700s. They want to clean out 700s. What
they're trying to do. They keep getting
stuck here. Back towards point of
control would probably go now.
Point of control on this session is 44s.
Hey,
that's my guy. Tyson requesting 4K. What
a difference the end of last year and
this year has been to when we started
working together. What a difference.
Maybe you can tell chat
what changed in your trading, my friend.
What changed in your trading? What got
you from blowing up and struggling? I
know we went over like strategies and
like making it simpler and one trade,
but what what was the difference? Cuz
that's what your second or third payout
in quick succession. What's been the
difference for you, bud?
[snorts]
So ES can't get through it. New York
open
dangling around the VWAPS. We're doing
the same thing. We're just in between
this red block and this gray area. I
don't really want to execute a trade
here.
Slowing down. There you go. Slowing
down. Less trades, less size. Let them
work more. Wait for the setups. There
you go.
I'm proud of you, mate. That was um that
took a lot of dedication and hard work
from you to change your style and refine
and refine and refine.
It just proves process. You stick to the
process, you will end up making money.
If you start following the money, you
end up going wrong.
Super proud of you, buddy.
Okay, just trapped between these two
boxes still. If you're wondering why I'm
not executing anything, that's why we're
building liquidity. I want to see what
we do with this liquidity. Sellers keep
getting very aggressive around these 50s
without getting the breakdown. They are
probably looking to wash us back down
into this low volume node or at least
the edge into twelves. They keep getting
aggressive here trying to get the wash.
There is a passive buyer who keeps
absorbing everything on this tape here.
If this passive buyer gives up, then
they get the wash. If the passive buyer
keeps holding it, then we can expect
this market to try and rotate higher. I
don't want to trade in this tightening
range, right? There's like 30 40 point
range here developing for the last I
don't know 10 15 minutes and just want
to wait for us to leave that.
It's been a pleasure to work with you,
Tyson. It's um I love working with
students and be able to take them to
profitability. It's a good feeling.
Makes me feel good. That's what I've
missed. That's why I wanted to come back
and do this again.
[snorts]
All right. Sorry, I'm just watching. If
you see me looking up here, I'm just
watching Matt. They're trying to get
this squeeze. They're desperate. They
keep absorbing these 50s and then
they're getting aggressive top side and
then not getting their way and sellers
come back in like this. waiting for some
some form of sentiment shift to come.
Maybe you guys can give me just a moment
and I can get some water, maybe even a
snack and come back.
[cough]
All right, here we go.
Silver new new alltime high. Is it 91?
It was those hundreds, wasn't it? Hey,
I'm 19. I was looking to start trading
ID. I'm really sorry. I'm 40, so I don't
I don't know what IDW means. Chose the
wrong mentor. I've heard a lot of them
are scams. Do you think I should depend
on a book?
Mind you, I'm a CS student. Uh,
I don't think books help. Like, it's
good to read books,
but you're going to have to learn and
find your own path, right? It's the path
of 10,000 hours. Same as any skill. All
right. Losing that shelf now. It's
coming down to this low volume node that
we just talked about. All right. So this
passive buyer
who's been trying to absorb the 50s. He
lost. We come back down into value area
low on the session. All right. If we
lose this, we trade lower. If they
rebid, this is the rotation here. All
right. So there's a rotation here. There
can be a rotation here. There can be a
rotation here. Right? We have to wait
now for momentum.
Um that would be my honest opinion. Uh,
my friend, if you're 19,
do as much as you can for free on
YouTube. Like, watch my videos. Watch
other people's videos.
See if there's someone you connect with.
See if there's a style that makes sense
to you. See if there's a form of
pedagogy, which is like a teaching style
which you like. Once you like that
style, go and watch all their videos as
much as possible.
Reach out to people who are maybe in
their community or watch their videos.
Make sure they're legit. Make sure you
like get get some form of verification
that these guys are useful, that they're
not just going to charge you, you know,
three, four, five, $10,000, which is
what most of us do when we start and get
ripped off by someone who's absolutely
shite. And then, and only then, once
you've gone through all their videos and
you think these guys are good and people
have told you they're good, should you
consider doing a course or being part of
their community. And that includes with
me. I might not connect with you. Maybe
I'm the wrong teacher for you. Maybe I
trade different style to what you like.
That's okay. There's plenty of styles
out there. Find the one that's right for
you. Look at this wash right into the
low volume node we just talked about.
All right. So, rotation lost it back
down into this. Do they bid over this
now? All right. So, these will be cover
points for shorts. Balls will want to
hold these levels. If they don't hold
these levels, we are opening ourselves
up for a huge amount of liquidity to be
built to come back down into here.
Initial balance now set as well.
Alex, would one or two kind of paid
tutorial sessions over Zoom be possible
at any point in the future? Um, if
you're in the mentorship program, yeah,
but I won't do it for people that I
haven't worked with because it'll just
be too many unknowns and variables of
how you trade.
Uh, I use it, Nick. I use it on a M1 and
an M5
previous week low. No, it's not the last
zone. There's one zone we could hit. I'd
say all the way down here underneath it.
330 to 260 is possible if if we stay
heavy. That is a big if. We remember we
are inside of initial balance right now.
So, here's back to previous week value
area low. This is a big big big level.
Remember shorts this morning got stuck
550 to 5:30. All right. The shorts got
stuck 550 to 5:30. That is the area
bulls will want to defend because they
will want to leave them stuck there.
Reverse cup and handle looking for
lower. Possible. It's possible. You
can't can't rule it out. But uh I'd say
right now we are still inside of
previous week's value. We are inside of
initial balance.
You have to be careful of a uh reclaim
of value and then we'll just go back
into a rotation again. Right? For me the
market has been weak but it's been in a
rotation but we are definitely leaving
current week's value. The problem is is
when you look left on the hourlies or
even on the dailies and you see the
amount of structure we've built out over
the last I mean it's months and months
now guys. We're talking about going back
to
October. All right, we're talking about
going back to October levels.
We are making higher lows. The problem
is the market cannot make a higher high.
So, every aggressive buyer at the high
of day or every potential breakout is
getting caught, right? But we are making
higher lows on the daily.
Two ticks, Mick. Two ticks.
So, back into these lows again to this
gray box again. This shelf again. See if
they pop up and how they act. Right. So,
if they start reclaiming, they're going
to try and get back up into here again.
This is just a big old rotation right
now. This market can't make its mind up
what it wants to do. In my mind,
we are seeing weakness across the board
though.
Anchored volume profile. AVP.
Who just asked that? Just just
Niko TV. Sorry, completely butchered
that, but that's all I can see. It's
your name.
[snorts]
Rejection of gray box there.
Possible fade there. Where's this buyer?
That guy from 17s
still acting as a level
617. Still buy side trapped there.
I just I'm waiting for this to develop a
little bit more. Maybe I can get one
more trade out of this today. I know I'm
a little bit rusty right now, so I'm
trying to be careful. I don't want to uh
do anything silly.
We're right on that 20-day
SMA support on uh the Q's and ES has it
just underneath the lower day right now.
So, we know that's a big area, right?
There's lots of bids just underneath us
here as well.
feel like we want to trade lower. It's
just is this passive buyer going to keep
showing up? It looks like we want to
trade lower to me. [snorts]
This can be a pullback that holds. It's
very deep already. It's a shame we
haven't had a retest of this up here.
Really?
Are they going to break now?
There's still someone on the tape. Every
aggressive cell is being absorbed.
Even that last lot will trade through
it.
These sort of 90s to 85s is there as
this passive buyer keep absorbing there
again. Every flush through he's
absorbing it again. The same thing. It's
crazy.
Someone doesn't want this to uh trade
lower.
You see how every flush is so quickly
snapped back up. That's just a passive
buyer. Just soak. Just a full on soak. I
show you on bookm. That's three times
we've done this move.
One.
Move this along. One. Two.
Was the one before? There was the one
before. There was one before. Every sort
of dip into here, it lasts a nancond.
It's absorbed. Now he's coming back on
the book here. It's interesting.
And again, dips soaked and absorbed.
There is a passive buyer absorbing as
much as he can down here right now.
Doesn't mean he gets his way. I'm just
saying what there is. [snorts] Now he's
moved.
Do we see follow through to 80s? Now if
we trade under 80s I think uh or
under 73s there's more chance he's still
come back on the tape. Endless
absorption down here. Endless
absorption.
So remember the buy side delta the
outlier today was at 17
just in that rotation the gray box to
gray box on your screen. That's your
rotation right there.
Having a look at the broader market. AMD
doing all right today. Relative strength
there. Bitcoin doing all right. I bit
up.
Remember, we're pretty thin on that way
down. That drop was pretty quick from
those 40s and 50s. Just be aware of
that.
What's my best advice for people that
are starting? I think I just gave it,
didn't I?
Do as much as you can for free. Speak to
people in communities that uh can help
you, can offer you advice.
Do not trade your own capital.
Learn one trade setup at a time. Right?
One trade setup at a time. Do not try
and do too many setups at once. Learn
one trade setup at a time.
Still can't get through those 15s. Is it
15s? [clears throat] 17s, isn't it? 17.
That's still a big level up there. It's
where the buyers got stuck earlier
today. Through that, there's a squeeze
back to I'd say 50s. But so far, every
little pop up into that area, they keep
reselling.
Question is, is there follow through to
downside? I want to see I'd like to see
follow through to downside,
but we know 50s. This is where buyers
got stuck at 50s and below. All right,
sellers got stuck, sorry, down here.
And we know we're currently holding
these pivots here on the rotation.
Buyers got stuck up here from 50s for
the wash. We're now building out
liquidity. The question is, are we going
to see this or are we going to see a
reclaim and a recap of this first? I
have no idea, folks. I can't tell you.
I'm not Nostradamus. All I know is that
every pop into 17s like that again, they
keep reselling. So, every time they're
getting aggressive, they keep reselling.
And I know there's a passive buyer that
keeps just stepping in here over and
over and over again. How are we looking
on CBD? Let's move this along.
Yeah, no divergence on CVD yet.
Everything looks correct
[snorts]
to the 17s. They still can't close over
17s.
It is a bit messy.
And if they get a squeeze, they're going
to come right back up to here into the
50s where we sold from.
Don't see a beautiful setup here at the
moment.
[snorts]
Just in a range. Here's
your edges for the day.
That's your range. At the moment, it's
unwilling to move outside of that. Very,
very clear.
So, we're in rotation. My least favorite
trade as we all know. [snorts] So,
probably going to come up to these 50s
now because we were thin down. We're
going to come back up and repric it and
see if there's a seller still there. And
if not, then the squeeze is on. What a
gross market.
If it's been like this all the time I've
been away then
don't care that I've missed it.
You can see it in the daily. The daily
just looks dreadful. It's absolutely
dreadful. We're not going anywhere. We
haven't gone anywhere. You've had that
from that pivot in I don't know mid
December, 17th of December. We haven't
gone anywhere. We've just gone sideways.
So, reselling point of control. They
didn't even get to that gray box above.
Oh my gosh. Market, come on. Make your
mind up. Make your mind up, market.
Do we get something? I'd like another
trade here.
Buy zone still negative. Still under the
17s,
but inside value. I think if we get
underneath value area low in previous
week value area low, we've got an
expansion model. We just have to watch
that initial balance.
traed through it too much
back to the sixes
value low just below as you can see but
our Current value area low is also
previous week value area low. That is
your edge right now in this market. That
is [snorts] your edge into that level.
Can we see some follow through today?
[snorts]
If the broader market starts to sell,
tech will probably get weaker. It's been
the weaker asset. So, we'll see.
Here's value area low. Remember,
previous week value area low under this.
So, this is starting to look like we
want to sell through. Now, this is our
edge. If we start trading under and
under IB, your cover is to like to here.
So, it's a shame they didn't get a
little bit higher.
We're starting to break now. They
couldn't reclaim. They lost 17s. If we
trade, this is the big level here. If we
lose this and we lose this, this is
possible.
Okay, starting to see follow through in
this market.
Big seller here. So, I expect a little
bit of a shift around this point here.
Big seller here. Just came on the tape.
See if we can get a pop to resell.
Can we get to lower day and under IB?
Then we know where we want to go.
Really good. Remember 550 was the level
I told you before. Remember 550? This is
the level that uh sellers were stuck.
should put this in 550 to low of day.
550 right here. Right. That's where
sellers got stuck this morning. That's
where their delta is. Aggressive sellers
came in at 550 on the dock down to low
of day. So, this is why I'm saying there
were big sellers down here. I expect a
bit of a shuffle. We want to see if we
can get a pop to fade now and then trade
through them. You do not want to be a
new money short into where everyone was
stuck this morning. [snorts]
And we see how we trade around this
core. Now we can look at this level here
as well. There we go.
80s.
Okay. [sighs] I expect we will one of
these markets will make a new low day.
ES come down. Double bottom yet. hasn't
broken down. We have got the 20-day
below it. So again, mean reversion type
trade.
Maybe we can go as high as 80s, maybe
even 90s where a big seller came in at
90s. Let's see if we can pop into 80s or
90s and if they offer a ref.
Be careful of the reclaims here.
Here
we go.
Really nice. Come on, baby. Can we get
lows?
Can we get low of days here? And a snap.
He's back. Thank you. Right, runners
now. Let's see if we get lucky down into
there. Let's go.
Let's go.
Let's go. Let's see if we can get follow
through now.
What have we got on the tape? 505 500s
whole levels. I think we can get weaker.
So, we respect the 500s for a whole
level. Okay, we respect the 500s as a
whole level.
Starting to break now. Broader market
starting to break with us. We're in the
weaker asset. It's exactly where we want
to be. We want to be positioned short on
the weaker asset.
It's beauty. It's a beauty. Let's see if
we can get downside follow through. So,
if we get really lucky, we get 400s and
even like these 300s down here. I mean,
that would be a pretty big move, but I'm
not going to rule it out. All right. If
this market wants to go trend, which
would be outside of initial balance, if
the market wants to go trend, these are
your targets. All right. This is a
weekly target. This is previous day low.
Is it previous day low or is it previous
week low? It's previous week low. My
bad. Previous week low. [snorts]
Yeah, runner only. Same for me. Runner
only.
It's a nice trade.
Runner [snorts] only. And I'm not going
to add back on just because we're in
rotation. I cons maybe I'd consider it
up into here if I see a strong rejection
and buyers getting caught. But really, I
just want to manage this position now
and see how low we can go. Yes. Here we
go.
Here we go. What a beauty.
[snorts]
What a beauty. Holding from 650s is a
great trade up here. Great trade. that
break. Really nice, mate. Really nice.
Okay, ES through its 20-day. Seeing if
Spy can join in. We're coming into our
50-day here on the QQQ. We want to see
VIX break out of 18. That is clearly a
put there at 18 based on the reaction
earlier. I've had that level in for
months now. If Vic starts breaking out
of 18, we can possibly get all hell will
break loose in here. [snorts]
How low can you go? How low? I I need
all these as like theme tunes when we're
doing this. All right, breaking. Lovely.
Let's see if we can get more follow
through. So into the under 500s now. Can
we get follow through downside? We just
want to see pressure. Previous week open
31. previous week low 406s. These are
some of our targets under there. We have
some old balance ranges down into the
300s if we get really lucky. [snorts]
VIX is starting to break through it.
Okay, so we would love a 5m minute close
here above it on the VIX above the 18s.
We've got one minute left on this
5minute bar. That would be really good.
[snorts]
Nice. We're going to break lower.
Looking good here.
Just be careful as spy comes into its
20-day right now. So, just be very
careful as spy comes into its 20-day
here.
Come on, VIX. I want VIX to close high
here on this 5m minute bar and then
maybe offer a little pull back into 18
and then I want them to rebid VIX and
then we'll get follow through downside.
Just manage your positions.
This is a really nice move here.
[snorts]
Little bit of shelf being developed
here. You can see it right here. So into
sort of 90s, right? a bit of a shelf
here into 90s. You can see it. You want
them to stay heavy. There we have a low
volume node up into 22s. So, you want
them to stay heavy from 90s. 22s max. It
looks like it's wants to break for that
previous week low. Here you have a buy
side delta caught offside at 11s
interestingly. So, 511 big buyside delta
spike there. [snorts] So, someone tried
to come in and buy the market there like
a bit of a wally.
No tariff news today. I don't know.
They've kicked it down. Kicked it down a
road again
like they do with everything. Cook the
books. Kick it down the road.
Everything's fine. Nothing to see here.
It's all good. Kick it down the road.
[snorts]
So, watch this shelf here. 90s. If they
squeeze, we're going to probably come up
to here. So 90s break. We have a little
nugget here.
This is where the buyer got caught who
tried to buy it there for some weird
reason, but that's what he did.
And SPY right now stopping right on its
20-day. We're now breaking below the
50-day on the queue. That is not a good
sign for the market if we stay heavy
below the 50-day, especially if we get a
2550 cross. I know lots of you don't
believe in that, but there are many
traders that use that as sentiment.
including institutions,
believe it or not.
Unlike that [\h__\h] weird old man with
glasses and a cap who wants to tell you
otherwise. But hey,
70s here now. Let's see if we can get I
really want to get to 30s and even 06.
Just nailed $800 short and 300 away from
passing a Lucid Eval. Congratulations,
man. Glad I was able to help you with
that.
Slipping off my chair. [snorts]
All right. Make sure you're not entering
short down here. I mean, those who trade
with me know that. Look how you're
extended from flow zones. You're
extended from any kind of level. We are
developing a little shelf here, but you
would not really want to be entering
short here. There is a little shelf
here, but you do not want to be entering
short here. Your short opportunity was
like on this break, even here, maybe
even this here. I think is where I got
in. Yeah, you are extended away now.
600 each on my PAS, 400 each on my
Evals. Let's go, buddy. Let's go.
Made some money back. I lost from
overtrading yesterday. That's good. Just
passed a 50K on two nice calls, Alex.
Nice work. Nice work, everyone. Yeah,
everyone passing evals, making money.
Congrats. If you've not made money
today, if you've lost money today, or
maybe you've made some errors, just take
a step back, take your foot off the gas,
just peaked over this little gray box.
Remember, we're thin in here. Like I
said, there is offside delta at 12. So,
this guy right here, it's a big buyside
outlier. big big buy side outlier there.
[snorts]
So I'm interested how we react into that
12s and if we get above we're going to
retest the IB. All right, this is your
sentiment for the day. This is actually
a really nice day now because you have
initial balance, previous week value
area low, current day value area low,
all pretty tight. All right, so as long
as you reject that, you're looking for
trend day lower. If you reclaim that,
then we're going to go into a rotational
market. So you have a clear level of
confluence here with three levels all
lined out together. All right. So, you
can use this sort of gray box here as
your sentiment for the day. Are we going
in a trend lower or are we going in a
rotation? This will tell you how we act.
Do we stay heavy outside of there into
there? Do we fail to get above or do we
just go above, reclaim, and start going
back inside value?
[snorts]
Three W's today. My best day of the
week. Thanks for the assistance. You're
welcome.
Oh, Jason, I had to say, my friend, I'm
really sorry to hear that. I feel I
mean, all of us got [\h__\h] by Khaled.
What an absolute See you next Tuesday.
I'm sorry to hear that. Lucid won't do
the same to you, though. AJ's a good
dude.
Okay, here comes the retest. So, this is
the outlier right here into where did I
say 11s and twelves. If we squeeze
through this, we're going to test this
gray box above. But this is where the
buyer got stuck before. If we squeeze
through this, we're going to retest the
box above. So far, we can't even get
through that outlier I just talked
about. [snorts]
No close above that outlier yet.
So, the outlier is at 12. We just peaked
to 14 and instantly sold off. So, he's
still stuck up there. If we get through
him, then we will retest this. I would
not be long, guys. The only time I would
consider a long today is if you reclaim
all these levels and look at like
something like this. At the moment,
you'd be looking short anywhere in here
for a continuation. You do not want to
short the low of day. You're looking to
short pops off good levels.
I show you the outlier. See this guy? I
don't know if you can see this guy.
This guy right here. And it's out. Oh,
where's he gone?
It's outlier by volume, right? Delta buy
at 12. So around there, he's stuck. He
is stuck. So you can lean on his pain
for now if you want. If you're already
in this all the time he's out the money,
you can lean on his pain. If he starts
to reclaim, we're going to touch up
here. [snorts]
Going to have a little break for a bit.
Just a moment here. I'm going to stay
with you guys cuz my neck's sore, my
head's sore. This is a lot of work for
me. Like cognitive load compared to what
I've had to deal with this week. So, I'm
not super fresh here.
Just give my eyes a break for a minute.
You've got the levels to look at.
How many uh likes we got on this stream?
I want to do some giveaways coming into
the new hour.
Man, over half of you just not smash
that like button. Come on. Come on,
team. There's over 500 of you watching
here. Just smash that like button for
me.
Smash
the like button for me and we'll do some
giveaways.
Divergence on uh cumulative delta. Let
me have a look for you.
Looks all right on
NQ. Oh, you said ES. Let me check. Yes,
for you.
Uh, no, there.
No, it looks all right.
Looks all right.
I'm looking on a five minute though.
Maybe you maybe you're seeing some
divergence on a lower time frame than
that. On a five minute looks all right.
No, I can't see any divergence. the
highs and low peaks are uh in line.
Okay, you can see again we can't get
through that player at 11. I just gave
that to you or 12, wherever it was. That
player that we talked about, I showed
you him on the Delta profile. He is
still stuck at those twelves, right?
He's still stuck at the twelves for now.
Trader Rick, thanks for joining, my
fellow Brit. I hope BISE is treating you
well.
Where is Discord? Discord comes as part
of the um beginner to advance program,
right? So, if you do the beginner to
advance course, it's uh I haven't even
had a chance to put the prices up like I
was supposed to. That's how ridiculous
this year has been. It is then still 649
right now. All right, 649. It's a 20hour
course. You get a version of the flow
zone indicators come with that and
discord all included in a price onetime
fee. That isn't a monthly fee. It's a
onetime fee. There is no free discord.
It's only for people who do the course.
I've talked about this many times. The
reason being I like trading with people
who trade the same way. It's important
especially for occasions like the last
few weeks when I'm not there that
everyone knows what they're looking at
and are trading in the same way. If you
want to do a top up, there is I think
it's about 7h hour course now on trading
volume profile and order flow. All
right, which went live just before
Christmas. That is 399 I think.
Thanks to Richardson's appreciate it.
What city did I live in when I was in
the UK? I was in London. Originally from
Sussex, but I moved to London in my
teens and never left until I moved here.
Oh, well, yeah. I mean, you're seeing
bullish delta. Yeah, you're seeing
bullish delta on ES, but there was no
divergence because it's matching what
we're doing. So, the I'm seeing bullish
delta even on the cues here and here,
but we're seeing the market try and move
higher. Where that would be a problem is
if we're doing this and we're seeing
bullish delta. That would be the
divergence, right? [snorts]
Oh, MSTU. Did you really um Can you ree
me, my friend? Can you email me again
and um I'll sort that out.
Awesome, Stephen. That's great news.
Congrats on passing.
Thanks, Rosco. Yeah, I mean, the way
that the way the course works is because
it's from beginner to advance, I have to
do it as if you've never traded before
and then it builds and builds and builds
and builds, right? So [snorts]
I have to assume someone's got no
knowledge. It might be that you did the
course and then had knowledge and then
as we get through it gets more dense
with information once you've got a good
base.
[snorts and clears throat]
So this market still can't get through
those sort of 12 levels. If it can get
through 12elves, there'll be relief up
into here. At the moment, every pop into
these twelves, this little edge here is
being sold. You can see this is starting
to get thicker and thicker and thicker
sort of around here, right? And more
clear, I'd say even around here, more
clear dips are holding into this at the
moment. Relief will be back into this.
This is the sentiment up here. I want to
see the market trade into this. And we
can make a decision how we act from
there. Ideally, something like this or
if you're looking for the range
rotation, then you're looking for that
move there.
I might well be done. This is my first
day back, so
want to force too much.
That's the kind of course I need. Yeah,
they're all available on the website,
guys. I would advise you grab them soon.
not not for my own benefit, but I did
say prices were going up in 2026, but um
as you know, I've been dealing with
personal matters and I have not been
able to adjust anything. I had haven't
had the time to do anything yet. So,
prices will go up. They should have gone
up already. That is my fault.
All right. Still hanging around this big
delta outlier. Can they cause the
squeeze up to those sort of 30s, 40s,
that kind of level?
Got a bit of a spoofer on the tape up
there right now into the 530s. He just
left the tape. Right, time for my first
bathroom break bake of the day. We all
know what that means. Probably come back
and we're 100 points lower, but let's
see. All right, be right back.
Oh, it's a reverse bathroom break. I
can't remember the last time that
happened. [snorts] Okay.
[laughter]
Yes, daily. This is daily. Yeah, I'm
here Monday to Friday 6:15 Oh, sorry,
9:15 for you guys. 9:15 Eastern all the
way into lunch.
All right. All the way into lunch.
What platform do I need to trade on when
you're joining your course? Uh, it's up
to you, but I teach on Trading View. All
right. So, you can just get a free
edition of Trading View. That's what I
teach on. I go through it all on the
course like literally the first few
modules we talk about it.
[laughter]
I purposely I did a double flush JD
hoping it would move lower. [snorts]
[laughter]
Okay, ES back into IB. We've just done
the same. So this gray box being tested
now. Remember this is the area we talked
about. This is current value area low on
the day which we just tested and failed.
Right? Think about the edge of blue to
gray right here. This is previous weak
value area low just above. This is
initial balance. This is an area of
sentiment. One, two legs. Do they sell
this now and look to break lower? If
we're having a trend day, that's what
we're going to look to do.
If we're going to reclaim, right, then
we're going to go back inside value and
probably come all the way up there.
Those are the two trades. Right now,
we're looking like a trend day. Looks
very, very good right now.
Remember, if you're short, if you just
took that short while I just left that
push up, you want to be respecting these
levels here. You want to be moving your
stop down. You want to be protecting
some and then holding to see if you get
expansion. There's no guarantee of
expansion.
>> [snorts]
>> Looking good here. Did anyone take that
short just while I stepped away? That
was the gray box.
Yes. Yes, I do. um da in the afternoons
give [snorts] the levels I'm looking at
any specific trades when I'm especially
if there's like an active setup a good
setup.
Yeah, lots of you got short there. Nice
work team. Great work. So already
looking good for you. You should be like
s 20 30 points. Just respect these these
kind of levels here. 500s down into
these 90s, right? Respect respect this
area. If you get a break underneath this
483, then I think you're going to look
really good. But just respect this. We
know buyers came in around this area
we're at right now, the whole number.
Respect these levels,
right? Whether that means moving your
stop break even, whether it means moving
your stop positive 1R, whether it means
taking a little partial, it's up to you.
But just respect the levels.
Really clean rejection on ES as well.
that um IB very very very clean.
Okay, into these 90s. Now, we talked
about this gray box, this node here at
92. You want to see the market move
under this and stay heavy for you to
continue to hold. Now, it's retesting a
big level here. This gray node right
here, you want to see the market move
under it and stay heavy.
What IB do you use? Yes, 1 hour. That's
uh for me that's the only IB initial
balance, the first hour.
Also, everyone else in chat, love, uh
I'm looking at course at the moment. Do
you call out the entries on your trades?
Help us along the way. I mean, isn't
that what we've been doing all morning?
Telling you the levels to look at, where
we're looking to go, what the setups
are.
Pretty sure that's what I've done, which
is why all you guys got short when I
went to the bathroom. That's You
literally had it there. I literally told
you what to do.
Nice, Danny.
Oh, on Discord. Yes, in in the
afternoons. That is in the afternoons if
there's a setup I like. Yes. And it's
not just about me. It's fellow members
do the same when they're looking at
something. They more often than not we
say I'm looking at this level, looking
for this level to hold, looking for
expansion here, looking for rotation
here. That's the whole reason we have
the discord for members only. So
everyone trades the same way. I'm still
looking like this market is trying to
find dips at 94s. We want to see it move
under that. For all you guys who are
already shorts,
big seller coming in here. You need
continuation lower now because they're
starting to be aggressive. There's a
passive buyer starting to absorb 500s.
We need to see this be aggressive lower
soon for you guys to be comfortable
because if they keep absorbing here,
you're going to see a lot of sellers get
caught. So, we want to see this break
lower and stay heavy under this gray box
for you guys. Right? There's someone
absorbing the tape in here right now
because we just had a big market seller
come in. Right? We're looking for this
for you guys. If you don't do it and we
start to reclaim this, you do not want
to be like holding and readding.
There's a chance for a flush straight
down to 80s here if they let this go.
It's pretty thin between this right now.
Let me just change this book map in case
I can't see
being passive. There we go.
>> [sighs]
>> I think there's a chance to move to 80s.
Right. Be very careful here if they
start to reclaim. You want these this
push up here into these imbalances to
fail. And we have some imbalances here.
You want this to fail. You want this.
Show you
right here.
Right. The problem right now is this
aggressive seller didn't get his way.
Might be that we need to drift into this
and then you'd be looking for that here.
You have to cover some into these. And
if you get lucky, you get a break lower.
This guy right here is stuck right now.
Stomach is rumbling. I need to eat.
You're long 255 534. I mean you're why
there's no close back above you. Even if
you got that right, look at the draw
down you're having to sit through. Let
it close back above and hold that. I
would say [snorts]
rather than on that first test like it
might you might well be right but let it
close back above and hold that level and
prove to you okay we want to go back in
rotation at the moment there's nothing
to say it wants to prove to go back in
rotation where you've got long
back into this delta again the same
level as we had earlier at twelves
reselling that twelves there you go so
this is the imbalance that we just
talked about. You want that pop to sell.
You need a break lower now. All right?
Because they've popped up. They've sold
it. Point control shifting lower. You
need a break lower now. You do not want
to see this just hang around in this
this area for a long time. It needs to
start breaking lower for you guys to be
comfortable. It's just filled that
imbalance. It's failed where we had that
old delta level. It's the same level
I've talked about for the last, I don't
know, 20 minutes, the twelves. Now, it
needs to break lower. It's as simple as
that. It has to start breaking lower.
Otherwise, you're going to have too many
sellers get caught here. [snorts]
Here they go. They're going to try here.
Can they get a break?
Here they come. This is where the seller
was stuck. They need a break now down to
80s. There you go. Right. So now, can
they get follow through? You don't want
to see them start to hold this. This is
where that seller got stuck last time
that I talked about. You got to get
underneath sort of 84s. You get very
comfortable when you get under 84s for a
break of low day.
So far, they're tr they're still trying
to absorb these levels. There are buyers
down at 80s and 77s. I'm somewhat
surprised we didn't just trade into
that, but still a passive buyer down
here. Clearly,
clearly unwilling to let this retrade
the lows.
This shelf here becoming very very very
important now. This right here.
[snorts]
Do you have a free video on how to trade
with anchored volume profile? Uh there
is a video on like volume profile
mastery. You can just do it on there. I
don't use the anchor on that, but it's
the same. It's exactly the same concept.
It's literally identical. Doesn't matter
if you use anchored or fixed or
whatever. There the same concept.
New to trading and I only use top step
with one screen. Would this course be
good with that setup? I mean top step's
just a just a prop firm. It's got
nothing to do with anything else. You
need to learn to trade. It doesn't
matter what you trade on. You need to
learn to trade.
Doesn't matter what what you trade on.
The concepts are the same. You can trade
on any platform you want.
All right, you can see them rebidding
500s here. 100 lot there at 500s. Still,
they can't get a close over 12. This is
starting to look very, very, very messy.
Someone is going to get hurt here soon.
They cannot sit here forever and ever.
Exactly level two. Exactly that. Point
control and psych level now. and gray
box. All of it. Node there. Everything.
Vick's pulling back in a little bit as
well. Bit of a twoleg back inside after
squeezing through 18s. Let's see if they
rebid on VIX for that curl and go. And
if they do, then we'll get downside.
They don't
and maybe we do go back into range
today.
Time will tell. This is why I'm saying
for that short that you guys took, you
have to be proactive.
You have to respect what we built out
beforehand.
Okay. Through those twelves now or
attempting to get through the twelves.
ES back to IB.
If they start reclaiming, there is
obviously that IB to VWAP potential
trade on the ES. Same kind of story on
the ENQ. If they do start reclaiming
this shelf and they do find a rebid,
right? If this is a fail, if this
becomes a failure to break lower, right,
and they do do this move, this is
possible. Absolutely possible. Big if
because we're nowhere near reclaiming,
right? If this is a fail break and we
reclaim and base, this here becomes
possible. But at the moment, it's way
too early to say that. There's still
quite a good chance that they can move
down into this, but time will tell.
Back to the 500s again.
135 lot here looking to be picked up.
Did they sell through him and trade 90s?
That's the next level really. Nothing
really in between.
There
they go. Reclaim instantly. Do they
resell? No, not yet.
Little shuffle here at 500s. Just
watching the tape.
Back under 500. Still no follow through
down to the 90s and 80s.
ES came back up to the IB rejected so
far, but still no big close. It's right
at its 20-day. That's the big problem.
So, if you look at the spiders, they bid
off the 20-day. The low of day was the
20-day SMA on the spiders.
I think we should see followrough. It's
just like here we go. Finally. Now, can
they get under 90s? Get 84s is the big
level. I think we talked about
sort of under here under 84s and then
maybe they get down into this. We will
see. Time will tell.
Rebidding 90s again. Oh, this look messy
tape.
What are the horizontal lines in the
gray that show the volume? Well, you've
you've just answered it, my friend.
They're volume. That's what they are.
They're they are volume.
[snorts]
What does it mean when I say reclaiming?
Well, if we've traded, look, if we think
about if we've broken under this level
and we've retested it, we're still
heavy. If we get above and hold above,
that is a reclaim. All right, is bull
saying no, we're controlling this level
now to go back upside.
This gray box still holding
still trading between here and here
right now.
This just looks pretty ugly at the
moment.
What's the time? 8:20. Do a giveaway in
a minute. If this market just goes to
sleep, we'll do a giveaway.
Yeah, I've got PC down here now on
Ninja. I know it hasn't moved it down
here, but for me, PC's flipped down here
at 500s, not up here. I agree.
Okay, back into the IB
and see if they do reclaim or they
reject. I' I'd use this as a rough level
from 530 to 560. I'd use it as a 30
point range here.
And if they do reclaim, we can't rule
out the move to 80 and 600 613
or relief.
[sighs]
Right. Maybe we do one giveaway now and
then we'll do one top of the hour. Let's
do that. I'm getting bored. I want you
guys to be happy. [snorts]
All right. Where's Nightbot?
Thanks, mate. Appreciate it. Appreciate
it loads.
All right,
you guys know the score. Just type FZT
once in chat. It's the code you can use
on most prop firms to get you the best
possible discount.
FZT flow zone trader. Just type it once
and we'll pull a uh random winner.
Starting to lift this market now up to
that previous week value area low. Give
you guys a couple more minutes to do
that.
And like I said, ES ESIB to VV up taking
place. That's already about to tap it
already, but maybe a trade for Tyson
there. I don't know. The reclaim. That
is the reclaim. Someone asked what's the
reclaim. This is a reclaim. All right,
we've reclaimed this key level. The next
drift is into 83s and then all the way
up into here into 12s. All right, so
that is quite literally the reclaim we
just talked about
guys. Just a tiny bit more time
into that previous week value area low.
Uh, next step is
gray box and then the twelves. So, what
I'm going to do is just remove this now.
Don't need that
gray box and then the twelves
All right, let's pull this winner,
guys. You guys who spammed it won't win.
I should have said that. I felt like I
said it every time. But if you spam it,
you don't win.
Okay, the winner is Paul.
Paul 1 1906, are you here? Paul
1 1906, are you here, my friend?
Yes. There you go. Okay, Paul, all I
want you to do is send me an email
info@flowzonetrader.com
and just send me a screenshot of you
logged into your YouTube. I'm making a
note of your name now. And uh once we
get off the stream, I'm going to sort
you out with a free Apex account. I'll
send you a code. You can use it for any
size Apex account you want. Remember,
right now Apex is on sale 80% off.
They kindly support us on this show and
if you use code FCT, that helps me get
more codes. I can give them back to you
and it's a rinse repeat. All right.
All right. Back to trading. We'll do
another giveaway uh at the top of the
hour when I finish.
I'm sure none of you have emailed me
here. Here we go. Uh who was it that
just emailed me? I'll reply to you
whoever won last week. Sorry about that.
Apologies about that. But I did just
reply to you.
Okay, so getting stuck up here for a
moment.
Let's see if they pull back and hold
here or even all the way down here to
507s again.
So do bulls now step in at around the
30s somewhere around here if not all the
way down here which would be ugly. Bulls
really you'd want to see them step in.
Developed a bit of profile here. This is
like kind of ugly this distribution
today. But uh maybe they hold here. If
not, back into this IB.
ES did the move. Right. When we talk
about the IB to VWAP move.
All right. Look at the reclaim. This is
actually very very clean on ES. Right.
We build and then the relief straight
into VW up. Right. We call that Tyson's
trade
because it's the trade that I made him
focus on to get him his payouts, which
he got another 4K payout today, I think
he said. And he just made another I
don't know what was it 400 on each
account or 600 on each account.
info@flowzonerader.com
info@flowzontrader.com.
We have to see how much relief they get.
If they get continuation of relief,
we're looking for VWOP and point of
control or the old point of control on
the session up here into 50s.
[sighs]
Lots of you should have
had a good day today.
So, it's just it's good for me to just
get back in the saddle and just feel
feel out what the market's feeling like.
right into that next node, the gray box.
And then above that, if you're long,
you're looking for view. So I just
messaging family here.
Am
[sighs]
I going live tomorrow? Yeah, I hope so.
Unless Unless something changes, I'll be
live for the rest of the week. Unless
something changes. My intention is to be
back to normal now as much as possible.
It might be the odd day that I have to
have off, but uh as much as possible.
We need to get these li these likes up
to 400. If we're going to do another
giveaway in 30 minutes, need at least
another 70 likes on stream, folks. Let's
get the likes up to 400 and we'll do
another giveaway at the top of the hour.
Lots of you watching this have not
smashed that like button. You do that
for me, I'll give you some free
accounts. That's the deal.
Yes, driving to its 24-hour VW up now.
We're almost at New York. Not quite. So,
we're in this little node here. Through
this, we're going to go VWAP and then
maybe even 650s. Can't rule it out.
Where's the next node? 616. Ready?
616s.
No, it's not based on reclaiming VUP
loop. It Luke, it's based on this is a
failed auction.
Okay, the market if we're going to go in
a trend day, it needs to stay heavy
versus the initial balance. We don't
stay heavy versus the initial balance.
So what we do is we create short stops
here. You guys sell that. Like I said,
you must respect structure here. We held
the uh I can't remember what level that
was. I have to look on the screen where
they got caught. 90s. We held the 90s
and we reclaimed the IB. Once we reclaim
this IB and value, there's one one trade
where it likes to go from initial
balance reclaim. It's to try and get to
a VWOP. Right? It's very very very
common. Once we reclaim an IB, if we
fail an auction outside of initial
balance, look back at the last few days.
Haven't been in here, but
right here you go.
Fails to trade under IB, goes to VWAP.
Fails to trade above IB, goes to VWAP.
Fails to trade under IB, low of day,
right at the end of day, goes back to
VWAP. I can go back every day and you're
going to see the same thing, right? It's
very very very common.
This was a trend day. All right. So, we
never come back down. See the
difference? We print above IB. We print
above IB. We expand. It wasn't like we
looked above and failed and came back
down. That never happened. There was no
look above and fail.
Right. Rejecting gray box for now.
It's an interesting one. This it can't
get up there. It very very possibly
comes all the way back down into this
shelf here. Right now, I would say bears
got caught under here and the drift
higher is very very much possible. But
we'll see unless the broader market
starts getting weak.
40 is possible here. 58. They're bidding
50s. Can they flush 40s? And then do
they move lower than that? We will see
in time.
[snorts]
How do you identify the initial balance?
Uh it is the first hour of trading. So
if you go from your 9:30 to your 10:30,
all right, just get a 30 minute chart.
9:30 to 10:30, mark out the high and the
low. That's all you have to do. Yeah, IB
is initial balance. Quite right. No
worries, Luke.
Thanks, Green.
Slow return for me, but it's nice to be
back a little bit.
I'll get you give you a readout on the
mag so you can see where they're at.
Tesla just over 2% down. Nvidia just
over 2% down. Microsoft 1.54% down. Meta
1.65% down. Google 0.83% down. Amazon
1.81% down. Apple 1% down. As an equally
weighted MAG, all right, if the MAG were
equally weighted ETF, uh we are 1.58%
down. Seeing some weakness in chips
though like Oracle 4% down AVGO 5.25%
down
tech se sector definitely getting hit.
We have a look at the breadth. Let me
have a quick look on
[sighs] how this market's looking.
Okay. So, consumers doing okay, real
estate doing all right, utilities doing
all right, healthcare doing all right,
tech down heavy, consumer
uh defense is okay. Sorry, not not
consumers. Consumer defense when I said
that was an error on my behalf. So, let
me bring this over for you. Can I
squeeze this in?
All right. If we look at the breadth
right names in the S&P in the S&P all
right in the S&P this is this is
basically your ENQ all right ENQ getting
whacked it doesn't have strength in
healthcare or energy.
All right.
So, the weaker we're in the weaker asset
here, right back down to these 40s while
I got caught monologuing like I was just
talking about. This is the big level
now.
Yeah, Peter. At least at least for me
personally, yes, I'm still managing some
positions in those that I've had from
last year, but yes,
I'm certainly not buying the froth.
All right, ES rejecting the VWOPS coming
back down to its IB. We're doing the
same trade here. Now the question is
does it hold the initial balance now or
is this a two leg which gets sold into?
All right, so this level here key is
this a twoleg which is now sold into
i.e. is this a huge bare flag one two
which is now sold into or do they rebid
this area here which they've been
bidding all day?
I'm still in all my positions. Uh but
remember my positions are long-term
positions as in for like most of them
are forever holds if not one to two year
swings.
Yeah. So I'm not I'm I'm not like
oversized in something. Uh it's not like
a trade for a couple months. Most of my
positions are longterm. So, I can tell
you right now I'm down a little bit on
Netflix, which I opened yesterday. Just
tiny tiny tiny positions to get my feet
wet. Uh, Meta I'm still up on. Very,
very small amount. Uh, Amazon I'm up
8.37% on. AMD I'm still up 37% on, but I
locked in 80 90% of my profits there.
And Apple I'm still up 22% and and I'm
not looking to sell that.
These are like core positions that I try
and hold.
Even if I go through draw down in some
of these over a year or [snorts]
whatever longterm, I'm confident in the
assets I'm buying. They're less specul
uh speculatory buys. They're more like
position buys on vehicles that I think
have potential for more growth in the
future.
All right, ES trying to find a bid in
front of IB. We are right on IB right
now. How much time we got left? Running
out of time. 20 minutes left.
It is possible we go into a bit of a
rotation down here for a while if it
can't make its mind up.
17 to 20 ft.
[snorts]
Has
it been like this the rest of the week,
guys? You get some nice moves early and
then has it been going to sleep?
I guess there's not been much follow
through looking at the daily
rejecting this kind of shelf here. Now,
this is key.
Previous week value area low, we did
just reject it. And that gray sh that
gray box, we just rejected in front of
it.
But we're inside IB. They're just
stacking both sides now. The bookmat
looks awful. It's just uh
stacking both sides. And the bid and the
ask, it's not very pretty.
Don't think there's a huge amount of
edge in here right now.
Yeah, definitely left sellers caught
around those 500s right now.
No doubt about it. It's just can they
get back down to them? Let them out or
not.
in bitmap for stacking pulling do I just
look at the DOM or do I have some other
kind of tool I don't use any tools for
bit map naked as naked as possible for
me
I'm back yeah I'm back I'm back I'm glad
to be back all right back to IB Again,
they're trying to aggressively sell
through here. There's still a passive
buyer on IB
Delta
still in line. No big divergence here.
Maybe ES wants to come for its VIB.
Maybe we come down to this delta at 12.
I don't know. Just looks a bit iffy
right now. the tape. It's just looks
like they don't know what they actually
want to do with it. Normally, I'd be
thinking about leaning on this short
side, but uh
first day back and all
and it's definitely been a passive buyer
just like trying to absorb everything.
Just waiting for him to piss off and for
like market to have like strong
momentum. We're not really seeing that.
We're just hanging around at the IB low.
Here
comes the selling. They're trying to
force it again. Seller coming in here.
And again, some absorption taking place.
Someone is gobbling it up today on every
like major pull. Even though we've moved
lower, someone is like adamant on
gobbling it up. Just waiting for him to
disappear out the tape.
Yeah, exactly. And they keep reloading
that bid.
Maybe like like I said, there's there's
delta outlier at 12. Point of control is
actually at 500. So like this is still
the level down here. If this is a twoleg
that we then sell into. All right, we're
starting to see this here. If they don't
rebid this, this is where we get a
breakaway from. All right, so we've come
back up. These boxes were here.
Remember, we missed we just missed the
VWAP tag, but we had divergence because
ES did hit its VWAP. There's your two
leg. There's the backside of this,
right? This is the question now. Do they
rebid here, right? Or do they lose this
now? And we've got these levels to
attack.
They're not making it easy though, I'll
tell you that much.
So, here's that move into those twelves
again. Remember, we've talked about
those twelves all day. Over under, over
under when we're under them, we kept
rejecting and rejecting, rejecting,
rejecting, rejecting. Now, we've come
right back to them into this gray box.
So, let's see how we act. They rebid
this order. The bid start to lose
traction. ES back into its initial
balance low and its 20-day. All right,
that's the key thing. Q's bid off their
50-day today. We've already lost the
20-day. We're trading between the 50-day
and the 20-day right now on the Q's. ES
little bit stronger. It's bidding off
its 20-day at the moment. Hello. I'm
glad you're back. Question. How long
have you been trading and how long until
you became profitable? Um, I've been
back at it full-time for
six and a half, seven years. I was
trading before that in my uh like early
20s.
It took me a while to adjust to futures.
Um, took me a while to adjust to
futures.
I probably been trading solely futures
for
we at now three or four years.
I started in in in like swing
investments and then I moved from that
um into like small caps and then smaller
mids and then large caps and then just
into futures.
No worries.
All right, back to these twelves again.
Big old delta outlier here. Point of
control just below that 500.
That big standout number. Someone trying
to buy this again. I don't think he's
going to get his way. I think he's going
to get washed out here. Here we go. He's
going to get washed out.
Oh, could have, would have, should have.
That was probably a very good short
here.
All right. So, if you took that, you'd
be covering some here now. And wait to
see now if you get that breakaway. One,
two, backside. If you get a breakaway
under here, you can attack this level.
Okay. Looks like you're going to get it.
Here's the 500s. I told you that buyer
here, you can see he's been too
aggressive and he's going to get himself
caught. So, cover some into this. Now,
the TP some into this because you got to
respect looking left at what we have.
And if you get a breakaway under here,
you can look for the 400s. All right.
get a breakaway underneath, you can look
for the 400s. Don't expect it. It's if
you get it, you can hold your runner for
that.
Small caps are fun trading. Yeah, I
mean, I left it dried up for like must
be a good couple years. Um,
took some big losses in small caps,
though. It's way too aggressive. Had
some really bad habits.
Hence, creating my flow zones is the
whole reason
the whole reason I created this whole
thing, right? Losing point of control
bottom side of this shelf. Now, if
buyers don't start showing up soon,
you're going to get a breakaway towards
those lows that we've talked about.
[snorts]
Where are they bidding? 80s7s. The guy
is still below like we talked about
earlier. Yeah, 50s. Yeah, here comes the
breakaway, guys. Here's the low of day
value area low here. So, cover point
here. And let's see if you get that
breakaway to previous week value uh
previous week low all the way down here
if you get lucky. And if you get through
that, there's a big block down here. So,
this has just built out loads of
liquidity on a two-leg. And now we can
see if we break away from this gray box,
right? Ideally, we break away from this
gray box for those of you short and you
can make a ton of money. All right.
Ideally, you get something like this
now. Oh, let me draw it for them before
it goes without me. Ideally, you get
something like this now. That' be the
most ideal move. You do not want to see
this. That's a failed look below again,
right? You don't want it to reclaim
this. All right. If they cannot use this
area to protect, if they cannot short
here, I'd probably be done with it for
the day to be quite honest. Oh, where
have you gone? Right. They want to use
this volume to trade lower from. If they
can't use that volume to trade lower
from, it will be problematic.
Lots of bids underneath here for it to
trade down to. It's just uh
Are they going to let it happen? How
long got to lunch? 13 minutes. They
should They should let it happen.
So, this gray box so far rejecting. It's
what you want to see. And you want a new
lower day
and then down into here. All right. So,
you're looking for gray box to reject.
Break underneath this. Use all the stops
to get down into here. That's uh that's
what you're looking for at the moment.
You do not want it to reclaim the gray
box. A reclaim of gray box means leave
it the f alone. All right. If it
reclaims the top side of this gray box,
just leave it alone. Be done with the
day. But all the time we're doing this
right now, we look good. See if we can
get a snap of this low of day and then
if we can get down to previous week
open, which is 30s, and previous week
low, which is 06s. [snorts]
>> [snorts]
>> And we've got 10 minutes left. I want to
do another giveaway. Have you got me up
to enough likes yet? You still have not.
We said 400. We're at 362. So, we need
just under We need 38 more likes on
stream. And we'll do another giveaway.
Yeah, I agree. I agree. You can see them
here on the book. Like 70s, 60s, 40s. Is
there anyone below 40s? There's some
thin stuff and then down to the 400s,
which is where I would like to see us
trade today. If we're going to get weak,
that would be like a really good cover
point.
What you are looking for
is this right. TP1, TP actually there is
a TP2 which will be at 30
TP 2 TP3 anything beyond that is a gift
down into here and if we think about
that as an extension let's see off this
two leg could we get there well we can
definitely get into previous week low
and a measured move would be it's not
it's not un it's not not doable you know
it is possible but this is more probable
This is possible.
Let's see if you get follow through now.
All right, you taking the low out. Let's
see if we get follow through now down
into here for you guys.
Looks good. Looks good. It just took a
while to develop. Looks good.
It's a shame this popped up as much as
it did uh and didn't make this. But uh
ES was very clean. Very very clean.
[snorts]
Here you go. So congrats if you got
this.
Looks really good now folks. You built
all these buyers now have come in in
this two leg. Just think about this.
They bid here. They bid here. They bid
here. They got caught. We're moving
away. We're going to use all their
liquidity. Remember 30s I said is
previous week open. 32s is previous week
open. That's your TP2. So TP1,
TP2, TP3. And if you get lucky, you get
into this block. All right. It's looking
great. Fantastic trade, folks.
Fantastic trade.
Really nice.
And we're short on the weakest assets.
Exactly what we want to be doing.
Good confluence. Pay yourself along the
way. Hopefully get the 30s for that
previous week open, but if not, you can
just pay yourself on the way down. Don't
be too greedy. But this looks really
good for a breakaway.
I very rarely do Asia. I live in I live
in Los Angeles, mate. I have to I have
to sleep at some point, right? I have to
sleep at some point. Unless I think that
Asia is setting up with something really
good because we've had like some major
consolidation during uh the New York
session or something. It's very rare
that I trade Asia.
You're very close to those 30s. Don't be
a dick for a couple points or whatever
and pay yourself along the way here.
Spiders into these uh
20-day moving average. Let's see if they
flush through this 20-day. Let's see if
uh VIX can go back through the 18s. It's
very very close.
But nice a nice trade to end the stream
there.
So you are in a trend day scenario here.
We are in a expansion model here. Right?
We rejected previous week value area
low. We've rejected IB on the return
back in. All right. We squeezed over.
This was a bull trap and we are in
expansion mode. So we're looking for
this and this. Now
do not be buying this. There's no reason
to buy it. It's not held.
>> [snorts]
[sighs]
>> Lots of bids coming in here. They're
trying to get this back up to that
shelf. They want to get out, break even.
They're trying to get out to that shelf
to get themselves out. I don't think
they'll be able to do it, but you never
know.
That's what they're attempting to do. I
think the more of them that come in and
force it, the more they're going to get
hurt.
Alex injustice bought the order flow
course. Do you need anything to
activate? No. Like if you've bought it,
it will it will show in your uh when you
log in to the back end of the Flowzone
community, it will show there. If it's
not there, just shoot me an email. Or it
might be that you've used a different
email or something to originally and I
can add it add it back onto your profile
for you.
Another sell re-entry. I mean the only
place would be this can act as
resistance low volume node. All right.
So if they sell this and if they drift
up here. So there could be a sell here.
There could be a sell here. What you
would not want to do if it does this,
I'd be done with sells for the day. All
right. If it reclaims this level here, I
would be done with cells for the day
until that point. Yeah, just look to
keep looking for these
trader doc. You're welcome.
Sup, homie? Just found your channel. Do
you use fixed range volume profile in
your setups? Uh, it's very similar. It's
very similar. It I'm using anchored to
the 930. Right. Anchored for the New
York print. It's exactly the same thing
as what you're talking about.
It's just the only way I can have it on
the right hand side. Okay. Here you go,
folks. You're getting very close to
previous week open now. 430s cover
point. Previous week open through that
previous week low. You look fantastic.
Here
we go. Very, very close to the 30s. Like
I always say, don't be a dick for a
tick. Especially remember, you got 5
minutes until the new H1. Don't be
stupid and be like waiting for
everything and get caught out in an H1
spike. At least at the very least move
your stop into the money. Um, excellent
analysis. Had multiple wins with you
today. Again, first day, best I found so
far. Thank you, my friend. Means a lot.
It's very kind of you. Thanks. You
helped me a lot with my strategy today.
You're welcome.
So, reclaim of 25500 is over for shorts.
Uh, yeah. Yeah. Basically, I'd say you
want to be very careful. If we do this
and hold, all right, then we're going to
leave shorts versus here trapped. And
then this opens up this move here for a
grind back. Like you, we've done a
two-leg pullback. All right, the
pullbacks happened. We've lost IB. We've
lost previous week's value. We're
trading lower. If we start reclaiming
these levels, it means sellers didn't
come in aggressive enough to force us
lower. You don't want to be short. If we
start reclaiming a level like this, all
right, because we're going to get
squeezed out, you also don't want to be
short if we start taking out all the
lowhanging fruits. All right, remember
our low hanging fruits, we're starting
to take them out.
Market only wants to move so far. Let's
like, you know, be realistic here. Our
trades today, we started getting short
up here. I think it was
right somewhere up here.
for this move and then we reshorted or
you guys reshorted this. I think I
reshorted this for this move and then
some of you took this for here and then
this breakdown here for here. There's
only so much. All right. If we get if if
panic comes in, great. Well, we're going
to be covering the flushes on panic. We
don't want to enter new short positions
as we trade deep into discount, do we?
because this blue box is a 2W week
value area low which means it's a very
very discounted range. All right, we can
look at that. We talked about it right
at the beginning
of the day.
All right, right here.
Right. So, if we leave this, we are now
starting to trade into this. We are
leaving this
Okay, we want to be careful as we trade
into here.
Yeah, 400s is a big big big level. 400s
and what's that? 350.
400s and 350 is a very very very very
big level. [snorts]
So, we don't want to keep adding short
the closer we get to it. Think about
riskreward. If you are adding short down
here as we're getting closer to target,
your risk is getting bigger, your reward
is getting smaller.
Great job today, Alex. It's totally
impressive. Thanks, man. Great session
today. You're welcome. Jade,
how do you personally manage stress
regulating the nervous system with
scalping quick decisions or after a
session? uh breath work for me. Yeah,
breath work for me. So, I went and did a
breath work course probably three years
ago now. I did a three-month breath work
breath work course. I then did after I
did that, I did an instructor's course
cuz I enjoyed it so much. And I use
breath work to regulate myself both
before I come on stream sometimes if I'm
in a stressful trade, which is kind of
rare nowadays unless I've made a mistake
or if it's an A+ and I'm sizing up. Um,
but yeah, you might need to do if if
you're finding stuff tough, you probably
need to do a nervous system reset. It's
like a double breath in, single breath
out for a long time and be looking at
getting better and better and better at
doing that.
Thanks, Ero.
Oh, I can't remember. I'd have to look
it up. I'd have to look it up. Um, my
instructor, I'm actually going to a
class today in Venice. Uh, Daisy Daisy
Mack spiritual mixtape. You can look her
stuff up. Good friend of mine.
Would
I consider today a break of structure on
the hourly? Let's have a look.
Let's have a look together. Let's just
do it on here.
It's very hard, man, cuz we're just in
consolidation. Technically, yes. On the
hourly, technically, yes, we're leaving
this. This was the attempt at the new
high. Yes, technically. But the biggest
swing points are here. This is why this
is so big. And this is the old PC,
right? Technically, yes, I would agree.
But, you know, look how many weeks and
sessions we've spent in range here. It's
very messy. You want to be very careful
oversizing on what we consider a break
on an hourly structure if there's a lot
of support like sat down here
from this. Right? This is why I just
said 400s to 350s is such a big level.
Right? If we start losing this, we can
think about good night market. Right?
All right. Into lunch here. I'm going to
want to pull another winner. Have we got
enough likes? All right, guys. You need
to help me out here.
What did we say? 400. Are we not there
yet?
We need 17 likes. 17 likes and we do
another Apex giveaway. [snorts]
What's the settings for AP? That's
right. Right. I use ticks. If you're
using rows, you can just do a thousand.
I use ticks per row only because then it
m then matches what I do on footprint
style. Just have it set to right. That's
all I change other than colors and PC.
That's it. That's all you need. That's
all you need.
Nice Jay. Welcome. Thank you. Thanks
everyone. Muhammad, thank you man. I
appreciate it. Hello my friend. [snorts]
Hello. Hello.
All right. Thanks guys. You got me to
400. Right. So I will set up some
giveaways here.
Again,
don't do it yet. Wait for me to set it
up. And please don't spam it. If you
type it more than once, all it does,
right, is ban you from the giveaway. So,
do yourself a favor. Just type it once
when you when I say so, which is now.
Okay. [snorts]
FCT. All you got to do is do it once.
Type it once.
What are the me benefits of members? Uh,
you have more chance of winning stuff
like this giveaway. You have an
increased chance of winning [snorts]
and you get more shout outs. I'll see
your questions before anyone else's.
you guys a minute to do this. All right,
just be careful. We might come and
revisit this level we just talked about.
So, we just missed 32s. We came to 39.
Like I said, don't be a dick over a few
points, especially into lunch.
So, shorts will need to hammer this. If
they don't hammer this, I'd be probably
be done with it, honestly.
Thanks, Chris. It means a lot. I really
appreciate you. I appreciate all the
love and prayers and support I've had
from everyone recently.
Have I taken any trades yet? I've called
all the trades that I've taken. Um, I
haven't traded a lot today. So,
rejection in front of this, well, in
front of the bottom of this node to be
honest. So, I can show you my score card
today. Here's my score card for you. All
right.
Um,
working my way back slowly, trading one
at a time.
Short still looks good. Let's hope they
can continue this lower. Right, going to
pull the winner here. 5 4 3
2 and 1.
I trading places. I Are you here? I
trading places. I
I trading places. I you here.
Nice.
Okay. All I need you to do, my friend,
email me a screenshot of you logged into
your YouTube so I just know it's you.
Email that to info@flowzonerader.com
and I will sort you out with a free Apex
account. Okay,
so info@flowzonerader.com.
All right, folks. That's it for me.
First day back. Not a bad day back. just
slowly slowly slowly work working my way
back into it all. Um really appreciate
everyone who's reached out to me over
the last couple weeks. It's meant a lot
honestly much more than you can ever
imagine. And um I've missed trading with
you guys. It's good fun. Good to be
back. That wasn't too much of a bad day.
I've got to feel my way back into this
market. You know, I'm not going to be
able to size up and use all my accounts
together right now until I feel mentally
sharp enough and able. Hopefully, I've
been sharp enough to help you guys make
some money today. That's all I ever want
to do is help you guys make money. Um,
for all you guys that are new and just
joined the stream, I recommend going
through my YouTube channel. There is a
ton of free education on there. All
right, go through it. It will help you
make sense of what we do when I'm
trading in here, what I'm talking about,
all the terminology, all the setups I'm
looking at. And if you want to learn
more, of course, you can do the course.
There's no pressure. There's two courses
on my website, flzzonetrader.com. Make
sure you do everything on my channel for
free first. All right, take the
education which I'm giving to you for
free first. Save your money. Only if you
want to do a full in-depth course should
you do it. All right, I will see you all
tomorrow. Those in Discord, I will pop
in this afternoon. I need a break
probably for two hours now. I've got to
take my dog out and jump on a call, I'm
afraid. But I will try and come back in
the afternoon session to help you out
with a few bits. All right, peace and
love everyone. Use hard stops. Look
after each other. Please be kind to each
other. All right? There's too much
hostility out there in the world. Be
kind to each other. Take care.