Morning
everyone. Morning. Morning. Morning.
How's it going? Hope you're doing well.
Hope you had a good weekend. Uh you're
going to have to excuse the sunglasses
today. I have got a cracking migraine.
All right. So, not here wearing them for
any other reason, but the uh bright
light in my eye from there so you can
see me is just a little too much today.
So, we're going to take it nice and easy
here. But first day that we should get
some volume back. Okay, so excited to
trade these markets with you. Hopefully,
we get some moves. Um, as always, we're
going to start on the daily and work our
way down. All right, you can see very
clearly on our open today, we're trading
inside Friday's bar. If we think about
last week's uh levels, this was previous
week. So, we're trading right probably
in the midpoint of the previous week if
we measure that out from the high to the
low. Yeah, they go right into the 50% of
the previous week. All right. And we're
trading inside the previous day and
we're coming up to a low volume node on
the yearly profile. This dates back all
of 2025 and 2026. So, a little node here
as an underover. Now you will notice in
this node we have a cluster of of SMAS.
We talked about this in weekly in the uh
yeah weekly newsletter which you should
have got Saturday morning. Right? So in
here we have the 5day, we have the
20-day and we have the 50-day. All
right. And these are pivotal for
position traders. Right? This is how we
know sentiment where we are what we're
looking to do. And when they're tightly
coiled like this, well, we don't really
have a play. What we're looking at here
is probably coiling, coiling, coiling,
coiling, coiling, and then these
starting to contract and then we're
going to see expansion one way or the
other. All right, when we get tight
coils like this, right? Because when
we're in trending markets, we will hug
the five and we will break above or we
will hug the five and we'll break below.
All right, but right now everything's
coiled. And I have a feeling we might be
like this for a while this year. You
might see some volatility in these big
range rotations because if we are
actually going to put on a top, tops
take a decent amount of time to form.
They don't happen overnight. We might
still have some of this carry trade
unwind happen. Everyone's looking for it
in a day. It can take weeks or months to
happen. And we have obviously what's
going on in Venezuela on top of that.
So, lots of volatility. Uh tech is
gapping up this morning. You will notice
most the chip names are gapping up. They
have conferences after the close today.
All right. So, possibly some front
running, some positioning from the funds
into that. Maybe we get a sell the news
tomorrow depending what the conferences
are. All right. So, let's just move down
out of the daily look at the hourlys now
and go from there. We can look at the
value areas. All right. So, here we go.
This is what's going to become
important.
Last week's value is right here and we
have a shelf here and then a big shelf
here. All right, that's previous week's
value. previous day's value is down
here. All right. So, you'll notice at
the moment we are gapping up because we
closed down here somewhere. Yeah, down
here. That was the close and we're
gapping up and we're back inside of
previous day and previous week. So, what
we're looking at this morning is are we
going to hold above Friday's value? All
right. Are we going to hold above
Friday's value? If we are right, ideally
we want a pull back in to hold previous
day value area high, previous week value
area low, and we're going to look for a
blastoff from there. What we have to be
cautious of is these levels which we've
got marked out. I'm going to remove some
of these drawings. All right, you can
see this node here. We're starting to
get over it. All right, if we hold this
node, there's one place we're going to
go. It is all the way back into PC. All
right, so really from sort of 680 to
let's call it 740. to about 60 points
here is probably where the market wants
to go and test. Right? And the question
is if we get up there, is that an area
that we're going to fade or are we going
to find acceptance? So the early plays
are do dips hold into previous day value
area high previous week? Do 600s hold
instead if it's a very shallow dip and
are we then driving up into this area
here? But once we get there, do shorts
come back in and take control and rotate
us back down for a retest or maybe even
lower or are we going to go sideways?
All right, an area of value, right,
which we've done before. And if we do go
sideways, are we then eventually going
to look for acceptance back up here to
retest previous week? So everything is
possible right now because we're trading
back inside previous week, back inside
previous day. All right, we're trading
back inside these two profiles. So,
we must be careful of rotation. But so
far, I would say this down here looks
like potential excess. Uh those who
traded with me in Discord on Friday
would know we got long down here off
this. I think it was the naked point of
control. We took this long while it was
here, wasn't it? For about 100 points
together on Discord on Friday, which is
a nice trade. All right, moving into the
five minutes. You can see what's
happened overnight. Just this chart
here. If you look above, I'll make it a
little bit bigger for you. There you go.
Right, moving into here. You can see
here's the gap. Where's the close?
Right, here's the close. Here's the gap.
Asia sideways, London expansion. We're
still driving higher at the moment. Lots
of stops here. If we do get stuck,
whether it be here or here, right, and
we get stuck back under value. Lots of
stops here to come and pop. Can't rule
that move out either. So, knowing those
edges is going to be key today. Are we
going to hold these dips? Are we going
to get stuck and rotate? Are we going to
drive up to here and five acceptance? or
we going to come up here and there's an
instant short back down. If we find
acceptance, are we going to go back to
the other side? Is there a short back
there? Is there a look above and fail?
Or is there acceptance for a new price
higher? All right, we have to be careful
today. Monday morning, first major like
trading day of the year really. So, head
on swivel is what I would say. Head on
swivel. All right, let's have a look at
some of uh the broader markets and
what's going on. I'm going to make this
gray now because this was that little
edge and we're now over it. I did
actually play a little short here, but
uh stopped out uh in profit, but I was
looking for that rotation back down.
Right, let's get into it. ES
[clears throat]
exactly the same kind of thing.
Remember, we've had relative strength on
the ES,
right? So, if we're going to start
finding acceptance, I'd say this pivot
up here is very, very key. All right, n
let's just call it 940s, right?
Acceptance above 940s might allow that
drive up. We can think about this as a
swing point.
Yeah, it's also the 61 into 46. So,
we're going to have to be careful with
that on the ES, right? Do we find
acceptance for the drive or is it just a
push which gets sold into? Remember the
last couple of weeks, released last
week, every single push was sold into.
They were dumping inventory. Is that
still going to be the case is the
question. We look at the spy,
we can think about the gamma levels, all
right, it was quite clear. We talked
about it in Discord last week, right?
680, right? 680 held. It was a pivot. It
was a gamma level right here. All right,
little flutter under and we're back
above. Right, so I'd be watching the 85s
now. Do they find acceptance over 85s
and then it'll be the same levels 88,
90, and then 700s. All right, so if
they're going to go upside, that's what
they're looking for. If they have failed
follow through versus this, you'll be
looking for them to break that and come
all the way back down.
Let's have a look at the VIX, which is
starting to grind higher. So if we just
have a look at the daily here, right,
we're coming into a pivot where we can
see like we've been creating this sort
of flag higher. This area here is going
to be key. Do we find acceptance in here
for a drive to 16? Are we going to do
one of these in here for a while? Or is
this like a push and a fail and we come
right back down or are we going to
reclaim 16 and come back up to the top
side and run all these out? Right?
You're going to see lots of if buts and
may. That's what we're looking at today.
if buts and may while we set the
temperature and the tone for this week
and this year. All right, let's have a
look at tech because tech's moving.
All right, uh
Apple.
All right, actually flat here. So,
inside Friday's range, uh you'll be
looking for a pivot break over 71 here.
If they get over 71, I'd be watching for
a move into 72 and 7250s and 260s.
Amazon,
there's a nice gap up. All right,
leaving Friday's
volume. All right, so if they hold dips,
which they have been this morning,
they'll be looking to take out this
pivot here into 28 and try and get back
up here into 30 on Amazon. So decent gap
up on Amazon, leaving Friday trapped.
You want to be careful if they get back
under here, right? And if you're trading
Amazon, Google, same kind of thing. All
right. Yeah, Google was actually pretty
decent last week on Friday. That was a
decent close right into VWAP. question
is, can it hold any dip into sort of 15
and 14?
Meta
not as good. All right, opening pretty
much flat. There's your peak. All right,
so there's the two drive. We're back
inside that on Meta. So just building
out volume there on Meta. You'll see
it's the chips that are the ones going
Microsoft. All right, that's a little
bit better. Okay, so next pivot up here
on Microsoft. So if Softy can hold any
of these dips, right, can it get back
into 47s? But a bit of a gap up there on
softy. Uh yeah, about a dollar and a
half. This is where we get going. All
right, here's where we get going.
Remember these have catalysts coming
tonight. So some front running into
here. Decent gap up. All right, decent
gap up here. $4 gap up. Question is, can
it get back above 92s? If we zoom out on
this, we can see the importance of some
of these levels. All right, if we start
breaking out from here, can we get back
up to 98 and 200s is the question. All
right. Is this now
this play here? All right. Are they able
to do it into this catalyst tonight? I
don't know. But uh that's what it's
looking like it's trying to do. Tesla,
same thing. Gapping up.
There's Friday's volume. All right. Can
it hold above? Can it find acceptance?
If it doesn't, we come back down. Same
story as all of them. Uh as a equally
weighted mag [sighs]
gap up. All right. because the chips are
moving as an equally equally weighted
mag. But into that VWAP, um we can look
at a couple other names, broader sectors
like Oracle. All these chip names are
going to get going. There you go.
Oracle's going, AMD is going. Um I'm
sure INTC is going,
ITC is going. So you can see the chip
names finding bids here this morning. If
we look at some of sort of the more beta
names, what are they doing? Big gap up
there on
decent gap up there on Q. Decent gap up
there on MBTS. These are all the AI
related names. AGTI
might have some room to go before it
gets resold into maybe a little pivot up
here. So, yeah, some uh some strength
coming in tech there this morning, which
is uh worth being aware of. All right,
it's worth being aware of the tech we're
seeing in the strength we're seeing in
tech this morning. Can they sustain the
bid? All right, that's the bigger
question because when we've s seen
pushes last week, they've been sold
into. Right now, we look like we're
trying to get up to this previous week
want to control. What I will do is mark
out this whole area just so it's a
little bit easier. Let's make sure this
is nice and tight.
So, I'd say 680 690 to sort of 735 740.
That's the area where they're trying to
drive into.
All right, everyone. that has us
covered. Some of you might be trading
oil or oil related names. Uh that is all
moving obviously. So if you're looking
at I don't know OXL and all those big
big oil company names, they are all
moving this morning. They're all up five
plus percent. All right. So there's
probably a decent trade in there for the
next few days at least.
And let's go through this chat. Good
morning everyone. I'm probably not going
to get a chance to say good morning to
you to you all, but let's try. Good
morning Clint. Um, Absid Full Forward,
Toby, Red Plasma, Raphael, Mark, Larry,
the other Dave, Jeff Stewart, Gangster,
Garb Tarton Trader, welcome back my
friend. Good to see your name in chat.
Firewater, Asylum, Bart, Low Hanging
Fruit, Green Otter, Marrick,
Peter, Jonathan, Myin, Black Widow,
JSource, Inferris, NFC,
Aris,
Aristi, I don't know if I got that
right. [snorts] Uh, Zuzu, My Baby Cow,
these names are amazing. Peter Ellis,
Red Plasma, Gonzalo,
George B, Chris Thorne, Troy,
one-on-one,
Steven, Izzy Trades,
Mudum, Brandon, Chris Trades, and Envy,
John, Adjust, Rebby, Foster, Scott,
Morning, mate. Carla, Adam, Ammon,
Prrisca, Thumper, Duba,
Miguel, even Raph. Oh my god, there's so
many of you here. I'm not going to be
able to catch up with you.
Uh, Nick, Shimmy, Market Cap,
Kiwi, Poppycow, Daryl, Juan, Jade,
Radical, Maron.
If I missed you out, I'm sorry everyone.
Um, but yeah, thank you for joining as
this stream continues to grow. I'm
extremely thankful for you guys joining
me on stream each day. It's fun trading
with you lot. Make sure you smash that
like button nice and early. Hit that
like button nice and early. We will do
giveaways as always.
Um, you have what about another 48 hours
I think for the Apex sale for the 90%
sale. If you're interested, code FCT.
Um, Lucid have just announced a 35% sale
this morning on the 50K and 25K using
code FCT as well. The other ones I think
are 30% off. I'll get some flyers out
early. But as always, FCT will always
get you the best code for all your prop
firms other than take profit trader. You
need to use code flow zone there. And
uh, how long we got left here? Not very
long. 50 seconds, folks. So, nice and
calm this morning. Let's see if they
drive up into this sort of previous week
point of control area. See if there's a
short position here that we have up into
that or if they find acceptance.
Oh, did you Chris? Did you get a better
sale or a worse sale? Yeah, sorry guys,
those joining late. Um, I'm wearing
sunglasses because I've got a cracking
headache. It's uh nothing to do with how
I want to look. I've got an absolute
awful headache.
So, the uh lights from the um
I don't know what you call them, 4K
lights, whatever on my face so that you
can see on stream are rather bright.
Okay, here we go. Here's the open. Just
let this settle down for a minute. So,
all of the mag gapping up here. Biggest
uh gap up in Tesla there this morning
and probably going to drive out into
that previous week point control like we
talked about. That's the first target
and if they get back up there previous
week value area high. So this is the
drive into towards those 700s. See if
they can keep going here.
There is some liquidity resting up
there. Is there anything above yet? Not
yet. Not yet. So an old imbalance up
there.
Let's see if they get up there and if
they find acceptance and then we can
think about what next. The other trade
will be back under 600. All right. If
they fail 600, there'll be a rotation
from 600 to sort of 550s.
550s to 530s. So, if we can drive up
here and get stuffed, I'll join in for
the short, the rotation back down to
sixes.
If we drive up here and find acceptance,
well, I think about the move up into
previous week area high. I guess it's
not ideal, but I'd consider it much
rather play short side for the move back
down to sixes here,
which is what we're starting to see back
to that New York open. Some flush coming
in here. They find a bid here at this
New York open is the question. That blue
line on your screen
rather this gets a little bit higher be
more ideal to start the day.
We're back to these sixes like we talked
about this gray box. The sixes over
under here.
If they soak here, they're going to want
to go back to that old point of control.
If they fail sixes, there's a rotation
back down to value. If they lose value,
next gray box and old point of control
from previous days. So, just I'm willing
to play both sides here while we figure
out what we're doing. But just waiting
to see if we can come to a key level
first. I don't want to front run it.
Yes, still finding a drive. It's a good
drive out on ES. Check the bigs here.
Are we gapping down? Running lower. No,
not yet.
So, VIX is hovering just under 15s right
now. So, let's see if they find a bid.
Back to the sixes here. This is the
level we just talked about. If they
start losing this, there's probably a
move down into this block here. These
value areas. If they bid up here, then
they're going to try and get back to
that point of control. So, this 600,
same level that we talked about in
Discord. Folks, watching this to see how
we act here. Do bids come in? Do they
trap shorts?
very thin this market this morning. By
the way, folks, haven't seen the volume
come in yet.
So, if we lose these sixes, I'd say the
big move here is 603 is where big
sellers came in here. It's a huge seller
that came in at 603. So, all the time
he's comfortable, there's potential to
lose sixes and trade down the 550s. If
he gets knocked out, then the rotation
back higher is likely to happen.
Stacking some bids here between 87 62s
right now. Here comes the move back into
603. Driving through 603. Filling this
imbalance there. Still no short trigger
yet.
Reclaiming sixes. So good hold of this
gray box here so far. So I'm watching
this New York open now.
Willing to play both sides. So either
shorts will protect this or we're going
to see a squeeze up into previous week
point control. So what I'm looking at
couple of ideas here. Something like
this for a short trigger. Maybe this.
And if we fail this, that's the next
short trigger. If they hold this, that's
the long trigger. So, willing to play
both sides here so far. Stuck at VW up,
stuck at that New York open. They can't
get back over it.
Apple's losing a bid here as is
Microsoft. All right. So, you've seen
some weakness in a couple names. Tesa
still going upside. Nvidia still going
upside. They're trying to hold these
600s.
There's definitely a chance to move that
back down to 560 550 here
if they lose this with power, but at the
moment it's being absorbed. It is very
whippy down here on light volume
and they decide their positioning.
Relative weakness here definitely in the
cues
in the last couple minutes. Having a
look at the spiders.
You can see there's bids down at 560
which is previous day value area high
kind of level. I'm wondering if we flush
down to that and pick them up down
there.
Here's the test. We might get it here.
Here we go. Is there follow through now?
Still finding some passive buys here.
Can we get down to 560s is my question.
We wash now. Nice scalping a little out
on this flush in case we don't make it
all the way. It's 80s. Beautiful.
Cathering some more. Can we get follow
through to 60s? Stop moved in now. Let's
just see. We're under 600s. Don't want
to see this trade back off 603. Paid
myself either way here.
Very whippy.
Back to the sixes. Down to tiny size
now. Let's see if we can move lower.
PMI. Yeah, PMI 10:00 or ISM
manufacturing. Sorry, sorry. 10:00.
Still trading around these sixes. Right
on these 85s. Can we get down on this
runner down to 55s?
Here we go. Come on, baby. Down you
come.
Come on, baby.
Come on, baby. Down you come.
Nice. Lovely, lovely, lovely. Here we
go, folks. Make sure you're paying
yourself in this move. Here's previous
day value area high. All right. So, the
bids might come in here. We don't know.
All right. If they're going to bid
against this, then they're going to look
for the rotation back up. All right.
This is a huge area. Value area high
previous day, value area low previous
week. And they might well bid up off
this if they want to hold the rotation.
If they fail this, then we're going to
look for this move and this move here.
All right. So, I paid myself either way
now. Really nice W to start the day.
I mean, it's not the biggest move, but
40 50 points or whatever it is. We'll
take it on the Monday morning. All
right. We're willing to play both sides.
[snorts] Shame we didn't drive higher
first. If we could have got that uh
point of control would have been really
nice. All right. So, you're starting to
see some bids come in here. Some shorts
just got caught under 60. I'm completely
flat now, folks.
Nice play to start the day.
I'll be using chat if you caught some of
that with me.
Back to this gray box. And we said we
got to be careful here. All right, this
is an area bulls might want to bid off.
They will try and find acceptance back
over this. And this is to complete
rotation one. All right, so we traded
from here to here. Bulls are trying to
trade from here to here. This is the
level of competitiveness, let's call it.
And if they get acceptance, they want to
come back up here. If they fail,
acceptance, we're going to retest this
again. Bulls will try again. If they
fail, we move lower. There's lots, like
I said, some of you will be upset cuz
I'm like, if we do this, we do this. If
we do this, we do this. That's how we
have to trade, folks, when we're trading
inside range.
Really nice. Lots of you getting it. Oh,
that's nice to see on a Monday morning.
I absolutely love that, folks. Well
done, E-Rock getting it. Sucks. Deluxe.
Titan trader. Richard getting it. Otus
getting it. Alvo getting it. Chris
Cooper getting it. Gray Kitty. Nick,
David, Asvid, Calypso, Arist, DM, Troy,
Dim, Jeff, Steven,
Dia, Christy, Amina,
and Raph. Nice work, folks.
I mean, you know, it says, "I got the
buy." Oh, nice. So, you took the buy off
here. Yeah. I mean, that's equally fine
if you're play if you're trying to play
that range rotation, right? And then we
said if they want to hold this, this is
your partial point. Partial two, partial
three, partial four, right? If you if
you're playing the long back up, it's
what you're looking for. But you got to
get back above 600. If you can't find
acceptance here, it's going to keep
rotating until one side is caught off.
All right. So, those 600 still so far
heavy. The book is not that thick yet,
folks. I'm going to be honest with you.
It's not that thick yet.
Back down. We come retesting these
levels. If we lose value,
all right, we can drive lower and lower
and lower. All right, these are possible
here. GlobeEx is possible here. Closing
the gap is possible as well. All right,
so it really depends how we act here
now. Really, really depends how we act
here now.
>> [snorts]
>> Is it possible to raise my volume? It's
probably that I'm just talking away from
the mic. Um,
I'm pretty much maxed out here, my
friend, and it's uh 6:40 in the morning,
so I don't want to be shouting, but I
will try and talk into the mic a little
bit more for you. I'm sorry.
Okay, so we've got bid stacking down
here. 60s to 40s. That's where the
buyers are hanging out passively trying
to get filled. Is there much below?
There's a guy down at to decent sized
guy down at 487s.
Yeah, this is in my next block. Okay,
that's good to know. So, they're
respecting the areas that we've got
drawn out.
Yeah, news at 10. News at 10:00.
Still seeing buyers get trapped on every
push back towards sixes so far this
morning.
All depends. But is it willing to defend
here or if we're going to look to defend
a lower area right now. So this is the
this is the rotation here between these
two right now is your sort of lower time
frame rotation.
[clears throat]
So back down towards previous week value
area low. Will they bid around here? If
we start losing all these areas, we can
look and potentially will rotate all of
Friday.
Love you guys for the day. Hey, nice
man. Congratulations. That's a lovely
start to the day in the year. Okay,
they're still bidding down here. It's
still a bit of a battle.
Looking to see if one side gets caught
down here. There is a little bit of
excess short side. Sellers under 45s. Um
but these buyers can't get us back over
the 80s at the moment. So let's see if
we get back over 80s
if we're willing to bid up here. Looking
a little bit better. This is the level
though. They got to start driving
through these and through the 80s and
really back through the sixes right
where we looked for that short earlier.
So really nice feathering into a long
here. Peeling some off in case we flush
back down this big seller at 87. Right,
he is the level. I'm trying to see if we
can get acceptance over.
Can we bid back over 87? If we bid over
87, I think we go 600s. If we bid over
600s, we go back towards high of day.
So just taking peeling some off as we
got into that. See if we can hold this.
If we don't hold this, that's fine. to
run off again. It's just the same thing
over and over for me. Small size plane
rotations. See if we find acceptance or
not.
No, tell you when I enter a trade.
And I can't draw this out anymore. If I
try, if you are going to try and copy
me, you're going to lose, mate. Learn
how to trade.
Let's see if we hold these.
I want to see us hold a bid right here
right now. Otherwise, I'm going to cut
this.
Not liking what I'm seeing on the tape
so far. There we go. That's better. Can
we need to get acceptance over 87s here?
Here we go. That's better. Can we get
back over sixes now?
Come on.
Got to get back over sixes now. I'll
consider an ad if we start basing over
sixes.
All that rotation all the way back up.
Really good. Yes. Lovely. Okay. Squeeze
now, please. And then try and base
because I want to get some more size on
here with the push all the way back to
high of day. Yes. Here we go.
Beautiful. We've got a little node here
at 26's to be aware of.
A really nice just another quick
rotation there. 40 50 point rotation
there.
really nice off this area. We said bulls
will need to hold this area. This blue
line to blue line bulls have
successfully held this. This is the
level of battle. This is our level of
battle. So, we were short this morning.
For those of you asking for the trade
from here to here, I was now long from
here to here. And I'm waiting to see do
we find acceptance for this or do we do
this again? Don't really want to play
the short again. In my mind, now we've
had the chance to break down. If I'm
going to play the short again, it's
going to need to be something like this.
Otherwise, I think we might have enough
excess in this little area here to do
this move.
They're starting to add liquidity higher
now, which is good. So, we've got stuff
to aim for with our runners. Come on.
Can we find acceptance here?
Really good. Really good.
I want to see us trade back through
between 23s
and 30 now. All right, 23s and 30. If we
can get back above that, I think we go
high of day. But that's that's the next
level.
Opening range now set, folks. Here we
go. Here's the test of 23s to 30s. Come
on, baby. Up you go.
Up you go. peeling a little off in this
push because lots of buyers are coming
in here and then market buying the high
here which always worries me. Here we
go. Here's the 30s. Yeah, baby. All
right, let's see if we can get back
above this and the New York open now and
then we should go hive day if we can do
that. And if we can go through hive day,
my expectation is to come into 700s now.
Really nice way to start the week and
the w and the year.
[cough and clears throat]
Oh,
do I think we trade up to previous week
point of control and then dump? I think
we trade up to it. I can't tell you if
we're going to dump there until I see
how we act when we get there, mate. It's
possible that like if I was a seller,
I'd be selling into that move, but it's
very possible we squeeze all the way up
to previous week's value. If we find
acceptance there, we will get all the
way up to the top side. Okay, so here we
just traded into those 30s, right? Look
at this level at the top. These 30s,
like I said, 23 to 30s is going to be
key. This is where we're trading at the
moment. There's a big node here that
we've developed this morning. So, peel
some off here. And then I'm waiting now
on the runner. Can we get back above the
New York open, squeeze out current day
high and get up to previous week point
control above us. Already paying myself
either way.
[snorts]
All right, let's get some volume on here
for the day now that we've been open a
little while. No, it's the wrong one.
It's not what I want.
All right, there we go. So, here you can
see the node I was looking at. 23 to 30,
right? 23 to 30. You'd want buyers need
to protect these 600s, right? Basically
96s. Buyers would want to protect this.
If we're going to see that continuation,
we're going to need to see this move
here or this move here, right? We don't
want it back under here now on our
runners. If we come under here, we're
going to expect rotate back down to
there again, which is going to be ugly.
But remember, we are an inside bar on
the daily. We're inside on the weekly so
far. We're inside value on the weekly.
Um, but we are above value on the on the
daily now, which is good. So, we're
trying to auction higher prices on daily
versus Friday.
back to these sixes again.
Yeah, Nvidia giving that move back. This
is the thing. There might be profit.
Like we said beginning of the stream,
every drive up we've seen profit taken
so far. Just depends if today's
different.
It's absolutely been a thing.
If we start trading on the 90s, I'll cut
the runner and that's fine. Paid myself.
Like I said,
we're just inside this uh what is
developing as a D-shaped profile this
morning.
Like I said, if buts, and maybe type
trade, see money, take money type
environment right now.
We lose these 90s, we'll flush 80s, I'll
be out. Loses 90s, I'm out. There we go.
I'm out. Yeah.
So, locked in. Could always reload,
but I don't want to play short here
inside this value. And we'll wait to see
us trade outside of this. Right. If
we're really going to get weak,
I'll need to see this stay heavy. Uh
what you need to be careful of down here
is of course this move here.
>> [sighs]
>> I'll give you a readout on the market
here. Uh overall equally weighted about
1% up. Tesla 3.22% up. Nvidia a third of
a percent up. Now that was 2 and a half%
up a matter of minutes ago. Microsoft a
third of a percent down. Meta 1.19% up.
Google half a percent up. Amazon 1.89%
up. And Apple 0 69% down. All right.
We're still protecting current value
area low on the day. Previous day value
area high. Previous week value area low.
All right. Until we trade under these,
I'm not thinking about a short now. I
think we're in a rotational market. So
until I see weakness under key levels,
I'm not thinking about a short. It
doesn't mean I'm having another go long
here. We're [clears throat] just waiting
now. Let this develop
back to point of control on the day.
Back to these sixes again.
Market seems very thin on the book. It's
amazing how thin we are. Start of a new
year.
>> [snorts]
>> Time for coffee news coming. Yeah, we
got 10 minutes till the news.
Being out this liquidity down into 75
and 60 again now.
So strong selling today has come in sub
80 and then 66s and then the lows. All
right. So that's where the aggressive
sellers have been and they haven't got
their way yet. All right. So I'd say
right where we are now, there was some
aggressive selling and then there was
more at sort of 78 down to 70 and then
more more at the lows. So those sellers
need to be back in the money if we're
going to see followrough underneath
value.
Yes, back down to its New York open
here. VIX trying to find a bid back to
the 15s on the VIX.
We're trading right around this point of
control. You can see this big D-shape
being developed here. These are the
markets Alex doesn't want to trade in.
How silver it's 7.38% up. [gasps] That's
how silver is.
So you can see these rotations. Trade
one today was from here to here. Trade
two today was from here to here. We got
a little bit extra out back down into
here now. And letting this develop
whatever it wants to do around here. I
don't want to trade in this little part
here. I want us to move away from that
and give us some sentiment for the day.
>> [snorts]
>> market waiting for news. Yeah, quite
possibly. Quite possibly
[sighs]
control up in these 600s again. That's
still the level. I still think we want
to go upside. Here we go.
We're going to do it now. back into
these 620s to 630s.
See if we find acceptance. Now,
if we go through here,
we're still looking at the same thing.
All right, short still. Remember, cells,
like I told you, have come in aggressive
here and here and not get their way. If
we start doing this, we will squeeze.
They will all get caught. And that's
where all the strong selling is down
here. If you ask me how, I know, I can
see it on footprint. All right. right
here
again in the same level.
These guys, oh my god, are you going to
help me out here? These guys, these
guys, these guys, these guys, these
guys, these guys, these guys are all out
the money. So, if we hold and pivot,
they're going to get squeezed out. Big
if, but uh it has potential to do it.
So, if we hold these sort of sixes, same
thing we were talking about earlier,
maybe got the chance to do it.
Oh, is that you, Jake? I saw it come in.
I'll be honest, mate. I've had uh not
the best weekend um to listen to
anything, but I did see it come in. The
intro and outro music and stuff. I I
appreciate that. Thank you very much. I
will I will take a listen properly this
week. I promise. But I've had a bit of a
tough weekend here. I got to be honest
with you. I'm not feeling too good
today. Pounding headache.
But thank you. That's uh awfully kind of
you to do that as well.
It's back down to these sixes and this
imbalance down to 90. Still waiting
here. We got to get through the news
here until we see what we want to do.
[sighs]
Yes. holding that New York open. Still
flat here. I can show you my board for
those that like, well, I'm not seeing
anything. This is my board right now
this morning. All right, cuz I'm not
feeling well. I'm not linking them. I'm
just trading one at a time, nice and
slow.
[clears throat]
Thanks, DK.
Appreciate it.
All right, still inside value on the
day. All right, you can see this big old
D-shape. Well, it's not even that big to
be honest. This is what we're building
out. We're not finding acceptance above.
We're not finding acceptance below,
right? We are rotating. I still think
we're going to do this at the moment,
but uh
let's see see what this news has to say
about that move. A
That's value area high. The 620 630 is
that node we talked about.
So we've only had uh 134 points today.
That's the size of the move so far.
How long we got left? Five more minutes.
What's this hourly candle looking like?
Pretty ugly.
Big wick top side right now.
Just missed our level. If we think about
what we talked about this morning on the
hourly, it's important to zoom out.
Right. This level here, we said big node
previous week. We just missed it.
We just missed it here. So, it got
stuffed into this. So sellers are
hanging out up here. All right. And
we've bid so far off this. All right. So
there is the move. That's all we've
done. Drive up into this failed. Didn't
quite make it. All right. I would have
liked to snap short up here. If we done
something like that, it would been
really good.
But instead, we're in a rotation now
while we develop some volume while it
decides who it wants to trap and where
it wants to go. And you got to be
willing to look both ways right now.
Can I mark out the imbalance I saw in
the 90s? Well, it's it it's gone now.
It's right here. You see this
this side imbalance?
It's off footprint. It's not off a fair
value gap or something. I guess you
could say it was here on a fair value
gap, right?
The actual imbalance is uh I'm getting
off the print right there.
Okay, back down to this value area
again.
Again, everything under 70s has been
sellers getting stuck. It's been passive
buying from 70s down to low of day so
far. So, it's been bids just sat there
absorbing the tape so far. And it's been
aggressive sellers being absorbed. So,
we are having buyers down there trying
to have a bit of a party.
And you'll see it on the CVD. If you
look at CBD right now, we've been trying
to make lower lows and we're not moving
lower in price. So, we've got price
divergence in CBD. We've got aggressive
sellers trying to move price lower.
There's a new lower low on CBD there.
And we are not moving lower in this
market. So, there's without a doubt
passive buyers down here at 70 down to
40s. We can see it on CBD. You can see
it on the book.
[clears throat]
I can copy trading my account. I was
able to flatten all my prop firms, but I
was using SIM account as lead and I
cannot get to close it. Any thoughts? Is
it it I don't know where the SIM's
linked to, mate. Is it a um like SIM on
a broker? Is it a ninja SIM or is it a
SIM from like Apex or something? Um you
should be able to just shut down your
system, reload it, and then reset your
SIM and it shouldn't it shouldn't do
anything hopefully. It's always a worry.
ICT made a video and he's talking about
me. Is that right? Well, I couldn't give
a [\h__\h] what ICT says.
You can go back into his uh little
dungeon of [\h__\h]
Okay, news incoming. Book starting to
really thin out here.
They're still passively buying these 70s
and below.
just joined any trades today. You were
here this morning. That means you were
here and then left J Source. Yes, two
trades. We took the short from the gray
box to the bottom and we took the long
from this blue line to the gray box and
above.
Alex, I'm Ninja Sim, what YouTube of
yours should I watch to set up my
charts? I've literally got a a video on
for free on YouTube on how to set up
Ninja uh my way. So, I don't know what
it's called, but if you just type in
Flowzone Trader Ninja Trader, it will
come up. All right, book really thinning
out here.
Print coming here, folks. 10 seconds.
Whippy, whippy, whippy. There we go.
There's the drive up. Trapping bulls
there into the 20s again. Whippy,
whippy, whippy, whippy,
whippy, whippy, whippy. Whoa, look at
this. What are you doing, Mr. Market? It
feels like it wants to move back up
through the 20s and 30s and get back up
to high of day, but they can't get
through this node we talked about up
here. So, it's selling up here and
there's buying down here. I'm going just
trap between them.
Oh, can we make a move out of this
volume, please? Market, pretty please. I
don't really want to trade from 70 to 20
all day. 50 points, it's uh can't do a
lot with that.
So back down we come.
Value area low.
Do they get caught down there? No idea.
Have to see if we can move outside of
this.
Still absorbing down here. These se 70s
and below that we've talked about. Still
finding passive buyers. If these passive
buyers get run over, then we should make
a new low of day here. They're still
bidding on this book down here at the
moment.
[snorts]
They're bidding 70s again and they're
selling 20s. That's all we're seeing so
far.
There we go. Driving back up. So, they
bid 70s again. I'm still waiting to see
can we get through 20s and 30s.
It's the same thing, folks. I've given
you the same levels.
Same thing over and over and over again.
Can we get through if we get through 20s
and 30s, we should lift to 43, which is
New York open. If we get through that, I
think we go high of day and previous
week control up here. So, we're still
looking at the same thing, but we've got
to get through all this first. So,
passive selling is taking place here.
Passive buying is taking place here. And
this is the rotation.
Back to PC. They should they got a bid
off these now on these 600s if the
buyers are going to take control and
have a go. They've just washed out a
little bit down here.
They've got levels on the book at 40s.
They should go and aim up here. They
just need someone a bit more aggressive
to come onto the book rather than just
like sitting back. So less fair. They
need someone aggressive to step on the
book here.
One big buyer will do it and it'll just
swipe all of this out. They're trying.
They just need to lift these 20s and
30s.
These guys out
[snorts]
seller at 20s. They got to get through
him and they'll run straight to 40s. I
think there's a 20 point shove up here
if they can get through this guy that
keeps reloading 20s and now he's moved
to 15s. Back to 20s. See if they can
shove up here. Come on. You should go
straight to 40s now. There we go.
There's the 30s. You got to get through
this and we'll run 40s pretty quick. I
think
35 on a book. Let's get through this guy
at 30 and then shove to 40s up to that
New York open we talked about. And let's
see if we bid over that. Really nice.
Lovely. Come on.
You've got more than that. Come on, weak
hands. Come on, you weak hands.
Head on brick wall. Please don't do the
same rotation again. [snorts]
Please. Please. We all know Alex hates
rotation. Let's not spend the first day
of a year with volume of rotating in a
50 point range. Let's go market. Come
on. Come on. Just get through this
little edge. You can see this edge here.
You can see it right here. This flat
edge. This is what they keep defending.
Once this goes, I think we get a swipe.
This right here.
This little node. Once this goes, we
should swipe this. And then this will be
target. And these stops will get us to
this. This will get us to this. This
will get us to this. Here we go. Thank
god for that. Thought I was going to go
crazy. Right. Here comes Nehil Copen.
Come on, baby.
Come on. Come on buyers.
Wakey wakey. I know you've had lots of
whiskey at the weekend, but wakey wakey.
Come on, Mr. Buyer. Let's shove it up
through the New York open, please. Yes.
Trying to make new high day here. Some
buyers getting caught here at 35. Just
want follow through now. We need a
squeeze up here. We actually need a
squeeze up here otherwise we're going to
get pulled right back in. Here's the New
York open tag. It's a TP here. There you
go. That's what I'm saying. They need a
squeeze up otherwise we're going to get
pull back into that value area high. So
your TP1 was here. Let's see if we can
get TP2. All right. The danger here is
that they sell back under here. We don't
want to touch this. Balls need to do
this move here now. Or technically they
need to do this move here now.
Really good.
Yes, new high day. You can watch those
950s, that whole number on ES 88s like
we talked about on SPY. Remember we
talked about the 88. Once you get
through 88s, we're looking at 90s.
Come on, Q's. Find a bid, man. Don't be
like chasing up here. You're either
already long or you need a little
breakout above and a pullback. Don't be
chasing the bid up here.
What's with the sunglasses? I've got a
massive migraine. That's what's with the
sunglasses.
Not for any other reason. I wish it was
sunny in LA. It's been raining. Here we
go. Back to Valeria high. So, they've
got to rebid this now. If they don't
rebid this, we're going to go back
inside the range. So, you need longs to
rebid this now for a squeeze out. We
just talked about this. Got to hold this
at level here. If they don't hold this,
we're going to go back in rotation.
There's nothing to do. The buyers have
really got to hold this pullback here
and do this. If they lose this, we're
going to go back in rotation and I don't
want to trade in here. This is my no
trade zone now, right? It's my no trade
zone for you that range rotations.
That's your trade zone. For me, it's my
no trade zone.
Minus two in London. Is it really? Oh my
gosh,
I forgot how cold that feels.
They're trying to bid value area high.
Yes. Back to New York VW up. Let's see
if it bids that old high
so I can show you my board here. Right.
Adding a little bit more. There you go.
Thanks. You guys always moan.
Like I said, just trading one at a time
because I'm really not feeling well.
No, you're fine, Tommy. You're you're
fine, Tommy. It's okay, mate. Don't
worry. Um, what chart are you looking
at? Sorry, I'm just watching on my
monitor as well. This is a one minute
chart on ENQ.
Yes. So, I I'm always on ENQ. If I'm on
something else, I will tell you to give
you a reason.
Yeah. So, you can see I'm going to show
you the delta divergence here that
played out this morning that we talked
about. If we go down to five minute
chart, really easy to see it on.
All right, as we were starting to pivot
up, all right, there were no lower lows.
We had lower lows in CBD. All right, so
what does that mean? It meant there were
aggressive sellers down here being
absorbed by passive buyers, which what
gave me the edge to look for upside. All
right, those of you who have done the
orderflow course will know all about
that.
And if you couldn't see it on CVD, you
could literally quite literally see it
on the bookmat by using Delta.
You have heating on it still cold. And
I'm sure that he is going to cost you a
fortune in if you're in the UK.
They're still holding this value high.
They're still trying to hold these 20s
here for a squeeze up higher.
They want to get a squeeze up higher.
They've got to get through this New York
open. And I've given you the pathing
about 10 times today for you guys who
are looking for this. So if they hold
value area high get through back through
the New York open. You got a bid over
the New York open up to the high of day.
If you get through high of day there is
here you go. Here's a bid over New York
open. Can we can keep seeing follow
through over this now to come and take
out high of day and then get up into
this. All right. So this is your target.
It's looking good. So you held the
shelf.
Held the shelf.
You're into New York open. Can you hold
this and use these stops to get into
here?
Right.
What's the weather temp in LA? I'll have
a look for you. It's raining though.
It's 57 today.
looking good here. It's just this once
this guy gets out the way at 55s, you're
going to go 70. They just keep reloading
55s. There you go. 50s and 55s coming
and then you should go se 70 here for
your next move.
You got to get through these 50s and
55s. Let's go on markets.
Interesting mate about your migraine.
I'm in uh
in Canada and my whole family has a
headache since Saturday night. Best
theory we have is maybe full moon. Maybe
I think mine's stress if I'm honest.
Nervous system is uh absolutely shot
right now. I'll be honest with you guys.
Uh, no. The course uh discount finished,
I'm afraid, my friend. Um, you can use
code FCT. I think that will get you 10%
off.
I might it might just be the on the main
course, but uh yeah, we we we ran many
many discounts over the both the
holidays, but they're all finished now,
I'm afraid, buddy.
But you can try code FCT. It might get
you 10% off if you're lucky. I I
genuinely don't know cuz I haven't
talked to my web developer about what's
on what's still running and what's not.
That's not me trying to say I don't like
I I just don't know. I'd have to talk to
my developer. But you can try it.
20 up 20 down kind of day sadly. Yeah,
it feels that way, doesn't it? I still
think we've got a chance here though.
It's just all depends on this New York
open. Can they bid back above value area
high now sitting at 25s?
So are they able to squeeze above or is
this a look above value and a fail? We
are stuck at this new open though this
blue line that was your TP1.
It's just can we see further development
above it
[sighs]
slow isn't it?
It's slow.
Microsoft and Apple trying to go red to
green here though folks
at those high beta names. RGTI, MVTS,
ONQ, IN crazy
good t good day traders. If I was day
trading, I'd be looking to day trade
those every day. But with my uh stocks
and ETFs, I'm looking for swing
positions and there's just too much
volatility in those.
Okay, back to value area high. They're
still trying to bid off it. If they lose
the bid though, we go back to VPO, which
is 600s again. But they're still trying
to bid off this.
[sighs]
Got in at 16 and out at 40. Not a bad
day. That's That's nice work. Where's
the 16s? Got in at 16. So, you just took
here to here. There you go. So, you took
the shelf the shelf to the open and you
probably had runners in case and it
hasn't gone. I mean,
honestly, guys, I think any money you
lock in, I I'll show you guys what I
shared the team this morning.
Um,
we talked about
the need to lock in uh
And we talk about it.
I don't know. I'm sure I had it some
somewhere. I'm sure I said lock your
money in.
Maybe I just can't read right now.
There you go. Be nimble. See money. Take
money Monday. There you go. I knew I had
it somewhere. I knew I had it somewhere.
Oh.
All right. Still stuck at this open.
Shows in valid code. Yeah. FZT, not FCT.
Flow zone trader. FZT. FZT. It's going
to work. That's what will work.
Okay, back to this New York open.
They're still trying to find acceptance
above this New York open and search for
the high of day. That's what they are
attempting to do here. Uh once we get
through high of day, like I said, if we
run these stops, we should come into
this block up here. That's what they're
attempting to do here. So, any of you
who are still long,
you might be getting it here. They're
trying to build up to go. Just every
push up here into 55 speed. So it's so
thin on the book. It's insane.
Where is Mr. Volume? Is he going to come
back today? Back to value high again
here. This is not a good look here,
folks. Because you've just pushed and
failed.
Trying to find a bid as well.
Not able to get up to that high of day
yet. And now you're back to value area
high. If you lose value area high,
you're going to go VPO.
They're still bidding value area high.
These rotations are tiny.
Back to the New York Open.
Shelf again. Same shelf.
Back on that last push again. They're
having another go. It's now It's now or
never for the Bulls. I say if they can't
get back through
50, then they're in trouble. If they get
back through 50, you're going to run
higher there. I think it's the last
attempt that they've got. They just held
Bpo another time after a failed look.
Look all this liquidity above. They
should come for it.
They should really be gagging to get up
into 80s now. Here they go. Wakey wakey,
Mr. Bulls, where are you? Let's go into
80s. And if you run 80s, you should go
700. You should run the stops there to
get into this uh level up here. So once
you get through here, you should there
should be enough stops to get you into
that. So if you're long from these any
of these, you should be trimming,
trimming, trimming, and then holding on
just in case they want to come all the
way up here, which would be really nice
for you guys,
right? I'm not in a position, so I want
to be uh transparent about that, but if
you uh if you can base and go, be nice
for you guys. You don't want it to come
back under value, though. If you start
losing
this shelf here, right, you've had so
many attempts. What you don't want to
see is that. And that will happen if you
start losing that shelf. So, you want
bulls to actually be a bit more
aggressive and step on the tape. When I
say step on the tape, I mean be
aggressive and run through all the
offers above. Like run, if you can look
at bookmap, run through these offers
above, right? We should come and someone
needs to be aggressive. These passive
buyers need to step up and push this
price up aggressively to fill these guys
which will cause a cascade effect up
into 700 because they will all get run
out of the market and that's what you
need to see. You need to see big green
bubbles start to step in here rather
than just nothing on the bullet. There's
no passive participation here. So you
need a big aggressive player to come in
and get the job done for you.
[snorts]
Shouldn't
be that hard to take a 28 lot out.
That's how
lacking volume we are.
Remember,
smash that like button for me, folks. I
want to do an Apex giveaway today.
Um, I'm going to do a competition as
well. We're going to do um another
funded next giveaway this month. At
least one, maybe two funed next
giveaways. And we're going to do a lucid
giveaway as well. So, starting to get
some more stuff for you guys, which is
fantastic.
Yeah, I would agree, mate. I would
agree. It is making heavy weather. It
is.
We're not seeing anyone step
aggressively on the tape. Someone keeps
reloading selling at 60s.
So, we had some decent size buying up
there on that last shove. Just over a
100 lot from sort of 57 to 60s. So, it's
like a bit of an outlier delta there.
Once we get through that, there you go.
Through 60s. Now, we should lift to 70s.
We don't want to see him resell this.
We need to reclaim 60s, push 70s here
now because you've got some outlying
aggressive buying coming in here. You
don't want them to get stuck versus
passive selling. You just want one clean
snap that you can exit your position
long on [clears throat] or at least trim
it. Feels like it's coming,
but it's felt that way for I'd say 15
minutes. They've been building to do
this. So you can see them stacking 67
and 70s right now. We should just lift
and get through there. Here we go. That
I don't like. There was a big buyer came
in there and got stuck. There is a
seller around 62. Reloading. Let me pull
this down.
Where are you?
There he is. Yeah, I don't like that.
They had the chance there.
Uh, I don't think that's I don't think
that's true. I don't think all of this
is due to Venezuela. I think if you just
look if you just zoom out on the daily,
then you'll see this is what we expect.
So, back down to this shelf. Now you can
see the edge of these gray shelves where
this New York open is. All right. So
you've got a clear shelf
here, here, and here. And if balls don't
absorb and complete, they will get
trapped and you get a move like that.
They've got to absorb these shelves
cuz they've made hard work moving up.
And if we look now,
starting to transition to aggressive
selling up here. We should run these
guys out now. Here we go. Come on. Why
are you [clears throat] making it so
hard?
Correct. Is just oil related. Well, oil
and gold,
both reserves. And they got the biggest
reserves of both of those in the world.
up 750 on the funded. Might call it a
day. Too choppy. E decent decent day
that back down to low of day, which is
giving you a nice potential here.
Back down to that shelf we just talked
about. New York Open again. You don't
want them to lose this. If you've been
long in this, you know, do not sit in
this too long. If they can't complete
the rotation, be willing to take it off
and come back in later. You don't want
to hold through a flush.
Yeah, I see that. Why I'm up.
It's just a broad It's a broadening
market like as in sector which is not a
bad thing.
I have three AP Apex accounts right now
at 103.13 but I don't understand do I
have to check the net liquidation or the
cash value?
Uh
yeah the liquidation your your not just
your realize your realize after cost.
So, if you're at 106,
you you're fine.
You'll get an email after today, after
the close, like within an hour or two
afterwards.
Gosh, this is slow. I didn't think we'd
be this slow today, be honest.
If did any of you buy out of interest? I
know lots of you bought this as did I.
Did any of you buy and hold on to it?
Are any of you still in this looking to
complete this rotation? It's a really
good hold if you are. I think you're
going to get it. It's a really good
hold. I think you're going to get 700s
into here.
I have a full-time job, but my days off
I listen to you make so much sense.
You've taught me plenty. Thank you, sir.
You're welcome, man. No worries.
Lucid might have the best best deals
out. Yeah, I talked about it at the
beginning. I think it's 35% off the 25
and 30ks and 30% off the rest right now.
Code FCT,
you're in. Nice man, Tyson. Great work,
mate. Great work.
All forwards still have five micros. I
think you're going to get it. They're
going to try and run. Big seller coming
in here. If you squeeze him out, you
will get the move. He just market sold
60. They're starting to They're starting
to panic now. These sellers, they are
starting to panic. They know this high
is about to get popped. So, they're
starting to add more weight here. If
they get run out, it's going to be
nasty. That was a big sell there. 89 lot
came flying in on the market at 60.
Right on 60. Come on. Lift this guy out
and make him run his stops. Come on,
buyers. Be kind to the team here.
Come on. You got to get a squeeze. His
average is at 60. Came right in at 60
with 100 lot.
Come on. Get back above 60.
[\h__\h] me. It's slow. Huge lot coming in.
Oh, big seller coming in here. Chasing.
He's chasing the market down. Got to be
the same guy. So, 100 lot followed by
what is this size here? 26 26 26 26 26.
So, he's dumping 25s at a time and then
another 100 and another 50. You got to
get back above 60 for this to be valid
now. I wouldn't re bid down here
anymore.
It just had its chance. So, we had a
huge market seller come in at 60.
All right. 100 lot came on at 60 and I
said if you get above him, you should be
all right. They had him trapped and they
failed and then he has chased it down
with size.
So, you got to get back above 60 here.
If you get back above 60, all these
sellers will get caught out. I can show
you exactly what I'm talking about.
Right, these guys came fly or I'm going
to call it this one guy came flying in.
This was his 100 lot that I talked
about.
See if I can make you guys see it. This
was his 100 lot, right? And then after
that, once we broke down under this
shelf, he came flying in market side.
You get back above 60, he will get
squeezed out. Even even Yeah, you're
coming into it now. So ideally, this guy
gets run.
All right. So all these guys, but mainly
I'd be watching this guy here. This is
the guy setting the tone right now. This
will be the same guy adding in. We'll
get back above 60. [snorts]
Same level. See coming at the same
level.
We can probably see him here. Right.
Look at this transition.
He came in here,
added heavy here, added the lows. We
rebalanced his level 60. This is the
battle now in here. If you get if you
get above 60, you'll be all right. But
uh I would not be adding any more to
your position here. You do not want to
be adding to this now.
Here
you go. Here's 60. Here's the battle.
They are adding more and more liquidity
above, which is good. You just got to
get through it.
Someone doesn't want to get hurt here.
Someone's like, "Please don't run me
out." Here you go. If you run him, you
should do it. You go higher day point of
control. It's coming. [\h__\h] me. They've
made this hard work for you guys. If you
if you've managed to hold on to this, I
think you've done incredibly well.
You've been incredibly patient if you've
hung on to this. These were your buy
opportunities even above here. This has
made it very, very hard, but you're
about to run this. And this should get
you up into this shelf right here. You
go. [\h__\h] me. They made that hard.
Congratulations everyone who took that.
There's your next TP. Let's see if you
can get into gray box above. And
previous week pointing control, I have
around 700 705. All right. [snorts] Good
work. Good work team. Really good work.
Anyone that's still in this, you look
fantastic now. Buyers starting to step
on the gas. You should lift now into
that 700. Really good. This is what we
looked for this morning. I was a bit too
impatient for it.
Really nice.
God, that player at 600 made it
incredibly hard work. Incredibly hard
work.
So 85s 95 700. Um, what I will tell you
is 78 has offside delta.
78 is 352 buy side delta. So, you want
to be bidding above 78 as in you want
the market, you shouldn't be bidding,
you want the market to hold a bid above
78. The same as we talked about 60s,
it's now 78. You need to get above to
allow the buyers to be comfortable
because they came in aggressively there.
You should have You should have been
sold selling some of your positions
here.
W trade. Nice. Still holding. I lost 20%
of my hair, but I'm out at 684. Nice
work. Low hanging fruit. W
dodler doubler F. Oh, I'm not going to
repeat that. 20 up, 20 down. It's one of
those days, mate. We talked about it. I
was in it, but it's difficult to hold
through all of that. I'm flat. Good
work, though, mate.
We're in the golden pocket now. Let's
see if someone will come. Well, I think
we're going to have to lift a little bit
more and then see if someone will come.
I think they're going to want to test
this gray box and point of control,
but I could I could easily be wrong.
Maybe they slap it before that, but that
would be my expectation. New highs of
day. ES running. Mags found a bid,
right? Every mag is now green other than
Apple. So, that's all finding a bid.
Ray, Ray, you are something, my friend.
Totally impressed. Is this your first
time with me, Ray Ray? You're just
joining me for first time. Welcome if if
you are.
Welcome. Welcome.
The longer you're with me here, mate,
the more it will all make sense and
you'll start to see what I'm looking at.
God love first time here. Nice. Yeah,
all those first timers, welcome.
If you're wondering what what is on your
screen right now, right? I trade all the
flow, but I use my flow zones and the
key levels. All right, so if you're
interested, there's a ton of free
education on my YouTube. Start there.
You're new to the stream. You're
probably thinking, what am I looking at
on the chart? Start on the free
education on my on my YouTube. And if
you like that and you want to learn
more, there are links down below to the
20our course and the volume and
orderflow course.
Oh, got you. My bad. Ray, Ray, yeah,
initial balance. Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you, Tyson. IB now set.
So, high of day, IB. Purple on your
screen. Initial balance. So, what can we
think about here? If we're going to get
a trend day, we're going to have to find
acceptance above initial balance and
probably above this gray box. If we're
going to get an IB rotation day, it's
very possible we do something like this
and come back down. All right, so be
aware of fail breakouts today. All
right, if we can get through this huge
chunk here, we do have this looming all
the way up here at 800s, right? Anyone
who read the newsletter, these are the
same levels, right? These are the levels
from the newsletter, the rotational
points.
I will remind you, we are still an
inside day. All right, we're still
inside of Friday. We're still inside of
the previous week. We are still inside
of the previous week's value, but we are
moving daily value higher. We are trying
to find acceptance of daily value
higher.
Boom. Here we go, folks. Here comes the
lift. All right. So, you should get this
full TP. We should get into this gray
box and previous week point control. I
would say hold even if you are able to
hold one micro in case you get all the
way up here and you can, you know, if
you get an expansion, right? If you get
an expansion candle, something like
that, just move your stop into here. You
never know in ca just in case they do
this move for you because even one micro
that's an extra $200 per account for
you. All right,
Alex, I want to thank you for your daily
reminder of discipline. Happy New Year,
buddy. Happy New Year to you, my friend.
So at the end of the day with my opinion
about your methodology, is it all about
liquidity and identifying value? Yeah.
Well, all the market's ever doing is
looking to identify value because that's
all any market does, right? It's looking
to see where buyers and sellers most
agree on price. And then if there's an
imbalance, if we have more buyers than
sellers, we're going to move up. we have
more sellers than buyers. We're going to
move down and search for a new level of
value. It's of my opinion that when
we're searching for value, we are going
to run stops. ENQ especially is absolute
liquidity [\h__\h] right? It wants to run
for stops. So that's what we do. We
build, we are always in two phases of a
market. We are either building liquidity
when we're in contraction, which is
arguably what we're in at the moment,
right? where we're squeezing tighter and
tighter and tighter and tighter and we
compress more and more and more volume.
And at some point, we're going to run
stops at least one side of that, if not
both. And if we go into an expansion
model or a trend model, then we're going
to look for the next block of liquidity
to to go and attack into. And that's all
it is. So all we're doing as day traders
when we're trading futures is the same
as you do on swing, but you're you're
having to be, you know, a little bit
more precise and a little bit more
focused in because the rotations like
you've seen today can happen five 10
points or 20 point rotations. Um whereas
if you're like a set and forget on the
whole swing, right? Then we can look for
things like holding above previous days
value area high, holding a bid at
previous week value area low, trying to
complete the rotation to the naked point
of control. All right, early in the
session. Okay, we get up there,
fantastic, job's done. Maybe then they
sell back down. If they don't and they
want to rebid it, then we're going to
come and test the other side. And I
would expect it to fail here. And we
don't fail there, then fantastic. means
we're going to auction up and we just
look for the next level higher and the
next level higher. That's all we do.
So what I ask myself every day is where
are the key levels, right? Where do I
want to trade around? So for me that
comes down to location. And the next
thing I ask myself is who's in control?
What is the momentum? That's that's kind
of it.
Grinding its way slowly. It is. That's
exactly what it's doing. Grinding its
way slowly. We came right into the edge
of this gray box. Look, we're right into
the edge of this gray box. I'd love them
to come and tap this. I think this is
accurate. I mean, according to Trading
View, it's accurate. Who knows? Maybe
Ninja has it somewhere else. But, uh,
it's here or hereabouts, right? This
gray box is point of control. Maybe it's
here. Maybe it's here. But this is where
I have the exact line. But that's why I
put this gray box out here.
momentum trader. It's reversing from
here. I mean, it can get stuck up here.
I'm not I've not seen enough yet to say
that it's done, but it's an area where
they might want to sell from. There's I
would not deny that. That's why we have
it marked out.
Just remember how you built liquidity on
the way up. So, you're going to need it
to, if I was going to be in a sell,
right, I would want a fail breakout with
some, you know, exposure of buyers
caught up at the highs and then a move
back down. Um, this flat top here, we
can have a look how much buying was in
there.
It's a decent amount.
There's a decent amount. The excess,
let's have a look on my other screen. We
have a little excess into 90. I wouldn't
say it's the biggest, but it's okay.
Okay. And we've seen that transition
from buy side to del to sell side.
I would rather it comes, you know, it
has one more shove up, but we built lots
of liquidity to run,
right? And what we'd really like is like
something like a big shelf developed
here. So, if we have something like this
developed here, right, and we get above
it and we see buyers come flying in and
then we get stuck under that shelf,
under that shelf would be here, wouldn't
it? Then we can look for a cell and it'
be TP1, TP2, TP3. Might well be that it
fades from here, but uh you know, you
have to respect all these levels that we
built out. This node here is
interesting. I'd rather it comes up
higher. Like I said, one more shove and
then build out a shelf and then use all
those late buyers to go lower.
Is the footprint on Trading View? That
that one I just showed you is yes, it's
on Trading View. At the moment, we're
holding a buy side imbalance in 60. So
if you remember where we had that big
seller, he was at 60, right? Remember
over here? So there's a huge seller at
60. We need to get back above that. Once
we got above him, we ran it. We have a
buy side imbalance here that we're
trying to hold. If we fail that, we're
coming back to value. If they don't bid
value, we will go rotation. If they bid
value, they've still got a shot. We're
walking value up. Remember,
it's the first time I've seen failed
followthrough up there. Don't like the
high, but it is the first time we've
seen failed follow through.
I wouldn't say that high is the best in
terms of excess. I think ES's one looks
much better.
Yeah, I agree, Peter. Like the volume is
so low. I was expecting it to like come
back on and turn on today. It's very
low.
Very low.
All right, folks.
You emailed last week. Um,
info@flowzone trader.
Check my spam now.
What's uh what's your email?
Let's
go man too.
Not seeing it, bud. Do you mind doing it
again for me?
I'm really sorry if I've missed that.
I've I can't see it. I've just checked
my spam and searched for you as well.
Let me check. Uh, actually
check here.
Oh, I see it. I see it. I see it. I see
it.
My bad. I'm really sorry. It went to
spam. It did go to spam.
I see you. All right, I'm going to reply
to you now, dude. Okay, they're still
trying to hold value. You want to be
careful if pushes start to fail here.
All right, so they will try. Buyers want
to hold value and complete this move. If
you see a push that fails and we come
under value, this move here can
collapse. I'm just going to reply to uh
Rusco here.
There you go, mate. Should be all
sorted.
Should be all sorted.
Okay, I can finally announce it. Funded
next and just emailed me. I've been
waiting to announce this for you guys.
have just added some uh new stuff for
you guys. So, they've added a one-day
pass for a bolt-on. Okay, so
it's going to be the most affordable and
most flexible speed challenge that you
can do. So, you can pass this in one
day. You can receive payouts. The next
day, it's available just for 50k
challenges. And there's a limited time
exclusive challenge. So, it's $99
onetime fee. It removes the entry cost
traditionally associated with it and
gives you access to 50k. And you can add
a no loss limit and a no consistency
rule to that as well if you want to. So
it's $99 right now. If you want it, no
loss limit, no daily loss limit, $129.
No consistency rule, $199. If you want
both, it's $149.
One day pass, just so that you guys are
aware. I will stick it all on social
later, but they messaged me about that a
couple weeks ago. It's finally just gone
live by the looks of it.
Okay, so getting stuck like we just
talked about at this shelf. All right,
we've developed a bit of a shelf up here
that buyers are not able to get
acceptance back above right now. We're
starting to see that potential rotation
back down to VWAP off the IB trade. It
is possible. I'm still a little bit iffy
on it yet, if I'm honest, just because
we've moved PC up, everything's moving
up. I just would like to see it trade
into here first. I really would like to
see it trade into here first. Just one
more push.
You sent an email of the free indicator.
Okay, I'll get I'll get on guys. I'll
get on all those later. I'll apologize
to you. I've been away from my desk. I
haven't had a good weekend. I've got a
massive migraine. I'm doing my best to
be here. It's why I've got sunglasses
on. It's not It's not to look cool. I'm
sure I look like a bit of a dick right
now, but uh
I wanted to be here for you guys. I
promise once we're done on stream, I
will get on top of all the emails.
Anyone that's emailed anything I've
missed, I promise I'll get on top of it.
All right.
What levels are the downside and how to
find them if you can, Alex? Well, if
you're looking for a downside, so if
you're in a balance day, if we're going
to fail initial balance, if you're going
to reject this shelf and come under
here, you can look for this shelf and
VWAP. So, I'd be looking for the 20s. If
you're fading this, I'd be first of all,
I'm looking for 40s. Acceptance under
40s, 20s, acceptance under that, back
down into the 600s again. Acceptance
under that value area low on the day
down here, 84s. Um, and you don't think
about anything beyond that unless you're
going to find acceptance under previous
days value. Right? At the moment, we're
not seeing that. At the moment, we're
getting this. Right? So, we've come from
one side, grind up to the other side. If
we don't find acceptance up here, we're
going to come back down to this side
maybe or the midpoint. Try back up
again. We can do this all day until one
side wins.
I would have really liked it to come and
tag this either this morning or here.
Yes, I saw someone say maybe maybe
Tyson's trade setting up. For those of
you who don't know, Tyson's trade is
this purple line to this green line and
it is uh absolutely starting to work
out. We are rejecting this shelf. I
would have just liked a bit more excess.
If we had excess like this up here, this
would have looked really good. But hey,
it is what it is.
>> [laughter]
>> Yeah, I wish that's what it was. JD,
have I been watching the Blues Brothers?
I haven't. I absolutely love that
though. Here's a question for chat. This
will show how old are you. Which is your
favorite Blues Brothers film, though?
the original
with Twiggy
and Scatman
and Artha or the 2000 remake.
Original. Original is so good, isn't it?
The longest car chase known to man.
So good. I love that film so much.
definitely showing our age. Like if if
if if you're a young gun in here, you're
like, "What is the Blues Brothers?"
Well, if you like blues music, go and
watch it. It will some of the all-time
greats are in it.
Incredible. Incredible musical film. And
I don't like musicals, but that is that
is a top 10 film.
Yeah. Like I said, I don't like the
short yet. like you're getting that
trade from here to here. For me
personally, I don't really like all it
is, folks, is that we don't have excess
up here, right? That's all I don't like.
What I like to see is
a nice big bullish candle up here with
tons of buyers trapped in and then
seeing the transition. We did have
buying in here and we saw a transition.
There is no doubt about it. And we held
this imbalance. like sellers are in
control here, but it just feels like
nothing more than a pullback to fill
some imbalance. And uh yeah, I'm not
sure yet. It doesn't feel high, how can
I put this? It doesn't feel high
probability to me when there's a low
hanging fruit above without excess. It
looks pretty good on ES, I would say.
But bulls are still in control. If you
moved to like a five minute chart, do I
have it on here? You will see that balls
are still in control.
We move this off.
There we go.
I'm a bit worried I'm going to have to
take this IWC in for a service and I've
only had it 18 months.
One of the pins in this
is loose and I'm worried I'm going to
wear it one day and it's suddenly I'm
going to look down and it's not on my
wrist.
I can bang that in.
Sellers need to get below the New York
open. Yeah, I would agree with that.
this [\h__\h] strap on the IWC. Honestly,
it's a ridiculously expensive watch. And
I bought it just before they bought out
the new strap and clasp. And I think the
new strap and clasp, I don't think they
sell the new clasp. I think I have to
get the new strap and clasp, which is
like [\h__\h] [snorts] 1,800 bucks or
something stupid
cuz they have a design fault. It's so
dumb.
Me ranting. I'm sorry.
There we go. That sounds better.
Yeah, that's loose. Take this out. Like
I say,
should be warranty at least.
[sighs]
No, I'm English. Not Aussie, mate.
You We trading inq.
I'm English, bro.
Tiny drop of nail varnish will stop it
walking out. Oh, thanks, man. I'll give
that a go.
Market's asleep. Market feels asleep.
I'll give you a read out on a mag. Tesla
3.91% up. Nvidia a third of a percent
up. Microsoft 0.20% down. Meta 1.43%
down. Google 0.73% down. Up. Sorry,
what? Meta 1.47% up. Google 0.71% up.
Amazon 2 or 2 and a half% up. Apple 2/3
of a percent down. Broader names like
AMD's up 3/4 of a percent.
Why is Oscar's Health found a 10% bid?
What's gone on there? [\h__\h] cut that
last year.
Let me have a look at some of these.
Sorry folks, I just want to uh
you
scum. What are you doing?
mate. Do I take a position on that?
>> [sighs]
>> What's that gain there?
200 center. Oh man, it's [\h__\h]
tempting.
That is tempting.
Give it Give it this week to develop.
Yeah, they all like it.
Put that on the watch list again.
Sorry if I was talking to myself there.
Yeah, right. It's It's just dead.
Market's dead.
Soccer fan. What? Football fan you mean?
Yeah. Arsenal fan, mate. Top of the
league.
Vintage watch parts. Oh, it's not
vintage. It's It's new. It's like 18
months old. It's new. I can probably
take it in for a repair.
It's just annoying.
Ly What's that? Eli Lily.
Jesus.
You're on a mad run, isn't it?
Mad run. That thing is just a [\h__\h]
beast. Honestly, look at that. Jeez.
Absolute machine. I don't really want
that. Pivot's good.
I don't know. I'm too stingy for that. I
think healthc care is due like a a lift
and bump. Here we go. So, they're
finding a bid here. They want to come
back for this if they can
see if they lift up and go for it. If we
see failed follow through to this shelf
again. So this shelf here is what's
holding price. This is your overunder.
If you're short, this is your overunder.
Like you need this to hold
that gray box. They did just try and
aggressively buy that and get hit. So
there's passive sellers sitting in that
gray box right now. And you can see them
on the book at 70. My my issue would be
if they lift through that, you are going
to go 700. Right? If they get through
that gray box, I don't think you want to
sit through this short. So, if you took
this short here or this short here, you
should be covering some and looking for
a continuation. If you see this, you
want to be out. Don't risk hive day cuz
it's more likely we're going to take out
the PC at that point.
So, sit in what you've got, but uh don't
be stubborn.
Someone's playing games on the tape now
and you got a buyer just running away.
Um,
cut off time. I think it's uh midnight
uh east coast time tomorrow I think.
Premier League champs this year. I
bloody well hope so. What we now seven
seven points clear, six points clear. I
hope so.
Do I use market or limit orders? Uh
limit orders to get in wherever
possible. If I can get on a pullback,
I'm using limits. If I'm forced to take
a break above a candle and I know that
it's still good RR, I will mark it in.
Um, I will add, normally I'll limit in
my first position, I'll add on a market
because it means it's going in my way.
Um, I will exit with limits at key
levels, but I will drag my limits down.
If I feel like I'm not getting filled, I
will drag my limit down. So, for
example, if if I was long, right, and I
had a limit up there and I was long from
down here and I saw this not coming, I
will drag that limit there to get filled
basically on a market fill or I'll just
drag it below it so I get a quick fill.
I always have my limit staggered where I
want. So, maybe I had a limit here, a
limit here, and a limit above. And let's
say I was long down here. So, we hit
that one. We missed this. I can drag my
limit below and get filled on one of
them. And maybe I have one left with an
entry price of there. For example, I'm
not in a position now. I want to make
that clear.
Yeah, I saw United have sacked him.
I mean, who they Here's the bigger
question. Who they going to replace him
with? You just spent all your [\h__\h]
money on a load of [\h__\h] players and
they've sacked your [\h__\h] coach. No one
wants to go to that club.
Like
obviously I hate United but I actually
want them to be half decent. I think
it's healthy for English football. This
looks like it wants to lift. They are
getting aggressive here up here into
60s.
Yes. Trying to do a flag break as well.
Uh yes, I do use a ATM strategy. Yeah.
Do I have a minimum RR? Not really. Um
like I look for honestly the way I trade
it's more about high probability. Do I
think we're going to go to a level like
one I don't really like trading
negatively. It's not something I'd ever
look for. I know lots of other people
do, but the more you tune in here,
you'll see that I'm normally looking for
50 to 100 point trades because I think
ENQ most of the time will make those
available. So even if you think about
what we got today, what was our RR
today? So we were short
in here for this move down into here and
we would have been risking the top of
this volume. So it's like a five R there
if you want to do it our ways. And then
the other way around we were playing dip
longs and adding into them. So our
average did move
but dip longs
back up to here. And we were adding over
600s, remember, as well. And some of you
are still in it. I'm not in there
anymore.
And this is your new shelf between this
gray box. You can see this gray box
acting as resistance and this box here
acting as support. These are your
rotations. Basically, 50s to 70s, 20
point rotations right now. You're not
seeing follow through though. So sellers
still defending. Passive sellers are in
here. You have seen aggressive buying in
here and we're not seeing follow
through. How do I know? We can literally
see it. All right. Look at these guys
here.
These players here aggressively buying.
91 lot, 88 lot, 190 lot, 92 lot. We're
not moving higher because this seller
here is passively absorbing the tape.
Okay. So that's the rotation that we're
seeing at the moment.
I haven't taken a trade for a while now
because I think we want to come up into
this area, but this is not a good area
to buy. The best area to buy was those
value area lows that we talked about
earlier.
Praying for Southgate or Southgate to
United.
Not a bad idea. I think he'd scrap most
your team though.
What do I think of Barcel? I've not
really watched them much this season if
I'm honest.
This may be silly, but every time I buy
or sell a limit doesn't set where I put
it. It buys like it's a market order.
Any suggestions? What are you uh
executing on? Otus
Celtic are [\h__\h] stupid.
Like, you can't believe
my buddy Glenn was telling me about that
the weekend. They had that awful start.
They put Martin O'Neal in. He absolutely
does an unbelievable job. and then they
get rid of him and then go on like what
a 12 game losing streak and now
have replaced him again. So [\h__\h]
dumb.
So dumb. Like he was doing a good job as
in manager. Should have just let him
take the job. He wanted the job. Just
let him keep the job. Embarrassing. They
lost to who they to at the weekend. Was
it Rangers at home?
I was trading a 50k Apex full Apex
account today. Can you explain the rules
in the 3K profit goal? Can I hit it in
one trade? Yeah, you can hit it in one
trade. No worries.
Uh swing for Tammy. Yeah, in swing
positions. Yeah, not really day trading.
Uh used to, but my brain honestly can't
handle doing this.
um doing it live, teaching on Discord,
running the mentorship and course
program and trading stocks as day
positions. But what I do have the
capacity to do with my brain is take
swing positions.
It doesn't require as much management.
Trading View Otus, I'm not sure then.
Notice you should be able to like right
click and
be like buy limit. My one's not doing it
at all. By
you should be able to set a limit um
where you want it and and drag it. Um
just make sure when you I don't know why
I can't do this.
Hang on.
Let's log into sim.
Will it let me do it now? There we go.
Okay. You should be able to be like
that market only. Here you go. You
should be able to set your limit here.
So maybe you're on the wrong one. So you
should be able to set your limit there
with what you want and you can add your
stop loss and take profit. Um if you're
trading
via um trade of eight, that might be
slightly different. I don't execute on
Trading View, so I can't fully tell you.
I'm really sorry, but you should be able
to set a limit. Not sure why that's gone
wrong for you.
I got here late, currently on the West
Coast. Could I recap the trade entries
and reasons? Yes, I can make it really
simple because we went over it in here
first. Okay, so we were talking about
we were in uh developing a wedge. All
right, and we can notice this volume
node here. If I zoom this in, this
volume node here is 600s. So if we found
acceptance above 600s, we were looking
for a squeeze out to 700s. I also said
you have to be very careful of a look
above and fail. Um where do I draw? So
these are the moves I drew out this
morning and that was then followed by
D. Watch the edges remain flexible.
There is a shelf at 600. So those whole
numbers are pretty nice over under
levels today. Hold 500, test 600, hold
700. But
be aware that should say of a look above
and fail of each level. So if we go back
into what we saw this morning,
right, the opening drive,
we had the shelf at 600. All right, so
opening drive, I left this alone. I was
hoping they would squeeze out to here
and I would think about that short back
down to test this. We didn't make it.
All right, and where I got involved is
this, this, and this. And then I started
playing short here for the completion of
the rotation back down to a previous day
value area high, previous week value
area low. So the first trade was short
the old volume shelf with a look above
and fail like we talked about in
Discord. This move down to here. Once we
got down to there, I was waiting to see
if we put in a higher low and we trap
sellers down here, which is what we do
in this move here. So this is your cheap
buy for the rotation back to New York.
So, if we look at what that looked like,
you can see I've still got it
highlighted,
right? We had sellers stuck
in this move here.
Once we pivot over that and we hold, I
now know sellers under 560 a quart and
we played long
back up the other way. Those were the
two trades and what you're now looking
to do ideally is complete this move if
you're still long and holding to
previous week point of control. This is
why I said I still think we have
unfinished business there. It doesn't
have to do it. Volume's low but one two
leg higher low higher low right in
intrim low. They are looking to complete
this into here the upside. So they're
looking to trade 690s, 700, 705, 740s.
Acceptance through 740s will get you
back up to 800s. Right? So those were
the trades they were. We talked about it
in pre-market show. We talked about it
in Discord from early this morning and
then we executed on here. Hopefully that
helps.
No worries. Otus.
Uh, I am Monday to Friday, Daryl, but I
took Friday off. Well, I was going to
take it completely off and have a long
weekend. Um, because I thought we'd have
a rubbish day and low volume. It ended
up being a really good day. So, I was a
bit devastated that I missed that
morning. So, I came back in the
afternoon and we traded long Friday
afternoon because I missed the sell. So,
Friday afternoon,
we traded this. All right. So, this was
an old naked point of control from the
week from like three weeks before and we
traded long back through here um for
this hourly move. So, the H4H1 so I can
still remember it. See this this candle
here is 2 hours uh two at 2:00, sorry. I
traded this long up here. We got 100
points out of it. So, we traded from
what 280 to 380. This was the move that
we got in Discord. Anyone who got that
with me in Discord can let you know. I
know Adam Bowden got it with me. A few
other guys got it with me. Um, that's
what we traded on Friday in Discord.
Some of them held on to for acceptance
higher. I didn't. I just took my 100
points and got off.
And I'm sure some of you going to be
like, I don't believe you. So, I should
probably just go and find it, shouldn't
I? Um,
where do we have the old naked control?
Here's my entry. So, where were we
talking about it? Okay, here when I was
first talking about it.
300 test 315 key and then we start
getting long or that move upside right
and I had two attempts that was first
attempt and then I added and had a
second tenth and then on this one we
ripped 100 points through all these
levels you can see like Nathan getting
it with me lots of guys getting it with
me there you go
all right
so that's the advantage in being Discord
>> [snorts]
>> Uh, okay. You guys are all new. So,
Discord is for members only. You need to
do the beginner to advance course. Uh,
it's all on my website.
www do www.flowzonetrader.com.
It's all there, folks. All right.
Everything's there. that will get you um
the 20our course and uh and Discord
comes with that as does one of the
indicators.
And then if you want to do a top up, if
you want to do the volume and orderflow
course, you can do that separately.
Uh, so Alonzo Alon Alonzo, if you go in
the course as you get towards the back
of the course, you can go and do that
now if you want like cycle down to the
last few modules, there is an email and
it tells you what to do.
It's not a paid thing, it's a pro thing.
Uh for sorry one of you asking about
volume footprint. You come to these
candles. It's right here. Volume
footprint. Um you can only do it if you
pay for pro membership on uh Trading
View. Okay, here we go folks. So I think
now you're probably going to get this
move. All right, so it's completing
really a giant cup and handle.
It's a bit of an ugly one, but there we
go. It's trying to complete this and
this is its target. All right, so TP1,
TP2, TP3, and runners up there. Those of
you who are still long,
that's why I just didn't think I didn't
love the short. You would have heard me
say it like it can do it, but it's not
something I love because we don't have
enough excess up here. So, I think we
will want to run that, which is what
you're starting to see. And I think this
is the low hanging fruit is up into
these sort of 700 705s.
It's an in from 60 running going. Nice,
man.
How much money do I get from YouTube?
[\h__\h] all, man. Between like 600 and 800
bucks a month. And those have been my
best months. And that was only in the
last month. But as you will notice, I
stream without adverts on, right? So, I
could make a lot more. Well, I don't
know if there's a lot more. I could make
more, but it won't benefit you guys. It
would be a pain in the ass for you guys.
So, what I do is I'd stream for free and
I turn the adverts on afterwards.
Okay, here you go, folks. So getting
through these now. So you've just
expanded higher date. We should try and
get up into these sort of 700 707s. You
want to be selling a partial into this
next push up into it. Okay.
Yeah, quite right. It's And I obviously
I pay tax on that as well, right? So you
know, realistically I'm making
300 bucks out of YouTube each month. I
mean it's uh it's it's it's nothing.
It's It's a nice little tickler, isn't
it? Like I don't know. Pays for a meal
out each month.
All that actually happens is I reinvest
it in stuff. So that will pay for the
guy that's doing like the thumbnails of
my YouTube or whatever.
All right. So you're getting some buying
coming up here at 90s is a little bit
caught right now. Another buyer. There's
a bit more excess, but I think you're
still going to see one more shove up. I
don't think it's finished yet. I think
they're looking for one more shove up.
We got a slight divergence. ES hasn't
made the new high yet, but it is trying.
It's tapping into its IB. We should see
one more shove up. We have seen a new
high in ENQ and some excess above it for
the first time. Think we're going to
come into this gray box here. But you
guys should be well positioned. Most of
you, I assume, are either long from down
here or long from the 600s or maybe you
reaccumulated
this New York open. Look at the
importance of this New York open, this
blue line, right? We're bidding over New
York open, trying to complete this move,
this move, right? Pull back one, pull
back two. This is where we're trying to
go. And please sell into this, not all
your position. Please take some profits
because we can definitely come up here
and then get slammed. If you get really
lucky, you're going to get a 100 point
runner all the way up into 800. And I
hope that happens for you. Oh, don't
move that. I hope that happens for you.
I hope you get 800. But you must take
some profits into sevens.
Okay, while this sets up folks and uh
hopefully lock in your money, I'm just
going to use the bathroom and then I'll
be back and I'd love to do a giveaway
with you guys shortly when I get back.
So, if you guys can smash that like
button, how are we doing? I want at
least 450,500 likes on this video.
Okay.
All right. So, same levels, folks. Balls
now got a hold the new value area high
and this shelf at 70s.
All right. But this is uh let's have a
look at this excess. It's a little bit
better. So, I'd say buyers now are
caught above 690s. All right. Buyers are
caught above 690s. sellers to control
690 to 685s. So buyers are caught above
690s. So if you are long, you should
have taken profit, like I said, into
this gray box. We talked about it into
this gray box. You should have locked
most in. You'll need them to rebid here.
All right. If they can't rebid there, or
even if they do, and they can't get back
above 690s, you are going to see a
rotation now. So you should be down to
small size.
New York open. Why does it need to hold
above that? Okay. So, let let's let's
think about this realistically.
If you are a fund manager, all right,
you are not necessarily dictating
what you're buying and when you're
buying. What you're told is like you
need to buy
a 100,000 shares of Tesla at a market
price of this and we will give you a
bonus if you buy X amount below VWAP for
example for our clients. The easiest way
to get massive size into the market is
when when there's high volatility. Why?
Because most volume is traded there. So
if you need to get big size in or out of
the market, where's the chance to do it?
is going to be in the high volume areas.
Right? So, this area here, we've got to
think at that open, that is the level
that all the cash players went, "Well,
I'm long today. [\h__\h] it. I'm long."
Right? Not the guys playing off key
levels, the cash players, the market
making cash players or the funds who are
like, "I'm long. I'm long and my job is
to get long until we get here." Or, "My
job is to get long for the next 3 weeks
until we get here," for example. Right?
So,
in terms of this level, it's a bit like
a VWOP or a T-W where they will keep
rebidding it if they have more size to
buy at that level. If their order was
bid there and rebid here and rebid here
and rebid here and rebid here and
they've still got more to buy, they will
keep buying it because that is the cash
open. And for me, anyone who's watched
my stuff on cash gaps and stuff like
that, cash is king in this market
or in any market.
Okay, so look at the gray box. We just
rebid off it. We literally just talked
about that, didn't we? So rebidding off
it. So this isn't crystal ball stuff,
guys. This is like you can see it
happening right in front of you. And we
talked about the 90s being the important
level. The buyers got stuck at 90s. So
if we fail to get back above 90s, if
sellers hold 90s, you're going to rotate
between 90s and that gray box. And if
the gray box fails, we're going to come
back down to point control. And if we
lose that, you get a bigger rotation. So
those who have joined me for weeks or
months or even years will just be used
to seeing the market move this way. Now
Skucks Deluxe just Skucks Deluxe I think
I said that right. Just missed your TP.
What the upside? Um I mean missed final
one. You might you might still get it
but like I said you want to be very
careful now. Buyers are caught above 90.
Right. This is buyers being caught. So,
this needs to reclaim this and do this.
If it does that, you're fine. But if you
keep rejecting 90 and you do this, we
can get a bit more of a collapse. All
right. So, that's what I'd be looking
for. You need to, if you're still long,
you've held this gray box. It's a good
hold. Remember, you've accumulated here.
Hopefully, you've sold some into this.
You've held that. You need to get back
above 90. If you start losing this gray
box, I would say don't touch it. Cut
your position. Personally, it's what I'd
be looking for. Really, you want this to
hold and go.
Uh this is my flow zone pro. You can get
this on the website. A version of it
comes with the course. So everything you
see here,
you see we probably went into a buy and
a sell. Yeah, a few buys and sells once
we went sideways, but then we've been in
trend since right just protrend
up here. higher time frame trying to
trying to get bullish higher time frame
and lower time frame trying to join when
we're above the waves.
No, I draw those gray boxes. You would
have just if you rewind it, you would
have just seen me draw. They're just
based on volume, right? So, I draw them
based on volume. You see this shelf
here? That's what it's based on. This
shelf here, gray box. This shelf here is
based on a shelf created last week. So
if we look at
right this
right this shelf right so it's just
where remember if you've got high volume
it's where we found acceptance of price
it's where buyers and sellers are
agreeing on price
again you want this to hold you want
bears to fail to get a breakdown if
you're long Right? You want this to be a
failed breakdown so that you've trapped
lots of bears in here and above 90 you
should have the ability to go. If bears
get their way, we'll start rotating
lower and I would be done with longs for
the day or at least for this session I
would say unless they rebid this. But
that would be very very ugly. Uh because
if they start to lose this, right, if
this happens and we start to lose this,
then we're going to have all this buy
side volume trapped and VWAP. And if we
lose New York VWAP, and if we lose that,
rotation back down to current day value
low, which would be 24-hour VWOP and
lower time frame ALGO probably by the
day time we get there. So there is like
another 80 point downside if they let go
of these. Until that point though, bulls
are in control. As long as they hold
gray box and they have squeeze
possibility above 90,
I wouldn't be buying up here as a new
money position. Right. We remember we we
were bidding basically off low of day
today.
Yeah. Win rate is uh normally like 68 to
73% month depend like somewhere around
there is my win rate. But what I will
tell you with that is I take a lot of
like what I consider break even trades
which are basically scratch and so they
might be considered a win right so it's
probably I'll be honest it's probably a
little bit skewed so like a win where
I've made one tick two ticks but
not necessarily the ones banking right
whereas uh RR you saw today like I think
RR is hard as well because both trades
today were like five are um but we're in
a lower
lower volatility kind of day, right? But
we try and get 40 50 points minimum is
what I'm looking for.
Hope that helps. I know it's probably
not that useful, but I always think win
rate can be a bit skewed.
Can we see a cell of 700 to 738 in this
box? Yeah.
Yeah. in here you're talking about?
Yeah. But you're going to need them to
trap, right? So if we get up
anywhere from here can be a sell, but
remember it's got to prove yourself. You
don't want to be like sell some here,
sell some here, sell some here, sell
some here, and they come up to 800 and
you blow up, right? Because you'll be
front side because what's happening
right now,
right? This can still happen, right?
Doesn't have to happen. That can still
happen. What you need to see if you want
to sell in this gray box is some kind of
shove up with exhaustion and then lower
high and leaving buyers trapped. So what
that might look like, it could be a
candle like this. This is an extreme
version with a nice long wick where you
know passive sellers come in. Maybe
you're watching footprint, maybe you're
watching bookmap, right? Something like
that into there. You don't want to get
front side just just because remember
what I talked about at the beginning of
the day. What are we talking about?
location
and momentum. Is this a good location to
be short in? I'd argue it could it could
be a very good location to be short in.
What is the momentum currently? It's
bullish. We don't want to short against
bullish momentum.
While this is slow, I want to check out
this funded next thing cuz uh see how
good this is.
There's the website updated.
Here we go. So, they're starting to
squeeze. They're trying to do it. They
want to complete it. The gray box is
holding is holding. They want to get
above the 90s. I told you that's the
pain point right now. Bulls need to get
back above 90s because they are out of
position right now. And if they get
above back above that, they can look for
the squeeze out. They've got to start
getting back above the 90s.
Uh for me, Brett, New York session,
right? Because that's when the most of
volume comes in. But um you know, you
can measure
what's happened overnight. Sometimes is
useful coming into a new session, right?
if we're gapping up or gapping down.
How do you tell when it's a short
squeeze or long buying? Uh, it's more
about the looking left and seeing where
that liquidity is. But I mean, it can be
both those things at the same time,
right? If it's market participation, as
in market order participation, then we
know it's people chasing in and stops
getting run, right? If it's just gradual
limit up buying absorbing, then we know
it's just genuine buying with a passive
seller walking it up. It's very
different.
I don't trade forex. No, never have.
Never have traded forex.
My old man lost a fortune back in the
day trading forex. Never I've never
touched it. His horror stories.
Do I wait until the after 50 minutes to
take a trade? I don't. I don't. It
doesn't mean I always take a trade at
the open. If there's a setup at the
open, I'll take it. Like, I took a setup
before the open uh as well today. Uh it
didn't work out. I mean, I did make
money, but it didn't um
it didn't go all the way down. Where is
So,
when I talked about the look above and
fail 600s, this is way back. Let's get
down to today.
As you can see here, I was playing the
look above and fail for 600s. All right,
moved my stopped in, locked in some
money. Yeah, there's no rules of when to
trade. I don't like trading GlobeEx
unless there's a really good setup
because volume is so low. So, you can
get skipped on, the spread can open up
if some news hits that you're not ready
for and the spread opens up, you're
going to get absolutely cooked. I'd much
rather trade the New York session. Plus,
it limits my exposure mentally to be on
the charts because this is a tiring
game, folks. If you're going to sit here
and try and trade, you know, New York
session and afternoon session and then a
bit of Asia or I'm going to stay up and
trade like you're just you're going to
burn out so quick.
If you put the volume profile on the
Asian open,
then the PC aligns with the double top
area. Hopefully, it bounces. Huh? If you
put volume profile on Asia open, what do
you mean then the PC aligns? Oh, then
then the PC aligns with a double top. Is
that what you're saying? Um,
I don't think that's possible, mate,
because or you
you mean the point of control was 500 in
the in around 500 or 490 in the Asia
session. Is that what you're talking
about? And then London held the dip.
Maybe that's what you mean cuz we're
nowhere near any of that right now.
Maybe I just misunderstood what you
meant. Right. So this remember the 90s
we kept talking about 90s is important
because this where buyers are trapped
above 90s. They still cannot get above
90s. Buyers have got to get above the
90s right now.
Right. This is where the buying came in
here. Right. These buyers are currently
trapped in the market and most of it
came in I have to look at my other
indicator. Most of it came in at 88 and
90. Above that is thin but 88 and 90 was
some big time buyers.
So we need to get back above that for
the bulls to have a shot of completing
it. If they can't get back above that
they're in danger of a failed break
higher. [snorts]
I'm pretty new and was told not to trade
after until after 15 minutes. I think
whoever told you that is very wise.
Yeah, if you're new, let it calm down.
Absolutely. I I completely agree with
that because it's very volatile and in
the open and you'll get caught out. So,
I would agree with that, Nate.
Watching RSI to get into overbought and
cross EMA pointless. I think it's not
pointless on higher time frames.
I don't think RSI really cares about
anything on like a one minute or a tick,
but I think on higher time frames it
could become useful.
Uh we're we're not at yesterday's top.
I'm watching the profile here. We're
coming into previous week point of
control. We're above old value. We left
Friday's value. Friday's top value was
55 54. It's way down there. Unless
you're talking about TPO. Maybe you're
talking about TPO
in terms of time. But yeah, I'm watching
to see if we can get into previous week
point control and then if if we sell
look above and fail or if we base.
Do I look at expected high of the day in
ESNQ? Not really. What do you use for
that? The like gamma for the expected
move.
What strategy do I use for swings?
Exactly the same as I trade with. I look
for just everything's on much higher
time frame, weekly, daily, 4 hour. I
look for price to move in. If I'm long,
I want to be long biased as much as
possible in swing positions, especially
when I'm looking to hold for multiple
months. Um, unless we're in a bare
market, that's different. And even then,
I'd rather be long in SQ or something.
Um, but I look to buy in areas of demand
where we have a good base and volume
built out where I can see short sellers
are getting themselves caught in the
market where we run liquidity and we
reclaim and then I think okay, we've got
a good move higher. So, I'm I mean I'm
still holding a lot of my positions from
last year. I'm still long Apple from I
have to get this out. I always forget if
it's 220 or 202
my average on this.
So Apple I'm actually long yeah 202. So
I added a bit. So I'm long from 208
average in Apple. AMD um I was long from
the 158 but I sold most of it into that
like 280 move. I'm still holding a
little bit.
Amazon, I'm only up 5%. I'm long from
216. That's a small size. Meta, I'm up
12%. I'm long from 590s. All right. So,
I'm looking for discount prices. I'm
looking for shorts to be trapped. And
I'm looking for potential for expansion
at least up into a first level.
And the same if I was getting short
bias, right? I'd look for, you know, a
blowoff top followed by some
consolidation of buyers trying to come
in at a extreme premium price and then
I'd be looking for us to move away from
that level. Here we go. Bulls finally.
Gez Louise. I mean, what's the time now?
We've They've taken all morning, haven't
they? Two hours to try and come up to
this uh naked point of control up here
from the previous week.
I'm not long Tessa. I'm not long Tessa
at the moment.
The long was when everyone said Elon was
uh a word which we can't repeat on here
and that it should go to hell. That was
the obvious buy opportunity. Uh it's
driven up towards 500. We've seen some
decent profit taking. Doesn't mean it
can't go higher but yeah moving into
more robotics which I do think I've got
a good shot this year. I've made a note
of some ETFs I want to look at actually.
Just haven't had a chance to sit down.
Um, see, give some to you guys if I've
got it here. Please tell I didn't delete
it. Um, yeah, I want to look at uh NLR
and nuclear power this year if we're
going to get a run into AI and data
centers. Um, I think BIO's been
absolutely smacked. So, I want to have a
look at some of those. Um, IBB or
something. Um, and I'll still look at
the data centers. I just wonder if
there's been too much exposure too
quick. But if they offer, you know, if
we go into a panic market, I would do
want to accumulate some of the
speculative names cheap if possible.
Yeah, I hold over earnings if if I'm
positioned well for them, Eddie. So, I
wouldn't buy in a runup to earnings and
hold. Like, if I was going to buy in a
run-up to earnings, I'd be assuming it
would be a sell the news and I'd trim.
But if I'm buying and I'm looking to
hold multiple months, multiple years,
then I'll hold through earnings. But
only if I'm confident in the play and if
it's a thick name. Yeah, it's a thick
name.
Am I looking long? No, because we're
coming into the key area. You should
have already been long. Um, I'm
currently flat, guys. I haven't touched
it since. Look, I can show you. It's the
same as earlier. I don't know why I'm up
2 3,000 on the day or something. Um I
haven't touched it since
I haven't touched it since this long.
Was it here? First go, second go up into
this. I cut it too early. That's right.
You're starting to see three drives
here. So you you want to be careful if
they don't make a new high here.
One, two, three. Ideally, this completes
and then you can think about backside if
they really want to do it. You might go
sideways here. It's possible. It's what
we've done before.
Yeah.
There's here again big levels up here
that we keep selling off and here and
here and here and here. So, this is
where the buyers were caught, right? So,
if we go back to Tuesday the 30th,
that's where buyers were caught offside.
That's why we've sold that every time.
There's a big level this gray box. It's
a big level.
How did I learn to get into the habit of
staying disciplined? Uh, by losing.
Genuinely, that's the answer. by losing
lots and lots and lots and lots and lots
and lots of times
and then realizing that the way you're
going to get or the way you are going to
make more money trading is not by
trading more. It's by going through your
stats and seeing what you're good at and
sticking to that.
So if if I get long now, I am chasing
the market because remember our longs
were all the way down here, right here
and here. We were looking to buy in
discount on the holds of value after
shorts got caught. If I'm trading long
now, okay, maybe we get lucky and it
gets at 707s, but that is a watch my
French here. That is not a good long
position to get up into here. All right,
because the risk is that we come to
point of control, we come to New York
open, we come to VWAP, we collapse down
all the way down here. So, how am I
going to set my RR there? So, negative
RR trade. I I don't want to do that.
That's just a that's just a poor
location to trade in. Especially we got
three drives. We haven't We take out the
high then
to take out the high. I just don't want
to do it. Even if it's one of those,
right? Even if this worked out, even if
you hit long now and it worked out and
got to there and you gave yourself a
dopamine hit for making money, it's a
it's an awful trade.
So, you've got to get out of like the
dopamine hit chase based on money and
you've got to get into the dopamine hit
chase based on good process. That
includes losses. Like, you have to
congratulate yourself for taking a good
loss. If you enter a good trade and you
stop out at the correct level, it's just
how it is. You're not going to get
pocket aces. Well, you might think
you're sitting at a table with Jack Jack
and you're like, I'm good here. But the
guy opp you has got the guy opposite has
got pocket aces. Sometimes that is going
to happen. That's the market.
Okay. So, back to this gray shelf again.
Starting to leave some volume trapped
higher now. So I would now tell you that
uh in that initial balance high which is
a purple line one of you just asked you
have a huge amount of buyers uh stuck
there aggressive buyers at 83. So the
two levels that buyers are now stuck at
are 83 and 90. So if they can't get
above 83 you're probably going to get a
rotation back down into this shelf of
like 60 to 54. You not got a lot of room
to play with stuff. So they're going to
come and test this IB now and buyers
need to get back above that IB and they
need to get back above 90. So you can
see this shelf developing but the actual
buyer he's here and he's here. These are
his two pain points. This is where he's
underwater right now. Right? So he's
bought huge here and here. If we get
back above him, all right, then he's
going to be a happy man and he's
comfortable. But if we keep rejecting
here and here, he's going to start
stopping out and now we're add cell
pressure.
I'll show you him. See him right here.
Right. I can see his delta. See this
right here? 83 and 90. That's his pain
point.
We get back above those. He's nice and
comfy.
Purple line is initial balance. That's
your initial balance.
New highs is on a yes. So maybe maybe we
can get this move to point control.
See they're struggling at that 90 edge
of the gray box where that buyer's been
stuck. My expectations is it should go
point of control, but it should have
already done it. It's a very slow market
again. I'm not in anything here. I'm
just calling what I'm seeing. I've
already have my trades.
VIX low of day as well, folks. So,
everything timing here for a potential
squeeze up
that 90. What do we say? 1985. That's
the level. We're now stuck between 90
and 85. Right. So, we just give it.
We just talked about it. Let's see if
the buyer reloads at 90 and if they soak
they're trying to soak 85. He tried to
reload there at 90. He just came in and
just literally as I said that he's 153
lot long at 90. So he's just added if he
doesn't get a breakout soon he's going
to get very very unhappy and get caught.
So here's the move back to 85. He's now
trying to soak 85. So, we've got a big
player here trying to absorb his book at
85 and add at 90. If he does not get his
way, he's going to have too much size on
this book and you're going to see a
nasty snap. So, he needs this to break
above 90 soon
because all he's doing is adding buyside
delta here. And there's no sellside
delta. They're just soaking this like
passively sitting reloading, reloading,
reloading. But the moment this breaks
90, we will go 700. But if he can't get
his move, he's going to get washed out.
So, this is one player who might be
stuck here.
I'm always interested in these moves
when there's like 50 to 100 points to
play with, but not when we're talking
about five point rotations.
So, you can if they don't get back above
85, he's going to be caught.
He's getting caught here. They're being
aggressive. He's caught. He's starting
to stop out here. They're going to wash
him out now by the looks of it. If he
can't get back above 85, he's offside.
So 78 is by side delta. 75 by side
delta. I'd say under 75. And you can get
a little snap,
little low volume node there. And value
area high on the day for me, not for you
guys, but for what I'm looking at Ninja
Trader is 75. So if we drift below that
based on delta, we're going to come all
the way down to 50s. Well, definitely to
60s and 50s. So, his stops are starting
to get run here. He's starting to get
bit a little bit panicky. He oversized
between 85 and 90 and he hasn't got his
way. And if they snap here, it's uh
night night, sweetheart. There you go.
Goodbye, buddy. So, he just caught him.
He got himself caught.
And you can't see that in candles,
right? You cannot see that in candles.
That's me telling you what's actually
going on.
This This right here told the story. All
right. You see, I said 90 and 85.
There's the move up to 90. Here's 85. He
added so much in here and here. And he
didn't get his way. So, he started to
panic. Sellers came in and now he's
stopping out. And there's the rotation
all the way back down to point of
control that we just talked about.
Right? So, it's happening right before
your eyes. That is the advantage of
understanding order flow.
looking for a push down to 608. I mean,
I I I would say respect what's in front
of you, right? Your inside value.
Respect this P, right? Your inside
value. If you get underneath,
it's dangerous, isn't it? If you get
underneath 50s and underneath the New
York open and by that time hopefully
VWOPS here. If you get a snap of that
then I think you get back down to those
low 600s. But don't if you if you've
played this short on what I was just
talking about if you've played that just
pay yourself because we're inside right
think about previous week
think about current day. We're inside
the rotation. You got to pay yourself. I
mean, there's clearly an aggressive
buyer here today
who just got washed out. So, who knows
if he comes back on. So, we're going
back to 85. So, 85 to 90 is that same
point. So, he's just rebid aggressively
from 67. So, the question now is can he
get back above 85? Is he if he can't,
he's just going to be stuck again?
How do I know where the buyers and
sellers are? Do you see them on the book
map? Yeah, I'm literally That's exactly
it. And that's why I have them literally
watching them. I can see their pain
point. I can see how they're
participating.
No, I haven't done the giveaway yet.
We'll do it at the uh 15 minutes or
whatever it is. We'll do it then.
I tell you what though.
Divergence ES and it's holding above
initial balance. They just rebid it. All
right. Here's 85s. And if they get
through that, he wants to check 90. If
they get through 90, you probably get a
squeeze.
You get through 90, I would say probably
going to get uh previous point control,
probably going to hit 700s.
Can you use regular volume profile to
spot them? Um, no. I mean, you you'll be
able to see the levels of of some
importance, but uh not to the same
extent because you won't be able to see
if they're a buyer or seller or where
they're stuck or how much size they
have. You'll just know that, oh, there's
a node there. You won't know who's
participated there and what their pain
point is, right? So, if you see a new a
huge node, you don't know if it's, you
know, more selling in there or more
buying in there.
So they rejected 90s again, getting back
under 85s again. You can see this
rotation so important. 85 and 90s, I'm
telling you, they are your levels right
now.
Delta tells you, yeah, totally,
totally.
always away NFC and the amount of times
I have that it's unreal.
Tell you more about my dad and
background in trading. Uh long story pro
better to go if you go on my page and go
to the podcast. I did a interview with
um
Austin Silva. It's all on there.
This is confusing. Do I sell a course?
What's confusing? I do have a course for
sale, but what's confusing? Let me
answer your question now. What are you
confused about?
CBD on ES. Yeah, no worries, mate.
you're making lower highs.
So, there's uh passive buyers on ES. So,
you're seeing more aggressive sellers on
ES, right, than you are aggressive
buyers. So, you're making lower highs on
ES. So, you've got passive buyers
walking price up right now. So, it's
bullish.
ES is bullish. You've got a Let me show
you. Where are you? Uh
this right. See this right? More
aggressive selling, lower highs
moving up. That means there's a passive
buyer walking price up because the
aggressors are the sellers here. That
might start to shift. If you get an
aggressive buyer coming, you can really
start squeezing.
But this is bullish, right? If you if
you if price is moving up and CVD is
moving down, it's bullish. Means you've
got passive buyers and aggressive
sellers getting absolutely clobbered.
So, let's think about it. You got market
order selling. Sell more. Sell more.
Sell more. Somewhere. Somewhere. Yeah.
See the divergence. Yeah. Nice.
Okay, here we go. They're through the
90s. So, my expectation now is the 700s
and that previous week point control.
Michael Kane.
I've never heard that.
this new words to him. You're the first
one speaking this language. May I mean
very possibly. I don't know. I don't
know what people's backgrounds are.
Michael Kane.
Almost there, man. Very very close.
value area high now moved up folks. So
690 now value area high. We're still
rebidding. So we're still continuing to
move value higher. This is still very
bullish. There you go. So here's 700s.
Lovely move into 700s here. So, make
sure you're locking some in. You're
seeing some aggressive buying take
place. I think you might get a little
tickle higher here. There was passive
selling at 700. I think you might get
one little more shove up through it.
Yeah, cuz they're adding above now.
They're adding into 705s and 710s and
even 720s. Is there anyone top side of
that box? 737. What's the top side of
our box?
738. Yeah. So, that looks good. So, I
would be trimming your longs now. All
right, trimming your longs. So, your
short didn't last very long. That one
player got stuck, but the moment they
reclaimed, he took over. Like we said,
we had a strong buyer on the tape. 85 to
90s. He's now in the money. And you
should be trimming your long position in
this squeeze up. Here comes point of
control. Finally, they [\h__\h] tagged
it. I mean, how long did they take to do
that? Incredible. Anything above this is
a bonus. You can see a little reaction
there into PC. Anything above this now
is an absolute bonus.
You've never seen anyone talking about
value area maps and footprints. Yeah,
because most most people on YouTube are
full of [\h__\h]
Bro, bro, I got a fair value gap, bro.
Oh my god. This guy ICT told me how to
shut [\h__\h] up. That's the problem right
there.
That's not a digger, you guys. That's
just like what YouTube is, right?
The truth is everything works. It's just
how much detail do you want?
I could dumb it all down for you. Like
you can use the gap, you can use fair
value gaps. Like you can they exist.
They're just not necessarily accurate
because where you see a gap won't
necessarily be where the imbalance is
because the imbalance is like based on
how that transaction took place.
Well, brother, you killed that trade
from the start. I got stopped out, but
it's fine. Oh, you're welcome, man. No
worries. No worries, guys. Which bookmap
package do I use just so I can trade
with the same info? Uh you just need uh
standard one just with CME data or or
just some data feed. You don't need
anything special guys. I don't use any
of like the huge indicators or you you
literally if you're reading price you
don't you don't need it. I mean I know
some guys like having icebergs and all
that stuff. My opinion is you don't need
it. But
look that's just my opinion. You guys
should should use whatever you whatever
resonates with you. If I if I don't
resonate with you, don't don't don't
trade my way, you know, and and that's
fine. There's plenty of ways to trade.
No, I mean, we don't we we don't go
short just because we hit an area. This
this is a level of interest, right?
Imagine you go short. Now, we talked
about this, right? Imagine you got short
here in the edge of the gray box and
you've added short here and the price
squeeze up to here and you add and now
you're full size in here and they go,
"Well, [\h__\h] it. We're going to go and
take this out and run all the stops."
Right. We don't short. We talked about
this. We don't short front side. All
right. Right. The We are doing this
right now. Right. There is the maybe a
little snapshot down to here. That was
that was all you could have probably
had. We're front side. We're going to
need to leave volume trapped. We're
either going to need excess high or
we're going to need to build out a shelf
and leave volume trapped for the
rotation back down. But I'll tell you
now, until you get below this, right,
every short can be soaked off here or
here, right? We can bounce off here. We
can bounce off here. But if we get too
much volume in here and we leave that,
right, if we have this huge shelf and we
leave that, then you're going to get a
nice short.
I've seen some profit taking here. Just
depends if they rebid this now on this
value.
Big sell off that strong sell. Let's see
if they drive back up and resell it. And
that's what you're looking for.
Remember, you're looking for failed
follow-through. You're looking for this
kind of move. It's quite nice. You're
looking for failed follow through and a
leave of rotation. And then you have to
respect each level on the way down
because it's created structure.
PC was good. That was good level.
Right. Look where we are. 85s, right?
85s and 90s. So if he doesn't rebid
this, then we know he exited at PC.
You've got an imbalance now all the way
up to 95. Looking a little bit better
for a short now. So if they push up and
start failing, then maybe you're still
above initial balance. I will tell you
that. And ES is comfortably above
initial balance as well.
They're trying to bid 80s now. We know
that he came in at 85 and 90s. So I
would be interested if there's a big
reaction on the next shove up. If I see
buyers mark it in and get absolutely
clobbered, I'll be interested in this
fade back down. And I will be scalping.
It's not a protren until we get
underneath this huge shell.
So into initial balance we go.
Where are they bidding? 80s70s.
Still got unfinished business higher.
They're still offering up higher right
now.
Let's see. Here's the 85s again. Can we
get a close under IB and 85s? VPO
moving. All right. Interested in this at
the moment. Looking good.
See if we can see some follow through
here. Lovely. Okay, let's get under now
and start being aggressive.
See if we can get into 70s. We've got
some imbalances down at 72s.
And I'm going to consider everything
counter trend will be soaked. All right.
So, every short I'm not going to give
any room considering everything counter
trend until we leave this huge volume
area. Here
come the 70s like we just talked about.
So they've read added 83 now. So I want
83 which is Vpo now and IB above that.
I'm not interested in this short side.
But if we sell that,
here's the test of it reaction
that buyer there is caught so far.
Big level. Big level.
Nice. Good reaction. It's what we want
to see. There we go. Bang. Just called
it. Literally gave you to the tick.
To the tick. I just gave you that cell.
So filling some of these imbalances.
Let's see if we can get 67s. Now,
if we're going to hold this dip, I'm not
interested in holding any longer into
this gray box. So, you can see this cell
right here. I just gave you this exact
cell. This is your cover point.1, cover
point two. If we leave this, if we leave
this, we will get a beautiful drive
down. And I will add heavier if we leave
that.
Did I remove VWAP from my charts? No.
There's your New York view. There's
24-hour VW. They're there. They are
there.
But in these 70s, we just talked about
these 70s.
Sellers are in control
as in in the last 5 10 minutes. As long
as we stay under 83. Here we go. We're
filling some of these imbalances in.
Watching Vicks. See if it's trying to
find a bid
which would help us. Here we go. Maybe
we lows if we get lucky.
Maybe we sweep these lows if we get
lucky and get down to that New York
open.
Yes, still above its IP. Still got
relative strength over there.
There we go. There we go. Lovely.
Lovely. All right, moving stock down
now. Protecting this even more. And
let's see if we can get under this shelf
now. Can we get under the New York open?
So, covering more into that little
pocket. This top of this gray box here.
Should have probably extended it. See
this little node here hovering some in
front of that. I want to see if we stay
heavy. Now, as I said, it's counter
trend, smaller size. You lock in as we
go.
Sellers got caught at that low on that
last candle for sure. They they came in
on the breakout. I still think it's got
a chance to move lower, especially if ES
starts breaking down under IV. That's
what I'd be watching at now.
If ES lets go of IB then u we get a
really nice move continuation move.
You actually want this to pop and fail
here so I can get more size on or not
and we just manage this.
Okay, coming down right into that green
box to please cover some point of
control here. I actually have PC up at
that last level, the 83 is where I
shorted. I actually have it up here. So,
you know, we're playing for 20 points
here. It's all we've got. But there we
go. and and we're looking to see if we
can break down under this. That's where
the fun and games will start if we can
break down under this.
Yeah. How we doing for likes? We got two
minutes left. I want to do these
giveaways. I'm just going to manage this
trade.
How are we doing for likes?
Let's get these likes up, guys. We need
at least at least 400 likes. Come on.
640 of you here. It's going to cost you
absolutely nothing. Smash that like
button for me so we can do some
giveaways.
By the way, the market by the way
sometimes the market moves. How useful
is it to keep an eye on the last two
highs and lows on the 15-minute? I mean,
it's useful if you're trading off that.
And I don't know what time frame you're
trading off, but I mean, it can show you
minor swing points, but
I wouldn't say it's like one time frame
is better than another. I use hourly
personally. What I'm always looking at
is hourly hourly runs for expectations.
We're coming into this thick area now,
guys, this gray box.
So, trim some, please, if you haven't
already.
and let's see if we can break below.
We're looking to see if ES wants to join
the party underneath initial balance
high and that will really help us if we
get that. I'm not ruling out a move back
to 600 which would be mega. Then it
would be an 80 plus point trade and
ideally I can get some more size on if
we do that. But I've trimmed into this
node. So I'm short from the 83s.
And here's the bid off this gray box off
the node. So maybe they re revisit back
to 80s. I'm not going to let it come
back above that
into this little low volume node. We can
have one little push above into sort of
73 74. Be interested if they react
there.
Just in front of it. Yes, still finding
a bid in front of IB high. I will do
this giveaway, folks. I promise. I'm
just trying to manage this trade. Once
I'm out of this, I'll uh we'll do the
giveaway just in case I get really nice
move here.
Little low volume node into around 73.
I'm watching just see if they can drive
up and react. Yeah, I know. I know. I
know. We're into lunch.
I'm managing the position.
Thank you. Thank you, bud. I appreciate
it.
Don't want them to rebid this here. It's
good follow through. Nice. I need a new
low now. Come and clean out this guy at
50s.
They're bidding 55s. There's a buyer
coming in here. He keeps stepping on the
tape.
Yeah, he's stepping on the tape here. H,
I might be done with it.
All right, I'm going to be done with it
just so I can do the giveaway. There we
go. Just close. Hello. Close me out,
please. There we go. All right, let's do
this giveaway for you guys.
So, you see gray box to gray box again,
eh? Surprise, surprise. [sighs] If you
get follow through, I think it'll be
really nice.
Hope I haven't cut that early. Anyway,
right, get this set up for you guys.
Okay. Apex giveaway code FCT. Type it
once in chat. Don't type it more than
once or you'll get pulled out. All
right. It will automatically pull you
out. Just type it once in chat.
I'll give you guys a couple minutes to
do that.
>> [sighs]
>> All right, 30 more seconds, folks.
All right, let's pull this
MSTU. Do you hear MSTU?
MST EU.
Let me know you're here in chat.
There's your breakdown of new low. Look,
we rejected gray box to gray box
rejected. That was really good.
Please pay yourself. Please, please,
please, please, please pay yourself.
Okay, congratulations, mate. All right,
all I want you to do is email me
info@flowzonerader.com
and send me a screenshot
um
mst tu. So, I'm just making a note of
you. Send me a screenshot of you logged
into your YouTube and I will sort you
out with a free Apex account. Any size
you want, right? Any size you want.
Um, that's me done for the day, folks.
I'm going to take some rest here. Um,
congratulations everyone. Some nice
trades. Uh, I think we did the best we
could with this market. Those of you who
bought the uh dips and had the patience
to hold through for this sort of cup and
handle or W, whatever you want to call
it, W or cup and handle, right, into
this level. This was the level we had
all morning that we were looking for,
right? It was the exact level we talked
about pre-market. It was the level we
talked about in Discord. You've got your
move. Your low hanging fruit's gone.
You're in a rotation. Don't be expecting
too much, right? The volume still seems
somewhat
slow. All right. Somewhat weaker, right?
It will start to pick up. I promise you.
Wednesday, Thursday, Friday, we have
bigger catalysts. Bigger catalysts. Um,
and we'll um
he didn't say here before he won. Um
because it came up on my screen.
And I'll uh I'll see you guys tomorrow
morning. All right. We'll do same again
tomorrow. Uh those in Discord, I'll pop
in this afternoon. Please trade safe,
folks. Don't don't be forcing your way
in an like aggressively the wrong side
of a rotational market. It is a see
money take money day, right? Just
respect the levels in front of you. You
can see it is respecting PC is then
respecting the shelf. It's respecting
this shelf. This shelf is probably going
to respect these and these. So you have
to lock in profits. Do not have these
huge expectations of a 400 point move or
whatever you've been used to from last
year. Just right now the conditions are
tightening. So lock in those money and
uh go and enjoy your time with your
family. All right guys, peace and love.
Prayers to all of you. Take care.