Morning all.
Morning. Morning. How's it going? Hope
you're all doing well.
Welcome back. Last day of the year. Last
day of the year. We've had some movement
overnight finally, but uh it might ruin
the setup today, but we're going to
we're going to find out either way. Have
a bit of fun together. do some giveaways
and just end this year out strong. Okay,
so what have we seen on the daily? We've
been talking about it. We've been
trading inside. We were trading inside
the previous week's range. Here's your
Monday, Tuesday. Yesterday, the inside
bar we talked about overnight, we gapped
down. All right, we came and filled into
the Friday close. All right, so creating
efficiency in here, closing Friday, this
gray box you would have seen, it's been
here the whole time into this low volume
node which we've repriced. We have found
a bid off there. All right. On the uh
job numbers, if you want to believe
them, I would say that is about the most
obvious cooking of the books I've ever
seen. But hey, they are what they are
and uh this is what they do. So,
apparently they're revised and they're
really good. They're better than
expected. [\h__\h] But anyway, they
revised them perfectly at the perfect
time to buy that dip.
And uh now we uh can come back and look
at the rotation back above us. So, we're
looking at the same area. So right now
what it looks like at the moment is a
look below and fail as we come back into
the previous week range, the previous
day range, and the range on the on the
current week. All right, as we come back
inside that, if we go down to the
hourlys, we're going to see a little bit
more of an idea of what's going on. All
right, so what I'm actually just going
to do here
is
just do a fixed range from Sunday's open
All right. So, that's the current weekly
range. This blue box, if anyone was
trading premarket, this blue box is what
I gave you uh in the weekly newsletter
and all week. And we talked about this
node here. Someone asked, do I look at
volume outside of value? And I said yes.
And that's why. All right. So, once we
close a gap and came into that node,
it's clearly found a bid. It's been a
very aggressive bid off that jobs number
and we've gone straight back where
straight back into current week and
previous week and previous days value.
All right. So if we think about this
previous week's value is here. Previous
days value is
here.
Current week's value is here. All right.
And you have to ask yourself are we
finding acceptance below at the moment?
The answer is absolutely clearly no. We
could not get outside of previous week's
value. It had an attempt to leg down
here and it instantly got reclaimed. So
what does that mean? Currently
everything outside previous week is not
being accepted. We're not accepting
lower prices. So what what are the
possibilities this morning? We can go
into more of a rotation. Absolutely. Um
we can potentially fail this uh point of
control, right? Two times point of
control, which is where we're failing at
the moment. But I'd be very careful
about think being too slanted into being
bearish. That's a decent reaction. So
what would I be thinking? Well, can we
hold
uh previous day or previous or current
week value? All right, so do bulls come
in and sort of defend let's call it
680s. Right, that's the first level. Do
bulls defend 680s? That's neat here.
Sorry about that, Tim. All right, if
they defend 680s, what are we looking
at? We're looking at this same rotation.
All right, if bulls defend 680s, right,
that' be a higher low. We're looking at
the same rotation back up to 740s and
then it's the same play as yesterday. Do
we find acceptance through 740s? All
right, and can we get do they do
something like this? All right, all day
or do we get something like this and
come and try and get to the other side
of the weekly value considering we've
just done a look below and fail. Are we
now going to come to the other side of
the week? That would be the first thing
I'd be looking at. If bulls do a deeper
drive this morning, right? If bears
defend point of control, current week,
previous day, which is where we're
currently finding a sell around these
sort of 17s,
seven in the teens, 720. All right. And
if they fail outside of current week and
previous day value, then we'll be
looking at this pivot here. All right,
previous week value area high. So, I'd
be watching 680s to see if it's
defended, 630s to see if it's defended.
If that isn't defended, then I'm going
to assume we're starting to uh
potentially drift. All right, because
this is overnight volume. We're probably
going to drift down into here, 518s, and
possibly all the way down into this old
naked weekly point of control. Right, we
have not tested that since we broke away
from it. This is the area I've been
really waiting for price to come back
to. So, we have to be flexible. All
right, we have to be flexible because
we're trading inside a previous week,
inside a current week. We found a bid
without acceptance and we're back to
value on those previous week, current
week, previous day. All right, so we
need to be flexible here today. Do not
be too rigid, but I would say
possibility or a dip opportunity here
and here would be the first things I'd
consider. right? Unless unless we push
and fail right at the open and then you
need to see do they just slap us back
all the way back down. But be flexible
today. Remember it's very light volume.
Last trading day of the week uh of the
week. Last trading day of the year,
right? Very light volume. If we just
move up into a fivem minute. Do I need
to make this bigger for you guys? There
we go. We move up to a fivem minute. You
can see how we've had that nice curl off
the bottom. So Asia sideways, London
expansion, gap been filled, gone back
the other side, reclaimed 21, reclaimed
200 into point of control. And for me,
momentum at the moment is with the
bulls. It's just a question of if and
where they step in. If they don't step
in, they don't step in. That's as simple
as that.
Okay, high time uh lower time frame
even. God, get your words out today,
Alex. And let's have a look to see if we
can see
any divergences or anything going on in
the ES. Let's have a little look see
here.
Same kind of setup here on ES. All
right, we talked about this earlier in
the week. Right, taking out this pivot.
It's got another high to aim for over
here.
There's your pullback. If they're going
to hold this and accelerate, they can
look for that all-time high move. This
is probably a nice 30. Yeah, right into
the sort of bull zone scenario for a
pullback to hold. So, it all depends.
Are they able to get going or are they
going to get caught in this same
consolidation here? All right. So, do
they fail this and do this? Do they keep
squeezing or do bears just say no, no,
no, no, no. You're not coming back into
this old balance which we created. If we
look at the spiders,
right, you will know I've talked about
it. They've had uh
new highs created a complete opposite to
ES. All right, this has not created a
new high up here. All right, so we have
divergence in the spy.
Yeah, exactly the same scenario.
Nothing's changed there. Finding a pivot
off this little stop start we talked
about. All right, bid off there. Might
get stuck here. Might rotate more. Might
come down. try and rebid if they start
losing this. This is where bears can
really actually take control.
So, nothing too much to look at. Q's
exactly the same. All right, little
undercut here.
Found a bid back to this chop zone. All
right, this is the zone I really don't
want to trade in if I can avoid it. I
don't really want to start a new
position there. So, I'm open to dips,
open to push and holds, open to push and
fails, and open to re offers under here.
I don't really if I can avoid it, I
don't really want to trade into this
zone ideally in an ideal scenario. Let's
have a quick look at the VIX. All right,
still the same thing we've talked about.
You can see
this is still happening here, folks. All
right, still can't get through this
pivot, but we are producing higher
highs, higher lows in this pivot. It
must get through here to find
acceptance. Otherwise, this can be a
huge build out of liquidity
for a flush moment if the market does
want to break higher. And
let's have a look at the MAC. How we
doing for time? Yeah, we got to get
through this.
All right, Apple back inside yesterday's
range. Look below and fail. Closed the
gap. Slight gap down, but inside the
range. Amazon
pretty much flat inside yesterday. Oh, I
I mean inside if you consider the after
hours, but most of the range was created
here. So maybe a slight gap up
possibility to go there on Amazon. It's
possible.
Google inside yesterday's range. Didn't
look below and fail, opening flat.
That's not a very good looking chart
right now. Meta, remember that had
strength off a catalyst yesterday.
Currently opening inside of yesterday's
range. Nothing really to see there.
Microsoft, same story. Opening inside of
yesterday's range. Uh, very slight gap
up. Nvidia, this is the one. All right,
this is the one. Nvidia finding a bid
here this morning. Trying to fill this
gap. All right. It's got to get back
above the 190s to really go. So any
pullback on Nvidia which holds I'd say
88. Yeah. Anywhere around the 88s, if
it's able to hold that drive up to 190
and start accelerating through that,
then um it's back on the table for
bulls.
Tesla um this continues to just drip
down after losing this ledge here that
we talked about. All right, just in a
strong channel down right now.
What is that print? That's not print, is
it?
No. Uh underneath New York uh view up at
the moment from yesterday. Question is,
can it start to offer a bid and clean
out some of these stops? All right. And
maybe return back in here and then make
a decision if it can get back inside or
not. But it's seen weakness there all
for the last week or so. Dripping lower
as equally weighted ETF.
slight gap up. Okay, so as an ETF, we're
equally weighted, slight gap up. We've
got targets to aim for. Let's have a
look at some of the border names. Oracle
inside yesterday's range. AMD has found
a little bit of a bid with Nvidia.
APGO, same story. Little bit of a bid
with Nvidia. Let's have a look at some
of these
big gamma explosion names. IN doesn't
look very good. Inq
going on there. MBTS RGTI
that looks
that looks messy actually. 30-year.
Sorry folks, just go through everything
very quickly. That been sold back down
in
still not through that key level.
Good for bulls.
Mood finding a bit of a bid these bonds
this morning. Okay.
All right. Let's see how we go.
Let's just see how we go here. Oh.
All right. No need to get aggressive.
Very, very simple. We either hold the
sort of 80ish kind of level this morning
and rotate back up towards these. All
right. So, we're either going to hold
this this morning.
Come on, brush. We're either going to
hold this around here for this move here
or we're going to come back down in here
and see if they hold this. So maybe
there's a flush opportunity down to here
and see if they hold that. If they fail
to hold all of those and bears will take
control of this market, right?
Something in my mouth here.
All right, morning everyone. Morning.
Morning. Morning. Morning. Sorry I
haven't had a chance to uh get through
your names for a little while now, but
good morning. Welcome.
What indicator do I use to mark previous
value area high, low, and point control?
Um, I mark them out with horizontal
lines myself. No indicator.
No indicator. Okay,
where we at? Nothing else coming here.
No other news expected.
Market opening in about 70 80 seconds
here.
Zoomed in on some of these. We will do
some giveaways today. We'll give away
some Apex accounts and some courses
again.
Yeah, 80s is a big level whether they're
going to hold this or not. If they don't
hold 80s, there is a flush scenario down
to 37s. All right. So current this area
here is current value on the week right
created from Sunday open to now right so
can they open this kind hold this kind
of area at the open if not this flush
down to here is possible right so
we just have to see here opening in a
very interesting area I'm not against
buying dips if uh if I see them want to
participate I'm also not against uh
waiting to see if that previous week
value area low is tagged back into looks
like a decent level to buy off if we are
going to see some bullish momentum on
the last day of the year. Happy new year
everyone.
Getting a bit wonky. 5 seconds left
here, folks.
Nice and patient. No need to force
anything. Here we come. bids coming back
in here straight away off this open
around this previous day close. Let's
see if they flush them out to previous
week value area low
should be down here. And let's see if
they bid off that or not or if they just
trap the shorts early which is at the
moment what they look like they're
doing. We just swept previous day low
there in the New York session.
Some shorts definitely got caught down
there underneath the 70s. We're watching
this already to see if we drive up and
reclaim previous day value area low
here.
Is there anyone interested in
participating this early or we going to
come back down for those value area lows
weeklys?
There's definitely a few shorts called
down here sub 70.
We know this 80 is a big level. And if
we if we fail 80s, we know this is a big
level. They're starting to try and bid
this now.
Sell it up here into 95s. Are they going
to reclaim previous day value area low
is the big question
or bullish momentum upside. All right,
they've held 80 so far. Here we go.
Here's the attempt to get back towards
it. There's still a seller there at 90
and 95. Looks still very thin here at
the moment.
Yes, very low volume. It will be low
volume today. It's been low volume all
week. It will continue to be low volume
until we get back to normal
after the holiday season.
Morning low hanging fruit. Great name.
Great name. Love that name.
They're still not letting these uh
shorts out underneath previous day low.
Here's the acceleration. All right, I'm
getting interested in this now. What we
going to do at previous day value area
low? This is what becomes key. What are
we going to do up here? They're going to
resell it or we going to find acceptance
back inside? Are we reselling this or we
going to find acceptance back inside?
Just waiting to see if there's a trigger
up there.
Give you a little readout on the mag.
Tesla third of a percent down. Nvidia
150%
up. Microsoft 0.09% up. Meta third of a
percent down. Google third of a percent
down. Amazon 0.17% down. Apple 0.10% up.
As equally weighted mag, we are 0.09%
down on the session.
So, a little bit of a mixed bag going on
here. If they fail this, like we talked
about, if they sell this, it is possible
to come all the way back down to
previous week value area low.
Sure, these line up there. 36 40s there
or thereabouts.
Most of the magnell red outside of Tesla
feels like they want to come down into
this. So, I'm trying to be patient. Like
the opportunities really are are we
going to come down into this and bid off
or lose it, right? So, probably need to
be patient for this. I think they had a
chance here to rebid over and they
failed. So, shorts took control here.
probably want to complete a rotation
into this and then uh we can sort of see
what's what once we get down into there
and reassess what's what
50s what we looking at 40s and 30s I
think kind of area
globe here previous day low in VWAP on
the ES as well same for the spiders
this.
Feels like they should just complete
this rotation down now.
Just being patient here.
Yes, it's coming down. It's that same
level that globe XM what we talked about
previous day low on a spiders all sort
of around this level.
So from here to sort of 30s
down into here ideally
and see if they auction off this and if
not if they lose this then we come down
into this.
They're finding a little bit of a bid
early here in front of it all. It's a
bit front running by the looks of it.
If they accelerate through here there's
not much until we get up to 700. There's
a VPO here from the current day at 75
which we just came into. And if they get
through that then uh it's possible.
Sorry. Croaky throat. We go up to 700
which is
not ideal the way they've set it up.
I'll be honest with you. They're front
running at all. We need it to come a
little bit lower first on on absolutely
everywhere that I'm looking right now.
Control on the session right here. Get
some volume on early. That is annoying
that they've come into no man's land
there. But there we go.
Thin volume. We kind of expect nonsense.
There we go.
This is also slightly incorrect by the
looks of it. Okay, back up to like I
said, we can come all the way up to 700s
if it wants. This is value area high on
the session here is 80s. We're starting
to find a little bit the bid here. The
bid is a little bit early in my opinion.
It's a bit early in front of this. All
right. So, I want to wait for this or
acceptance above this. I don't want to
get caught in between the two. Not much
to do if you get caught in between the
two.
How do I have conviction whether the
market will stay in a value area on
certain days at open or will trade out
of it like you mentioned yesterday? Um,
it's really based on where that volume
is and where we're opening up. Are we
opening up in value, out of value? How
are we shaping up? Who's trapped during
that session? How do we create volume
during that session? All right, here we
come back down into these key levels.
Previous week below. So, the question
now is, do we find a bid here? It's the
big question now. Do we find a bid here?
If we don't find a bid here, we will
come all the way back down for these
lows. Okay, so they need to find a bid
here. the bulls if they have uh a chance
in holding us up today for that drive
and acceptance back into here at the
moment. And you would say bears are in
control because we've rejected the old
point of control up here.
We've rejected previous day value.
We've traded under previous week value.
All right. And if we don't do one of
these, then bears will look to complete
the rotation all the way down. And you
can't rule out this move down here
really. But let's just see.
Still very early in the day.
It's good job from bears so far. Very
good job from bears.
Having a good spike here as well. So
there is some alignment. Just going to
let this just settle down though. Very
very very low volume.
Guessing no Santa rally. I mean, we did
hit alltime highs on the spiders a
couple days ago. I don't understand when
uh it's past Christmas, you've hit
alltime highs. It's not like we're
trading at lows, is it? We're trading in
on the cues at a midpoint of a range and
the breadth has been actually a little
bit better if we want to be unbiased um
outside of tech.
I wouldn't be too um
I wouldn't come down on the market too
hard. just like try and put it that way.
Right, they're finding a bit of a beard
in front of previous week low here. We
had lots of short selling coming in here
at 24 and 3435.
So VWAP and value area low and previous
week value area low still probably the
triggers to see if they get relief up or
if they resell it. So this kind of area
now that we're in, do they start to
drive through and up or are they going
to resell this VWAP resell value area
low? These are the sort of 35s I just
talked about where sellers came in with
strength.
Or are we going to do this sort of look
below previous week and start to find a
bid, which is what they're attempting to
do at the moment? Not convinced yet, but
h let's see. We just tapped right back
into this same level as previous week
value low.
It's very thin on the book. I'm looking
at like sizes of sixes and fives on the
book right now.
Would not take much to move this market.
The big player comes in or move quick
either direction. So, I want to be uh
positioned the wrong side of this.
Definitely left some sellers under 25 so
far.
Still early. They're starting to retest
this player at 25 and see it on the
order book. They sort of started coming
in at 35, 30, 25, 23s, 20s, and then
14s. So, it just depends if they let
these sellers out or not. They're trying
to get back down to let them out at the
moment. Point control now flipped lower.
They're letting them out now. We're
starting to drive lower. And if we get
acceptance under here for this previous
week low, there is a deeper drive into
GlobeEx available. So right now bears
are defending right this area here. We
talked about if they defend this we can
come down into this. If we get this move
here this will probably offer a squeeze
up because we have low volume here. So
still just waiting here. Not really too
interested at the moment. Nothing
perking my interest yet.
If we reclaim I'll be interested. If uh
we flush really deep and I see it being
more aggressive I'm interested as well.
Mag has starting to bleed a little bit
more. I'll be honest with you. Tesla
about to go green to red. Microsoft
0.27% down. Meta over half a percent
down. Google 0.27% down. Amazon 0.3 or
0.29% down. And Apple 0.19% down. So the
only one that's clinging on there really
is Nvidia. The rest of the market
doesn't look particularly good. But we
are into a level of interest. This is
previous week low down here. This is
previous week value area low down here.
Very simple. We either reclaim this and
start squeezing or they're going to
flush versus this and come down to these
sort of GlobeEx lows.
And we do have that old naked point of
control. I've got to remember where that
is on a weekly. Where is him? Where is
he?
So next ups would be 520s and 330s. So
we need to remember those 520s and 330s
if they remain heavy. Big big if. We're
building out nice volume here right now,
which can be used as a shelf either
side.
Pretty slow, isn't it?
Pretty slow for a morning open. We've
we've gone stuck in a 10point range for
the last one, two, three, four, five,
six minutes. Wonder what we expected.
I want to say these bears look a little
bit stuck, but balls are not coming in
and squeezing and the volume is just
non-existent. It's just absolutely
non-existent. So, I don't really want to
think about
trap right now off no volume.
And what size was that? That just got
absorbed. 47 lot. Oh, so small. So,
CVD is still heavy.
They're trying to resell this. Here we
go.
There is some absorption taking place
here. I just don't trust it's so thin on
volume. It's unreal. There definitely
some absorption here into 17s. I think
they should probably flush all these lot
out. They've been here so long. PS
making a new low. I think INQ is going
to join it.
Might have literally gone to sleep here.
Market is absolutely asleep.
You understand? And we're 15 minutes in
and we're struggling to move 10 points.
This is uh
wild in not a good way. Wild in a very
slow day.
All right, new lows. ES.
We still haven't taken out that previous
week low. This green line right here.
building up lots of volume here. It's
possible they drift all the way down
into here and take all this out if they
really want to
that node there into 570s and then uh
old value 525. But I uh I'm really
uninterested in how this is moving right
now. This is uh to see this in the
opening 15 minutes
to see 20 points like that. O I don't
know mate.
It's not filling me with the confidence
to do anything today. Tell you that much
there. Finally breaking lower. Well
done, Bears. That took you uh about 10
minutes to do a very obvious simple
move. Jeez Louise.
Okay, so flushing coming now. Finally,
they've using this volume for the
breakaway. This is the next level. This
blue box and that's GloEx low from
overnight. We get through there. There's
an old fact I'm going to put these on
the screen so we can remember these. We
have one little one here
and we do a white dotted line for naked
PC. Maybe we remember it.
Maybe we do as red.
Make it P.
There we go. So all the way down that
print. Yeah. Good.
Okay.
Drifting lower. All of the mag now red
other than Nvidia. This is so slow
though. This is uh really slow.
These breakaways are uh a whopping 10 to
20 points. I mean it's uh but we are
starting to leave volume. This is the
next level. All right. This was the uh
volume created back in 15th of December.
We did uh flush through this overnight
and then refound a bid. So it just
depends. Are they going to hold this
look straight up straight back down? We
talk about that all the time
and I'd say bears are in control of this
current session all the time. somewhere
under this right here.
No, don't want to change it.
There we go.
And this is their target. This one and
this one. And if they get really weak,
then we can think about all the way down
to there. Like I said, this uh this was
a spoof move. All right. This is uh if
you believe that newsprint, you're
[\h__\h] not reading any bit of
information ever. Um, absolute bollocks.
Can't believe they get away with doing
that. But they do. They do get away with
it.
Readjusting the numbers in a positive
favor when we come into a very key level
of the stock market. Who who' have
guessed?
Am I not trading today? I mean, if I see
something I really really want, I will
trade. But we're very you got to
understand, we're very low on volume
right now.
So, uh, I would have to see something
that's really screaming out to me to,
uh, take a trade.
Unfortunately, the way they've set up,
like this rebid this morning was really
good.
You could argue there was a short here
off the morning drive, but watching like
such low volume.
Could have, would have, should have.
Maybe there was a an opportunity up
there for the short. I'm more interested
as we're starting to build out levels
now of like how we act.
You know, if we uh reclaim value and
start very simple, if bulls reclaim this
and this, we go straight back upside.
So, I'm open to that. If bears defend
this and I think we have auction left to
finish, I'm open to that. You're
starting to see aggressive bulls come in
in front of this level. for his previous
week. So, this is perking my interest.
Back to previous week low.
Do they sustain a bid through here or
does this just have the door shut on
their face and do we actually want to
trade lower? There's still low hanging
fruit lower right now. I will say that
much.
There is still low hanging fruit lower
right now. There's still this blue box
and Globeex
and you can see previous week low key
level there with the volume above. So
bear's currently defending that.
I'm just not in a hurry here, guys. Like
last day of the year.
Not in a hurry here.
So still unfinished business lower.
Do I think there's a crash incoming and
in another market? Can you bet on the
Chinese market, for example? I wouldn't
be betting on the Chinese market if you
feel that the US market's going to go
get derailed. You're better off to take
short positions on the US market or but
you know, it's probably a bit late, but
there's a reason there's long exposure
right now into gold and metals.
Okay, back to previous week low again.
They're starting to try and reclaim.
They're going back to this gray box.
These are your triggers up here. Did
they reshort this or is this a look
below and fail and we go mega mega
squeeze? I'm not ruling anything out
because the volume's so light here. All
right,
so bears came in at 17s to 25. So that's
the the level bears will want to defend.
All right, 517s to 525 is where they
came in heavy. That is where they will
want to defend. If they don't defend
that, we can see a squeeze.
So here's the test of 17s. We just
talked about it
literally to the tick.
Yeah, exactly. CB, it wouldn't take a
lot to push it around, right? You get
one big player come in and uh this
market changes direction very quickly or
expands very very quickly. That's
exactly what I'm getting at.
And you wouldn't want to be the wrong
side of that because it will skip if
that is what's going to happen. We're
starting to see some bids turn up on
Tesla and Goo here now folks. We still
have low low hanging fruit below for
sure, but we're starting to see some
bids. I'd say shorts under 93 a quart.
All right, so if bids start to hold
above 93, the rotation is from there up
to sort of the 17s, the 25s we talked
about. All right, a big if button may
right now while they start to make a
decision.
Do I think after hours are going to be
important after the 1st of January? Uh
what? Because of the silver legislation
coming in in China, you mean?
I don't know. There's been so much talk
about it. I would say it's probably
priced in, you know. But unless unless
there's a discrepancy in what people
think is going to happen and what
actually happens. All right. They're
starting to leave these shorts
underneath 90s core, right underneath
here.
We have some shorts caught. We just
talked about it underneath 90s right
under here. Shorts are caught. If we
start to see this expansion now through
these levels, you're going to see the
squeeze. So, I'm starting to get
interested in this. We talked about this
17s, didn't we? 17s to 25. If we start
getting through that, we're going to see
expansion back upside and squeeze them
all out. Here we go. All right. Very
interested now. So, there's the 25. 17s
to 25s. Here comes VWAP. Looking for
bullish momentum to continue this higher
for a squeeze now.
And if especially if we get back through
previous week value area low. It's a
shame we left low hanging fruit here.
But if we do this I'm very interested.
So some of you asking was it going to
trade? I just need to wait to see the
setup.
We created a new point of control up
here at 25 shorts. 17 is still the level
for shorts. All right, so they will want
it back below 17s right now. Balls will
want to get back over 640 to really take
control.
Coming back into these 17s. Let's see if
bulls defend this and leave these shorts
cooked. If we go back lower into this
gray box, letting this rotate for a
moment in this gray box before I make a
decision here.
17's big level here. I can see on the
book. keep trading into it there or
thereabouts. If I say like an exact
level, you know, you got to give it a
few few points either side, folks.
See, that didn't take much to reflush
that. That was one player and it wasn't
much size. This is the worry. What did
he come in with? 37 lot and then he ran
a 100 uh 100 lot stops there. So, it's
not taking a lot to move this around
right now. That's this is the concern I
have.
still underneath VWAP, but we're trying
to reclaim previous weak lows here. ES
is also stuck at VWAP.
This is possible. We're not there yet to
do it, but it's possible. They can also
reject this gray box and complete
rotation to here. So,
I don't think I want to be bearish down
here at the moment. just because how
we're building out. But uh see
and they reclaim and see these 17s big
level
big level. Here comes point of control
again. Are we going to start to see
expansion? Can we get through value? Can
we get through VWAP?
They are attempting to do it.
Squeezing coming here. Here's the 25s
now. Can they get back up to 14? take
control.
Rebidding 25s looking good now.
Here's VWAP.
You'd want this if you're bullish to
hold a print between 25 and 17. You
wouldn't want it back below 17 in an
ideal scenario here. We're trading
around this gray area. There is a lift
available here and a squeeze.
Here they go. They're trying. Here we
go, folks. So watching now for trigger
back through 40s to add.
Can we get back through 40s for the ad
point of control now at 24 on the day?
Be careful. Won't take much to move
this. Trading small size here until we
really start to confirm our ad heavy if
we start to base above 40s.
ES back above VW up just about and then
see if it can close a fivem minutee
candle up there though. Might need a
pull back here on ES be careful.
Very thin, man. Very, very, very thin.
They're rebidding again here at Vpo.
Just be careful if they lose this. We
did leave imbalances. So, the first
imbalance would be down to 12 and the
second imbalance down to 98. actually
right into these VWAPs on the ETFs right
now.
sensitive area say
right visiting these 17s again
this is my over under really
needs to hold this and get aggressive
upside otherwise I'm not interested
don't like that this one big player just
came in
let it rebid if it wants
this is the problem It's so thin. It is
not taking much. This is one player just
feathered in and suddenly we just washed
20 points off very light volume. Like if
we're going to look at this, these going
to be tiny. 26 25 7 28 44 8 42. So into
these buy side imbalances.
This guy wants to get a new low. He's
starting to be more aggressive.
What's your game, son?
Anyone
bidding down?
Okay. You were a buyer at 80 then 65.
Where are you now?
75. Okay.
Sorry, mumbling to myself. I was just
looking at who's been bidding lower and
moving the book around.
Right. They're trying to have another
attempt here again. 7 17 It's the same
level, folks. Right. 17 to 25 is where
sellers are willing to be aggressive in
this gray box. If we lose this gray box,
all right, we haven't had the I
feathered in long from sort of here.
Draw from here to here just in case we
got this to add heavy. We didn't. So,
cut it. We're losing this now. We might
well revisit this, this, and this. All
right. If they lose this, we might well
revisit it. Creating fairly standard
D-shape down here after leaving value.
And we have not been able to reclaim
previous week value. So technically,
this is bearish right now.
Just what I'm seeing on the tape isn't
really matching the the levels. That's a
little bit weird, but whatever.
Expected.
Silver. Yeah. Well, silver's very
volatile right now. I'm uh I like that
trade when everyone forgets about it and
it's less crowded because I want to take
swing positions on it.
New hour coming up here, folks, as well.
New 4 hour, new hour.
This last hour doesn't look very good,
does it?
Take care, Adam. You like the short?
Yeah, I mean the short is possible
versus this gray box. It's just what I'm
seeing on the tape doesn't feel very
good for that move. Technically, it
looks it looks like there's a possible
setup there to drive lower. I would
agree with you. We've we've had an
attempt, but what I'm seeing on the on
the tape, it just doesn't look very
good. The only time they're
participating is in these 17s and 25s.
They're trying to find a bid here,
honestly.
Even up here on the take, you can see I
said 17s and 25s. All the re all the
passive reoffers are up at 25 and 30s.
No one's like aggressively stepping on.
Um,
no one's aggressively stepping on either
side right now. There's like one guy who
seems to step on for like 10 20 points.
Like he's trying again now. Maybe
they're trying to get these fields down
to 90s.
Again, absorbed off nothing. Like what
were you absorbed off? [\h__\h] tul lot.
What's in here? A nine lot. Man, it's so
guys, it's really thin. I don't know if
I'm going to uh anticipate unless we
start breaking like big key levels. It's
very very very thin.
It feels like a uh it feels like a
glowback session.
Watching the book. That's what it feels
like.
They call.
Yeah. Under 90s is where they've been
stuck, these bears so far this morning.
Yeah. I don't blame you. I don't blame
you. Uh Ter Z can I don't blame you. I
think half size is a good way to be.
Look, you they can't get under these
90s. So these guys that were stuck here,
right? They can't get under here and
they're not willing to be aggressive
unless they're up here, the sellers. So
sellers are being aggressive in here and
not in here at the moment. And these
guys here are stuck. So we're just like
building out. And this is not very big,
folks.
That's your rotation right now on low
volume.
So maybe we come back up and test these
17s again. I mean,
yeah, there's not there's not much here
until then. I mean, you've got this
previous week low that we're rejecting
off, but the all the volume is up above.
All the volume is up here. No one's
willing to transact down here right now.
testing previous week low as well. What
copy do I use? Affordable indicators.
Affordable indicators.
I think they want to go and test the if
they get through previous week low, they
want to go and test these 17s again.
It's it's a big if if they can get
through this level we're at now, these
sort of 609 610s.
Then they just want to go and drive up
and test 17 to 25 again and see if those
sellers are still there. There is a
seller come back on the book here
actually trying to walk down for the
first time today. He's moved to 610.
anchored volume profile. Volume on the
right. Anchored volume profile.
There he is at 610. Let's see if he
actually fills. They lift through it.
They're going to go 17s. They made it to
15s. We just talked about this. They're
going to want to go. What is this thin
book? Did anyone see that? That filled
through and stayed there.
Well, that ain't right.
Shouldn't be filling and leaving it.
That's bizarre. That order at 610.
Weird. Very weird.
We like skipped him
and left it on the tape so it didn't
like it didn't fill all of him. Not seen
that. That is a That is an odd one. Back
to him again. Now the 610s.
They're going to try and lift this.
Honestly, look how thin the book's gone
above. There's nothing here until 27s
now. It's that thin.
So back to 10. 17s to 25s is where
shorts are willing to play at the
moment. Nowhere else by the looks of it.
Back to this gray box. And honestly, if
this is a higher low and we lift through
this, I'm still willing to look at this
rotation above 40s.
If you look at bookmat with me, you'll
see what I'm talking about here. Like
it's just there's nothing going on,
folks.
the size of these players like eight
lot, nine lots and then we've got a wall
which is a whopping 29 lot I mean and in
between it's very look all these dark
patches is very very thin in
participation
not much either side this is probably
current value on this sessions not not
much either side going on
just a slow day very very slow day which
we did expect obviously we did expect
this.
Do I prefer the trade of eight 50k apex
count or rhythm? Rhythmic trade of eight
definitely trade of eight. Do I think
trading will get heavy again on the
second or there'll be another light day
and everybody will be waiting for the
fifth. Um I don't know. It's probably
going to take a little bit of time to
pick up volume again. Depends how
desperate. Honestly, a lot's going to
depend on tax season. It depends if they
can start. Here we go. So, here's the
move to 17 again we just talked about
and rejection of 17 again so far. And if
they squeeze through 17, we're going to
go 25s. And if we squeeze through 25s,
we're going to go check 40. And it's at
that point where I'll be become vaguely
interested in this market and not
before. You can see this lift to 17
right here. I keep talking about that's
the level that they're willing to trade
at. 17 to 25 is where they're willing to
offer. They're not really interested in
selling low. So, they're not being
aggressive at the lows so far. I'm can
only go by what we've seen so far today.
Things can change. Uh, what were you
saying? Volume. Yes. I don't know. Yeah,
I think a lot would depend on tax
season. I would have expected, to be
honest, any big losses that they had
earlier this year that they'd start to
lift out of them and maybe rotate back
into them cheap, but we're not really
seeing that into the end of the year.
So,
let's have a look at the uh
calendar.
I mean, yeah, fifth fifth is where it
gets in more interesting for sure. Uh
probably the seventh is going to be the
first big move big mover. ADP employment
and then job openings and US factory
orders and that's followed by initial
jobless claims the next day. So seventh
and eighth and ninth are going to be big
days. How much do they cook the books or
do we actually get real stats without
the [\h__\h] Um
you know do they uh miss 80% of CPI out
next time again and pretend like they
didn't include stuff and not talk about
it which what they did last time. Do
they cook the books like they did this
morning?
Who knows? Tell you what, there's buck
all job creation and uh unemployment has
been ticking up every month since
January and all you have to do is do a
little bit of a deep dive beyond the
[\h__\h] that they put out and you'll
see that. So, will crack start to open
in January? Maybe. I' I'd expect in Q1
there's some volatility coming.
Oh, yeah. I'm asleep.
>> I am asleep.
Well, I haven't traded this morning.
You've never seen me make a trade. Are
you the same guy talking [\h__\h]
yesterday?
[\h__\h] moronic.
See you.
What do you want me to trade? You You're
desperate for me to trade like a 10point
range. I've told you I'll be interested
once we get over 40s. Like,
[\h__\h] me, man. Amount of people in here
who is so impatient.
We've had some banger trades this week,
even on low volume together.
Yeah, I know. Well, you got to think you
got people are skirting around YouTubes
and Discords wanting people to hold
their hand.
Is this chart delayed? It will be
whatever the smallest delay is. 4
seconds or 6 seconds. No more than that.
Just stuck here in this Dshape. This is
all we've got here this morning.
Everyone's so desperate. He hasn't made
a trade. What the [\h__\h] have we done?
What do you want me to do in here? You
want me to trade at a PC when we've got
haven't taken low hanging fruit and
haven't found acceptance above and we're
just rotating like
you make that trade mate. You you
[\h__\h] make that trade. Good luck
and come crying back to me in a week. I
lost all my money because I don't know
what to do.
All right. 17 is still the level being
defended by bears.
Still the level being defended by bears
right now. P has shifted down in this
session.
Bears are in control all the time. when
we're defending this sort of 17 to 25,
this sort of gray box. All right, if we
get acceptance above that, I think we
have squeeze potential because we're
very thin in this move down, right? We
were thin up, thin down,
but we have unfinished business down
here and down here. And that's really
based off the higher time frame, not
just based on overnight, right? We have
unfinished business. If we zoom out on
the hourlys,
all right, we have this node here, which
we have pre-market. It might be that
they want to close the weekly opening
gap based on a new god I can't draw a
New York session rather than just in
pre-market
for efficiency reasons. If we get
through that we're watching this old
value area high and we're watching this
naked PC. All right. So if they fail
fade this if we get this expansion move
if we're thinking about
it's kind of awkward how they've done it
but uh yeah we could get a three sigma
move into it is possible.
Double bot no still not broken into
Gloveex. They're trying. There's just no
aggression, guys, on the tape. There's
literally like no aggression on the tape
today.
If we lose 26, can we get to 25412? 26.
If we Yeah. Look, if we lose 26, the
first level is that 550, 560, that node
that we came into uh dating back to 15.
If we lose that, we can trade into 520s.
If we lose 520s,
we will trade into 340s, right? So, yes,
we can. We absolutely can.
Look, we just can't. There's no
aggression down here. Like I keep
talking about, the only time sellers are
willing to come in is 17 to 25. They are
not willing to step on the gas down
here. You have to understand that like
they are only willing to sell up here
right now. There's some selling down
here, but the aggressors, the people
controlling the market, they're only
willing to sell here. We're not seeing
them sell here and walk this market down
with followthrough and push it lower.
Not yet. We're not seeing that. Which is
why I'm very apprehensive about thinking
about a short on low volume at low of
day without seeing them want to just
step on the gas.
When you refer to the tape, can you
explain to what I mean? Quite literally
the tape. Quite literally the tape. Time
and sales order book 11 level two. The
book map is how I like to view it.
Quite literally a tape. It's the
equivalent of like a receipt being
printed nonstop, right?
What's the red cloud indicator? It's the
flow zones. Flow zone pro. Everything
you see on here
comes with the course.
I'm imagining there's also probably a
bit of a put at 685 on spy.
Seems like there's probably a pull there
on spy
cuz we're just pinned above it.
ES
wants to come and clean up, but it
can't.
Just trading the same level back to the
17s probably here. We might get a lift
back up and check them if they're not
going to be aggressive lower.
Point of control now has shifted to
607s.
So, still the same level. You see this
gray box has kind of moved down. To be
honest, we've moved this shelf down into
here. All right. This is where we're
transacting big volume.
They need to make a decision away from
this area.
Tesla's trying to go red to green.
Nvidia 0.64. 64% up. Microsoft third of
down. Meta just under half% down.
Google's gone green 0.10% up. Amazon
0.28% down. Apple 0.10% down. Nothing's
really moving here, folks. Five gamma
exposure names, RGTI, MBTS slightly red
on the day. IQ found a bid that second
day in a row after this catalyst
yesterday. IN%.
It's just spread quiet. Just feels
quiet. Sleepy
day. Yeah, exactly.
Small IB. I mean, yeah, we got a little
bit time left for that IB to be set, but
I mean, I'd say the the problem is not
the IB because the initial balance high
would be right up here, like 100 points
higher. The the problem is we've gone
too in here, right?
We're not expanding this range yet.
I mean, maybe there was a snapshot there
to be had, but I just didn't really want
to trade the open on a low volume day,
but that's the only thing I've seen. The
rejection of PC, the rejection of value,
and that trade back down. And they did
reject it twice here in fairness. But,
uh,
yeah, I'd say bears have the edge in
this market at the moment, lower time
frame, as in in this market today.
It's just are they actually going to
show up and be aggressive?
What is the key component that drives
gold? I mean, it's the same as
everything, right? But it's it's
currently it is the hedge to the dollar
and to what's going on in US. You got to
understand that uh Asia has started
selling here. We're starting to see
aggressive sales now. Finally, some
aggressive cells have stepped into this
market. You've got to see that uh
with the rates going up in Japan, they
have exposure to US, right? And if
people want to unpeg the USD and
minimize exposure into things like the
cues, then they're going to start
selling. So, where is a safe he safe
haven? Safe haven is into gold.
Okay, GlobeEx been cleaned out on ES,
not quite cleaned out on ENQ and we're
trading at 685
on the spy
in control. We're le finally leaving
this area. So, these are the next two
zones.
So, we're into one of them right now.
Globex is down here. This is the
overnight low. This is the uh pivot from
the previous week value area high dating
back to was this the 15th. So let's see.
It is so slow.
What is this indicator? Which one? The
main one on the on the screen is flow
zones. Flow zone pro.
This is just volume
anchored volume to the 930 open.
Okay. Globeex taken on ES. Not taken yet
on the spiders on the uh on the Q's.
Vix is trying to get going. It's just
dancing in range though. Currently
the volume. Yeah, it's it's it's a tool.
It's not even an indicator. Let's just
come over to here, projections, anchored
volume profile, right? And then just
draw that on. All right. There's some
bids shown up in this first blue box
that we've had on our screen.
Right. This is
off that weekly profile.
We did trade under this overnight. This
is the the overnight low, this orange
line.
Bears have come in versus 92s. All
right, that's where they came in. 92s to
83s is where they came in with strength.
So slow. So so slow. All right.
Value area low on this session now 88.
These 90s are key. This is where they
started aggressively selling. Are they
going to remain aggressively selling
these 90s?
At the moment, it looks like yes.
They're trying to protect value area low
on the day.
Some passive buying down here.
Some divergence on CBD starting to show
up. There's definitely a bit of passive
buying down here. I'd rather just they
just get a move on and flush it all out
in a hurry. We can do something. So,
back to the 90s again. Back to value
area low on the session again.
Still unfinished business below for the
Q's but not for the ES.
So they started selling into 92 on that
way down. The next block above that is
at I mean it's not very far. It's at
601, right?
And point of control is at 606. So I'd
say
Yeah,
this node here is where they sold 92 is
right here. Flow zone still downside.
Still unfinished business lower.
How much does London high London Asia
high and low play into your analysis? I
mean, I do care about Here we go. So,
they're going to lift this now
off that blue box. Like I said, we had
passive buyers down there. You could see
it on the CBD. We're going into these
92s to 94s now. And if they lift this,
we're going to go up to the point of
control. And they're just going to keep
rotating and churning until someone gets
aggressive. And we're just not seeing
that at the moment. Uh how much does it
affect my analysis? I mean, it does
affect it, but uh I don't believe we
always need to to sweep all the levels,
but I do care about GlobeEx. I don't
care as much about GloEx as I do New
York because I care about the volume in
New York. But I do care where
participation happened. Like we for
example in in London when we broke down
under that low. All right. What we
actually traded into was the high volume
node back from Monday the 15th of
December and we didn't find acceptance
underneath it. So
this here
right this blue box is a is a high
volume node from 15th of December. You
can see we don't find acceptance
underneath it and we rebid off it. So
this is still an important level for me
right because this is low well this is
low volume. This is what should we call
it [\h__\h] low volume right? So I do
care about the levels and how we act at
them. We know buyers showed up here.
Um, if we get acceptance beneath that,
then this is actually the uh
value area high from that week. These
are all the same levels from the weekly
newsletter, right? Nothing's changed.
Later, can we go over CBD? Yeah, we can
go over CBD.
>> No worries.
595 is a 20-day. Yeah. I mean, that's
that's it, mate. We're just at mean
reversion. Like, if we go to a daily,
we're at mean reversion. All right.
We're starting to bid with these sellers
keep coming in now under 86s and getting
stuck. We're back inside. So, we're
leaving sellers under 86s stuck right
now. Right. Under 86s. Oh my god. They
keep being aggressive under here and
they're getting caught. This is
compression. This level still matters.
Sellers need to defend this level. If
they don't, the squeeze happens. If they
defend it, we can keep moving lower. But
uh I will tell you now from 86 to 83,
it's tiny range, but that's where big
big selling stepped in. And we're not
trading under that yet. The range is so
small, guys. You you have to understand
what I'm looking at here. Like I'm
looking at this pathetic amount here,
right? Like these guys are currently
caught. If we let them out, this is
possible. If we keep them caught, we've
got imbalances up here to come and fill.
But this is like, look, you're talking
about like 10 points. This is why I'm
not overly interested right now.
But if we lift through all of this and
we run all these stops, then you know,
maybe there's a 30 point trade to be
had. All right, here we go. PC like we
talked about.
Remember, ES did sweep Globeex. ES has
taken it. Here comes point of control
and previous week low and do we find
acceptance above this? Now if we find
acceptance above this then we can look
for a move up to 30s.
I would say this is uh very much a see
money take money environment folks. So
let's see if we can uh find acceptance
or bears defend this P here.
If we can get through PC, I think
there's a move up to 30.
We need to get above and base though.
PC back tests. They've left imbalances
all the way down to 93 cuz we're very
thin.
There we go.
That's the problem with it being so
thin.
down to 93s. We probably go here for a
back test into these imbalances. So, one
imbalance is uh 600 to 97. The second
imbalance is 95 to 93s.
So, do they fill those? And if they
flash back through those back to value
area low, they will need to bid off you.
Bulls will need to defend 86 if they're
going to rotate. Even if you're a
rotational bull, even if you're just
looking for rotations, you do not do not
want do not want it trading under 86 is.
Look how dark the look map is. There's
just nothing happening here.
I just don't want to be overly uh biased
in this market.
Save gray box, right? They're defending
gray box. Balls will want to defend.
Balls want to defend here.
This is the rotation,
right? Bears win this, they flush. Bulls
win this, they pop. I don't want to be
in here,
right? This is where you get trapped.
So, either acceptance above, hold below,
or acceptance below.
In normal market conditions, is it
possible to predict move up or down New
York open based on how much liquidity LR
LR equal are above or below the starting
point at New York open? No, I don't
think necessarily at the open. What
matters at the open really is you've got
to understand that
uh big institutions are not paid to run
out that any liquidity created. That's
just a a bonus. Big institutions will be
told their positions. They're quite
literally told you need to buy
5 million of Apple today uh at an
average price of this and you will get a
bonus if you can buy at an average price
under this or under VWAP etc etc. So
sometimes that's why market on close and
market on open imbalances matter because
they're trying to rifle through you know
billions and billions of dollars worth
and and that's the same at the open.
They use that liquidity to just get in
and out the market quickly.
So the first half an hour to hour is
sort of important for them to get
through their orders while there's
liquidity for them to have the ability
to do that.
Yeah, exactly, TJ. So, where bookmap is
dark, there's just no one on the book.
Literally, there's just no players there
or no players of any significance.
Right, back to Vpo again. So, let's see.
Now, this is the second attempt. We did
just hold like we talked about. All
right, we didn't come all the way down
here. We held those imbalances that I
gave you and we're back to Vo again. I'm
waiting to see if we can find acceptance
above gray box. All right, above gray
box. Otherwise, they can keep defending
it.
There's just no uh size here. You're
talking about tiny little rotations. You
know, it's only going to take one player
to come in and just be like, I'm in. And
this thing will go 30 points and it will
feel like 300 points because we barely
move.
Yes. Thank you, Miguel. Initial balance
now set.
Thank you. Thank you, mate.
I don't think it's even bulls are weak
as hell. I just think the market's just
slow. You got to remember like
we've done we've done the moves this
year. Done the moves this year, right?
It's still early. We're only an hour in.
Just wanted to say appreciate your work,
boss. Been following your channel for a
couple weeks now and I've learned so
much from you since. Hey, you're
welcome, man.
So, just testing this gray box over and
over and over and over and over again
right now.
That's awesome, Green. Glad you're
enjoying it.
Okay, so maybe the test value area low
again. No imbalances left lower now.
would build the board already. So, it's
85s maybe for a retest.
Think the market is going to go all the
way down and eventually recover in the
new year? All the way down to where?
Where do you think it's going to go all
the way down to? I don't I don't have
too much of a bias right now just
because of on a daily of where we are,
right? We're we're we're right at the
mean. Ballinger bands are starting to
contract. We can produce a higher low or
one more shove higher. If they want to
absolutely, you know, destroy everyone.
If everyone's everyone's bearish bias
based on macro environment and they want
to be nasty, they will. Um, do I think
the state of the economy is good? No, I
don't. Do I think that always matters in
the market? No, I don't. Even if you
think even if you believe that we are
early stage of, you know, 2008 kind of
scenario, I don't think we have quite
the same issues. But if we're going to
go into liquidity crisis this year, uh
it can take a long time to pan out. All
right? You're going to need data to back
it. You're going to need panic to set
in. Um you'd be surprised how long
markets can just hold up and drift
around. No one really wants, you got to
remember, no one really wants to see
that move. No one really wants to see
that move. So, if they can avoid that,
they will. I mean, everyone talked about
that happening when uh Japan put the
rates up, and I said, you know, it's
probably priced in because we already
know. We've known about it for weeks,
and this is the thing. But what really
shakes and moves the market is when
something isn't priced in. If you want
my opinion, I think we end up doing
three rate cuts next year. I don't think
we do one. I think we do three. Why?
Because I think the data will actually
come out saying that this market's weak,
right? Lack of job creation. Job
creation that is or companies that are
doing well have no job creation. They're
not hiring. They're on hiring freezes.
They're actually lowering their labor
workforce. Uh and they're pivoting to
AI. So everything's pivoting that way.
That means you've got less consumer
spending which affects retail and
commercial more. Um, you've got, like
I've talked about many times, uh,
uh, more delinquencies, more small and
medium businesses shutting down, uh,
more repossessions of, uh, cars month on
month for the last four months now.
Unemployment up since January, so 12
month uptick on unemployment, and I
think, uh, you'll probably see the repo
start to happen in the housing market as
well. So, I think that all combined will
lead lead to the Fed to a big pivot and
starting to do mass cuts. The question
is, do we sell versus those mass mass
cuts? That's kind of what I think.
Payout approved. Good man. Good man.
Good man.
RIP's made 395,000 today. probably
trading silver, I'd imagine if he was uh
trading with that much size.
It's just delta. It's It's just trading
views delta. This one you mean? It's
just trading views delta.
We're sort of just kind of asleep here,
guys, and show you what I'm looking at.
This is where sellers keep trying to
come in. This is value area low. Sellers
need to find acceptance underneath this
if we're going to drift into some of
these pockets down here. Every time we
come down here, we're seeing absorption
with very, very low numbers. All right,
so it's just a question of can we pivot
down and start puking. Every time we
come up to VPO, we keep getting stuck.
Get rid of this. We don't need this
anymore. Right. Every time we come up to
here, we keep getting stuck. You can see
buyers have been caught above that. And
then there's a selling block up here.
This is the 17 to 25s I keep talking
about. That's where they're willing to
be aggressive, right? So there's just
you think about value area high is at
626 on the session. Value area low is at
85. You're talking about a 40 point
range day right now. That's what we're
talking about. So when guys like this
guy doesn't trade, I will trade when
there's
a way when there's size to be traded,
when volume's there, when we're breaking
away, when it looks good, I'm absolutely
here to trade.
I think you you could well be right
Raph, but uh time will tell, my friend.
You could well be right. I mean, we're
not finding acceptance under value area
low. We cannot expand under it.
So, I guess traders who trade rotation,
you could keep dip buying this, selling
this, dip buying this, selling this, dip
buying this, selling this, dip buying
this, and if you get acceptance through,
selling this, and then maybe you get
lucky. It's possible.
If I make 2K a day for eight days, can I
take the 3K max twice without making any
profit in the next eight trading days?
Okay.
I make 2K a day for eight days. Yes.
Yes, you can. As long as you're sticking
to the other rules, yes, you can.
As long as your size is consistent, as
long as you're not losing more than 30%.
Or 50% now is it on the account.
Back to value low again.
off.
Is there more people saying I don't
don't trade? It's hilarious. What do you
want me to do?
You want me to fight over like 40
points?
Exactly. Exactly. Get paid to sit and
wait.
Okay. Back into this same value area.
low level
mag doesn't look too good outside of
Tesla
in video. Sorry. Test is flat.
back to value very low. I mean, I can
show you my books, guys. Like, I'm not
It's that one scout. That's it. And I
never sized in because we never bid
above, right? That's it. That's my day.
It's okay. I'm not I'm not expecting not
expecting much today. I've made it clear
in Discord members know. I think
yesterday was actually quite a good day.
We caught What did we catch yesterday?
caught actually some follow through. We
caught those saying I don't trade. Uh we
took this twice, right? We took
this and this, right? Nice moves. Nice
follow-rough moves.
Don't understand. People probably just
don't aren't willing to sit and watch
the whole stream.
I want instant gratification. The market
will not give you instant gratification.
You will become its liquidity.
Can I say historically is it wise to
look setups on the 31st of December? I
mean I can't say historically
every every 31st of December will be
will be different.
All right. Still seeing absorption in
this blue box. It they cannot trade
through it. So sellers have come in the
same level again. 85s is where they're
trying to sell
just in a slow sideways grind.
The indicators are my flow zones, mate.
Flow zone pro
version of it comes for free when you do
the 20our course.
Yeah, I mean that's fine. There's just
nothing to show, right? Like do you want
me to show 42 bucks? I mean we I can't
remember where it was. We had like one
attempt I think it was there. One
attempt there and I said I'm not going
to size unless we get above I think it
was 40s at the time. So I never sized. I
did say it all. Like there's no point
showing there's nothing going on.
When you show the footprint from Ninja
Trader, are they available stock? Uh
Ninja Trader does actually have uh
footprint charts called volumetric. If
you're trading on prop firm or you have
an account with Ninja Trader, it is
available uh for free. I have a video on
how to get that set up for order flow on
YouTube. one of the newer videos. You
can go and check that out. It teach you
how to do it. All you need to go is into
your prop firm trade of eight settings
if you're trading with trade of eight
and uh click on you basically have to
put a a button that is not normally set
on to uh allow order flow and then you
will get uh volume and volumetric and uh
cumitive volume delta and VWAP on your
Ninja Trader chart for free.
Uh, I should mention, probably didn't,
we did a flash sale yesterday. It ends
tonight at midnight for the 20our
course.
Are they going to really try and bid
this now?
Jumpy spread. Um, for the 20our course,
code is
2026, I believe. That ends at midnight.
All right. So 20% off the 20our flow
zone of course ends at midnight. Prices
go up next year. Prices go up tomorrow.
Take care. Carla
are you use VWAP trade
or do I use it? I mean you can see it
here right? New York VWAP and VWAP.
Back to value area low again. This
thing's like completely asleep.
Completely asleep.
This is where the shorts last came in.
Do they get relief? Where's that little
node? 89s, 91s.
Tesla's turn red to green. Google's
trying to go red to green.
Is the market going to find a bid? Big
question mark.
Maybe we do an Apex giveaway in 15
minutes. We do one in 15 minutes and
then one in an hour and 15 minutes.
See, there's 731 of you. Um, let's see
what the likes are in. Have to get these
likes up if we're going to do giveaways.
All right, let's get these likes up,
guys. I want 500 likes on here. We're at
214 and there's 734 of you currently
watching. So, let's get these up. Smash
that like button. Doesn't cost you
anything.
and we'll do a couple Apex giveaways.
Maybe we'll give away some courses as
well. Okay, here we go. Back through
value. Here's the lift up to that 90s we
just talked about. The problem is like
when I'm giving you these levels, what
I'm asking myself is, do I really want
to trade from 84 to 90? Do I really care
about six points? Normally, when we're
looking at these nodes, we can look for
like 40 points from one side to the
other. Six points is uh
uh
what shall I say? It's not turning me
on.
It's cuz the range is so tight. If you
imagine a normal day where volume's
good, right? If we fail to get
acceptance here and we reclaim and this
move here, that that might be like a
40point move, not a sixpoint move,
right?
We can trade off stuff like that, but
when there's nothing going on, I don't
want to trade for six six points. Some
people love trading for six points. I'm
sure there are other YouTubers, all they
do is take, you know, 10 ticks or
whatever it is.
It's just uh it's not how I trade, guys.
Those who have been here long enough
know I'm looking for
good trades where I can hold runners for
50, 100, 150, 200 points on good days.
We just don't have that environment at
the moment.
Oh yeah, email me. Is there an issue on
it?
Yeah, email me.
There's been a few bugs and stuff
recently, unfortunately.
I think my dev is off as well.
B-shaped profile. I mean, if you went
from the top of the session. Yeah,
B-shaped profile.
Bearish profile. I'd say within the New
York session though, most of it's being
done down here at the moment and we're
not breaking away from the B, right?
We've done the damage early.
The damage was repricing this huge run,
repricing this whole thing and now just
stuck.
>> Uh, yeah, probably Lindle. I would
probably agree with that. Yeah, we went
over it earlier, didn't we? was uh
yeah fifth you've got ISM manufacturing
and auto sales uh Jan 2nd there is S&P
US manufacturing I don't think I don't
think many people will be playing Jan
2nd but yeah fifth and sixth I still
don't think like fully we do have PMI
but I think the market will get going
Wednesday Thursday Friday all right if
you have a look at Wednesday ADP
employment ISM services job openings US
factory orders all all important
Thursday jobless claims, trade deficit,
US productivity, consumer credit,
Friday, unemployment report,
unemployment rate, hourly wages, hourly
wage, year, year-over-year. You got to
know hourly wages been going down.
Unemployment rate has been going up for
the whole of 2025. That will matter.
People will care about that. And you
know, University of Michigan community
consumer sentiment 945. Not sure we will
move the market with that like we used
to, but I think those early reports will
matter. Thursday and Friday I think will
bring volatility into this market.
Yeah, normal time, normal time close
today, no market tomorrow.
Always trade the same amount of
contracts in an A++ setup or you adjust
your contracts depending on volatility.
Definitely have to adjust them on
volatility, right? Because your risk is
going to go up. You can't be risking a
fixed rate. Like if you're normally
risk, I don't know 10 points and we're
in a highly volatile day. If we've got
VIX at high teens and 20s and we're
doing 200 to 400 point rotations in ENQ,
which it has been doing frequently this
year, you can't be risking 10 points.
You're probably going to need to risk 40
or 50 points, which means you're
probably going to need to size down. Um,
but I do like to size up in A+ where
possible. But sometimes that size up
might just mean I have to size down and
I'm holding for the full rotation.
Multiple rate cuts continues the bull
run.
I wouldn't be so sure. Historically,
yes. Well, actually, no. In a healthy
market, yes. Uh people will say, "Well,
it's cheaper to borrow and to go risk
on." But you have to include all the
other factors. Why? If we do rate cuts,
if they're only predicting one and we
end up doing three and there's a panic,
you have to include why. Why that's a
problem. They're trying to stimulate
something which is not moving.
How did you do this year when we just
kept hitting alltime highs over and
over? I seriously struggled during that.
Do your system still work? Yeah,
absolutely. Absolutely.
You've just got to use things like FIBS
uh for projections of where we're going
to go to higher and just not fight it.
You just can't be fighting alltime
highs.
Back to value area low again.
Sleepy, sleepy market. Okay, how we
doing on the likes, guys? We got enough
here to do a giveaway.
We are so far short. More than half of
you have not hit that like button.
Let's get these likes up so we can give
away some stuff.
Still trading around this blue box value
area low. This is the high volume node.
Remember, dating back to
Sunday and Monday the 15th of December.
That's where we're finding a bid.
ES is coming down to its 20-day new
lows, but I don't think that means
it's not necessarily a sign for a long,
okay? It just means that the breadth on
ES, you got some other sectors getting
hit. That's all it means, right? So, if
you have a look at the market as a whole
right now, it doesn't look very good.
Look,
right? So, why is Q hold Q's holding up?
It's just Nvidia, right? Nvidia and
Google and Tesla have a heavier weight
and AMD and and INTC have a heavier
weight in the cues. So if you look
broader sector finances and healthcare
and real estate and energy all right
going down means that ES is going to be
heavier doesn't mean it's an automatic
long in ENQ whoever just said that it's
uh
this whole uh SMT
bollocks it's just divergence you got to
understand the breadth and by
uh this is a one minute right now that
you're looking at. This is a one minute.
5 minute is here.
We're just still just flat.
All right. What we up to?
We need uh 21 more likes. We'll give
away some Apex accounts.
Be quite funny if we close the year
at a zero standard deviation on the
20-day.
Just giving them absolutely no edge
coming into the new year.
Eight more. Almost there. Get this set
up. Assuming you guys going to do it.
Six more likes. Almost there.
Okay.
So, just type FCT once in chat. Please
don't spam. If you spam it, you will be
banned from the competition. So, just
type it once in chat and I'll give away
a free Apex account at random. FZT FZT
Blowzone Trader FZT.
the code you can use right now to get
90% off
Apex
and the code you can use on most of Pop
Burns. Right, while this is happening,
oh, it's starting to melt now. Finally,
I might just go and try and get a coffee
here while you guys enter and when I
come back, we will pull the winner. All
right.
All right. Can we pull this one up?
It's so funny that 100 people go missing
because uh suddenly realize I'm not
going to give them a call out directly
for them. So funny. What a weird place
YouTube is. All right.
Winner is uh Raph Raphael Garcia 1819.
Are you here? Raphael Garcia.
Let me know you're here, Raph,
so we can give this away.
There we go. Beautiful, man. Just shoot
me an email, okay, dude? Just with your
screenshot of you logged in. in
info@flowzonerader.com.
I'll sort you out an Apex account. We
will do another giveaway in about an
hour or so.
if I've got the will to uh stay online
watching this. Okay, GlobeEx now swept
reaction after sweeping GlobeEx.
Finally, they're just back into some
imbalances here.
They finished this auction.
Not convinced. Yes to 20day.
QQQ. Is that your 50-day?
Are you you are okay? Yes to 50day.
Yes. Sorry. QQQ. Where are we at on the
daily here? Well beneath it. That
adjusted. Hang on.
Okay.
What is the purple circle with a red dot
on your chart?
I don't have a clue what you're looking
at.
I see a purple circle there.
Oh, this I got you.
It's nonsense. is two days old.
Very, very quiet.
Bears did take control. They defended
well though, but they probably hit their
main target here into Glowback. The only
thing left for them to trade into is
this. This is the old value area low.
Remember this dates back from uh I keep
going over it over and over again into
520. That is the value area high. Sorry,
from uh 15 the week of 15th of December.
We've swept GlobeEx. We're back to
initial balance. Now, if we start
trading back inside of initial balance,
we go back into a rotation. It would be
a look below and fail. If we hold
initial balance, there is the chance of
a trend. We cannot rule out a trend.
There is the chance of a trend if we go
uh if we keep rejecting IB and value on
the day.
on Trading View, the lows haven't been
broken yet.
As you can see on the top set platform,
uh, yes, they have. The orange line is
the lows. They have absolutely been
broken.
Absolutely have. You can quite clearly
see they have. So, I'm not sure if you
have delayed data there, my friend. You
might, if you're not paying for Trading
View or something, you might be 10
minutes behind or something like that.
Apex or Lucid, which one? Uh,
really depends what your uh ambitions
are. I'd say Lucid probably has the best
is the is the most trader friendly
platform right now to use in terms of
passing, in terms of payouts, in terms
of growth. Apex is uh probably better
for scaling if you know what you're
doing. I've got a video on it. So, if
you're just like brand new to trading
and you just want to like get used to
some software and trading it, I would
say if you're not going to trade on SIM,
then do Apex because it's only going to
cost you 20 bucks. If you're half decent
at trading and you're starting to like
find your footings and you want to grow
and you don't want to deal with trading
draw down in these stuff, I'd say look
at Lucid, look at Fun Next, look at uh
Tradeify.
M andq is is your M andQ different?
Maybe maybe you've got a divergence
there. No, MQ is also taking the lows.
So, I'm not sure my friend what you're
looking at, but they both taking them
out.
Okay. So, this is the area. Now, trend
versus non-trend will be defined right
here. All right. trend versus non-trend
will be be defined right here. So, it's
an area of interest.
How much is it to activate Apex at the
moment in the sale? It's 60 bucks. Yes,
I think uh all
someone can tell me if I've got this
wrong. I think it's 25, 50K, and 150K
are about 20 bucks per eval. And then to
activate it, it's about 60. So all in
it's about 80 bucks. I think that's
right. Or is it 40? I think that's
right. I think that's right.
The funding tick rule changes messed me
up. Same with me, mate. They stole a
[\h__\h] ton of my money
and didn't reply to me. And uh I will no
longer Oh, almost spilled my coffee. I
will no longer participate in them. I
think their response to everything has
been nothing short of a joke. So, no
more trading with them. And I lost
accounts because I didn't trade with
them over Christmas over that 5day rule.
So, yeah,
funding ticks are dead in the water,
unfortunately. And it's very sad because
I've taken some nice payouts from them
for the last few months.
I don't trade with my fun futures. Got
nothing against them. Never traded with
them.
never trade with them. You've got my my
five picks are are those ones that I
posted last week. Apex, take profit
trader, Lucid. For me, those are the top
three. They could be in any order that
you want depending how you trade. And
then it's followed by Funded Next, and
uh Tradeify.
Those are the six for me.
All right, back to this IB, folks.
There was a seller at 67. There's an
imbalance up to 71.
And uh we will reclaim at 77s. All
right. So, I'd be watching 67s and 77s
to see if they reject or they reclaim
and hold.
Yes, right at its 20day. And uh the Q's
QQQ has found a bid at its 50-day right
now.
I don't trade with Borox like some of
the guys in my team trade with Borox. I
don't trade with them. I'm just trading
with those five. I think that's enough
uh for for me. But you know, you can go
to the
site, you can use FCT. I don't trade
with Topstep. I do not trade with anyone
who will not provide Trader 8 and Ninja
Trader. very simple.
So, uh yeah,
don't like Topstep.
I think their offering is good in terms
of uh payouts and stuff, but I think
their business practices are
not very good. Let's just be polite. Not
not very good. I think they can [\h__\h] you
guys over very very quickly
uh by uh owning the software as you
would have probably experienced the last
few months.
Best account for Lucid Flex account. Is
it called a flex account? I think it's
called a flex account
in my opinion.
Let me have a look. It's amazing value
for money.
Still rejecting this blue box and this
IV. So, this is uh we can kind of let's
get rid of this. Uh redo this for you
guys. There's my delete button. There
you are. Right. This is the kind of
level
right here that bears are trying to
defend. That's under over for sentiment
for the rest of the day right now.
Um,
yes. I think the Lucid Flex account,
probably the 50K, honestly.
50K, 78 bucks, onetime fee, no monthly
renewals, max loss limit, 2,000, which
is not the best, but there you go.
Profit target 3,000. Um, free. It's
They've moved it to 50% consistency, so
you can pass it in two days now. use up
to four minis or 40 micros. Um, no
consistency when funded. That's that's
probably the one to go for
in my mind.
So, here we go. We're going to test this
IB. Let's see if we can get acceptance.
There is a little imbalance like I
talked about up to 71. And then I' I'd
be watching this area here, right? It's
very simple. If bears are to produce a
trend day, right, then they will want to
reject this with like a two leg and
something like this. If they're unable
to do this, if this is a look below and
a sweep, we will go straight back in and
we will try and attack up here. If we
find acceptance through here, we will
try and attack up here. Those are the
two options. There's always two options
on the table. I'm more willing to play
the long if they're going to find a bid.
At the moment, I'm not too bothered
about doing anything.
What happened to funding ticks? My guess
is that um it was too easy to get
payouts from. They probably had some
liquidity issues. So they uh
retrospectively changed the rules and uh
denied a lot of people payouts
unfortunately and then removed capital
from people's accounts based on the new
rule changes which they bought in
um and then just acted I would say the
CEO acted like
well a bit of a dick to be quite honest.
He didn't reply to people like me who
were saying you know this is uh you need
to look at this this isn't good and his
response was uh well arrogant and wrong
and uh they will lose business because
of it. It is as simple as that. They
they have they have absolutely shafted
themselves um because people have lost
respect for them.
It t it can take years to build up
trust. It only takes a moment to get rid
of trust. Right. So I think that's
probably what happened.
Which profile am I using? Session or
fix? This is this one right here is is
actually anchored, but it's basically
session to the 930 open.
So, they're still finding some dips
here. So far, there's some passive
buying here, but like I said all day,
the volume is very light. Very, very
light.
would the flow zone indicator signals be
different if you choose regular trading
hours versus electronic hours? Yeah, it
would it would slightly differ for sure
because it can only move based on the
candle structure you give it.
Four hours a massive head and shoulders.
Yeah, I mean we were talking about that
yesterday. It is and they've broken
down. The problem is where you're
breaking down into.
Right. So if we if we start losing bids
under 520s then we are going to go to
330s. Right. But if we do not lose that
right we can still keep bidding up and
down in this range. You got to ask
yourself like is this market really
willing to do a 300 point sell on the
last day of the year. I'm not convinced
it is.
We've been over this numerous times now.
Right? If you are the person looking for
this move here, which is fine, leaving
this volume retest stayed heavy. The
question is really, are you going to
trade inside this? Right? So, you need
to see this move here. That's when I
become very interested. I wouldn't be
selling under this.
That's dangerous.
Right now, we're just seeing not much
happen happening at all.
Very slow. Back to IB again.
next two to three days maybe. It would
be nice. Uh
Lorny, I think I've said it right. It
would be nice. I'm here for it. I'm here
for that fade uh back into the old
value. I'm here for if they want to hold
a bid down there, I'm here for that as
well. If they don't want to hold the bid
and we go full panic mode, I'm [\h__\h]
here for that as well. I will absolutely
slam SQQ for a few months and let this
market do whatever it is it wants to do.
I'm willing to honestly I'm willing to
trade both sides at the moment. You have
to be willing to trade both sides at the
moment. Does the macro environment look
good? No. Can we still drift higher?
Yeah. If it wants to, it can. So, that's
why I try not to be too biased until we
clearly make some decisions, right? If
we're clearly going to go into a major
major sell and leave major divergence
where RTY and ES takes highs and ENQ
doesn't and we start to sell tech and
the panic starts to come in. Obviously,
I'm going to sit bearish. I'm not going
to be looking for dips. But uh you know
let's deal with that next year if and
when it happens.
What rule changes did funding ticks
make? Uh they made rule changes to the
amount of money you need to make each
day to qualify for a payout. They made a
rule change on to how long you have to
hold trades for. Um
uh I'm trying to think what else. There
are some other bits as well.
Still can't get through this low volume
node. This gray box. Right. So still
can't get through the gray box. We're
building volume here now.
any players underneath
525 that's in this box. Anyone under
that?
divergence between spy and QQQ. Uh all
it is is on sector. That's all you
really need to think about. You just got
to understand spy is 500 stocks. Q's are
100 stocks. Q's heavily weighted in tech
and very heavy weighted into the mag.
Right? So if you have a day where
breadth is good, for example, bank
sector's doing well, healthcare is doing
well, energy is doing well, but maybe
we're having a selloff day in something
like Nvidia and the chip names and ABGO
and you know, etc., etc. Um, that's when
you see relative weakness. If you're
looking at divergence, you want to play,
technically speaking, you want to be
long on relative strength and you want
to be short on relative weakness.
Sometimes you have a catch-up trade
where sectors are rotating. All right,
so they might sell one sector to the
next to the next to the next to the
next. Okay, let's just focus on here now
because there might be a trigger coming
here in a minute.
Right into that imbalance we just talked
about at 70s.
Like one trade here today if possible.
So
they just faded the gray box we talked
about. This is where sellers trying to
defend. Buyers want to get through and
above
back to this same level again. Can we
find acceptance back inside or they're
going to shove this back lower?
Uh, you missed the first giveaway. We're
going to do some more. Okay, I'm
starting to perk my interest here.
Seeing some bullish action coming into
value area low. If we're going to find
acceptance and drive up, right, if we're
going to find acceptance back into value
and pivot, there is a chance for us to
get back into 607 615. Sellers took
control at 17s and 25s as well. So,
there is a chance. So, it sounds like a
massive move, but it's about 30 to 40
points. It's all it is. But you're
saying there's a chance. There is a
chance if we get over the gray box and
base. Yes, because we're going to go
this will be a look below and fail back
into IB. But this can still be defended.
So, I'm going to try and give this a
little bit of time. See if we can do
either this or this. I would I would
consider this. If we look above and fail
and come back down, I will consider the
fade.
It's not ideal. So, I'll consider it.
The one minute rule is the rule that got
me on a scalper in NQ. 1 minute is so
long. I think what's [\h__\h] up about it
is like
if you've timed your entry well, right,
and the market moves 30, 40, 50, 60, 100
points in one minute away from where you
are and you just want to pay yourself
even a little smidgen of money and move
your stop break even, they're going to
take that away from you. think that's
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] I get it. Like maybe
they should say don't close your full
position or stuff if they want to really
bring something in that helps traders,
but like
I don't know. Clearly traders were
making too much money trading uh within
a one minute period otherwise they
wouldn't have bought that in.
What is the gray box indicator? Is it an
EMA?
Gray box indicator. This is just a gray
box that I've drawn in
th this gray box. See low volume node
that I've put in because I know this is
where we broke structure to the
downside. This is where sellers are
trying to defend. That's your IB value
area low and low volume node. This is
where sellers will try and defend. This
is where buyers will try and pivot back
above. This is like the battleground
zone.
underneath it is an EMA. Those clouds,
those are EMAs.
Any box you see put on the screen is not
an indicator. It's something that I'm
putting there. It's a level of interest
for me. This is a level of interest for
me. This is a level of interest for me.
This down here is a level of interest
for me for demand. This is a level of
interest for me. And then above there's
probably some red boxes somewhere. All
right. is a level of interest of supply.
The way I like to trade is to let
ideally not on days like today, which
has been awful, is to let price come
into a level of interest. And if I'm
looking to buy in a blue box, I want to
see aggressive sellers get caught
offside. Right? That's kind of what I
want to see.
Starting to look good here. Can we see
some aggression to get involved here?
This is better. Hello.
Hello. Here's value area low. All right.
What I'm watching here is 84s.
That's where big selling came in is into
84s and 85. So, if we can drive up
there, if we get through that, then I
know we're going to leave sellers
trapped.
Some selling coming into 70s. We want to
see it lift to 84. like every four or
five points feels very hard to get at
the moment.
Right into value area low here. We want
to get back into 84s and really we want
to get back above 88s and 90s. Here we
go.
Can you lift to 84s? Here we come.
He doesn't tell me what he's looking
for.
Patience is a virtue.
Can we get through the 84s? You can see
this right right in front of 84s. Right.
I can tell you right now there's there
was a seller this morning at 84s. I can
see he had big size there. So, I'm
looking to see if we can get above him
because if that's his average price, he
might want to stop out. If we can't get
above him, then he remains in control.
All right. So, this is how I'm looking
at levels and what I'm thinking. There's
not much size on the book. So, if we get
above 84, is there a potential squeeze?
Yes. To 600 and to 607 if we can get
above 84. So, I'm already long peeling
some off into 84 in case we reject.
Right. I'm trying to be proactive
because I don't know.
I really want to see now
75s down to 70s hold. Here we go.
Testing 84. You can see how accurate the
84 is. Right. Look at 84. Right. 84.
This is why I'm peeling some off into 84
cuz I know this is where a big seller
came in.
They're going to have to hold these dips
into 75 to 70s. If they don't, I will
just stop out on the rest. And that's
fine. I do not want a failed look
inside. Remember we talked about the
opportunities here are going to be
this move here or
this move here if they have unfinished
business. All right. I'm willing to play
both. I am willing to play both. Right
now I'm trying to get long or this move
here. I've already peeled some off. I'm
not going to reload unless it really
proves to me. I will just stop out on
the rest and that's fine because we are
in a very very low volume. What I do not
want to do, right, is just be like, I'm
going to risk down here. And for some
reason, some big seller comes in and
goes, "Fuck you." in one candle because
this might look big, but it's actually
tiny. It's only 20 points and it
wouldn't take a lot. If we can build
here, we look good.
What platform are you using? I'm trading
on Ninja. What you're looking at is
Trading View. What I'm trading on is
Ninja. It's over here. Right.
You see this player here? 84.
Can you guys see that on the book? I
might have to move it up a bit.
Need my other hand for the mouse. All
right. This Where's it gone? Need that.
I need that to show you. All right. This
guy here is a big seller. All right.
This is the delta. I can see at this
price. This is why I knew we'd probably
come up and test him. He's still clearly
there. All right. He's present and he's
passive because this is aggressive
market order buying. And this is passive
selling into this level with an
imbalance. So I know there's still a
seller there. Once we get above that, I
know that the seller is out the money
and everyone below him is out the money.
And then we can think about a squeeze,
right? So I'm trying to use their pain.
I'm positioned in case we do it. But I
don't expect us to have to do it. That's
the difference.
Hopefully that makes sense. That
definitely those of you who have traded
with me a long time and have been around
long enough will know how I trade. to
trade people's pain. But this is a see
money take money environment right now
at 25608. There are a lot of buyers that
were offside and got trapped on my
delta. Would you be looking to scale out
there also? What did you say my friends?
608. I mean yeah I mean look that's
that's the gray box right point control
right here. That's it. That's exactly
it. So, we want to try and get what
we're trying to do is get from here to
here. And I Yes, I absolutely would
scale some out there. And if we find a
trade through here, then we're going to
go and test current day's value area
high, which is previous week's value
area low. Right?
So, all all it takes is some patience. I
would say to you, if you haven't peeled
any off, I would peel some off into here
just in case, even if it's 10 20%.
What indicator is that? The one on Ninja
Trader. It's called
City.
But you can just do it on here, guys.
You can just It's the same level on
here, right? You You would just need to
look for where
you had a big delta C here. And then you
use spikes in volume profile. Can you
see this spike? This guy right here.
This node. This is a high volume node.
All right, it's the same level. All
right, so that's when you put confluence
together.
They're going to go for it again here.
They're trying. They are desperately
trying.
Lift it. Lift it. Lift it. Lift it. Come
on. Someone turn up. ES is banging into
GlobeEx lows and initial balance as
well. So we want ES to follow what ENQ
is doing, right? We want ES to get back
through IB. So if you think about what
we're doing right now, we're long in
relative strength based on where we're
positioned to IB.
So still passive seller up here. And
let's check CBD. Uh was it JD that
wanted to go over this? Be a good time
to do it.
CBD is actually in total alignment right
now. So, we're not seeing in this part
any uh
any uh hidden divergence or anything
like that,
but we will go I'll go over it with you,
my friend. Here we go. 84s. Right. Let's
see if we can get through this little
imbalance above and see if we can start
a squeeze. Where's that little [\h__\h] whit
saying I don't tell you what to do or
anything. Get the [\h__\h] out of here,
goons.
I'd like to see another trader give you
a precise levels like 84 exactly.
We want a base above this node now. We
do not want to pop and fail. We need a
base above. We want the flow zones to
start supporting. It might be that we
need to build out some liquidity cuz
this is uh a little bit naughty how they
developed it. If we're very lucky, they
will just do a straight squeeze here and
run all these stops. Uh which will be
fun, but it might be that they need to
offer something like this. But uh let's
see. Hopefully, we get going
that just woke up.
Wife was out on a boozy run last night.
Still off work.
Lucky woman.
Is gold following NASDAQ? I don't know.
I've not looked.
Look.
Uh, no.
That's definitely not following NASDAQ.
That's definitely your imagination. I
don't I don't see that looking the same.
Oh, I don't know. I see what you mean.
Morning drive, get stuck, fade. It's
different. It's different. It's holding
a different pivot.
It's holding a different pivot.
It's just this part. Morning drive fade.
Try and hold the pivot. I get what
you're saying, but I don't think it's uh
particularly following.
All right. So, maybe some relief. Can we
get some more relief? Let's uh just
check
fib here from the high to the lows. We
want to be careful as we come into 30.
Where is the New York open? Let's double
check that as well. Yeah, we want to be
a little careful here. Make sure you've
paid yourself some money here uh just in
case into this area. Remember, I think
this is a see money, take money kind of
environment right now. Pay yourself. Pay
yourself. Pay yourself.
No worries, man. No worries.
All right, we're going to do another 15
to 30 minutes. We'll give away some more
Apex accounts. I'll give away uh one of
the um introduction to the market
courses as well.
I first time for me here seeing that me
the person with different way of looking
at the charts I can see that we have
let's say some same bias for the move I
think you're saying so you look at the
charts differently but you're seeing the
same bias right now it's good like I
said I will never talk [\h__\h] about
someone else's trading methods there are
a million ways to trade the markets you
need to trade whatever suits you
whatever setup suits you whatever way of
looking at the chart suits you um never
stop learning. I never stop learning.
You never stop learning when you're a
trader. And the moment you stop learning
and you think you know it will the
market will humble you. Okay. Into this
next node here. And the only thing left
right now is to get into this pocket up
here. All right. So I would say there
were some sellers at 96s. The next one
that stands out to me is 6 600 601. And
then we're going to go VPOX 607. And I
will just say you are welcome. All
right. You are welcome. We absolutely
called this well ahead of time when we
were down here. I was telling you what I
would look at if we get back above the
gr gray box. If we hold the gray box and
we will look for expansion. All right,
very very simple but it required a huge
amount of patience. And that there is
trading very very simple huge amount of
patience. All right, if you make it too
complicated it's going to be too hard.
If you don't have patience, you're going
to lose. Really nice.
Make sure you are locking yourself in
there. This is so thin. If you're
looking at bookmap with me, it is
incredibly thin right now. So, just be
careful. See money, take money. If I'm
saying see money, take money, it's
trying to encourage you to pay
yourselves, not to be too aggressive,
not to look for too much.
I would uh ideally this pullback holds
sort of 8485. So, I don't want it to
flush back down to value low. So, I'm
looking for this to hold 8485.
That same level where we talked about
those big sellers, right? The 8485.
This same level here, it's now PC.
Right now, it needs to hold this for me
to feel good about comfortable at
holding because this was the shorts pain
where they came down. If we trade above,
they need to hold this. If they don't
hold this, I'm not going to sit through
this wash. All right. I can always read
down here as a new position. I want to
see them hold this. No, not holding it.
All right.
So, we'll wait. For me personally, I'll
wait for a reload now.
200 Oh. Uh, you made 265*
4 C money. Take money. I'm done. Hey,
dude. Look at that big payout yesterday.
You've just locked in another,000.
Are we talking about the same guy when
we were having one-on- ones, mate? Look
at you absolutely killing it. That's
what I'm talking about. That's the
difference between knowing your setup.
What's your setup? You know your setup.
Tyson knows his setup. IB reclaim back
to VU up. Pay yourself on the way.
[\h__\h] love it. One setup. That's all
your all that Tyson trades. This setup
here or a fade underneath. Very, very,
very, very, very simple. Stick to what
you do well.
Like I always talk about having the
eight iron. When you're a beginner at
golf, get around the course with an
eight iron. Leave the driver in the bag.
All right. Don't get the driver out. You
get the driver out, you're gonna put it
in the pond. You're gonna, I don't know,
maybe put it in a bunker. Maybe you get
so pissed off you smash the driver. All
right. Imagine that driver is your
trading screen. That's what happens when
you're oversized, when you take setups
which are not in your wheelhouse. Let's
say,
am I one and done? At the moment, I'm
done with it. I will happily reload like
I talked about. If I see right
aggressive selling coming in here and no
acceptance, if I see passive buyers
holding price here and absorbing, I'm
willing to take this. What I'm aware of
is that we can do a look above. We can
fail. We do have weakness on the ES. So,
I'm just aware of it. If I see passive
buying holding price like right now, we
just had aggressive selling step in
underneath 79 and 80. So, if we can't
move under that, I'm going to know that
they're going to start to get stuck. But
you know, we've got about 30 minutes
left and I think, you know, we didn't
get much, but there wasn't much to get.
So, we got
the reclaim.
That's what we fought fought over today.
Like 25 30 points. That's all that's all
we got to play with at the moment. Can
we hold above this low volume node? If
the answer is no, it's going to be a
problem. We can wash right back down.
Like I said, there there isn't much
volume. I want you to understand, guys,
when I'm looking at this,
right? I'm not seeing a huge amount of
bid support here. All right, if we look
at the amount of support here, we're
looking at nine lots, 16 lots, right?
I'm not seeing good bid support. I can
see someone soaking because we've got a
64 lot on the cell. I might have to move
this over. You can see that this area
here, they are trying to absorb into
these 77s, but I'm not seeing like us
walk up. And what I want to see is all
of this disappear. I don't want any bids
underneath. I want to see them walk
price up like they're trying to do now.
I want them to start moving their limits
up and up and up and up. And I want to
see these start to lift and disappear or
get run over, which we are arguably have
a shot of doing. But what I don't want
to see is this these these big gaps when
they're just removing themselves, right?
Because it's not going to take a lot to
sell through.
This is what I say, what I mean when I'm
saying I'm I'm looking I'm watching the
tape, right? When people say I'm tape
reading and they're looking at a candle,
just tell them to [\h__\h] off, right?
They're just conning you. That is not
tape reading. The word tape reading
actually comes from not even looking at
bookmap. It will come from looking at
time and sales. That's tape reading. Can
I tape read? [\h__\h] no. I cannot read the
time and sales. If you give me a time
and sales, I can see when it's flashing
red and see when it's flashing green.
Uh, but I wouldn't be able to tell you
like a big order that went through
unless I have some kind of filter on it.
Very hard, especially in a market like
NQ to read read the tape that quickly,
which is why I use bookmap because it
leaves the orders on there for me to see
historical orders.
What time frame do I use for uh what do
you mean random channel? I I start on a
daily, right? We go from weekly to daily
to for me, I normally skip four 4 hour
because I can see it on an hourly bar,
right? To hourly to 5 to one. And when
I'm looking at the tape, there is no
time frame. I'm just looking at where
orders are placed.
I actually compressed the delta profile
by like four ticks. Two two ticks, mate.
Two ticks for me.
That's it. When they used to literally
print trades. That's it. That's the time
and sales. It's like the receipt being
printed. That's exactly what I'm talking
about. Now we have a digital time in
sales.
Yeah, it's it's in the course um
technique, but I'll tell you now, I
don't have any um there's no magic
settings. Thank you. Yeah, it's all
right. That's the fresh one. Thank you.
Um I don't have any magic settings,
right? All I'm looking at is
standard bookmap. The more important
thing for bookmap for me is the level
two uh where I want to look at the
volume profile delta.
By the way, what can you say about the
concepts of understanding the market in
the way that ICT teaches? Look, the way
ICT teaches is good. There's no way of
like I I'm not going to deny his his
teachings are not bad. You have to
understand that most of them come from
WOFF. All right? the theory like the
algorith you understand him saying that
one algo controls the market that is the
same as wov saying one man controls the
market it's the way of viewing the
market it's how I view the market I
don't actually believe a single
algorithm controls the market what
actually controls the market are
institutions and volume that's what
controls the market real buyers real
sellers um the idea of a fair value gap
is just an imbalance it's an aggressive
engulfing candle that moves away from an
area and leaves a gap in price. Can you
actually see the gap in price? Well, I
can tell you now this gap here. I'd much
rather look to see if there's actually a
genuine imbalance. And look where the
imbalance is. It's actually up at 90 to
94. If we come over to here, what's it
showing? 90 to 94. So, the imbalance is
actually higher, not where you would see
it on a fair value gap. So, the
teachings are good, but they wouldn't
they're not necessarily accurate, right?
That's best way of putting it. Well, I
would actually say the imbalance is
actually 90 to 92. Um, teachings are
good, but uh, lots of it is made overly
complicated. Order block, I'd call that
flip block. What is it? It's SNR.
Resistance becomes support. Support
comes resistance. That's all it is.
How many rows do you use in your
anchored session volume? Uh, yeah, you
can use a thousand or I've actually got
it set to tick, right? So, I have it
ticks per row set to two. But you if not
I would have numbers of rows and I'd
have it set to a th00and. Okay, have it
set to a th00and. So you can see we came
right up to the top of that imbalance.
All right, right up to 90. Not into this
low part. Right up into 90. And the
imbalance goes to 91.75.
Right. So this is a prime example.
No, right now you're looking at a one
minute chart.
Auction market theory. Yeah, correct.
Uh, you're probably right there. Um,
dubia dub dubia. Have I said it right?
Dub dub your trades. Dub your I like
that. Dub dub city.
You're probably right.
All right. How many likes we got? I want
to give away some more stuff. You guys
have been fantastic this year. The
growth on YouTube has been immense,
especially in the last month or two, and
I love trading with you. It's very rare
we get idiots in here. Most of the time,
you guys are here to learn, here to make
money, and that's all I care about. I
don't really care about me. What I
actually care about is you guys learning
and making money.
And we have a pretty good track record
on stream. I don't think I've had too
many red days this year. There's been
definitely been some obviously, but
there hasn't been too many. And the ones
that have happened where it's been big
red. The ones that stand out in mind is
when I had Ninja Trader fail on me and
start reversing my uh positions, which
was
deeply upsetting, but I battled out of
it over a twoe period, which is good.
Um, right. Let's try and get 50 more
likes, guys. Let's try and get up to 500
likes.
Did I see receive your email? Let's have
a look. I I see it, Raph. As soon as I
get off stream, I will um reply to you.
Same with Nathan and same with Kaden.
All right. Can see them. As soon as I
finish stream, I'll get back to you.
All right. So, Graybox still holding.
We're trying to hold PC. So, buyers
right now are trying to do this move.
They're trying to defend this and do
this and complete rotation.
And if they get through this, they get
lucky. What do sellers want? They want
to print under here and use this to trap
buyers to move lower. That's the battle
right now that you're seeing emerging.
All right, I'm flat and out of this
right now. All right, we traded from
like here to here. I tried to hold the
runner to see if it wanted to keep
going. It didn't want to hold. What I
wanted to hold was right here, right?
Didn't see it. Didn't see too much
participation being aggressive. You
might see another attempt, but at the
moment, I'm happy to chill.
Almost there, guys. 30 more likes and
we'll give away some some fun stuff.
What silver doing today? I haven't
actually looked at it. Where's the
volatility in the market? 8%. Oh, failed
follow- through day coming up then. Is
it?
This is what we talked about. All right,
anyone that's been here the last few
days peak top
failing to follow through inside bar,
right? What matters now is this. This
will set the tone if this happens.
Right, we could look for a trade from
here down to 50% if we get lucky right
back into this pocket. And then normally
what happens in on golds and silver and
copper is this consolidation can happen
over months. So in here we might well do
this and have a reattempt later into
March. Really depends
how much this news from uh China is
priced in. We will see
how much we continue to decimate the
dollar. Let's have a look at that.
It's trying to recover. It is trying to
recover a bit.
You can see where I was changing money
over.
This is where I was pulling pulling
money out of USD and transferring back
to uh great British pound. Not now. I'm
going to be [\h__\h] broke if I get keep
getting paid in dollars.
At least most of America doesn't leave
the country. E,
you're not going to understand the the
weakness of it elsewhere.
You didn't realize I got long.
Really?
I thought I made it pretty clear. Uh
what is the consistency rule in in Lucid
Flex? To pass the account, it's 50%.
Once you are passed and into the uh past
the evaluation stage, there is no
consistency rule.
Do I think we rotate to opening high?
Uh,
I might be asking a lot
right now. I'd be watching this to this.
All right, just play level to level. All
right, if we come come here to here,
that's your first rotation. If we get
acceptance above here, this is your
second rotation. If we get acceptance
above previous week value area high,
then we're thin up to here, right? But
don't I wouldn't be positioning myself
long with the expectation of getting
there. Okay? Don't don't do that on a
day like today.
We're not trend up. All right? We're not
trend up.
How important is it for me to
incorporate level two data?
Um,
I'd say it's where my edge comes from.
I'd say it's where my edge comes from. I
don't think you have to do it. Do I
think you can build strategy without it?
Yeah. Um, I feel much more confident
knowing who's trapped in a market. And
uh you're not always going to get that
data out of candles.
So
but you can incorporate other things.
Ar my does my course go over the
indicators and how to use them. Yes.
Don't we don't do one-on- ones, but in
Discord we do I'm trying to do it
bi-weekly at the moment where we have uh
like one to two hour lessons and
everyone joins in and we frontload any
questions and then we do them everyone
can be welcome to talk up and I try and
teach. So if anyone has questions that
day or on a setup that day or something
they've missed or how to use something
we go over it, right? And there's it's
not extra money. It's it's it's a
onetime fee. You don't do monthly fees.
Not not at the moment for anything.
How many days do you have to trade for
Lucid? Uh two days to pass, I think. And
I think 5 days for a payout, I think.
What provider do I use for level two?
CME direct. I just pay for it on
bookmap. Same on Trading View. I just
pay for it. You don't need to do that.
You can probably find a good deal, but I
just pay for it all so I know it's
working properly.
All right, let's do a giveaway. I want
to give away some stuff for you. Let's
do another Apex account giveaway.
Let me just set this up.
Remember, you've got until I think it's
until the 6th for uh Apex for the 90%
sale. So, code FCT. Just type it in chat
once, please.
Just type it once. Give you guys a
couple minutes. How many indicators do I
use?
Uh,
I mean, this is like a an all-in-one
tool.
So, really, this is all I'm looking at
and volume. I don't necessarily need
this, but it just for me, this keeps me
the right side of of the trade. Like, if
we're in a trend, I want to fade it.
Like, you can argue today like, should I
have just listened to my indicator? I
mean, it gave me a sell signal. We
rejected point of control. We rejected
this. Should I have just faded the
opening drive? Well, the answer is
clearly yes. I didn't feel comfortable
putting size on in a low volume market
on the opening drive today. But we
talked about what did we talk about
having to hold? If it didn't hold 680s,
we were going to rotate
to 630s. And if we didn't hold that, we
were going to rotate to 520s. And we did
all of them. One, two. I mean, we've
just missed this.
So maybe
ignoring it was foolish of me today. But
there we go.
I'd rather ignore it and be flat than uh
at least I didn't fight it the other
way.
Give you guys a minute more to do it.
Guys, if you keep spamming, all that
happens is you get pulled out of it.
Right. So, over on the giveaway where
it's recording you, it pulls you out for
spamming it. So, please don't type it
more than once because all you're doing
is hurting your own chances of winning.
What's the Discord? Discord is uh only
available if you do the um 20our course.
It's just for students. It's not free,
unfortunately for you guys. It's not
free, but uh there is no monthly fee.
All right? So, it's a onetime fee. But
the reason we do that is so that
everyone's trading the same way. Means
that we have a good community can look
after each other.
I give you guys 30 more seconds.
Sorry.
Okay, let's draw this winner.
I don't know how to say that. Mel Mel
15.
M A C H A E L 15. Mel 15.
Are you here, Muel? Give you a little
bit longer to reply. Otherwise, we'll do
a reroll. So, make sure you let me know
you're here.
They're trying to squeeze this at the
moment. Watching the book. They're
trying to get back over the PC.
10 more seconds. Mau, you need to let me
know that you're here. M A C H A E L15.
There. Thank goodness for that. I hate
r-rolling. There he is. Or they are.
Sorry. Don't know. Um,
so what I would like you to do is email
me,
okay? info@flowzonetrader.com.
Okay, info@flowzonerader.com.
Send me a screenshot, please, of you
logged in to your YouTube. I've made a
note of your name. I need to see you
logged in with that name so I know it's
you and I will give you a free Apex
account of any size. Right. What are you
guys saying? What's the buy and sell
indicator? Okay, for the last time
today, guys, the indicator you're seeing
here is the Flowzone System Pro. All
right, you can buy it on my website or
you get a version of it for free with
the course. All right, I would advise
just do the course and upgrade if you
like it. Um,
go through these. Uh,
how much is the course? Right, right now
it's 520 and that sale ends at midnight.
Okay. So, if you go to
flowzontrader.com,
the last time I'm going to go through
this guys. All right. If you go to
flzzonetrader.com,
come to this course here,
buy now. And if you type in 2026,
and hit apply, you will get a discount
from 649 to 519. All right. Prices are
going up tomorrow. So, this is the last
chance you've got to get it on sale and
last chance to get it at at 649 or 519
till midnight. If you want to do the
orderflow course, right,
this does not come with Discord.
You can use code launch. Again, this
ends at midnight
and you'll get 100 bucks off. You can
get this for $299. All right, so this is
6 hours plus. I would I would advise you
do the uh beginner to advanced course
first, especially if you're a newer
trader. This is a 20-hour course. It
comes with a version of the indicator
and it comes with Discord. All right.
So, if you're looking to join the
community, start there.
Do I still blow funded accounts? Yeah,
of course I do. Of course I do. Still
happens. It's been a while, but yes.
Yes, it does happen. Especially if I'm
trying to be more aggressive with them.
It doesn't happen if I'm taking my time
and building them. But sometimes if I
get an account, I'm like, "Right, going
to try this method with this. I'm going
to be more aggressive. I'm going to
trade this session." I don't necessarily
put them all together, but when I take
my time, no, it doesn't happen.
Yeah, we're working on it. Actually,
Noah, um, Adam or Bowden as you might
know him is, uh, working on it for me at
the moment.
Yeah, you can see I saying, look,
they're trying to force the squeeze
through PC. They did the squeeze. We're
back to this same level, though.
Remember this level, uh, 94, I think I
said it was, right? Back to this same
level. Nothing's changed. It's the same
level.
where we just squeezed back to.
We're trying to find acceptance over it.
So now they're going to try and produce
a higher low and complete this squeeze
up into this gray box. That's what they
are attempting to do. Attempting to do.
Do I use a trade copier? Yes. Affordable
indicators trade copier folks.
So it's best to start with the trading
course. Yeah, the 20 I would say start
with the 20our course. All right, it's
20 hours and then you'll get Discord for
free and you'll get a version of the
flow zones for free as well. Right. If
you want to upgrade later, we can sort
that out after.
Starting to see a squeeze attempt above
point of control here. Remember, they're
trying to get up to 6604. All right,
this is where they're trying to get up
to at the moment. So those of you who
are still long, that's where you're
trying to get up to 600 604 and this
kind of level here 602. So you want to
get through this node, through the low
low volume node up into 602. So if
you're still long from this gray box,
this is what you're looking for. This is
the higher low now being set. Right? So
they did one, two. This is the failed
attempt to move lower. We should come up
into here. And if they if you get lucky,
you get this. So if you are long, you
want to be trimming some into this and
hoping you complete the move. There is
absolutely no guarantee in this market
that you will get up into here. So you
will pay yourself into this move.
All right. Maybe if I wasn't doing the
giveaway, I should have been a little
bit more focused in here to grab some of
this. It's probably going to work quite
nicely.
Any tips on auction theory? It's it's
all in the order flow and volume course.
That's that's my tip on auction theory.
If you want to watch a free video, I'd
say start with my video on WOFT.
It's a bearish B-shaped profile today.
Would you agree? Um, like I said,
this part of it is, but what I would say
is context. All right. Yes, I would say
that's B. The problem that you're going
to have is this part of the move
happened very early. Most of this, if
you ignore the opening, how many minutes
is this? You ignore the opening three
minutes, four minutes, what are we
actually in? More of a D. All right,
more of a D shape. So, the question for
me would be, do they respect this or
not? This is why I'm saying pay yourself
into this and you just [\h__\h] don't
know because we're such low volume.
I would agree with you that we have
reacted all right from previous week and
previous day, right? We've left previous
day. We've left current week. We reacted
and came down. But we're finding a bid
where we just zoom out here. We go to
like a 30 minute
in front of this old balance, right? And
this big old fat node.
Old range.
Old range. This is why I'm saying I
don't want to be uber biased because if
we do this, I will be biased for this
move, right? Cuz I know we will want to
repric that. This is your old naked PC.
That's when I'll start thinking, okay,
we can break down, right? And once we
get down here, this is what I'll be
looking for early next year or this
year. If we want to do this, that's
fine. If we do something like this,
right, then I'll bid back up, right? If
we fail this, then I'll play the
continuation back down into here and
here. I don't want to be uber biased at
this point of the range because we think
about swing low, swing high can still be
pulled back for a continuation. I know
everyone's looking for this, but until
we really show acceptance into this
range, I want to be cautious.
Here we go. So, you're lifting. You look
really good. Anyone who took that, you
look fantastic here. So, it's the 603
604s. I think I said uh 608 is the next
level. And I would be trimming a good
chunk of your position. If you took the
long out the gray box we talked about
pulling back into and holding or if you
took this break here for the higher low
creation, right? Trim into here. Hold
your runners. You never know. You might
get lucky. You don't know. I would be
trimming a good chunk of my change.
So you got from 550.
Oh, nice, man. So you took the false
break of GlobeEx. So I'm assuming you
took the break. You didn't buy there.
You bro, hopefully you bought the break
back above. That's really nice. I mean
that is a fantastic trade and we expect
some sort of resistance up here. Uh ES
also into VW up here and VIX also into a
demand block down here. All right. So we
expect here I'd be trimming a good
chunk. Right. Trim. Do not be greedy. If
you got this or some if you got that
it's fantastic. Right. Trim. You never
know. You might get lucky on your
runner. You'd never know. It's uh last
day of the year.
Right, let's give away um the
introduction course. Right, this is just
a 2hour long course. It's not any of the
full courses, but I want to give one
away.
What's the coupon code for the orderflow
course? Uh it coupon code is
launch all in capitals. It's 6 hours and
I'm still adding stuff to it.
6 hours long.
Would I take a sell back down here? Um,
not for me. But I don't like trading
range rotation. Right. So, technically
speaking, let me just check on Ninja.
Technically speaking, the edge of range,
right? If I was going to look to sell
range, I'd need it to be up here, not
here. I know. I know there's a node
there, but the momentum where have we
trapped,
right? We've trapped sellers here. Low
hanging fruit's gone. Maybe there's a
sell down to here, but I would be uh
somewhat skeptical. Like I said, it's
very thin. It would actually not take
very much. Imagine they run the this
this group of stops. If they don't
protect it, it wouldn't take very much
to do that move. So, like for me
personally, if I'm going to trade range
rotation, I really want to trade the
extreme edge. I can see that there's a
node here. I know what you're looking
at, but I'd rather almost have it do
that and this move here, right? If I was
going to trade an edge,
let me set up this.
All right. So, just type course once,
please, in chat. We give away the
introduction course. It's only a 2hour.
It's good for someone who's never traded
before. All right, if you've never
traded before, if you have no idea about
trading or investing, it's very, very,
very beginner friendly. All right, it's
only worth 99 bucks. It's only 2 hours
long. It's not one of their mentorship
programs. If you don't want it, we can
roll it or we can you can give it to a
family member, whatever you want.
Everyone that's emailed me. I promise
I'll get back to you as soon as I get
off stream. As soon as I get off stream.
We do this and then get out of here.
Give you guys a minute longer. Sip of my
coffee.
I hope you've all got some fun plans
tonight.
Do I trade the New York open? Yes, I do.
Ronnie, you need to be here 9. My advice
is to join me at 9:15 Eastern time every
morning. All right. Because the first 15
minutes is important before the New York
open because I go over what I'm looking
at and why. All right. And that's the
important thing.
I buy the 28 hour course. Can I add the
Ninja Pro indicate to it? Yeah, it gives
you an option to add it uh for a
discounted rate if you want to do that.
Take care, Miguel.
So, I look for a break and retest model.
Uh, not always.
Not always. Depends on the setup I'm
looking at. Sometimes it's a straight
reclaim and I'm not looking for the
retest because I'm expecting a squeeze.
It depends on what kind of condition
we're in, what the market's doing.
It is a It is a model I like for sure.
It's a model I like, but I wouldn't say
every time I look at that. Okay, we're
going to pull the winner here, of
course. Five, four, three, two, one.
Simpleton Jeep. Simpleton Jeep,
are you here?
Yeah.
Nice, man. Okay, just shoot me an email,
please. Email me info@flowzontrader.com.
uh email me with a screenshot of you
logged into your YouTube. All right, a
screenshot of you logged into your
YouTube just so I know it's you and uh
you can have a free course
introduction course. All right,
when I decide to have one-on-one
mentorship dibs on your first client,
honestly, it's just I'd love to, but
it's just I would have no time. You have
to understand how much time I I give up
already doing this. It's a huge amount
of time, but uh it would be really nice.
Um
yeah, that's it. I do reply all the time
and we do try and do next year we start
doing them again. We do those Friday. We
try and do the Fridays together.
All right, folks.
Yeah, lots of good traders. Even when
I'm not there, lots of great traders
there. We have a nice tight-knit
community, guys. That's that's the whole
reason why we don't do like a monthly
fee to join or free to join because then
you get traders trading different ways.
What we have at the moment is, you know,
180 or 200 traders who some of them are
quieter than others, but some great
traders that I've known for five, six
years who can look after each other and
new additions coming all the time who
add a huge amount of value. Okay, it's
all about building a tight little
community who can help each other, you
know, so that if you're looking for a
trade, you can say, "Hey, I'm looking at
this. What do you think? Does anyone
agree? Are we all looking at the same
things?" And once you got people saying,
"Yeah, I see the same thing." Gives you
good confidence, doesn't it? You start
to build confidence in yourself and what
you're looking at.
Can I please show a snip or preview of
what is in the Discord? Uh, yeah, I
guess I can do that.
It's probably going to be full of lots
of uh
lots of uh happy new year messages right
now, but yeah, we can. Right. So,
pre-market said all the areas we're
looking at and what we're looking at in
the low volume. We go over all the same
levels. You can see it's just constant
chat from traders talking about what
they're looking at, any help that they
require. This is all in the futures one.
Uh giving out the levels. We go out the
key levels and the rotations,
everything constantly, every day. All
right. Just constantly what levels we're
looking at and why, where traders are
trapped and why.
All right. This the last two weeks
obviously has been a bit quieter because
we've been in um
in holiday mode.
Okay. And if we come over here, we have
uh coup's corner where they have setups
all together. So this is like a another
group community inside the group. Great
for traders uh looking to like build
accounts together on small size. It's
trading a very specific way together. I
also have my swing investments here. So
every time I'm looking at swing
positions, I'm look talking about what
I'm looking at and why I'm looking at it
and what my expectation is, where I'm
going to position, where my entries are,
where my exits are. We've had some great
trades in here this year as you can see.
Like here, what was this one? AMD and
got just under 50% out of that. Um, so
yeah, t tons and tons and tons and tons.
Um, what else? We've got the news feed,
economic calendar,
um, testimonials,
P&L, right? So, some of my traders
yesterday locked in over $10,000 and
took payouts yesterday.
There's tons in there, guys. There's
there's literally tons in there.
Again, there's no, like I always say,
there is no pressure. Um,
you've got to do what's right for you as
a trader. And uh, you've got to you've
got to trade within your means. That's
the one thing people I think get wrong.
Like they they try and get rich quick or
they think spending three grand or four
grand on a course is the answer. And
it's not. I've been there. I've done it.
Like you need to find it doesn't I'm not
doesn't need to be me. If I don't speak
to you, if you don't like the sound of
my voice, the way I look, how I teach,
the methodology, my pedagogy, teaching
style, for sure, don't buy the course,
right? Because you're you're going to be
aggravated. Find someone that works for
you. It's no different. I say this every
time people ask, it's no different to
being in school or to being going to a
new college or university. We've all had
it where there's a teacher that we love
and they just click with us, right? the
way they explain stuff makes sense to us
and we get good grades. And then you
have another subject that you have loads
of interest in and the teacher just
aggravates you. It just you don't like
how they teach. Maybe they're not visual
enough for you. Maybe they're too
condescending. It it could be anything,
right? And then you switch off from that
subject and your grades go bad. Well,
you better make sure your grades aren't
bad in this, right? Which means you've
got to find something that works for
you. It might not be me. I won't take
offense from that. I want you guys to
succeed. If if there's someone else in
the universe that you like, that teaches
well that you can make sense of, go with
them. Don't don't spend money on
something because someone else said it
was good. Do I believe my course is
good? Yeah. Do I believe 20 hours and an
indicator and a Discord for currently
520 bucks until tonight is good? Yeah,
it's insane value. But I'm going to say
that I built it. You might think it's
[\h__\h] and that's okay.
No, the orderflow. Yeah, the orderflow
course does not include the Discord. I'm
really sorry. It doesn't include the
Discord. We I actually put it to a vote
to a couple of guys um who've been with
me in a long time and we all made the
decision that what might happen is
you're still going to get guys trading
slightly different ways. And that's the
only I've been at this a lot a long
time. Been in many many many discords.
Okay. Where it goes wrong is when you
start getting traders trading in
different ways. It's fine to look at the
market in different ways, but when they
start when one's looking short and the
other one's looking long at the same
level and they don't agree and then it
just blows up. Before you know it,
you've got this cascading effect. Like
that's what we're trying to avoid.
Positive reinforcement of everyone
looking at the market in the same way or
at least a very similar way. And then
when they've got a question, it's easier
for people to answer to help.
Launch is not working. What for the
Well, I just checked it. It is capital
letters launch for the volume profile
one.
I'll check it now. I'm pretty sure I
just checked it.
Enter coupon code launch.
Yeah, it's working. So, for volume and
orderflow trading, the code is launch.
For the trading course, right, if you
want 20% off the beginner to advance
course, the code is 2026, right? And
that ends tonight at midnight. They both
work. I've just double checked them just
in case.
All
right, back to that gray box. You can
see the key levels, right? You can see
the key levels. So, what would I be
looking at the rest of the day? Like we
talked about, if you rewind this to
somewhere around here, one of you was
asking, can we get back up to the highs
of day? And I said, the rotation is from
here to here. And the next rotation will
probably be here to here or maybe if
you're lucky, here to here. And if we
get above that, then we can rotate
higher. But most of the dense volume has
been done here. These are the rotations.
I avoid, as you well know, I avoid
rotational markets. I don't like trading
in them. All right? So, they're not a a
favored market for me. But one of you
was asking about that short. It did work
out for you. You left volume trap, then
you came straight back down to this
side. Now, if they do the same thing
here and they can't reclaim, you might
see the auction resume lower. But like I
said, such low volume, guys. I'd be
very, very, very careful trading into
close today, especially on that
imbalance, on that MOC.
All right, any last questions before I
get out of here? I'm about to leave the
stream and we'll I will maybe I'll be
back Friday, but definitely back next
week, back to normal.
All right, I think we're done. Yeah,
happy new year everyone. Have a great
evening. Have a great evening. Make sure
you spend it with uh friends and family
and loved ones and do all that good
stuff. And uh I won't see you tomorrow.
Remember the market's closed tomorrow.
And I'll probably be pro probably will
be back Friday, but if not, definitely
back on Monday. Hopefully see some of
you uh some of you guys back on stream
then. If not, in the Discord before
then. All right, peace and love
everyone. Take care. Use hard stops.
Don't oversize. Remember, market's going
to be here in a couple days and the next
weeks and the next months and the next
years. You don't need to do anything
stupid. All right, just relax. Just
relax. All right, take care.