morning team. Sorry, running slightly
late there, but hope you're all good.
Hopefully everyone's doing well. Had a
good afternoon session. Wasn't much
going on, and I doubt there'll be too
much going on today, but let's get into
it in case. All right, as always,
starting off in the daily chart. You can
see we're opening up currently inside
previous day. All right, there's your
previous day [snorts] inside previous
week.
And so we're expecting rotation and
chop. If we think about where we're
opening up right at this 20-day, 50-day,
5day overhead, we have a little bit of
supply up here. And we have this low
volume node down here. All right, so
that's what we're aware of. We are very
aware that we can just continue
especially in low volume to build
liquidity between these. All right. If
we get back above this, then we've got a
shot of coming up here. If we get back
below this, then we've got a shot of
filling some of this in this big
imbalance candle here. Until we see a
break uh of one of those sides, we can't
really think about much else, right? The
only other option would be a fail break,
fail break. All right, and just dance
back into range. This is your liquidity
building stage of this market. So, we're
just going to be patient. It is possible
that the market wants to complete
rotation higher but you know this time
of year uh the only way I see us doing
something like that is uh if they start
they will need to go risk on which means
it will all be about tax to be quite
honest with you. Um if they feel like
they can put some tax risk back on into
end of year maybe we get [snorts] that.
But at the moment I'm not seeing it. So
I'm prepared for rotation. I'm prepared
for a very small inside day. And that's
what I'm thinking about. And uh beyond
that we can think about what next. Let's
have a look at the hourly. You can see
right here these key levels. All right,
this is previous week. Uh we're well
inside previous week's value. If we look
at previous days value, right, previous
day's value was set inside. Oh, sorry,
that's too big. Was set inside previous
week's value. All right, that was
yesterday's value. This is previous
week's value. All right, we're not
finding acceptance outside of anything
right now. You can see this is getting
very very tight. So, the [snorts]
options really are uh look above or look
below and fails or continuation trades.
All right, I'm not really interested in
doing anything in here. All right, if if
this is your your jam, all right, if you
if you like trading over these uh you
know, 30 40 rotate point rotations, by
all means, go for it. All right, if
that's your jam, if you love playing the
rotations, [snorts] that's what you
should look at. Um
am I disconnected here? Can you guys
hear me?
Hang on. Is there an issue here?
Yeah, you can hear. Okay, good. It's
just OBS playing up. [snorts] Okay, so
that's that's what I'd be looking at.
I'd be expecting rotation outside of
rotation. You know, you can if we base
and hold, you can look for this push up
to previous week value or a high below
rotation. All right, you have to be
careful with previous day and previous
week. But if we get underneath these and
we base and hold, then you're looking
for a drive into this little gap here
into this week and maybe all the way
down to here. These are the options,
right? So, we're building out liquidity.
It's either going to be this or this. It
doesn't have to be today. It does not
have to be today. I want to make that
clear. Uh if you just look above here,
you can see overnight we've done
absolutely nothing. Right? Low of day
yesterday, high of day yesterday.
There's Asia, there's London. Here's
where we're opening up. Right? were
boxed in. Right? So, you're either
playing an edge, playing an edge, or
waiting for the break, or waiting for
the break, or looking for a fail break,
or looking for a fail break. That's it.
That is it. These my least favorite
markets right now. [snorts]
Okay, let's go up. We're going to look
at some of the divergences at play here.
Just clean this up.
Okay, into ES.
All right. What you need to be aware of
with ES
is the relative strength it has right
now,
right? Is forming a bigger, we just zoom
out of this, a bigger divergence, right?
Here's old all-time highs on the futures
market.
Here's your higher low. There's your
pivot low in November. There's your
higher low. Maybe it has the ability to
do that. That's what ES is looking to
do. If we look at the spiders,
right, you'll see it's already done it,
right? So, the ETFs have already put new
highs in,
right? ETFs have already done it.
[snorts] Futures market haven't. All
right. So, that for me at the moment is
a look above and fail on the spiders.
All right. Where are they trying to go?
Probably the 700s. There's been a lot of
action up here for a long time. It
hasn't been able to do it yet. So, there
is clearly an issue up there on the
spiders. Uh we have gap fill potential
down here. I'd be slightly concerned if
we come down here and start doing this.
This looks pretty drastic as not a very
nice move. But again, because we're in
light volume, I want to be careful. So,
we are starting to see divergence. If
you go back historically and look,
especially when the sales have happened
across the market, you've seen stuff
like this where the spiders oh have done
a false break and where you've had
things like QQQ,
right, having divergence
lower high, lower high, lower high.
Okay, so you want to be careful there. I
don't want to be too uber bullish. We
can just let this play out, especially
in the low volume. I want to have a
quick look at the VIX so you guys
understand where we're at. Right, we're
drifting lower. We can stay down here
for a while. Um, if you look
historically, we're more than happy to
be down underneath these 20s and 18s for
50 plus days. All right, so I'm not it's
not like I'm expecting a huge volatility
spike this side of the year unless
something drastically changes. I just
don't see it happening. Right. I see us
doing sort of stuff like this, which is
that low vol kind of grind move. Um, if
we go and we can have a quick look at
silver. Some of you talking about silver
and I said yesterday, you know, we
expect a bounce back. There's a big
flush out based on the CME stuff. Now,
we have to see how we act when we start
coming into there. Is this the first
time where we see failed follow through,
right? Or was this just a big flush out
based on that margin requirement and
we're going to go again? Right. I would
imagine we just get some form of inside
bar and make a decision in in a day or
two. All right, let's have a look at the
mag quickly. See how we doing for time?
We got to get a move on here. All right,
Apple gapping down
inside yesterday's action. So, no real
edge here inside all of this. Nothing to
do. Amazon, you're going to see the same
story across the board. Slight gap down
inside previous day, right? Two inside
day bars here. Google slight gap down
inside bar. Meta
slight gap down, but it is trying.
Sorry, slight gap up, but it is trying
to get going. So, Meta had some positive
news this morning. I think it bought
uh an AI company or did some chipmaking
deal. I can't remember. I read it very
early this morning. But there has been a
catalyst there for Meta. Microsoft
gapping down inside yesterday. There's a
gap. All right. So, little week there.
Nvidia, that's a gap up. It's trying to
break out outside of yesterday. All
right. If we get above there, it looks
like there's a bit of a gap to fill up
into 190. So, we can set
price alert each side. Let's just set it
above pre-market high.
So, ready for that. There we go. Tesla.
That's a gap up there. So, it's trying
to claw its way back. Remember, we
talked about this level here on Tesla.
All right, that was the box. All right,
that's the drive just missing 500.
There's the failure. Does it come back
and retest that? Big question mark. Does
it retest that? If it does, do they
leave all these buyers trapped and
resell it? Or is this a look below and a
fail and a reclaim back to 500? So, we
can set a price low up here. 5 minutes
left here, folks.
Uh overall, as an equally weighted mag,
let's have a look what we're doing.
Slight gap down inside of yesterday's
junk. All right, so this should be
warning you right now, right? Most
stocks are trading inside right now. Can
have a look at some of the other names.
Oracle
gap up inside of yesterday. Let's have a
look at AMD. A chip starting to catch a
bid. Looks like they're trying to catch
a bid. AMD trying to get back going. So,
that looks like a fairly strong look
below and fail, right? And can it get
going? Question mark. Got a long way to
go to get back up to where it was. Uh,
AVGO, same kind of story. All right,
leaving this range, big squeeze out,
right? Does it fail and come back down
or is that a look below and fail on a
reclaim? Time will tell. We don't know
on some of these. Uh, some of the beta
names started to catch a bit of a bid
this morning. So, let's have a quick
look at those. OQ, uh, sorry, I don't
want to look at that. I all right. Not
got much going on there inside
yesterday. That's a big opening drive
yesterday which sold into lots of people
caught in that. There we go. IQ that's a
decent move starting to try and get
going. I did see some news on that
somewhere this morning. MVTS
no follow through there. RGTI trying to
do the same thing. So these big gamma
exposure names, these move pretty wild.
Lots of people stuck in some of these at
the moment. So I want to see if they can
get going upside and if they're faded
into or not. It's pretty much it. Let's
have a look at this. Uh 30 year
looking dangerous. 42 is the dangerous
bit we've been talking about for a
while. Looking dangerous here, folks.
This is not good for the market. This is
looking very dangerous in my mind. If
this gets going, we should be risk off
on the market. If there's good
correlation, sometimes it takes a moment
or two for it to come through and start
to happen. Let's have a quick look at
move.
The bonds are still dripping lower. and
a round off there. Okay. Well, we will
see. We will see. Probably nothing
happening this side of the year, I would
imagine. But let's see.
There we go. Make that nice and big. All
right. So, not in a rush to do anything
this morning. You can see here's your
edges. Previous day value area high,
previous day value area low. And guess
what? We're probably opening up bang in
the middle of these two right now.
Yes. Absolutely terrible. All right. No
edge to be played from there. Okay. No
edge. So, nice and chill this morning,
guys. We're not expecting lots to
happen. Smash that like button nice and
early for me. I'd love to do some
giveaways again today.
You guys can help me by driving these
numbers up. More likes we do, the
better.
And we got here two minutes into the
open.
All right, there are still some sales on
folks for those of you that are
interested. Apex still 90% sale for one
day pass and uh cheap activation code
FCT there. I think that ends Jan 6th. I
think you still have a 35% sale on on
Lucid. Same code there, FCT
um 40% sale on and TPT code flow zone
there. All the links are underneath if
you're interested. Fun next as well.
Still got a sale on
you sent an an email. Let me have a
look.
I've not seen any email.
Check the spam.
Can you send it for Oh, there you go.
You're in my spam. Is it Ian? Is that
you? That's weird. Why does it keep
putting people in spam?
I see you, my friend. I'm sorry about
that. That's very frustrating for you.
Um
There you go, Ian. I'll just reply to
you now. Sorry about that, my friend.
[snorts]
Okay, here comes the open, folks.
Nice and slow here. All right, nice and
slow here. Just give it a chance. See
how we go. this value area high.
There's a big drive up to value area
high and ES trying to close its gap
above that VWAP.
Let's see if this market has any follow
through today or it just gets its door
slammed in its face. What are we seeing
here? Tesla Z most things pretty much
flat or slightly red. Tesla 0.07% up.
Nvidia 0.07% up. Microsoft 0.14% down.
Meta 0.15% up. What's that crossing
there? Something's crossing. Is that uh
Nvidia trying to cross to get back
above?
Um Google 0.08%
down. Amazon the big loser this morning
0.70% down. Apple flat. So, not a lot
going on, folks. Not a lot going on.
This is what we expected today. We
expected not much to happen, right? So,
don't be forcing your way into anything.
That morning drive
sold back into not seeing much action on
the tape yet and I'm really not
expecting much today, but we'll see. We
will see.
Does anyone want to turn up? How are we
going to act if we get above this gap?
And uh you know the question really is
if they have any intention on going more
than a rotation, do we do something like
this and this or is that sold back into
and we just stay inside here? We will
find out soon enough. We will find out.
I'm certainly not in a hurry to do
anything right now.
Quite happy to sit here,
do some giveaways, have some jokes with
you, and if a trade sets up, fantastic.
But I'm really not expecting it today,
folks. Okay.
95380 you're waiting for. Yeah, I mean
that would be nice. Uh I'm not sure
we're going to get it today, but uh
yeah, I mean anywhere down there 3 340
uh is an old PC down there. Naked PC on
a weekly would be nice, but you know, I
can't imagine we're going to get much
today. I'm going to be honest with you.
I really don't see that happening unless
something changes.
We do have uh PMI coming 9:45. So maybe
we get a bit of movement after that. All
right. So this market trying to get back
up to previous day value area high right
now. What it's trying to do.
Bought for the gap fill. I mean maybe uh
I mean ES hasn't made it yet. We will
see.
We will see.
Just looks like a whole lot of rotation
to me. question is can the market get
going one way or another out of the
rotation.
So try and force this squeeze 32s 3745
is liquidity on the book. Can they get
going up there?
Every shove up so far into these levels
is being sold. It's not even into gap
fill territory. Right. The yellow line
is gapful. Previous day value area high
is the edge of yesterday and through
that well we can look higher if it can
get going. At the moment every little
shove
we're seeing some passive selling into
some buyers. Definitely just got caught
on that last move into 32s.
What's the dotted blue line on my
screen? This one here. This is previous
day value high. Previous day value area
low.
>> [snorts]
>> Uh bookmap is there's no such thing as
uh one minute on bookmap. It it is it's
inside the candles, right? It's not uh
it's not minute by minute.
It's buyer and seller each buyer and
seller showing up.
So, it's uh the seconds if you like or
ticks if you like, but it's not really I
guess it's closer to a tick chart, but
it's just based on how the market's
moving. It's not done over time. They
separate. You can see time on that. They
separate. Right, here's the drive up
into these 30s again where there are
some passive sellers up here. I expect
them to drive through 32s up to 42s at
the moment. Lots of liquidity set up
there looking to get filled. Can they
get going though?
And if they can, can they get into these
45s
where there's previous day value area
high somewhere around here at the
moment? Every shove up into 30 has been
sold by these passive sellers. Every
single shove up. Weakness in the ES. All
right, ES at low of day right now. So
divergence continuing to play out in
this market. This market is doing
absolutely nothing.
Where's VIX?
Just trying to catch a bit of a bid down
here.
Don't like what I'm seeing right now.
Let's see if ES can get back above it
New York open or not.
So bid here is 7:15
and they're going to fill and sell
through this. Can ES get back through
its New York open?
Relative weakness in the ES
complete split in the mag. Tesla half a
percent down, Amazon just under half a%
down, Apple over a third of a percent
down, Nvidia quarter of a percent down,
and then you've got Microsoft flat, Meta
1.45% up, Google half a percent up, like
and uh big divergence like we've talked
about and you're going to continue to
see that, right? You're going to
continue to see that in low volume
markets.
There's like bugger all to do.
[laughter]
You don't need to be here trying to
click.
Do I have a video on the delta on
Trading View? I do not.
It's just showing you delta. It's
showing you the aggressive. All it's
showing you is the who is the main
aggressive participant in that candle.
That's all it's showing you if you want
to follow that.
Okay, guys. I I'm not going to look at
chat for a minute. Just let me if the
market's just opened. you're hammering
in with uh questions right now. Just let
the market calm down. It's only 6
minutes in and I'll get I'll get back to
you. Let me just watch price action for
a minute
into
old PC's down here. ES trying to catch a
bid to get back up to its VWAP and New
York open
VIX down at low of day with ES not able
to move higher at the moment. That's not
a strong look.
We're right down at our New York open
down here. Previous on your controls.
Previous week, previous day,
very slow.
Very, very slow. So, I'd say this
morning buyers have been caught over 21s
so far. That's uh definitely a thing
over 20s. So, we need to get back above
the 20s and hold price. If buyers are
going to have control, uh if you're
going to play the rotation, then you're
watching these point controls underneath
you. Do those hold? If not, you're
watching the previous day value area
low. But definitely this morning, every
buying participant at 20 and above has
got stuck. They had one, two, three,
four, five attempts to get through there
and failed every go at it. And we've got
divergence between the ES and the NQ.
And you've got divergence between the ES
and the VIX for the second day in a row.
[snorts] And you're right in the middle
of this uh value at the moment from
previous day.
Um, all right. Let's catch up.
Do I look at the advance or decline? No,
not really.
Bro, show me your pro I hate I hate even
the way you've worded that. I'm going to
be honest. Bro, show me your profile
settings.
I am using volume profile, but unlike
you where it stay extreme, right, it is
covering candles. I mean,
hi, Alex. Would you mind showing me some
of your profile settings? I'm going to
speak to you like an adult,
bro. Just show me your profile settings.
Right, there you go, bro. There are my
bro settings.
Right. Tick per row two. Anchored VW
placement. Right, bro.
Jesus.
[\h__\h] what chance does humanity have
of surviving if this is uh how we now
interact with each other.
There you go, bro.
Good morning.
[laughter]
Okay,
still we have divergence
sellers coming in very aggressive these
lows right now.
[snorts]
Some big sellers at these lows getting a
little bit caught here. I still think
we're in a bit of no man's land right
now. I want to see us get to one side of
value and see what happens.
Sellers have come in more aggressive sub
700. All right, sub 700 all the way down
to low of day. Buyers are caught above
20s. The reason I'm not interested is
really like what is there to do? We're
talking about 20 point rotation here and
like
let's just see. ES very very weak though
by comparison. It's drifting.
It's drifting down with the VIX drifting
down. I mean, it's it's a big warning
sign if you ask me. I don't want to see
stuff like that. Gives me zero
confidence to place a trade seeing stuff
like that. Vicks at lower day. ES at
lower day. No, thank you very much.
I'm okay.
I'll wait to Jan if it's going to
continue to be like this.
Look at the cues. What we doing? Still
inside of everything.
All right. Some shorts have just been
caught here for sure. Sub sub7 700 down
to lower day. That's where they keep
getting aggressive. You are seeing some
buying activity trying to step in at
705s. They're not getting their way. So,
we've just got no real range to play
with right now. Every pops being sold,
every dips being soaked on passive.
There's no follow through either way
right now. We have to wait until we get
each side of value. Otherwise, there's
really nothing we can do with this.
No edge here. Yes, that's exactly what I
would say. Uh Troy, good morning
everyone. No edge here. Like possibly
they want to rotate back down to value
area low alone if we get through that.
You know the question is like can they
get beyond this or can they get
beyond this? All right. or is this
soaked or do they soak off here or is
this soaked or do they soak off here?
This is the problem. These are like the
more extremes. This is the [\h__\h] you
want to try and avoid if possible in my
mind anyway. These are the areas where I
don't really want to participate in.
And you can see here, look, we've had uh
some big selling at the lows and some
buying at the highs getting caught and
some buyers keep trying to step up here
and push the market high. They're not
getting their way. And the big seller at
the low tried to force the market down,
not getting their way. And you're
talking about 10 20 points here. I mean,
it's just I'm not interested by it. Not
in the slightest.
Exactly. Very low volume as expected.
Very, very low volume. Okay. Maybe now
into previous state value area lows.
Have a look at the mag. Tesla
struggling.
It's interesting. Apple, Amazon, Google,
Microsoft, Nvidia, Tesla, all red. Meta
the only one looking vaguely okay.
I'm unconvinced right now.
>> [snorts]
>> Getting close to previous days area low.
Getting close.
Vick's finding a bit in no man's land.
at the lower of day.
This is very slow, but this is even
slower than yesterday.
Made [clears throat] some money on gold.
Oh, well done. Well, that's uh what
percent up right now.
Rhythmic. Paul saying he's having issues
with rhythmic. Sorry to hear that.
Waiting as a skill. Absolutely is a
skill. Yeah, it's probably the most
important skill you're going to need
trading.
Okay, we've seen a decent amount of
selling come in down here at the lows
under 90s and they're not breaking lower
yet. So, I'm just being aware of that
where the volume is
non-existent really.
They're going to have another take
attempt to get into that value area low
by the looks of it. What they're
attempting to do and they've been soaked
off value area low or in front of it
again.
So every attempt to get down into here,
they are failing to do right now. We're
failing to expand value at the moment.
Doesn't mean they can't do it, but it's
what we're seeing at the moment. ES new
low of day. Fix at low of day. Oh jeez.
Jeez Louise,
I have a question for you, Alex. I have
100k Apex funding and two 50k accounts.
Can I copy them? Yep, you can. Yeah. No,
no, you can copy any account together.
All right, here comes previous day value
area low. See if they defend it or not.
If they don't, then it's possible we go
down to previous day low into sort of
47s and previous week value into 40s and
previous week open into 35. So, it all
depends how we act once we get to this
edge. Are we going to bid off this edge
or we going to see some follow through?
The follow through won't be huge. Might
be 30 plus points, but we will see.
Moment they can't even get through it.
[snorts]
Here come the sellers. They're trying to
step on the tape. There's been a passive
buyer here at 80 all day. So why I say
all day? this morning. Once he moves,
might see a bit more of a flush down
into value. There we go. So, he's
starting to move and value is 73s. If we
get through 73s, you got to be careful
for fail breakout versus breakout. And
50s or 48s will be the next spot. All
right. So, here comes the move into
value. Previous day value area low is
right here. See, there's a slight bid
off it. That blue line unsurprisingly,
you know, bulls will want to defend
that. If they are unsuccessful in
defending that, you will see a wash
through. There you go. They defended it
very well.
Well, someone just stepped on the tape,
didn't they? They said, "Fuck off. We're
covering here." And this is what happens
when you get low volume.
Hilarious. Absolutely hilarious.
So, we said we will wait to see what
happens. Well, [laughter] I can't I
can't do anything with that. I'll tell
you that much.
>> [snorts]
[laughter]
>> Let's see. Someone doesn't want it below
that, that's for sure.
Still watching ES, not through New York
Open yet. There's divergence everywhere
here, folks. [snorts]
It is messy out here. Very very messy.
So maybe down into this imbalance uh
which starts at 90 and goes all the way
down to 82s if they are actually willing
to hold. But there's no one on the tape
right now. I I'm not trusting anything.
and uh value area high on the session
currently at these tens. All right, so
we're you're really looking at
30 points at the moment in this session
unless we can start getting through this
and accelerating up here which would be
nice. They are now trying to do there's
VWAP. Can we find a bid now? This is the
question. Remember the buyers this
morning have been stuck at 20 and above.
Yeah, definitely 20 and above is where
the buyers have been stuck so far this
morning.
again. I mean, I don't see you again
have to be big bollocks to just bid
there with nothing. And uh if you did
have the big bollocks or you bid rebid
this, you're trimming some here and then
you're looking for this now. All right,
someone's in a [\h__\h] hurry all of a
sudden. ES has got going. All right, ES
just filled the gap. So, just be careful
of that. We've had gap fill on ES. Now
your next target if you are long is into
the value above. All right. So gap fill
for us would be 40s gap fill above. And
if you if you're really lucky you get
going into 20s and maybe even all the
way up there if they're if they're going
to turn the booster jets on today. We
will see. We'll just have to see exactly
what we thought about here. We're going
to have to see how we act up here right
into the other edge.
So see how we act into previous days
value area high here.
So just a rotation, right? One side of
the previous day's value to the other
side. Dshape yesterday, we're trading an
inside bar. It's a rotation until it
proves otherwise. Okay, it's all we're
looking at.
Gap filled on the ES. Next stop, stop
step stop. Get your words out, mate.
Will be 57s. Break through 57s. Maybe
then we can look for the fiveday on ES.
So here goes the cues. Can they get up?
They've just closed the gap. So once
they got back above the 20s, remember
buyers were stuck at 20s we talked about
this morning. Those buyers are now let
out. So buyers were stuck at 20s. All
right. Oh my gosh. Right here. They're
getting let out. Let me see if I can get
you on to see my buyers were stuck in
here in this big node here. 20s. All
right. And can we move back above that
now is the question. The answer right
now is yes. There's previous days value
area high. Are we going to look to
auction above this or are they going to
sell this at this point? Now that's all
we're thinking about now. Can we hold a
bid above this? Come and clean out
GlobeEx high time frame algo get into
23s, right? And if we get acceptance,
can we get up into here? So the plays
right now are very simple. Can we build
some structure here to come here and
here? Or is this going to be look above
and we're going to come straight back
down and keep rotating in yesterday's
profile? That's the option. Those two
things are the option right now.
>> [snorts]
[cough]
>> Watching this guy for days. All I see is
him talking. Never saw
trader yet live. Lol.
I'm not even going to respond to that.
You can [\h__\h] off and uh watch whoever
you want, mate.
I'm not even going to respond to that.
Good luck. Good luck on your trading
career. I can tell you now, it's not
going anywhere with that attitude
because you're not willing to learn.
You've got zero shots if you're going to
jump around looking for someone to
babysit you and hold your hand without
the ability to listen and learn. What
I'm giving you here is more than you're
going to get anywhere else. Trust me.
But you do what you want.
Okay, let's see then. No acceptance
above value. Are they going to offer
rotation or do we see continuation up
into here? Wait to see some volume steps
on the tape here. [snorts] If not, then
we're going to drift back down into
those 20s. Remember, 20s is where the
buyers got stuck this morning. It's
where they came back in for the
acceleration. You'd want to see them
hold above 20s if you're going to look
for a continuation. So if big if you
would want to see a buildout into here
if we're going to look for acceptance
above all these TPS failing to hold 20s
would mean more buyers just get trapped
above 20s and we are going to continue
to do a small rotation. So we're bullish
if we can look for this. If we fail to
hold 20s I'd expect this to be priced
back in again. All right. And we haven't
got much room or much ATR to play with.
So just be aware of that.
>> [snorts]
>> Are we looking more bullish? Yes,
potentially. But uh we've got to get
acceptance above value. Right. So, we're
currently the longer we're up here, we
will move current days value up. But
just remember, all that matters is where
those buyers came in. Right? Can they
stay aggressive? Can they get something
like this? All right. If they can't,
then this is a look above value again.
If they can't hold this, then guess
what? We're going to go right back down
because this is what we've already done
today. And this is what we did
yesterday. All right, so we're
condensing inside of yesterday at the
moment.
Here's the 20 check that we just talked
about. This is what's going to be key
now is do some passive buyers start to
absorb here into these 20s. If the
answer is yes and they can get back
above value, it's got a rebid
possibility higher. If the answer is no,
then we're going to go right back inside
current day's value because we're
already in previous days value. So
question is, can they hold 20s here? The
answer at the moment is they are trying
to offer a bid here at 25. So the volume
is so small folks. It's very very small,
but they are trying to hold above the
20s like we just talked about. But
again, for that absolute [\h__\h] in chat,
you know, if you can't decipher what
I've just given you, you've got no
chance.
[\h__\h] in chat. I quite like the rhyme of
that. There's another [\h__\h] in chat. All
right, let's see then if they can absorb
around here and get acceptance back
above previous days value or not.
Okay, here they go. They are trying.
Guess what we are looking at at the
moment? Looking to see if we can drive
through and find acceptance above PDC,
above previous day value area high. Is
there a move here? Big sellers came in,
well, not big, but big in this session
came in at 30s and below and didn't find
acceptance lower. So, at the moment,
we're looking bullish. If we can find a
squeeze out here. Looking good. And I
want to see them clear up to 55s because
we've got lots on the book here to 55s.
Here we go. Here we go.
Really nice hold reclaim. Can we get
through this? All right. So, I'd be
tping out on any drive into this. Now,
if you took any of this soak in here,
right, you want to be very careful
because we're so light on volume. But if
we hold this TP1, TP2, TP3, and the full
rotation will be up into 830s. Here we
go.
Didn't give me anything. Shut the [\h__\h]
up, you [\h__\h]
[snorts]
All right, there's TP1 into the orange
bars.
Oh, it's always nice to end the year
with a complete knob end.
Right, let's see if we can keep going
here. It'd be nice if we could. So, this
is GloEx and a higher time frame algo
that I use. This is based on higher time
frames, uh, EMA, fib EMA off higher time
frames. If we can get a squeeze into
gray, it'd be great. Here we go. Locking
some in here through this. And really
now it's just can we get all the way up
into sort of 830s that would be
fantastic. All right, so we have
liquidity in this gray box. All right,
this is a big pivot. So, you want to
peel some off.
Oh, this is going to be trade of the
day. I'm telling you, there's not going
to be anything better than this coming
today. All right, let's see if we can
get going then. If we get lucky, we get
up into here now, folks.
I've been here two days. I want him to
hold my dick while I go to the toilet.
Get the [\h__\h] out of here.
Beautiful move, guys. Make sure you're
trimming some into this runners only.
Now, if we get lucky, we will get up
into here, right? But remember, we're in
light volume day. We don't know if we're
going to get that. So, we're going to
protect ourselves. We're going to assume
we're not. Finally, we're getting some
confluence here. VIX moving down with
the ES moving up. So, finally, those
things are aligned. They haven't been
aligned yesterday. They weren't aligned
this morning, but we're seeing a small
amount of alignment.
They're still offering here at 75s and
80s which is good. So they are providing
some liquidity here. Let's have a look.
800 817 is on there. 840 850. So it's
good. They are providing some liquidity.
We just want to see if buyers are going
to be aggressive here. But we had the
best buy of the day there. All right.
Unfortunately, you know, I'm not going
to bid down here and just wait. I would
have loved to have been a buyer down
there if it just done something like
this. But this was the move here where
we backtracked to 20 and we're getting
going now. And we called it out ahead of
time. Told you what I was looking at and
why. And uh this is the next stop. So
let's just see. Really nice here. We
have some old imbalances here just so
you're aware from yesterday. So uh I'd
say sort of 77 to 80s and then through
that 800s.
So make sure you pay yourself.
[cough]
I know. I know. I know. I know, guys.
It's uh trust me, it drives me more
insane than you when I sit here
literally calling level two and tape out
and and order flow as it moves, which is
I'm telling you now, it's a skill. You
don't get that skill overnight. It takes
time. And uh I do it for free and still
I get questions. It's incredible. There
we go.
It's okay.
It's okay. Right. Positive attitude. All
right. And all we're seeing now, you
just want to be careful. You want to see
rebids come in at these same levels,
right? So structurally, we have a low
volume node here. Now, you want to see
buyers protect this, right? So, we'd
like it, if we're going to go higher, we
want a bear trap. But remember, this is
a liquidity level. We've talked about
this. This is from yesterday and from
last week, right? So, if we're going to
go higher, uh, you definitely don't want
it beneath this. And you'd want sort of
a little bare trap like that if you're
going to hold on. What you don't want to
see is a volume shelf built out. If you
remember the play yesterday that I took
short, what you do not want to see is a
big volume shelf being built out here.
All right? And then a failure underneath
and a rotation. So, make sure you're
locking in. That's why that gray box is
here. We know it's a big liquidity
level. We've just traded into it. Buyers
must step up now in front of previous
day's value area high. Ideally, a bear
trap in low volume and that your
continuation. Do not let it build out a
big fat shelf and then reject and come
lower and be holding on to your buys.
All right? You don't do not want to see
that. If we get back underneath value,
all right, if we're going to do this
move,
that is a fade. All right, we must bulls
must hold previous days value high in my
mind if they're going to rotate to
previous week value, which is up here,
right? They must hold this. They don't
hold that, not interested. I'm not going
to play in this. This is death zone,
right? We don't play in there. Well,
Alex doesn't play in there. You guys can
do whatever you want, but I'm not
playing in there.
>> [snorts]
>> Nice kitty saying thanks Alex done for
the day. What about full rotation down?
I mean yeah I mean technically if if
this is you could say you could argue if
this is a look above and fail especially
if they build out enough liquidity right
and then they fail the back test of this
and you could argue for this and this
and this absolutely could argue that
move. I'm not going to deny you that.
I'm not going to deny you that.
So buyers have a shot now and if they
don't hold this, that will be the end of
it and I'll be out on the runner.
Do I do this every day? Yes, my friends.
9:15 Eastern time, Monday to Friday.
Okay, about to cut the runner here.
Unfortunately, wanted to give it a
chance in case it wanted to keep going
to those. What was it? 830s. Trying to
remember. Yeah, 830s.
I still got a chance to hold it here.
So, I'm not going to rebid this. Not
yet. VIX also, by the way, closed this
gap and is founding a bid here. So, want
to be careful. All right, out this now.
Can always rebid if I want.
Where am I seeing buyers or sellers
further out based on level two? Yes,
level two, mate. Using bookmap. There's
the bid. Oh my god. Stopped me out by
[\h__\h] point or two. [snorts]
All right. I'm happy to rebid if it
firms up. Not before that.
Yeah, W's in chat. If any of you got
that with me from 20, what do we get?
20s to almost 80s is not bad. 50 60
points you probably locked in. I mean,
in this market, we'll take it. We will
take it.
Alex, did I see a big buyer at what did
you say? 76.
Um, I mean, we can have a look on here
together.
There's a big seller coming in now.
Let's see.
76.
Probably at the end of the auction
you're talking about. I mean, I wouldn't
say big. A 61 lot and a 39 lot. Yeah.
And then you saw the rotation. So, if
you just think about this, this came in
here, right? And buyers got stuck at the
highs, sellers took over. They had one
more retest at this level, failed,
sellers took over. We're going back down
to value. And we're seeing the same
thing at these lows now. the other way
around. So the new box, think about
this, starting to be boxed in, right?
Sellers at the low, buyers at the highs.
We're waiting to see if we get a
acceptance and a break back out above
this or break below. If we go below,
we're going to go back inside value and
that can be a rotation down. So you can
see these passive buyers sitting on the
book right now trying to absorb from 30
to 25. Right? That's where the passive
buyers are sat right now. Everything in
here is choppy while they make their
mind up. Remember, this is value area
high, previous day value area high in
here. The question is, did do these
buyers do a little look below, fail,
absorb, and then send it back up, or are
sellers going to come with strength here
for a break? Right? So, that's what
we're looking at when we're looking at
the level two at the moment. [snorts]
So, into this pacifier at 35, if they
snap him, there's a 10point shove down
very, very quickly. So, he's starting to
be filled, but we're talking about small
size here, folks. When we look at the
book at the moment, we're talking about
45 lot on the book. We're not talking
about hundreds of lots absorbing the
tape.
Lots of you getting the wind there. Nice
work, folks. Nice. Nice work.
Still absorbing around here for now. But
you can see you got to be careful here
because we're building out volume. All
right, you can see this.
All right, buyers will be looking for
this. Sellers will be looking for this
break below. We're thin down here. All
right. So, if sellers win this, they
complete rotation. If buyers win this,
then they will try and get through the
gray box and get up into there. Those
are the moves, right? Those are the
moves currently available.
[snorts]
[groaning]
Who does not want to learn? Please leave
the chat. We want to take care of our
families and become best version of
ourselves in 2026. So, please either
sit and learn with us or get out. Yeah,
quite right. Happy birthday. Yeah, happy
birthday, J Source.
I think I asked a question, but the Dom
level two is that bookmap? Yeah. Uh, it
is bookmap, my friend. I'm Well, that's
how I'm choosing to read it, but it it
it's up to you, right? So, I'm looking
at bookm
right. So on the left is my heat map. On
the right is my level two or DOM. All
right. So I use both. This is the main
thing I'm looking at is delta. All
right. When I'm looking for outlying
delta, my big big participants who are
stuck. That's uh where my edge comes
from. I'll be honest with you. You don't
have to use bookmap. It's just what I
choose to use.
What would I need to get back long? Uh
I'd need a strong reclaimed levels. So,
I'm not I'm not bidding in here. Oh,
don't move that. Jeez. Need that one.
Right. I don't want to bid in here cuz
we're not finding acceptance above
value. So, I'd need to see something
like this to get back long. All right.
Maybe a trigger here. And maybe I'd
consider an ad up there. Although, it'd
be very risky. Right. Right now, we
cannot get above previous days value.
So, it is possible that they rotate all
the way down to here. Right. And if they
get acceptance under this, then we've
got previous day's value and previous
week's value. All right, this would be
exactly the same as what we've done up
here if they do uh this move here. All
right, so this move here is this move
here. So it's a mirror, right? If you
think about this as 50% previous day
value area high, previous day value area
low at the moment, no acceptance above
above here. If they reclaim, maybe they
go for acceptance, but if they can't
reclaim, then the rotation is possible
because we're in a rotational market,
which is why I said you must take profit
into here and here. We're not in a
trending market, right? We're not in a
guaranteed trending market. So, we
position for the trend. We take profit
at key levels and we wait to see if it
wants to trend. We don't know if it's
going to offer that. It didn't offer it.
Now, what are we doing? Yesterday
was what? A rotation
here.
Today currently is a rotation here. We
are what? We are inside
bar on the daily. So let's think about
that
daily bar
volume and value yesterday.
Volume and value today so far condensed,
right? We're condensed. So we have to
play edge to edge take profit. Wait to
see if we find acceptance. Edge to edge,
take profit, wait to see if we find
acceptance lower. That's all we're
doing. We are creating liquidity for the
bigger move.
[snorts]
Uh no this uh the indicator you're
looking at is my frozone pro. It's not
free. All right. But it's not just a
ribbon. All right. So you get uh what
comes in that opening range uh globeex
initial balance uh multi-time frame
algos uh this box up here to tell you
what type of condition we're in. Right
now we're in liquidity building
condition that I keep talking about. Uh
so a version of it comes free with the
course if you do the uh 20our course
beginner to advance. Otherwise you can
upgrade to the pro version there as
well.
Yeah. Well that's it. um stock stock uh
genius USA I think that is starting to
look exactly the same pattern from the
last two days it's it's just a rotation
right so it's a rotation
yes quite right a lot of you saying very
similar to yesterday that's it because
we're we're back inside value we're not
on remember if if you joined from the
beginning of of the day right just
remember the beginning of the day the
first thing I always look at what are we
inside previous week we're inside
previous day we expect rotation We're at
the mean. We're not above this. We're
not below that as well, right? We're not
underneath this for continuation. We're
not above this node for continuation.
So, everything's saying build liquidity.
Absolutely everything in this market
from a weekly, from a daily, from the
EMAs, from volume, even on this higher
time frame daily chart is saying build
liquidity. From there, we went to an
hourly chart.
The hourly chart is quite clearly
showing you that we are currently inside
of previous days, previous week's value
and we're inside of previous days value.
So that's also telling you what build
liquidity. Okay? So you have to wait. We
talked about this earlier in Discord.
Those looking for this move here, right?
You have to understand that this has to
build it all out and you have to be very
aware of that move there. You do not
want to get caught in that. So you want
to see big break if you're going to look
for that move and a trade into an old
weekly value and point of control.
Fantastic. This was probably where
higher time frame buyers show up if they
do until that point. Got to be careful
because this is what the market is going
to do. All right. And once we use these
players, we can get a break.
Right? It's important that you start on
the higher time frame and work your way
down so you understand where you are at
versus the big players.
Rotation starting to take place now. So
those of you who like the rotation,
right, we keep failing this. We talked
about this. We will probably if we fail
this, we will probably come down into
here. Watch this low volume node here.
And then previous day point control.
Previous day value area low. Previous
week value area low. Right. I'm going to
avoid this like the plague. Like I
always say, avoid it like the plague.
It's just for me because I don't like
playing in rotation.
Curious around previous day value high
and previous day value low. Is that an
indicator is just manually set by me?
Yeah, I just draw it on, mate. Yeah. So,
I measure it out the previous day and
then I just put my horizontal lines on.
And really, you only ever need to do it
once, right? So, if you do your weekly
and daily levels, you set your weekly
levels on a Monday or a Sunday and you
do move your daily levels each day. So,
you just draw them once and then you
move them. It's not too hard. But yeah,
I don't have an indicator for it.
Do I follow market cycles at all or just
price action? my cycle has us going down
into Jan 5th or 8th. Uh, no, I don't
really follow cycles. I might I might
look at historical data and see where
edge is historically, where, you know,
where the market is likely to go into a
fade, but I don't pay too much
attention. Price and volume is king for
me. Cycles might work better for uh
swing positions if you're if you're more
focused.
So, anyone who took that look above and
fail
into my gray box
and decided they were going to fade
against value. All right, these are
coming into your TP1s. This is your TP2.
These are your TP3s. All right. So,
anyone who got short into I don't guess
730s, you need to be starting to partial
out now into these lows and see if you
find acceptance underneath these now.
But here's previous day and previous
week point of control. So, these are
areas of value from the previous week.
These were the most fair areas of value
from the previous week. It is also our
current value area low on the day. So,
you must be taking some profit here. I
don't use Elliot wave. No,
don't use anything like that. I am aware
of like two counts and three counts and
I don't really care about nine counts or
anything like that, but uh I understand
them. I don't use them.
I'm done for the day. Got long after the
open 20 point. No,
not planning to play D profiles.
I'm with you there. Fall forward.
That's a man
speaking my language. [laughter]
That's a man speaking my language. I'm
with you there, my friend.
Uh, whatever works for you. Stop genius.
It does. Look, just because I don't do
it, I talk about this all the time. Just
because I don't do it doesn't mean it's
doesn't work. There's many, many, many,
many ways to trade. Someone was asking
me yesterday why I don't use um VWAP
bands. It's just because I don't. It's
not because they don't work or anything
like that. It's just because I don't use
them. I have my own system. Here you go.
Starting to see follow through here now
and back towards this previous
[clears throat] day value area low.
Right. So, here's GlobeEx. If you see
follow through down into here, the next
levels will be down into here. So,
anyone who took that shot is actually
looking pretty good for you. But I would
be making sure you're covering some uh
Hello, Mr. Mouse. Here, here, and here.
I use pain. Yeah, quite right. It's
exactly what I use. [laughter]
Exactly what I use.
What indicators can we use to mark
previous day values?
Uh right here,
uh fixed range volume profile, right?
And you just draw it on just draw it on
from 9:30 to 4:00. That's all you need
to do.
So, it's a tool rather than an an
indicator, right? It's a tool.
No worries.
There is a big seller here. First time
I've seen a seller of size. 460 lot up
at 710. Let's see if he's actually a
player or not.
Let's see if he's a player. That's some
serious size compared to what we've seen
on the tape this week. Let's see if this
guy's legit.
That is uh
market wants to go and see if he's
legit. Take that much. There is an
imbalance up there. There's an
imbalance. 707s.
Is this guy real?
Yes, relative weakness right now. Vick
starting to get going upside. We are
just trading around the old point of
controls right here. I want to see if
this player is real up here or if he
lifts or is he pinning this market down?
That last shove up. We've got buyers
caught
into sevens. Uh their pain point really
is up around 704 to 707. And this player
is just dangling up here at the moment.
So I'm waiting to see if we shove up
into him and if he's legit and if buyers
get caught and if we continue to sell.
Not that I want to take it. I'm just
interested to see what he does. You can
see this liquidity being built out here.
So big shelf now being bu built out
here. So buyers are trying to come in
and get this move back into here. Let's
see if this guy's legit. We're about to
tap into him. We can see him on bookmap.
No, he's not. He's just pulled it. So,
he's a absolute fraud with massive size
and we're into this imbalance we just
talked about. And uh D-shape continuing
to play. So, hopefully you've locked
some in. No guarantee you see uh lower
lows here. I'm not going to say you
can't, but uh
it's a rotational market, right?
There's the imbalance tap and there's
buyers caught in that imbalance. We just
talked about it 707s. There's the
imbalance tap and there is buyers caught
in it. Now, can they come back down to
85s and come underneath
uh what's this PC where we are right
now? Can they get acceptance lower now?
They've got I tell you what, sellers
have got a chance here for the first
time today. They've got to move
underneath this volume. All right. If
this is a look above and fail into the
imbalance at 707,
this is a look above and fail. If
sellers can leave this, they've got a
chance for this rotation here. They are
trying. They
are trying.
Where did that buyer's pain come in? 98s
up to 707s. [snorts]
Where are we trading at? 87s and
spiders. Where's 85? Long way down.
[snorts]
Bit of spoofing going on in this tape
here by this seller. So, he had big size
in at 707s. He pulled his size. He came
back on with smaller size at 707. He's
now lifted to 22. So, someone's uh
someone's playing silly buggers, just so
you guys are aware.
But sellers have got a chance here. If
they if they can come in with size here
and give a flush moment because we've
built out lots of volume, there's a big
if,
but they've got a chance, but they need
to break away from this. They need to
leave this guy trapped and they need to
do this to complete the rotation.
They've got a chance. I'm not in
anything. I'm just saying what I'm
seeing. I'm not in any of this. I traded
the long up here and that's it.
So, there's point of control T again
here. sellers being aggressive here,
trying to move lower. So, this is the
chance that they have. We just talked
about it. Can they move aggressively
underneath this? We have an imbalance
here from 947 this morning. So, they've
got to get under
Where are these last pain points? Right.
The sellers from this morning are caught
under 78. All right. The sellers from
this morning are caught under 78. So, if
we can expand under 78, sellers will
really start accelerating. big if button
maybe. But that's what I'd be looking
at. [snorts]
I can show you what I'm looking at. Give
you an idea of it.
Right there is an imbalance down to this
guy. You can see these are this was the
end of the auction this morning. This is
the sellers who are caught.
Right? So these guys will be getting out
right now. We had an imbalance up here
into 707s from here.
Okay. We pushed and tracked buyers into
this. You're not seeing on a five minute
on on this, but I am seeing it on my
other chart. It was a uh 26 lot delta
lot who got caught here. You can see it
right here. Right on this spike. Sellers
need to take control and resell this and
get these guys out. Otherwise, this will
continue to develop in here. I don't
want to trade in this. But if sellers
are going to take control, this is the
chance that they've got to do it. Big
if, but that's what I'm just seeing.
Yeah, Joe. I mean, the only thing I've
taken, Joe, was this here. I said this
morning 20s was the level. As long as we
hold in front of 20s, there's possible
for a drive up into here and here. All
right. So, I was bidding small size in
here. I got more aggressive in here and
I was selling through this and then I
held right and stopped back out when we
came back into it. I held in case we
came up here. That's the only thing. If
you're going to wait for me for when I
buy and sell, you're going to miss lots
of trades because I'm very very fussy.
So, I even told you like if you want to
fade this back down to here, you can. If
you rewind the tape and do it. I didn't
take this. So, if you're waiting for me
to tell you, hey, I'm selling here,
well, you're going to be waiting a long
time because I'm not taking it. Sorry,
[clears throat]
I don't know what to tell you.
[snorts]
Big battle here. It's point of control
on the day. Point of control from
yesterday. Point of control from
previous week. Huge battle here taking
place. Let's have a little look at the
mag. Tesla7%
down. Nvidia half a percent down.
Microsoft 0.14% up. Meta the big winner
today off that news. It did had a have a
catalyst 1.29% up. Google 0.15% down.
Amazon third of percent down. Apple
0.40%
down.
And this shelf here continuing to
develop. I just be careful here.
This is the battle. All right. Look
above and look below. Nothing's played
out yet. Right. If bulls win, can you
can imagine up here? Bears win. Well, we
probably come and take these out. Both
things are possible right now. So,
that's why I'm saying both
because we're at a key level from
previous week, previous day, current
day.
[snorts]
What do I use to get footprint? I
actually watch it on Ninja Trader. Um, I
use Cydi, but uh, if you want it on, um,
Trading V, you can't get it. If you're
paying paying for the pro, [snorts] uh,
you need to
come up to here where you have your
types of candles and bring it down to
volume footprint,
right? That's how you get it if you're
having the pro account.
It is pretty good. I actually quite like
it on Trading View. It's pretty decent.
Okay, the chop continues.
The chop continues.
[snorts]
We've stalled out here, haven't we?
We're in uh
key area and stalling out.
>> [snorts]
>> How do you confirm breakouts? Well, I'd
rarely play breakouts. I play pullbacks.
But if you were going to confirm
breakouts, I'd probably be looking
things like volume to show you that it's
on side with you. CBD to show you the
aggressives are there on side with you.
if I was going to play a breakout, but
uh I'm I'm not a breakout trader.
That's what I'd be looking for. And I'd
be looking for it early in the rotation.
So, if you're looking for a breakout of
a key level, if it was a horizontal
level, you're looking for multiple taps
into it over multiple sessions before
you look for that breakout. If you're
looking for something like, you know, a
flag break on a higher time frame, you
want to be looking for leg one or two,
not leg three and above. All right,
here's the rotation back off the Dshape
into the middle into view up. And if
they want to go right back up to the
other side, they will now.
Starting to break through now. So this
rotation continuing.
So bears had the chance to take over
there. They failed to do what they
needed to do, which was get a strong
close and let these guys out of pain
that we talked about and that I showed
you on footprint. These bears down here
from this morning are in pain. All
right. And they got out break even or
close to break even causing this spike
up. Here's the shelf. We talked about
this. If they want to run it all the way
back up to here, they absolutely can.
There's your VWAP. That's midpoint. All
right. This continues to be an option.
This continues to be an option.
Everything's possible because we're
inside this. [snorts] All right.
inside this.
[cough]
No, I have a course on footprint.
There's nothing on my YouTube.
[snorts]
Mr. Big Player is back. 817 lot at 7:30.
What is he doing? That's some serious
size to be spoofing around with.
Yeah, exactly. That is some serious size
to be spoofing about with. All right,
back to point of controls again.
Everything condensed. Previous day,
previous week, and current session. This
is fair value for the day where we are
now.
The same things are possible here,
folks, that we've been over this
morning. All right. Exactly the same
things.
Yeah. Nacho is Miguel. Nacho is Miguel.
[laughter] I think Adam dared to do it,
so he did.
We are indeed. Yeah, we're inside
previous week and we're inside previous
day. We are. Yeah, we're inside
everything right now, my friend.
[laughter]
[snorts]
Waiting to see if we have a breakaway
here either side.
Me neither. Never heard of it.
All right, guys. Over 600 of you
watching. Smash that like button for me.
We will do some giveaways on stream. We
do giveaways every day here.
streams have been a bit slower with they
will start picking up when the volume
picks up and that will probably be next
year folks. But I'm here for it.
[snorts] Here
[snorts]
we go. Here's previous week point
control being tested. This is the
question. Are bears going to take
control and let those bears from early
morning out?
Are they going to let the bears from
early morning out? If so, if they let
them out, then I think this is possible
down here. It's a big if. So, we got
guys caught in here.
Question is, can they let them out
and get some cover points down here? And
if they get acceptance under previous
days value, then they come to here. If
we don't, then this is a mirror image of
this, right? You need to be aware of
this play here. This would be a mirror
image. So, you can see at the moment, we
built liquidity. We drove up, we failed
to get acceptance. We came down, we
built liquidity, we might well drive
down, might well fail to have
acceptance. So, you could probably split
this day or this session in half here
and they would look exactly the same
mirrored and reversed kind of thing for
now.
If if we do this next next leg that is,
what is this guy doing up at 7:15? It's
very odd.
On the book, off the book, on the book,
off the book.
Uh, sloth. Everything for everything for
the DOM, for um, rotation, for
footprint, for bookmap is in the new
course in the volume and order flow
course. Everything's there. Um, you get
a discount because you're already a
member, mate. So just check check in
Discord. There is a you get a 50%
discount
because you're you're an OG member.
Welcome Anthony. Thanks for joining.
Big buyer sitting at 660 is there? Let
me have a look. Uh can't see anyone.
I must add I lost lost $6,000 prior to
joining Flowzone community, but I've
been making it back my draw down. Hey,
nice. That's good to hear.
Good to hear.
Hey, I just want to say thank you for
doing this information you're providing
for free is changing lives. Oh, thanks,
man. Do I do personal coaching? I don't.
I don't. We do do like group sessions in
Discord, but I don't do one-on- ones. I
just don't have the time, guys.
I don't have the time.
It' be nice if I did. I actually love
teaching more than anything else.
[snorts] Find it very rewarding,
but I just don't have the time for
one-on- ones. But, uh, we do do like
hour or twohour sessions in Discord. I'm
trying to do them more regularly for the
members to join in. [snorts]
Inverse head and shoulders. I I don't
see an inverse head and shoulders here.
I'm not sure where you see it. Where's
your head?
Where's your head? I see maybe a head
and shoulders, you could argue. I can't
see an inverse right now. [snorts]
All right, they're going to try and have
another attempt here to leave volume. It
just looks very messy in here. Just you
you do well to sort of leave this alone
for now, I'd say.
Initial [snorts] balance now set as
well, folks. So, we're currently trading
inside of value inside of initial
balance. Where's our opening drive this
morning? Where's the first 15 minutes?
Inside the opening range. We're inside
of absolutely everything you can
imagine. So, if any of you did my free
video from the weekend on checklists,
well,
here's your checklist for a rotation.
So, if you're a trend trader and you
hate rotation, then um today's checklist
was it right inside the day, inside
previous value, inside your orb, inside
your initial balance, inside current
day's value. What's that screaming at
you? No trend.
If a spoofer shows they're spoofing, how
come they keep getting away with it when
it's obvious? Well, sometimes, mate,
sometimes rather than a spoofer, it can
be a liquidity provider. Um, so what
you're seeing is uh is an institution
providing liquidity and if they don't
get taken, they don't get taken. It's
also very hard to prove like
what's the difference between a spoof
and me putting an order on and saying,
"Oh, I don't like that order anymore."
Right. So, that's the other side of it.
Yeah, I would say on on the on the
hourly. Yeah, I would agree. But I can't
see an inverse. Someone someone was
calling for an inverse head and
shoulders. I was saying like you could
see you could argue definitely you could
argue potentially building a right
shoulder on the hourly. You could argue,
you know, potentially building liquidity
here. All I was saying is someone was
saying inverse and shoulders. I I can't
see personally where that inverse is.
If price goes down, why would it release
those pre previous sellers? They don't
have stop losses. Yes, exactly. Right.
So, if you were a short seller down
here, right, you'd be amazed how many
people would not stop out, but they
won't. This isn't a big move for a lot
of people, right? So, when they come
back down and if they start getting out
here, they get break even. There's your
push. And if they stay and hold, all
right, and they get let out under here,
then they might well add to their
position.
But yeah, not not everyone is
disciplined enough to stop out. Some of
them clearly were cuz we got these
shubs. But you would be surprised. You'd
be very surprised.
[snorts]
No worries. No worries. Mr.
Mr. Grant is that sorry. Trying to get
used to all your names again since it
changed. [snorts]
Okay. So, they're having another
attempt. these sellers back into this
buying balance down here.
Yes, back into its initial balance low
down here.
The question is, do we break away from
this level? Right. We could draw a
little shelf on here if you want. If you
really really want, right, do we break
away from this or not?
>> [snorts]
>> Is there a difference between OB if I
use rhythmic data or other feeds?
OB, what do you mean? What's OB?
There shouldn't there's there shouldn't
be any any difference in any price in
any volume or order block. No, I mean
there's an order block is just an area
of where you built liquidity and
normally a pullback bar. Um there won't
be a difference. Remember all futures
are on centralized exchanges. So all
data, it doesn't matter where you're
getting that data from. It comes from
the CME. Comes from CME if we were
trading NQ and ES. So it's centralized.
So everything you see is the same on any
single platform.
Order book. Yeah. I don't know. It's
still the same, right? So, like I said,
it's centralized.
You can't they can't It's not like
trading
spread bets and stuff like that. Book
just got very thin with this guy leaving
up here. Some Someone's playing silly
buggers at the moment.
Yeah, order order book has the same
answer. It's all the same, guys.
Centralized exchange, right? Futures are
on centralized exchange. Same if you're
trading gold or silvers, you're trading
on ComX, centralized exchange. Okay,
they are trying they're desperately
trying to leave and let these players
out. They're trying to sell. They're not
doing a very good job, but they they're
trying to do it. ES came underneath its
IB is back inside its IB. It's just a
question of acceptance now at this
point.
Yeah, I agree, Coop. That's uh how I
feel, my friend. Well, if we're if we're
doing nothing in 25 minutes, we'll do
some giveaways instead. Have some fun.
[sighs]
[snorts]
Back to this shelf. Top side of the
shelf.
I noticed that the New York session sets
the stage for the rest of the session to
be either bullish or bearish.
Today it's bearish session, so any
pullback to the upside is only a
correction. Um, I don't think so.
I mean, the New York session goes all
the way till 4:00 and uh, lots of things
change. I think if you,
how can I put this? You might well be
looking for a pattern that's not there.
Be very careful.
So, drive out of this now. And if they
leave this, I mean, there's a little bit
of volume here. You can see little
shelf. If they leave this and they come
right back to view up again. And we're
just going to rinse, repeat, rinse,
repeat, rinse, repeat.
I'm ready to go back to bed right now.
>> [snorts]
>> So fa at the moment I'd say what we
seeing failure to break down from
shorts.
All right.
This is where they keep piling in. They
need to get this move here to let them
out. They're failing to get that move.
We are not leaving this.
We're building liquidity down here.
We're in uh
in here inside this
inside this. Right. It's There ain't
much to do yet, folks. Right. While this
bunny's around, I'm going to uh
going to go and get a refill of a coffee
in a moment. Just see what happened. Is
this point of control now? 94s.
We see. [snorts] All right.
>> [sighs]
>> Market's waiting for FMC minutes. I
mean, maybe. I just think, guys, we're
just in a low we're in a low volume
stage. You have to understand where we
are on a calendar, right? They're
they're prepping for their tax right
now.
Most people are not at trading desks.
You know, there's no there's there's no
reason for this market to aggressively
move right now. And what's going to
happen in FOMC mix? Oh, we have split
decision. Some people want to do one to
two cuts next year. Some people are
aware that the jobs numbers are probably
being cooked and might be worse. What's
my prediction? I I think regardless of
what happens right in this ep minutes,
what is going to happen is the job
numbers are going to come and if they
actually print real numbers, they're
going to see that we're absolutely
[\h__\h] and they're going to have to do
more than one cut next year and then
we're going to price that in ahead of
time because that's what we do as a
market. What the bigger question is is
do people see these rate cuts as bullish
when the economy is in a bad way? That's
the big question right now because I
don't think uh we're going to go into
rate cutting cycle that's necessarily
great for the economy. Everyone being
like, "Oh, it's cheaper money, it's
cheaper this." Yes, but you need people
working and you need to be delivering,
you know, good growth in these
companies. You can't just have it in the
AI companies. You need a good good broad
sectors across, you know, the other
markets outside of AI AI. But hey,
who [\h__\h] knows? You know, we're here
to day trade. It really doesn't matter.
But I can't see uh the minutes offering
some huge surprise. Let's put it that
way. Right. I'm going to get a refill
and I'll be right back.
[snorts]
All right. Nothing's changed. Absolutely
bugger has changed.
Yes. Right at its IB. It's trying to
break lower.
We're going to sleep. We're in this
shelf. We're trying to leave this gray
shelf. It's what the sellers are looking
to do. They're looking to drive price
lower at the moment. Just whether they
can find acceptance. We're into a huge
imbalance down here from this morning.
Like we said, we've got these trap
players. Where is it? This one. We've
got these trap players down here.
Right down here. Right. So, this is
their pain right now.
680s. So, sellers need to get back below
680s.
So, down here. There you go. Right. So,
can we let them out now?
Do we let them out or do all these
sellers down here start covering break
even? That's now your question. We're
leaving that gray box though. And the
question is, can we get outside of now
previous day value area low? If we get
continuation, this is going to be like
what we saw to the top side. All right,
if we leave this, if you're trading this
move here, all right, your cover points
are here. I'll be very careful at 680.
You need to see continuation and then
down into this. All right, what we did
earlier today was this the other side.
That was the mirror. Did we get to
previous day value? We did. Yes, that
was the This would be a mirror of
earlier. All right. So, see how we're
reacting off 680s. That's because right
now that's where those guys from earlier
are stuck. We just went over it right
here. Right. This is where they're
stuck. So, understanding who's stuck and
where they're stuck.
And they are now covering
They're really you haven't got much to
play with. This is the back test of that
gray box. So, if you're going to sell
and you're convinced that we're going to
see continuation under 680, this is the
level. But, uh, personally, I'm not
doing anything down here in a D-shape,
in a rotation.
Not much for me to want to do.
Just saying what I'm seeing down here.
You can see the importance of that 680.
If we get continuation under it, we let
all those sellers out.
They are trying.
But on that last shove down, it was all
sell side.
So in here,
we look inside here.
That is completely different to what I
have on trading view, which is uh on
Ninja Trader. down here on Ninja Trader.
This is all sell side and then we go bid
up and I have down here
36 lot and 26 lot. So let's have a look.
I bet you it's reflected on bookmap. So
trading view seems slightly off there.
Where is bookm? Here we go. What's the
bottom of the auction? There you go. So
35 lot, 36 lot, 99 lot. So you can see
the flip here. Aggressive selling.
aggressive selling on this break of here
down into 80. There's the 80s right at
the low. They've tried to aggressively
sell the low. But look what's happened.
We've seen passive buyers down there.
Probably the guys at 80s that I just
talked about earlier,
right at 80s being like, okay, we'll get
out here. Get out there means they've
got limit buys there and other guys
absorbing. And you see the delta flip
from aggressive selling to buying. And
we're going bid back up now, right? And
this is how the tape moves. It's
literally, it's not [\h__\h] [snorts]
[\h__\h] algo or any [\h__\h] like that that
you hear of godly man doing it all. It's
nothing like that. It's actual
participants. Okay. And now we're going
back to this is the gray box. So if we
if you zoomed this out and you wanted to
think where is that gray box? Well, it's
just this dense level here that we're
battling over. If we think about this,
this is your dense level, isn't it? All
these sellers and buyers, we can't get
acceptance above and we haven't had any
continuation acceptance below. This is
rotation, rotation, rotation, squeeze,
no acceptance. Rotation, rotation,
rotation, drop, no acceptance. Rotation,
rotation, rotation. And we see what's
next. All right.
[snorts]
No, I'm not in a trade. I haven't been
in a trade since here. The only the only
trade
was this. All right, that's the only
trade I took. I would have loved to been
a buyer here this morning, but this move
here was disgusting. All right, what
what I would have loved to have seen
down there. All right, as we traded into
previous days value was something a
little bit like one of these. Thanks
very much. you know that is my buying
opportunity. But what they did instead
was they tapped it and just went boom
and then we squeezed and then I had to
wait for them to make sure that these
20s held. So if you rewind the tape,
this is where I was getting long selling
into that. I held a runner in case we
went back up here. I took the runner off
as we broke down under the underneath
value. That was it. That's all I've done
today, folks. That was probably one of
the better setups. The best setup would
have been here if they just didn't do
this horrible candle. If they had just,
you could argue to take that, but if
they had just done something a little
bit nicer, I guess that is what it did.
But this candle here was gross. The
reaction was very quick.
Literally tapped value just actually
missed value by a tick, but tapped it
and then went. [snorts]
This move was impossible to get.
I don't know. it it was at the 46 mark.
So unless unless that data came out a
minute late, but yeah, I mean it was
either way it was impossible to get.
Here comes the breaks and now they're
breaking away from this gray box. All
right, leaving volume. So all these
sellers down here not doing a good job
of breaking down, right? Can't find
acceptance. And if this is the volume
that's now trapped, they are starting to
stop out. We're coming back to VWAP. And
the question is, do we go back above
VWAP into this area here, current value
area high? And if we get through that,
do they go to here? And the rotation
will keep happening in here until they
find acceptance. And I don't mean until
they find acceptance today. Today,
tomorrow, next week, they can spend as
long as they want in here until one side
is cooked enough and they have a
catalyst for a break away from it.
>> [cough]
>> What is the indicator I'm using? It's
the Flow Zones Pro,
right? A version of it comes for free
when you do my course. Uh you can
upgrade. You can buy it on the website,
but you might not know how to use it
without doing the course, but it's uh
Yeah.
[snorts]
I would imagine I've not used it um Jay
Caresh, but I would imagine it's exactly
the same, right? Because all it's doing
is um
if it's if it's a heat map, all it's
doing is selling you showing you limit
players and market players. That's
that's all bookmap is. It's just a
visual representation of the book,
right? All bookm is is a visual
representation of the book. For me
personally, I learn best with visuals,
right? So, and I like seeing historical
data. If you're just looking at the
book, if you're looking at the DOM and
you're looking at the time in sales, I
mean, your eyes and your memory is going
to have to be absolutely incredible to
remember historical data, right? So, to
see a guy spoofing, you're going to have
to see him on the level two on the DOM,
put his order on and off and on and off
and on and off. Unless you've got insane
eyesight and insane memories, it's going
to be very hard to do, especially in a
fastmoving market. At the moment, the
market's moving quite slow. But if we're
in days where we're doing, you know,
multiple hundreds of points, it's uh
very easy to miss those players.
All right, so back up to value high. We
just talked about this. If we leave
this, get to view up through this, we go
back to value area high on the day. And
if we get acceptance through that, we're
going to come back up to previous days
value area high. And the rotation will
continue.
[snorts]
And ES coming back up to its New York
open and New York view up here as well.
Folks,
what a slow day.
I'm up a whopping 750 bucks. Fantastic.
[laughter]
To be honest, anything over zero is a
bonus in this market.
Oh, good for you, Rick. Is that your Is
that the long from yesterday, mate? Was
that a swing long? I remember you saying
yesterday you were getting long. Is that
the same one? We both talked about it,
didn't we? And I said, "I think they'll
do the stop runs first." And you said,
"Yeah, I think they will as well." I
think you were positioned
somewhere around here, right? And I
said, "I think they'll wash them and
then reclaim and that's what you had end
of day."
Yep. Same one swing. Yeah, I think
that's really nice.
Exactly there. Stop run and 692. Stop
run and then 692. Yeah, that that's
exactly it what we just talked about
here. I remember talking about it with
you yesterday when we were here in the
morning saying these are my the plays I
like is when we do this and then reclaim
wash all these guys out they become the
liquidity for market makers to get long
against and then that that's nice. So
and it's just held it. It's held it
nicely. So for a swing position I think
you look you look pretty good especially
especially that we're unwilling to break
below previous day's value today. Um,
that's a good sign for you.
I'd like to see it if if I don't know
how long you'd like to hold your swings
are, what the targets are, but I'd like
to see it hold a bid here uh and get
back into this for you for a swing. And
then you can see if you can find
acceptance above previous week's value.
Don't know what that was. What the hell
was that noise?
Okay. So, into previous day close here.
Pre-state value now above.
Nice. Nice, mate. Yeah. Good. I hope
that works out for you, buddy. I think
it's a it's a good idea, a good thesis.
Hopefully, it works out.
Oh, nice. So, Tyson just said,
"Requesting a payout at the close of day
effing finally."
Nice work, mate.
Nice work. Way to go sticking to a trade
plan, man. That was uh very proud of you
for doing that. What a nice turnaround
from I'd say midpoint of the year when
we probably went over everything.
Congratulations.
It's great to great to uh hear and see.
Really nice. Okay, so into previous day
value area high here. I actually have it
right here on my NT.
So can they now bid back above this? Do
pullbacks now hold? All right. So
structurally, we have this here. Uh I'd
want it to just hold this and do this
move here. Same as same as this morning.
Basically, same kind of thing. If
they're going to do it, yes, right into
VWAP, New York open, all those good
things. [clears throat] Can they find a
bid back up here through value or are we
going to go back in rotation again?
So, if Rick's going to get his way, we
want him to make his money. Obviously,
we want everyone to win on this stream.
We're not here to do anything else other
than make money. We want to see this
happen for Rick. That would be nice for
a swing position.
What we don't want to see is this market
collapse the rotation back down to here
again. This is definitely a squeeze out
though. So, it is possible, but we don't
want that. We want them to resqueeze
this higher
for Rick. We want Rick to win. Come on,
Rick. We want Rick
be a happy man. All right. So, we want
pullbacks to hold for him.
[snorts]
It's got a shot hit.
[laughter] No worries, man. It's got a
shot hit.
This candle here is full of sellers at
the lows.
As long as they say stay stuck, you look
okay. And this candle here was the big
buyers. So this transition here, I want
that to hold for you just based on a
very low time frame chart. Just what
I've seen here. If that doesn't hold,
then this pocket might come back down
for a refill. So I'd want to see this
hold here for a resqueeze. Otherwise, we
might come back into this pocket, which
I don't want to see because we've uh
sort of building this out here and this
out here and thin between. You can see
thin here, thin here. But we should get
going now. There you go. So hopefully
mate hopefully we get this move for you
now
and if we can find acceptance let's hope
we can find some acceptance over this
and ideally over this and then we can
get back into here.
Yes, back above its New York open and
view up as well which is good. Where's
the VIX surround PDC? I'd like to see
that start breaking down, but we look
okay for a slow grind higher here. Now,
if the VIX is going to start behaving
itself,
and I'd say uh basically 36es, 736 is
under that, we've got sellers stuck. So,
if we hold above that or around that,
736s down to 727s
are where sellers got stuck in here, a
lower time frame. All right. So the
question is can we do this sort of low
volume drive out now above those levels
and cause this squeeze. Here we go. So
750 755 765 all on deck here with
passive players. 775 looking above that
800 is there still player 830 840 there
is. So still got that liquidity to fill
higher. I think you look really good now
for a squeeze out. This is looking much
much better for a squeeze out here. Much
much better. Really nice. So,
let's see if we can fill these
participants into
55 and 65. Here we go. By time frame,
I'll go up here. I'd like to see us
print back above 55s now and find some
acceptance
in an ideal world. And ideally, I don't
want it back below 42 now if I'm looking
for higher prices just because that's
where that big seller came in and got
himself stuck on bookmap there. 95 lot
came in at uh sorry 42 732 and got
himself caught really good. Here we go.
Here we go. All right. So 55 65 and then
if we could get get through the IB I
would feel somewhat confident, right? If
we can get through this because this is
a big pivot. It's not just from today.
It's from previous day. This is
possible, right? This is definitely
possible in this session.
So, we want to see it get up through
here and continue to drive higher,
52s, 55s.
Imbalance here down to 43s. Where's this
big player came in? 42s. Where's this
guy here? 37s, was it? 31s.
So, want to see this rebid here. I don't
want them to collapse this down for you,
Rick.
Want to see them rebid it.
Oh, don't worry, Ragnarok. It's just
automated. Nothing happens even if it
does it. It's just uh Nightbot or
whatever. Don't Don't even Don't even
worry about it.
First payout across four accounts was
approved and Apex sent the funds now.
Alex, two months into trading.
High five. Love it. Love it. Love it.
Congrats, man.
Congrats.
So, this is a kind of level here. You
can see this sort of shelf.
There's three. It's unfortunately it's
three but I think this is possible. I do
think this is possible here.
You can see it's big seller here at 55
and once we run that might get a squeeze
out through up into these. Looking good
though it's just held previous day value
high. This kind of area here which is
what you want. Can we get up into that
now is the question for you.
Let's just do a bib of this probably
into that golden zone.
If we're above 61, then you probably got
a good chance. Yeah, we are. Nice. I
think it's going to go. I think this has
a good chance in going for you.
There you go. Beautiful. There's the
seller. Just got absolutely wrecked.
Now, can we get through 60 and find
acceptance higher? [snorts]
It's just held us to pull that interview
up in New York open as well. It's good.
>> [sighs]
>> Um,
you are looking at opening new 1 hour, 4
hour or in your strategy. It's not
important. Yes, it it is important. I do
care about the transitions on hours and
4 hours. Absolutely. Because they
provide more liquidity. Why do they
provide more liquidity? It's got nothing
to do with a magic algo or anything like
that. It's because higher time frame
traders trade transitions, right? So if
you if you are trading at a bank and
stuff like that, all right, guess what?
You're not looking at one minute charts.
All right, unless you're your job is to
scalp for that bank. What you're looking
at is monthly, weekly, dailies,
hourlies, 4 hours, right? So why you see
liquidity injection in those is because
of that. It's literally because of that.
So that's do I care about them? I
absolutely do care about them. Yeah.
What's the best strategy to pass trading
draw down? Um it is to you've got two
options right you've got one option is
to size down right if you size down the
trading draw down will not affect you
right if you're trading two three micros
it is not going to affect you I'm
talking about 50k account right it's not
going to affect you where people get
stuck is they oversize all right and
they get caught in a pullback and then
they blow up on the trading draw down so
the first one is to size down the second
way to do it I'm going to be honest with
you is to be very very aggressive and
use a trading stop and pass them quick.
Is that the best way to do it? I'm not
convinced it's the best way to do it. I
think you you will go through a lot of
accounts, but do I do that? Yeah, there
are times where I'm very very aggressive
with my accounts in eval because I don't
want time decay because I know I can
take consistent payouts for it. So, if I
need to get through a trading draw down
eval,
sometimes I will be aggressive with it.
And the other way is yeah, exactly what
Chad's saying. See money take money take
money off the table. Move your trading
stop up. You know, lock in small gains
consistently.
The first hour has a huge wick. I I
don't think anything has a huge wick
right now. I'm going to be honest with
you. I think you're probably zoomed in.
If we zoom like if I look at this, I
don't see any huge wick. I just see very
tight price action, right? Very tight
price action. Huge wick would be
something like this, I guess, up here.
Right? If we zoom in to this first hour,
right? What you're seeing is huge wicks.
if we're just going to actually measure
those out
of 40 points.
40 points is not a huge wick. All right.
It's not a huge wick. You can see like
the these are drives up, right? Because
we're finding bids off previous day
value.
But what I would say is nothing in here,
okay, is huge, right? This is tiny,
right? So don't get too zoomed in.
That's all I'm trying to say. Here
we go. All right. You're looking good
now. All right. So, TP1 for anyone who
was uh is scalping long. But if we find
acceptance above this is a big
multi-time frame pivot. All right. Goes
back to 29th of December, right?
Pre-market and then again yesterday at 2
in the afternoon and again yesterday at
10:00 in the morning. We find acceptance
above this. We should come up into here.
Looks good. Looks really good.
>> [snorts]
>> Can I talk to you about how I establish
who's stuck? Yeah, it's uh
it's effectively from Delta, right? It's
it's at key levels when I can see one
set of participants trade one way and
the market move the other way. That's
what it is. So if we see aggressive
sellers and the market's not moving
lower then we know aggressive sellers
are stuck. If we see aggressive buyers
and the market is not moving higher then
we know aggressive buyers are stuck
right and we trade their pain points.
Can I get
my idea on selling right now? What my
answer would be why what is your setup
to sell right now? I don't see a setup
to sell right now.
like your location, you could argue, is
not too bad. But what I'm now seeing is
we're back above previous day's value,
right? We have liquidity to aim for.
This isn't just this day. We zoom out.
All these stops are here. And if we run
those stops, we are going to search
higher. I don't think there's a good
idea to sell right now. But uh you you
trade what you want, right? I don't
think there's a sell right now. The cell
would have to be back
under here if you're playing a rotation,
right? This is not a sell. If you're
selling this, what you doing? You're
going to add and add and add. What you
doing when all these stops cover and it
comes up to here? You're going to add
and add and add and blow up. Right?
There's your momentum right now. Maybe
you get a pull back to here, but it's
probably going to be absorbed to go
higher. At the moment, I don't think
there's a sell from what I can see right
now.
So yeah, you if that's my opinion, you
you guys do you. If there's something in
here you like, you do you.
Never used a prop burn just my own
account. Is it worth looking into? Yeah,
I'd say it is worth looking into. Um,
just make sure you read up on the
trading rules for each one. understand
it's not like playing with your own
cash,
but uh the leverage is good.
If you've been used to trading your own
account, I would say probably better to
look at uh Lucid, Funded Next, or
Tradeify.
They're a bit a bit easier with the
rules. If you've been used to trading
your own account, start there.
Do I have an idea about Greeks and
dealer positions? Is it worth to pay for
data? It look gamma can be very very
useful. There's no there's no way of
denying it especially in a market run by
zero DTE. It becomes important. So yes,
can be very very useful at least to plot
it in your chart at the beginning of the
days and stuff.
And that's yeah, if you're on if you're
on tilt, Adam, just yeah, disconnect. I
mean, you're not going to miss much
today, honestly.
Okay, they're trying to hold this
pullback into these flow zones.
Where was that last seller stuck? What
was his size? 48.
Yeah, as long as 48 and sort of 30 39ish
hold, then there's a chance for a rebid
higher. If they collap, I wouldn't be
short biased in this market unless we
come back under value and we lose this
down here all the time. We're holding
into here, especially into here. There's
this rebid chance. All right. Is this a
squeeze? Yeah. Can they repric it? Yeah.
But I'd be looking, if I was bullish,
I'd be looking for them to hold here and
finish this now. Don't think there's any
reason to get short.
Absolutely no reason to get short in my
mind.
Is there any reason I don't trade my own
capital with futures? Uh I'd prefer
taking swing swing positions with my own
capital.
That's why
I think the the amount of leverage and
the amount of money you can make from
prop firms with very limited risk if
you're a good trader way outweighs the
reason to trade your own capital.
And uh I'd rather put my capital to work
in swing positions, which is what I do.
That's just it's just a personal thing.
It's just how I do it. It's not always
been the way. I traded my own capital
for years on small caps and large caps.
Um
maybe I'll go back to that if the
volatility looks well I think the
volatility is going to be huge next
year. [snorts] We'll see. But right now
the environment the uh
amount of money you can make from very
very low well huge return on uh on
investment right now.
Yeah, I do. Uh, anything that I'm
looking at swing trade is always posted
into uh Discord.
Yeah. Do I trade smaller in buffer?
Yeah, always smaller until you get out
your buffer, right? You've got to earn
the right to put risk on. Got to earn
the right to size up.
So, like I can give you an example right
now. I'm still long. Uh Apple, AMD,
Amazon,
uh where else am I long?
Hang on.
And I have been for months.
Where is investments? Here we go. So,
I'm long Apple still. I'm up 50% on
that. Sorry. No, I'm not. I'm up 29%.
Don't know why it says that. I'm up 29%
on that. Haven't trimmed any. I'm long
from 202. I think it was Amazon. I'm
only up 5%
on that one. Meta, I'm up about 10% on
that. Haven't trimmed any. AMD, I'm up
32%, but I've hardly got any size left.
All right, so I was long AMD from 180s.
We sold on that huge giant squeeze uh
that happened a couple months ago and
just holding a runner. And then uh my
big winner of last year was uh or this
year was open. Uh we were up about 480%
on that.
Okay, here we go. So resqueeze possible.
You're looking for uh initial balance
and above. Ideally, right, this you
would have seen. I've drawn it out
numerous times you any hold above here.
Ideally, you don't see failed follow
through here. Ideally, you see this or a
resqueeze up into there. Let's have a
look at the mag. How the mag doing? Not
too bad. It look like they're starting
to turn around a bit. So Tesla 0.44 44%
up. Nvidia 0.16% down. Looking good,
trying to go red to green. Microsoft
half a% up. Meta 1.25% up. Google over a
third of percent up. Amazon 0.16% down.
And Apple 0.22% down. So, we've got a
chance here. It has a chance if they can
get going.
Do you take swings with the same
strategy? Yeah, it's all exactly the
same, man. Uh everything's the same. It
doesn't matter what what you're trading,
what asset you're trading, what time
frame you're trading. Everything works
the same way.
No, no leverage for me, Joe. Cash. Trade
cash.
You're welcome, Eddie. Thanks for
joining.
No, that was C a cash position. I can
show you.
We bought at uh 198
think I think that's what we ended up up
on it. We bought at 198 on open and we
sold right into the peak when everyone
else started sell started buying it.
Maybe it was four. Maybe I got it wrong.
Maybe it was 400%.
We bought 198. Where was that in this
pullback here?
I think we actually bought early
and sold some and then rebid. So
there we go. 450%. That was close. 450%.
We got that whole move. It wasn't just
me. Lots of guys in Discord got it with
me and we sold up it. I think that was
it.
Yeah. Really nice. You can see my
channel's still on there from when we
bought it. All right, we'll rebid here.
And I was bidding against uh well
actually about against old mentors. So,
uh, that was fun. They were all trying
to hammer short and I was like, this it
it held on the hourly over and over and
over again,
right? Those of you who are here will be
aware of this, right? You can see this
is where I was getting long. There's the
accumulation phase,
huge accumulation phase, breakout,
pullback, acceptance, held on houries,
and everything after that was upside
until we got into key areas that we were
looking at and then, you know, sold. and
it's still actually holding in a nice
channel, but you know, not interested in
it. I got the move I wanted out of it.
Couldn't give a [\h__\h] what they do with
it next year. Don't care. Same with all
these names like RTI, OQ, all the ones
that can go on big squeezes. You know,
take your money when it's there. Don't
don't chase in.
Building some nice liquidity here. So, a
little bit of a shelf starting to be
developed here. I'd be watching now.
That's your over under.
[snorts]
Thanks, ma'am.
It's just the same play. You would have
seen like the accumulation. But if
you're going to look for, you got to
understand, I used to be a short seller
of small caps, right? So if you're going
to look to trade long small caps, what
are you looking to trade? You're looking
to trade people's pain. Most small caps
are pieces of [\h__\h] You have to
understand that 99% of small cap
companies are absolute turds. So what
are you looking for? You're looking for
shorts to be overexposed in it, right?
If they keep trying to hammer a beaten
market down short and you can see a
potential shift in that market coming,
here's here's the relief, guys. You
watch now for this initial balance high
gray box above you and see if you can
get acceptance.
If if there's too many shorts involved
in a company at lows and you start to
see an accumulation phase and you start
to see some inside buying and all this
stuff, then it's likely they're going to
start dropping news releases, right?
Because they want their exit. The news
releases come, you get shorts covering.
They are forced to jump over each other
to market order out and you get the big
squeeze come and then you get one pull
back in and then hammer it in again. And
if that holds a higher low, you get a T
plus2 scenario and we expand higher. And
that's exactly what we got over and over
and over and over again until you saw it
all over Twitter with everyone talking
about we're getting long open. You get
and that's your exit. That's when you're
like, "Fuck this. I'm out." Right? Same
thing as you saw on silver at the
weekend, right? That that blowoff move
high. How many people retail were buying
silver at that high? Lots. Okay. All
those extra buyers become the volume for
market makers and institutions to sell
into. Remember, you've got to pair off.
If you're going to sell a big position,
if I'm going to sell a million shares
right now, let's just let's talk about
right now. This is going to be a good
example, right? If I'm long here, right,
let's say 10,000 contracts, okay, and I
want to trim some of them. I can't just
sell, right? I need a buyer the other
side. So, where's my buyer? He's
probably going to be here because if
this is a short seller and their stops
get run, then he's going to become a
market buyer. And if I have a breakout,
a breakout buyer here as well, he's got
buy orders there. So, I know here maybe
I've got 10,000 buy orders. So once we
get through here, I can easily sell my
10,000 position without it affecting the
market, right? Because I can pair off,
right? It is the same but more important
in small caps because you have a lack of
liquidity. [snorts]
Hopefully that makes sense to you. Look,
that's why
it is a game of liquidity. It doesn't
matter what asset or what trading
vehicle, however you want to frame it in
your head. This is a giant game of
liquidity. That's all we're playing.
It's a game of liquidity and it's a game
of pain.
[snorts]
You bought the top by accident. What?
You bought all the way over here.
I I don't know what to tell you. Um
if if you I literally I don't know what
to tell you, J Source. I don't know how
much size you're in. I don't know how
much exposure you've got. I don't know
your risk tolerance. Like,
do I think we're going to go higher
here? My personal feeling is yes. Right
now, I think we're going to probably
squeeze out. But, you know, I don't know
your exact position. All I know is you
said you bought the high. So,
if you've sat through all of this, if
you've bought this
and you've sat through all of this,
you know, would I get out? I mean, I
probably would have got out here, but uh
do I think it can do this? I do think I
think there's a lot of stops here to
run. But, uh I don't want to tell you to
hold because you're you're in a horrible
position. But, there's so many stops
here that I think we go and run up into
here.
And that's when you'll get the squeeze
and the pair off of liquidity that I
talked about. So, here we go. Big drive
up. They're going to try and run these
stops now.
[snorts]
You missed the o the trade at the open.
Can you show the win again? Uh, I don't
think I traded the open, my friend. Uh,
my trade was here. I didn't trade this.
My trade was this this drive up. Looking
for the same thing we're looking for now
really to see if we can get back above
this. All right. So, there's probably
going to be a stop hunt. You'll probably
see liquidity come. There's the stop
hunt. You see that? That's the pair off.
We just talked about it. That's
literally the pair off here. All right?
Because everyone who's smart, who bought
down here, is going to use these stops
to trim their positioning. Remember, we
just talked about like a 10 a 10k move
here. You just paired it off. All right?
And I can show you that right here.
Right? These are all buy orders. They
are not sell orders. All right, so think
about this. If Alex bought low and he
has 10,000, right, limit orders, limit
order, sell orders here. All right, I
just paired them off with all these guys
chasing the market. Now, I've trimmed my
position without me affecting price too
much. Here comes the squeeze and they're
going to try and come up into here now.
Looks really good. I forget. I'm really
sorry. I'm still trying to remember
everyone's names who's new here, but uh
Rick Rick's long. It's Rick that's long
off the lows on the swing and I think he
looks good now. All right, so you want
to see price continue to auction higher
now and you can see how this is all buy
side. All right, these are stops. These
are either either market buy order
stops. All right, all their sell stops
getting popped. And this is where smart
people trim their position and now hold
runners up into here. Hopefully like
this is starting to make sense to you
all, all you guys that are new.
Giving you um
an education in liquidity here for free.
Doing my best to give you one anyway.
All right. So, this is the target up
here now.
This is what we were looking for earlier
today. The trade we took earlier today
from here to here. We were holding those
runners. It's the same trade, right?
We're looking to see if we can run these
stops to get expansion into here. It's
exactly the same trade now, right? This
is the same position. It's the same
hold. It's the same thing. We're looking
at the same levels for the same thing.
Really nice. Here's the expansion.
Right. I've be watching sort of 800
whole numbers here. Uh we are have got
some imbalances from yesterday. So, uh
97 to 99 is one and 806es
to 808 is another. And then value area
high.
Nice J source. There you go. There you
go. Brisker with a W. Love it.
Love it. Love it. Love it.
Really nice. Hopefully that makes sense.
I mean, does everyone understand what
we've just gone over?
Do do you actually understand why the
market moves the way it does? It's got
nothing to do with an algorithm. That's
not to say that algorithms are not in
the market, but the way it moves, right?
The reason we use volume, the reason we
use horizontal levels, the reason we
have things like flags and all these
things is if you can understand the
difference between the type of order
sitting at a level and understand what
that looks like, you will start to be
able to build a narrative. If you, how
can I put this? You need to create a
story of what is happening in the
market. All right? And when we come to a
junction like this, right? This is us.
We're about to turn the page here,
right? So, what is likely to happen?
Well, smart money will trim some
position into here. Now, if they reload
this, we're going to go here. This is a
look above and fail. Then, what I would
say is everyone who got long here sold
into this. Then, we have breakout buyers
call and we come back under and we fade
back down. Right? So, we are building a
narrative. So, if you hear me say this
is what I'm looking for here, but if we
do this, this can happen. It's cuz
there's two sides of every trade
available, right? If they don't have
enough shorts caught yet to get up here,
then this is possible, right? It's
possible. Doesn't mean it has to happen.
If they've got enough caught and they're
like, "Fuck this. We're going higher.
We've just done the damage." Then this
is the move. There's always two things
possible. If everyone tells you this is
100% happening, they're wrong.
Absolutely wrong. [snorts]
Awesome. That's great, Tim. Glad I'm
glad it's helpful. Glad it's helpful.
[laughter]
Awesome. Yeah, lots of you I think it's
helping a lot of you, which is great.
If you want to take on some risk, are
newer and want to actually trade live
without getting completely smoked, buy
and sell shares of TQ. I mean,
triple leveraged. I mean, if you're new,
just trade the Q's. Just trade Q. Don't
go triple leverage.
[gasps] But yeah, uh I mean, I do I do
take positions on those.
[laughter]
Stayed patient since 9:30. I got $25
today. Let's go. Hey, I love it, man.
That like the most important thing of
what you said is not the money. It's the
first two words you said. It is the
first two words that you said. Stayed
patient.
Really good. All right. Back to this
sort of gray box in IB. So, if we're
going to see expansion, you would want
to see them hold this. All right. If
they don't hold this, the rotation is
back down to where? Well, we have a
little shelf here. This can still do
this. It's possible to do that. It's not
ideal, but it's definitely possible. We
have a lot of stops here. Really, a sign
of strength would be this.
Alternatively, it would be this. What
you would not want to see is this. Now,
let's check the auction in here. And
look, let's look at the highs. All
right. It doesn't look too good. I'm
going to be honest with you. The amount
of buying here.
Draw this on. All right. Look at all
this buying. Bye, bye. Bye, bye bye.
Higher day currently is a buy. Flip to
sell. You can see the delta starting to
flip. We have buy side imbalance down to
here. So if they want to repric to here,
we want price to hold into here. We
don't want it to start coming under the
buildout of liquidity. If you think
about how they've built this, all
rightoom.
We want to hold this. All right, we
start getting under here. We look a bit
weaker.
[snorts]
Giveaway time. [laughter]
Oh, give me a second, man. Yeah, we can
do some giveaways. We'll definitely do
some giveaways.
[laughter]
Let's uh let's just manage your
positions now. Let's watch this tape for
a couple minutes, then we'll do it. All
right, we'll do it straight away
afterwards.
Thanks, man. Your discussions have
really helped me trade. I usually trade
the same on stocks, finding traps where
mainly shorts are trapped and would be
covering. Can I use your indicator on
stocks? Yeah, it will work on anything.
All right. All my indicator is the only
thing that it won't work on is the
GlobeEx positions, right? But it will
give you pre-market. All right. So,
these orange lines, not this line, this
is the higher time frame algo, but the
horizontal ones are GlobeEx. But yeah,
it will work on stocks. I use it on
stocks myself.
Yes, trade on tilt to totally there is
zero chance all tickers run without
being computer driven. There is not
enough manpower for Black Rockck to
handle all all stocks. Yeah, I agree.
Like I said, there are plenty of alos in
the market. There's just not one algo
dictating everything. That is just a way
of looking at the market. It's not
reality
to be honest. Mate, already made 380
just trying to see if I can get any
more. Yeah, don't try and squeeze I
don't know what's been said above. I
probably missed stuff, but don't try and
squeeze more out of stuff if you're uh
if you're chasing. I don't I don't know
what you've said. I've clearly missed
some messages.
hoping it continues up. I mean, it still
looks good. Pullbacks are still holding.
All right, you're still you're just at
IB. You're at this little gray nugget
here. I mean, it's possible it comes
down here. It would not be ideal, but
it's very possible. But as long as they
hold somewhere around here, if you think
about the swing pivot,
right? And if we think about multi-day,
right, there's your pivot, right? You
want it to hold there. Worst case here.
You want it to hold somewhere in this
range and then to complete this move.
I certainly wouldn't be looking short
right now. Personally,
[snorts]
what value do you have as your IB highQ?
What you mean? What price is the IB
high?
Uh 775.
I know CB. I know. [laughter]
There you go. That's awesome. Made $85.
Extremely happy because it's not the
money, but the strategy I was able to
use. Thank you. That's it. Once you
start focusing less on the finance and
more on your strategy, refine the
strategy. Stick to the strategy. If you
know you've got strategy which wins
multiple times, if you're willing to be
patient, you will start seeing success.
Success. Can't talk. Still holding this
in balance. Still looks okay right now,
I'd say. Still looks okay.
Yes. Not quite as pretty.
Can I use trend friends to help me
identify market sentiment before I place
a trade to check if I'm aligned with the
trend or going against? Yeah, you could.
Like, look, trend friends here, right?
So, your lower time frames today have
been neutral, but your higher time
frames have been bullish, right? But I
wouldn't use it solely alone. But what
do we look for? All right. Who did the
video at the weekend? Right? What's
this? Mr. 200. What's this Mr. 20? Where
do we see acceleration once we get
outside of this? Right? Why? Because
this is basically your hour. That's your
hourly pivot. Boom. Right. Went over it
in the free video at the weekend. If you
move down to lower time frame would have
given you more opportunities quite
possibly.
Same kind of area reclaim
in low volume. All right. So I wouldn't
rely on one sole thing you especially if
it's an indicator but does it provide uh
you know areas of incentive to help you
even if you played this inside bar. Look
at the inside bar build. There's your
white bar. There's the green arrow for
trend friend. There's your expansion
through the stop. All right. So that
there are ways of using it to help you
for sure. That's why we designed it to
keep it very simple. It's very beginner
friendly that trend friend and [snorts]
it's free. Having
and following your strat is what pays
over time. Yeah. From there, you learn
to adjust the sizing based on the
quality. That's exactly it, mate. A plus
trade where you know it's high
probability, you size up, you add into
it. BC setups small size or you leave
alone. I totally agree.
Hey mate, I just started trading today.
I made 380 on eBay. Any advice? Well,
just go nice and slow and trade again
tomorrow. If you've made that money
today, I'd ask yourself, is there a
setup here which is any good? If the
answer is no, I'd question being here in
the afternoon. Get off the screens, come
back tomorrow, do the same thing.
Yeah, prices trading is exactly what I'm
looking to do. So, I um currently have
20 uh Apex accounts for next year and I
have uh
two Lucid accounts. I'm working on
another Lucid account. Um I've just lost
all my
funding ticks accounts, funding t
funding ticks accounts after what they
did. Uh some will know in Discord
because I didn't trade over Christmas. I
had few of them removed which is a load
of [\h__\h] but there we go is what it
is and uh I couldn't give a [\h__\h] to be
quite honest given how they've operated.
So goodbye good riddance and uh I need
to add on some funded next and some
trade. Oh I forgot that I even had a
trader buy. I think I bought one. I
might need to be using that before I
forget.
H
I'm sure I have one. Let's have a look.
But yes, it's exactly what I'm looking
to do.
Yes, I have the count but it's not
showing.
See if we can get this fixed
in a minute since I traded with them.
It's weird. I don't think you can see
it.
Sorry folks. I only just realized that's
lucky you said that. Reminded me.
Maybe I need to sign some docks. It's
been a while.
Okay, I've got a problem in my trade
account. No account showing
there email them. Thank god one of you
just mentioned that. I would have uh
gotten
There we go.
Uh, why did I trade choose to trade
futures rather than QQQ? Uh, leverage
and firms and I I still trade QQQ. It's
just more swing.
Sorry folks, let me just deal with this.
What's happening in the market? Okay,
pulling back to that value area high.
So, it didn't continue, right? So,
failed to hold this uh gray box. So,
this is the move back down to value. If
they lose this down to here, if they
lose all of that all the way down,
right? So, the rotation continues. It's
unfortunate. never was able to hold for
that pivot, but it gave a good move up
from here to here and from here to here.
All right. And we still remain inside
the previous week's value.
We do giveaways in a second.
Sorry, I'm just online to their chat
because there's something wrong with
this. Right, I'll do some giveaways in a
moment. Sorry folks.
Few hours. Okay, perfect. There we go.
Good service. Good work. trade of eight.
All right, catch up with the chat and
then we do a giveaway here. Um
D,
I wanted to check this fib for this
runup. Would you anchor to the very
bottom value area low the current
session value higher small swing? Uh Mo,
it depends what I'm looking to trade.
Right. So, if I was looking at this
current extension, right, I'd go from
here to here. Or if you were looking for
this pullback now, I'd I'd just be going
from here, from this swing point. All
right, so back down to here. If you were
looking beyond that, if you were zoomed
out,
we'd be thinking from this high
to here,
and we just got stuck in sort sort of
this golden zone. So, at the moment,
like we're just nothing more than a
rotation. Um buyers did have the chance
there to come in. They had the chance up
here to really cause a resqueeze. So
there's one big leg up.
This is still a pullback. Question is
where do they hold this? They should
they can hold here. They failed to hold
here. They failed to hold here. It's
quite drastic. Maybe they offer this
later. Maybe they save that for next
week. I don't know. [snorts]
But there is a big shelf down here where
we broke out from. Right. So leaving
this. Remember it's these short sellers
here that caused this move. Buyers then
came in completed part one squeeze
above. Remember we talked about the pair
off like 10k for example pairing off. If
you were buying here and you wanted to
sell into this this is the squeeze to
sell into. They would have held runners
for this move here. Same as I did from
here to here holding runners. They don't
get that way. Right. So the question is
is there an area of value which they
rebid and try another attempt at it or
not? The problem that you've now got is
you need to obey structure and shelves.
All right. So you have these volume
nuggets little here now. So the question
is if buyers cannot reclaim all right
sellers can come back in and sell this
and try and get back down to this low.
It's possible if we get no acceptance
here. So if you get a look above in in
in this is possible to repric this. You
have to be aware to be able to take
every side of the tape when we're in
rotational markets. Can't be too
bullish, too trend driven.
>> [snorts]
>> Um,
nice. Nice. JS source.
What indicator do I have turned on? This
is my flow zone pro.
Comes with the course.
What pro volume profile am I using?
Anchored. Anchored to 930.
What do I think of FOMC today? like the
meeting nothing I I don't think anything
of it
promo code for your for the course the
volume profile and uh orderflow course
does have $100 off right now ends
January 1st uh code is launch capital
letters launch capital letters
um let me check if there's one on the
other course I don't think there is one
right now I will
Why do the candles change from red to
blue? Because we're underneath the flow
zones. Momentum has been lost. All
right. Bullish momentum,
bearish momentum
under the flow zones.
Where
can I see?
Uh FCT right now will get you 10% off.
FCT will get you 10% off the courses.
All right, let's do some giveaways.
I can log in here. It would help
Okay. Going to give away an Apex
account, any size. Just type FCT in
chat. Only type it once. All right. If
you type it more than once, Nightbot
will pull you out for spam. So, just
type it once. Give you guys a minute or
two to do that and we'll give away a
free Apex account. Remember, Apex still
on sale. 90% sale on Apex with cheap
activation until Jan 6th
[snorts]
Yeah, I see him. 605. I think it's just
an algo playing games, but we'll see.
He's never coming in like at an
aggressive level when he's lifting every
time.
Oh, I see him.
[sighs] Give you guys like 30 more
seconds here.
Yeah, I mean they got really aggressive
here on the cell. It wouldn't be
surprising to see them lift this a
little bit and then
see what they do into some of these. Do
they want to fill this or are they going
to go full reclaim? Anything is possible
right now in a rotational market. Be
aware of both.
Okay, how how long left? Let's give you
guys 25 seconds left and then we'll pull
the winner.
Just type it once in chat.
5 4 3
one.
The winner is Crypto Digital Wise 9699.
Are you here? Crypto Crypto Digital
Wise.
Let me know you're here. Crypto digital
wise.
He's sleeping. He might well be at the
moment.
Going to give him
There he is. Or there they are, I should
say. All right. Congratulations.
All I need you to do is You're welcome.
You're welcome. Send me an email. I'm
going to make a note of your name here.
Send me an email
info@flowzonetrader.com.
Uh, and I want to see a screenshot of
you logged into your YouTube so I can
see it's you. So, if you just attach a
screenshot of you logged in and I will
sort you out with a free Apex account,
right? Any size you want. Right. So
info@flowzoneontenttrader.com
right
we're going to give away a free
introduction to trading course. So just
type course in to chat once. This is a
very beginner friendly course only 2
hours long. It's not one of the main
ones, but uh
if you are interested or you want to
gift it to a friend, by all means do it.
But it's it's an absolute introduction.
It's only worth 99 bucks. Not one of the
big mentorship courses, just so you're
all aware.
I'll give one away. Right. While you do
that, use the bathroom. Be right back.
>> [snorts]
>> All right,
10 more seconds. Pull this winner.
Okay. Three, two, one.
TPT trader. I'm sure TPT trader won
already.
Or did you win a Apex account?
Either way, are you here TPT?
They won last week. Yeah. Oh, you're on
Apex World. Look at that. You're clearly
a lucky man. You should buy the lottery
ticket soon.
Okay.
Make a note of it.
intro course.
Same thing as last week then, mate. Just
um shoot me a uh email with you logged
in. Well, you can follow the chain of
the one last week and I'll sort you out
a introduction course.
Okay, market breaking down. So, we're
going back into rotation.
So, it failed to get back above here,
this value area high, losing VWAP.
Probably comes back down into here. I'd
be watching this like little pivot here
just in case, but
I mean, it's just nothing to do with
this. This is uh no follow through.
No follow through.
What the hell? Yeah. What the hell? I've
never won anything either. I don't think
I've ever won anything free ever in my
life.
Oh, Adam, you're fading it from here.
Okay. So, you're playing the rotation.
So, TP1, TP2, bonus territory, right? If
you're playing that rotation.
So, this move here
would be here if we do it. That's your
bonus territory move.
trader dock. I win stuff all the time.
Oh, man.
Take care, ma'am. Take care. Take care.
All right.
So, you've got until 1st of Jan
if you want to do the volume profile and
orderflow course
or the discount. Use code launch
capitals. Okay. Get your $100 off after
that. It's full price.
Uh
maybe we can do something with the
mentorship one.
I did just run a sale though.
Previous day low after lunch break. Um,
I mean,
look, if we just zoom out right now,
it's hard to think about it doing much
at all right now. I wouldn't I wouldn't
rule either thing out.
It was trying to find acceptance. It
couldn't. If we do this, possibly.
Um,
this is the level I'm really interested
in. if we can come back down there early
Jan.
You know at the moment the question is
are we looking to do this on the market?
There's the old balance range, right?
Are we looking to do that? How far does
that pull back need to come? If we come
back into here and buyers don't show up
and we've had remember ES has done this
or at least SPY has an RTY and they
start going into a bit more of a
liquidity crunch than
maybe we don't bid off that. So, I'm
trying to be so flexible right now based
on higher time frame like macro
environment going into a new year that
anything is possible. I'm trying like in
my head I'm trying to be flexible that
anything is possible.
How many of you here, if I do a flash
sale for you guys, like I did for
Christmas, how many of you here want to
do the 20our course?
Maybe I'll do a flash sale until
midnight New Year's Eve,
but I won't promote it. It would just be
for you guys on YouTube.
Okay,
let me see.
See if I can change this or not. Will it
let me do it?
All right, I've set up a flash sale for
you. So, code is 2026. It will only work
on the beginner to advanced course. It's
20% off. It ends midnight New Year's
Eve. I will not be promoting it. All
right. So, it's basically it's just for
you regulars that turn up, you guys who
have stuck around long enough. All
right, it's there for you. If if you
want it, there's zero pressure. Like I
said, if you're new here, I'd probably
go and watch all my free videos first.
Make sure you want to do it. But there
we go. Just for the regs. So, appreciate
you lot turning up each and every day.
Makes my life a lot more fun.
Let's face it, this is a very boring
boring job to do by yourself. Very
boring.
Very, very boring.
You're welcome everyone. Yeah, no
worries.
You're welcome. So, 2026, you want to go
to the In fact, I better make sure it
works. Today
before I tell you it all, make sure I've
not made an error cuz I didn't ask my
dev.
Trading course buy now
2026 apply. Yes, it's working. So, right
now it's 519 bucks right with that sale.
Prices are going up next year as well.
So,
for those of you interested, good luck.
Mark's gone to sleep again. Eh, it's
gone to sleep again. Can I link the
website? Yeah, it's it's underneath you.
Okay, I'll put it. Oh, let me let me do
it for you.
Where's YouTube?
There you go.
Thank you, sir. Thank you, sir. Sorry.
I'm just catch up with chat here.
Great analysis, Alex. You're welcome.
What are my plans for the rest of the
day? Um, it's a good question. I've got
a little bit of work to do um with some
of my other business stuff,
unfortunately. It' be nice if I didn't,
but I do. Um, it is a friend of mine's
birthday, but he I can't make it. He's
already left. So, he's gone to play golf
at uh Trump
um over by Palace Verdees.
>> What's the weather like?
It's a bit [\h__\h] right now.
So, maybe I'll meet him for some beers
in the clubhouse afterwards or
something. That would be nice if
possible. What's the weather going to be
like today? Please be sunny, overcast.
Well, it's better than rain. Uh, I will
take my dog for a walk
and try and catch up with some friends.
What divergence correlation do you use?
Uh, well, the main ones I'm watching are
the VIX and the ES and then the ETFs
versus NQ.
Ian says it's a good course. I'm quarter
of the way through through. Awesome.
Uh, does the $100 off discount code from
the twoour stack? Oh, no, unfortunately.
Well, I don't think it does. You never
know. I don't think it does, but maybe.
I don't think it does, though.
I'm new to the stream this week. You
said something that changed my trading,
so thank you. I made 200ish bucks across
most accounts and did it all week. My
buffer levels are almost full. Hey,
that's awesome, man. Congrats. That's
awesome to hear.
Adam, come to papa. Yeah, it's almost
there, mate. It's almost there. Uh,
let's just have a quick look for you
here. Make sure there's So, I haven't
got my charts up right now. There's a
bit of a reaction.
Yeah, this is where you can see where
these buyers stepped in before.
Is there a pivot here, here, and here?
So, I'd be watching 20s,
13s, 04s, right? So, you're starting to
see a little bit of a reaction here. Can
still trade lower, but uh
just be man. I'm not I think you would
have taken the short.
You would have either taken it here or
here. maybe here,
unless you took this shelf leave, but
I'm assuming you're short here looking
for this move.
Um, sorry folks, I'm just trying to
catch up with you. Do the flow zone
indicators work on Ninja Trader? Yeah,
you there's a upgrade. You can buy them
for Ninja Trader. Um, if you do the
course um or you're buying the course,
you get you can opt into an upgrade at a
discount, but you can get them all on my
website flowzone trader.com. So, if you
want them on NT, you can get them there.
Hey, Flowzone, heading out. Nice stream.
Great being here. Yeah, thanks for
joining again, Rick. I hope I hope that
that swing position uh works out for
you. Fingers crossed. [snorts]
Did I go snowboarding? No,
unfortunately. Um heard the mountains
out there got some incredible powder. We
got lots of powder, but the rain was so
bad that we had landslides on all the
roads to get up there. Uh, Mount High
only opened yesterday and I think it was
only like half of it open. I'm not even
sure Baldi has been able to get open
yet. And then there were two avalanches
and some of them died. So, yeah, it's um
haven't been able to get up. So, maybe
I'll be able to go in the next day or
two. Would be good. would be good seeing
as I just got my board waxed and
sharpened and then just sat here.
Do I play golf? Uh, occasionally very
badly. I used to be all right, but uh it
is actually on my list to do next year
to improve my trading is to get some new
golf clubs and to start going golfing
cuz I have a course 5 10 minutes away
and um to build up that patience and
resilience might be good for me.
Do I have some goals next year? Do you
have some goals next year as go back to
DJ gigs and touring life a little? No, I
have absolutely
zero ambition. Oh, that's right. The
game is on today. I have zero ambition
to go back to uh DJ touring life at all.
I enjoy engineering
um making some music and stuff, but I no
way. I couldn't think of anything worse
to be quite honest with you. [snorts]
No ambition to do that. Gold next week
and next year. I'd like to invest in um
some other businesses. I I'd like to do
something a bit more creative outside of
trading. Um something where I can
take a meeting one or two days a week
and actually have some facetime with
some human beings would be nice. I'd
like to do some more charitable work
next year as well or or do something
more some more give back stuff.
That would be fun. Um, probably want to
buy some more property next year if I'm
honest. Maybe in the US this time. Um,
yeah.
Do the indicators work on Ninja Trader?
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes. Superton, yes,
they do. Have I been to Dubai? Yeah, two
of my best mates live in Dubai. [snorts]
I have been numerous times. I've DJed in
Dubai. I've stayed there many, many
times. I bought my wife's engagement
wing ring from cars in Dubai. So, yes,
it's been many times.
Whis risking VWAP and node for runner.
Yeah, I think you look good still. Just
I would just ex I'd almost expect a pop
because of the grind down. So, just
don't let it get don't don't let a big
pop like
come and ruin all your profits. That's
all I'd say.
Uh
am I located in the UK? No, I'm in Los
Angeles from the UK, but I'm in Los
Angeles.
Do flow zones work on Trading View? I
can't tell if you're taking the piss
now. Well, we're looking at Trading View
and and you're and you're looking at
Flow Zone, so
[laughter]
does FZT work on Trading View uh as a
code? Um,
no. I don't think they have codes on
Trading View. I can give you a link for
a pro account, but I don't think you'll
save much money. You're better off, I'm
going to be honest with you, CB. You're
better off waiting for, and I don't know
if they have it now, but for like a
Black Friday sale or an Easter sale or
something like that, you will save so
much money if you can wait for the big
Trading View sales.
Take care, Connor 94. Take care. Flow
zone golf trip could be fun.
Yeah, Caribou Cup, Jan 14th. I'm not too
worried about Caribou. I'm always I'll
take some silverware, but I don't mind
if we go out with it.
What kind of music do I produce? Uh, all
sorts now. But, um, I had a pretty good
career in um, house, deep house or what
you guys would call EDM over here.
Have I done a video on bookmap in
detail? Uh, only in the uh, volume
profile and orderflow course. I haven't
done one for free.
going to call the market makers now and
ask them to push price lower at least
down to previous day value area low.
That's all I'm asking. It would be nice,
wouldn't it? Like it's teased it a few
times.
Have I ever read what algo traders and
quant say about scalping and technical
trading? Um I don't
no
DJed in Dubai. Yeah, I played the uh the
F1 I've played lots out there actually.
I played uh Atlantis. I played the F1
Grand Prix. I played is it Queen
Elizabeth? What's what's the ship that
they have out there? Planted. Played in
there. Um where else have I played? I
played loads out there. I used to play
out there a lot. Played for Cafe Mambo
out there. I forget what that place was
called. Let me see if I've got some of
the pictures. It was really good fun. I
used to go there two, three times a year
back in the day. Long time ago now. Long
time ago. Bass house G House music.
Curious what he listens to after saying
that. Well, um,
for for me, well, I won bass house
award, uh, producer of the year in 2014,
and I used to tour with Am Edge and
Dance. So there you go. Both both of
those I used to do. I'm good friends
with all that crew, Lorenzo and all
those boys.
All the North England boys,
Jamie Dugen and all that lot.
Trying to see if I find
when I was in Dubai.
Go back a long way. Jesus Christ. So old
now. What a shame. I look back and I
don't even recognize myself.
That's Miami.
That's Asia. It's got it's around here.
That's got to be too early.
Past it.
Good memories. I love looking at photos.
Good times.
That was Blue Marlin.
That was uh in the Emirates.
That was circle loco. That was a long
time ago.
I can't find it.
Anyway, good times. Um,
was I famous? I don't know if famous is
the right word, but uh I had a good
career. Let's just say I've got quite a
few discs.
Um
the data they present shown real
outcomes of thousands of day trades
across long periods of time. Probably be
a bit shocked at the evidence data that
all scalping is random. The outcomes
show everyone here gets totally random
outcomes. I think that's [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] I think that I think that's
bollocks.
It's all about entry and location.
That's bollocks. That's absolute
bollocks, mate. I'm sorry. That's that's
a quant saying that. Well, quants
probably get totally [\h__\h] random
outcomes.
So, I like I'm not buying into that.
Sorry.
If you're going to enter a random
position, you're going to get a random
outcome. If you understand who's
trapped, you're not going to get it. How
How else How else did I know that that
was going to happen? That's not random.
This gray box not random. This rotation
isn't random. This hold of this isn't
random. This isn't random. If you want
to enter here, well, you're random,
right? So, I just I just don't know.
That's just fundamentally flawed.
Sorry. Don't agree.
Um, they can say what they want, but uh
I don't agree with it.
Not going to lie, you helped me pass my
combound today. I was on a slow, steady
grind. Nine green consecutive days. I
took the short at IB high once I saw the
rejection on the 30 minutes, but your
long held. Oh, so you were going to be
short here, but that stopped you and
then maybe you came back in here. Nice.
$442 up today. Thank you, Alex. You're
welcome.
I mean, I don't know if I'm fun anymore.
I was I was probably fun in my 20s and
30s. Um,
stocks golf, snow milling, bass house
music. I mean, I I haven't DJed for
years and years and years now.
For a long time.
It's been a long time. But, uh,
I mean, I can show you.
Let me see.
I can show you some fun videos. You guys
will laugh.
But seeing as it's New Year's and
Christmas,
you guys will will have a laugh.
See me looking like an absolute wally.
Uh, get this on the right screen.
I'll make this smaller for you guys.
you guys bookm
and genuine
shooting our music video in LA. Hang on.
Get this up.
You guys see that?
This is many, many years ago. How many
years ago? It's got to be a decade. You
10 years ago.
I'm in here somewhere in a stupid red uh
outfit
somewhere. Somewhere here I am somewhere
around here.
Little cameo for my own record. That's
my mate Steph I did it with. So stupid.
There he is.
[laughter]
Good times, man.
Yeah, good times. Good memories. Good
memories.
Different life, man.
different life. But I toured a lot. I
drank a lot and I did all the
extracurricular stuff as well. I'll be
honest with you.
Surprised I'm still alive sometimes.
[laughter]
I don't look 40. That's very kind of
you. I don't feel 40. It's only when I
look back at me in my youth and I'm like
just feels so It's weird. It's like it
was Yes. It was yesterday and uh
back down. Here you go. Here you go,
Adam. Here's your cover. Here's your
cover.
Here's this shelf. So, full rotation.
All right. Look above IB. Fail. Look
above value. Fail rotation. Cover point
was this. Right. Runners now in case you
get down there.
>> [snorts]
>> Daryl Joseph. That's a That's a great
lyric from an old camel camel fat tune.
Is it Camel Fat actually or is it is it
um Salado? It might be a Salado record.
Can't remember.
You're going to get long off point of
control. [\h__\h] I'm not touching any of
this, man. This is uh no chance.
Not for me. You guys do what you want.
You You know how much I hate rotational
plays. So, you guys should uh
play what you like.
Play what you're enjoying. All
right, I'm going to get out of here in a
minute. Any That was a bit of fun. Let
you guys into my old career. Maybe when
I go back to London, I keep saying if we
if we buy a house here, I'll bring all
my discs and decks back and maybe we'll
have them behind me and maybe on like a
Friday afternoon, we we'll change the
stream after
after trading to a DJing stream.
Could be some fun.
be some fun.
Yeah. Boiler Boiler Room. Yeah, we call
it boiler house. I quite like that.
Boiler house. Cuz the boiler room is a
trading room as well, isn't it? We call
it boiler house. Boiler house Fridays. I
[\h__\h] love that, Adam.
>> [laughter]
>> Justin, I I randomly made $1,200 today.
There you go. There you go.
Do you DJ, Brandon?
FT after hours. Yeah, exactly. Boiler. I
really like Boiler House. That's That's
cool, man. Do I produce? Yes, I do. I
do. I'm still I'm still a producer. I'm
still signed to Warner Chapel. I
actually just reuped my publishing deal.
So, yeah, I'm still uh still produce and
I still write. Very It's It's much more
rare for me now. It's it's when I want
to do it and then I just either put
stuff out under an alias or I sell it.
Yeah, it's it's just when I want to do
it now. It's not It's not my job. This
is my job now.
But, uh you know, sometimes if I'm
feeling creative, I'll go and do
something.
I do actually
take talking about having a gig in
London soon. We'll be back in LA in
February. I'm currently in Asia. Where
in Asia are you, Brandon?
No, I produce on Logic. Everything I do
is in Logic. Unless I'm doing a mixtape,
I'll do it in Ableton.
All my old stuff is uh under a name
called Tough Love. I'm not part of it
anymore. I haven't been part of it for
four years. But Stefan's still my one of
my best mates. the guys doing doing it.
We were a duo together for almost
[snorts] 15 years.
I'm in China. I can't stand trading
there anymore. I actually uh DJed in
China.
I got I got flown out
uh by Spencer Taring
and
Mint, is it Mint Club in Shanghai? He
was like a resident there and he set up
an underground party which we went and I
got three songs on in before we got
closed down by the triads. I'm not
actually joking. I'm deadly serious.
was in Shanghai.
I was in Shanghai.
I want a Dubai vacation so badly. I'm
afraid of going overseas these days. Oh,
Dubai is super safe. No problems there.
When in Shanghai? probably 20
a long time. 2015.
[snorts] What? Mint's gone. Yeah, I'm
sure it has. I I used to know all the
guy All the guys there were the old uh
London residents from the West End.
It was all the same crew.
2015, maybe 2017. I feel like it's
before then. I don't think it would have
been there. 2017.
It was probably 20 uh it was it was
probably actually before 2014. I think
it's
maybe 2013 cuz Spence came over to see
me after that.
Yeah, I know. It's well over 10 years
ago.
I'm old. I haven't DJed in a long time.
Told you. Left that behind me
long, long time ago.
All right, folks.
Do I know a London DJ Mike Bond? No.
I've been to Mint. We stole a Rick Shaw
to get back to our hotel. Boy, I was
stupid back then. [laughter]
Do I know Max Chapman? Yeah, I know. Max
was working on a job with him before his
Oh, he's gone back to that. He's still
building again, right? He's building
houses and um and doing reverbs.
He just did a a tune with um
uh who's that singer? Oh, [\h__\h] It's
killing me.
Something man. Why can't my brain think
just sign it to defected? I say just
probably a couple months ago. Come to me
in a minute.
I used to be I used to do investment
banking in LA and I quit to do music.
Yeah, we've we've we've swapped we've
we've traded we've traded careers. I've
gone the other way.
Music look m music industry is fun.
Um
it's
what I love about trading is it's on
you. You eat what you kill. So if you're
disciplined and you have a system and
you trade well, you will make money. Uh
the problem with music or anything which
is creative is you're you're always at
the mercy of someone else's opinion, you
know. So, first thing you got to do is
like build your track record and then
you've got to go and get yourself a deal
and then you go and spend a [\h__\h] ton of
money on press and promo and then you
send it to radio and you know maybe they
don't like it or maybe before then you
can't get a deal because the ANR doesn't
like it. I mean I can tell you now my
two biggest hits which were big hits uh
got turned down for like three to four
years. Three to four years before anyone
would touch them. and we got told like
no one would like it, blah blah blah. We
were playing in them in our DJ sets. We
knew they were the standout records. Um,
my manager at time couldn't get it
signed. We went and cleared a Jodicy
sample. We gave it to Annie Mack. She
premiered it on the Friday and guess
what? My phone was [\h__\h] ringing by
the Monday with people wanting to do a
deal and then we did an album deal off
the back of it. That just shows you life
can change like that and it's all down
to someone's opinion. I think ANR is a
load of [\h__\h] nowadays. um they probably
care more about your metrics of Tik Tok
and Instagram than they do about your
actual ability. My belief has been the
same and maintain this the whole time. I
think there are some insanely talented
people that will never make it because
they never be given an in. And you would
have expected out of something like
COVID where you had so much depression,
so much hurt, so much pain, and so much
time that it would be some incredible
music come out. and instead we had
regurgitated shite and that speaks more
about the state of the industry than it
does about the artists in my opinion.
It's just my opinion, right? It's just
my opinion. Yeah, Frankie. I know my
last show in LA was with Frankie. He's
um I just actually saw this morning he's
about to announce residency at Pashia
this summer. Uh like
Yeah, I know Frankie well.
hard to make a living from it. Yeah.
Yeah, it can be. I mean,
these days you are sold everything.
Never get assigned, social media,
pushing, promotions, everything. Yeah. I
DJ and a lot of consulting work. Foreign
artists to bring Chinese artists
overseas. Oh, no. That's nice.
Do I like chicken tikka masala? I love
these questions. Uh, I love chicken
tikka masala. Can't get a good You
cannot get a good curry in LA though.
I'm telling you that. It's not like
being in Brit Lane or in the Midlands in
England.
[laughter] When I said any questions, I
meant more like, do you have any
questions about the charts that I can
help you with this afternoon? [laughter]
Oh, it's hilarious.
We're into discussing what our favorite
takeout is.
Yeah, I don't blame you. I'm I'm about
to sign off as well. [snorts]
Oh, it's funny.
I know. It's hilarious, isn't it? The
national English dish
is actually an Indian curry.
I I'm not I'm not a Greg sausage roll
guy. This is not my thing. This reminds
me of motorway stops. This jacket uh
Scot, this is Scotch and Soda.
It's funny you say that, SG Trades. I
was actually looking at that for a swing
position. Let's have a look.
The only worry is
it's uh
I think it's at a deep discount.
Right, we're back to to start of the
year. So if we think about we've given
back the whole year.
I will look at this because this is this
is interesting for me. Where did we
where's Jan?
Right. We've given back the whole year
and more. We're trading at deep
discount. Obviously this is direct
correlation to BTC. All right. So if we
have a quick look at BTC,
you're going to see it look very very
similar.
All right. Very similar peak high. We're
trading at what level? March 25. So MSTR
worse. Um I I I do wonder if this is due
a pop. I do wonder if this starts to
lift. Uh if we want to think about the
whole rotation
because I think it's been decimated
quite hard.
I mean, it can't even figure that out.
That's so bad. What is it doing?
That's [\h__\h] ridiculous.
How much we down on that swing to swing?
Let's just get the days right.
So, it's a two-year cycle.
down 72%.
Trading at the same levels
[sighs]
as 2024 highs. Doesn't mean it can't
come lower, but I'm not I am I'd be
lying if I said I wasn't interested.
Definitely if we drifted anywhere into
here. Um, but I think there's probably a
turnaround due even just for a pop back
in. If I was a short seller, I'm like,
this is how I would view this, right?
Even if we
do a fixed range from this break
and if we do an anchor from the high.
No, you don't want to do that anchor.
You're going to play bull. You don't
want to do it. Okay. Thanks, Trading
View. You absolute garbage piece of
crap.
We want to draw one on then.
Anchor this. Let's do an anchor from
here. Let's just do one from here a
second.
Big node here.
So, this is where I'd be interested in.
Let's let me just get a volume anchored
VWAP one second off the high
one more
and let me get one from this pivot here.
[sighs] It's not good.
I was hoping that would be underneath.
That's not great.
And I'm going to assume these guys are
all out the money as well. Yeah. Okay.
That'll be my only concern right now.
I'm going to be honest with you. So,
you've got this build out of a node
here,
right? If we can't hold that,
my expectations would be for a trade
down into 30s.
Okay. Do I think it's due some relief?
Yeah. I mean, it did have some last
week. Uh, I think at some point you're
going to see a trade back into here. All
right? Because you've got, this is,
you've got to imagine this is where guys
off these highs are stuck right now.
to 230s, let's just call it. This anchor
off the low is a problem. The fact that
they've accumulated since 2022,
all right, and they're now out the money
is a problem. And we've just failed. You
can see this trade back to it. They just
failed. All right, they failed the
reclaim. That was an attempt of a
reclaim of that anchor. All right. So,
I'd be careful. I wouldn't I wouldn't
feel the need to frontr run it. I'd be
careful for this drift. But at some
point, do I think this is going to
happen? Yeah. As a trade, whether it's
from here or here, it's highly probable.
At some point, we lift back into the
80s. Now, whether we reclaim that or not
is different, but that's still like a h
100 plus dollars even from here, like
$150 move. If shorts want to leave these
participants trapped, then they will
resell this, right? And then we'll use
the liquidity. Um, it really depends on
the macro sort of environment for next
year. Let me just check one more thing
while we're here.
Come on, Trading View. The [\h__\h] is going
on?
Oh my god, it's gone mental.
Can I not put
moving average on this? It's not going
to let me do it.
Let's just do
actually just want this 200.
Where's my 200?
Yeah, that's not good. What about on a
weekly?
Okay, that's interesting. So for a
weekly
that's probably a high probability play
a weekly back test
of this. So definitely in this in this
area here there is a possible bounce
around this weekly. So I think it's I
I'll say these things. I think it's at a
deep discount. I think it's probably
due a bounce up to here at some point.
It's going to have to get back through
this anchor first. This is an area of
interest to me. But if we fail this and
lose this area of interest, you've got
to imagine a deep rotation. This like I
don't think we come that far down. But
you just don't [\h__\h] know if Bitcoin
goes to [\h__\h] and we go into some
recessionary pressure and if if this
company has got overexposure, all right,
to that you don't know, but uh I would
say it's I would be interested along.
I'm with you. It's actually on my watch
list. I uh put it on at the weekend.
So yeah, that's where my head's at.
Hopefully that helps. Uh, the only thing
that would scare me right now is BTC
I think is going to have some issues.
All right, so they're trying to
accumulate. It's the same kind of thing.
BTC is trying to accumulate versus this.
Okay, but if they get failed
followrough, this is a peak high
breakdown, breakdown, failure. If we do
like a two-leg into here and you see
failure, they will come back for this.
Um,
you've just got to understand that
we have finished a,000 day cycle up here
on BTC
and an 80% pullback
uh is highly possible, not just probable
or a 78 to 80% which would take us, as
horrific as that sounds,
right? Let's just say 70% would take us
back down to here. And if you're like,
"That isn't doable." Well, it [\h__\h]
absolutely is,
right? 77. If we look at the pullbacks
after the cycles, after the big cycles,
they are drastic.
What was this one?
73. So, you have to be careful because
if we're measuring it out in cycles,
you see 80%. So 80 to 70% is possible,
right? And the and the cycle has been
huge. If we look at the cycle length,
it's achieved everything that you would
expect,
right? 1,000 days,
692%.
Right? If we look from this pin,
uh where's the days? 622 days normally.
So we normally we talk about a,000 days
maybe we go from here this accumulation
1,000 days
2,000%
you know if we go from here this first
big old bull run that we had
someone asked me earlier do I look at
cycles not for day trading but for swing
positions absolutely
There's that pin
uh over a thousand days again. So you
can see the cycle thousand days sell
thousand days sell thousand days sell
right the question is are we going to
see a 70 80% sale like here and like
here right that's that is a possibility
and that is what MSTR is exposed to
somewhere between 25 let's just call it
30,000 because it's probable that we're
going to come if we are going to sell
that this is the pivot right 30,000ish
If we see that, the risk exposure on
MSTR to that is drastic, right? That's
why we're seeing this, which will pull
us back down into the 50s. So, that's
the only thing I would say if you're
looking to accumulate here, if we start
losing BTC and there's you will see
panic start to enter in. All right. Uh
hopefully that helps, but it's something
that's worth watching for sure. Um,
definitely definitely for a bounce, not
necessarily for a long-term buy.
There you go. So, you can see how I
operate.
[snorts]
And the rotation continues, right? I
need to get out of here, man. What am I
doing? Um,
been trading silver more. Is it possible
to go over it? I can have a quick look
at it.
Nice bounce back today.
Right. Structurally
looks good.
All right. So, here's your failure to
make a new high from the other day.
There's the wash. Remember, this is on
the new futures
uh requirements, margin requirements. We
wash down key. Uh, in my opinion, we
hold this pivot. All right, this pivot's
held,
right? We hold the pivot. We've built
liquidity. We're going back upside now,
and we're going to repric. Uh, where are
the key levels? Well, clearly we go from
pivot high, pivot low. We're coming
right into one. All right, we're coming
right into that 61 fib.
If I was a short seller, it's very
simple. If I was a short seller, I would
want to be selling in this block here
and more notably in this block here,
right? I'd want to be forcing the hand
here. Now, if I can get a failure to
follow through up here as a short
seller, right? If bulls bulls are
trapped here, if I can use their pain
and come down and get a break, [snorts]
right, we can look for a lower price.
But overall, momentum is what? It's very
bullish. If we look at the daily, we're
bullish. We had an inside bar being
created today. This is what I talked
about yesterday. Macro wise, can this
keep going up? Yes. Silver um about to
have new legislation put in in China
where you have to sign all sorts of
[\h__\h] documentation to bring it out of
China. So, uh scarcity might or a lack
of supply, right? If we get more of a
lack of supply, we can have increased
prices. This is also a peg or a hedge I
should say against the dollar with gold.
All right? So Asia Asian markets
continue all right to come out
to come out of the dollar
to daily right Asian markets continue to
come out of the dollar they continue to
come out of
MAG or they might come out of MAG. Let's
just go
and beyond mags to be honest.
All right. Out if they come rotate out
of mags
and put downside pressure. All right.
Because they need
the extra uh equity to deal with what's
going on with the Bank of Japan. All
right. If they do this kind of move here
on the mags for early 2026, then I think
you're going to see gold and silver
continue to rally. It's big if but may,
but that this looks strong. All right,
this looks very very very very very
strong. Uh if shorts are going to come
in, they're going to have to come in the
next few sessions. All right, but these
bases can take a while to form. I would
say that in the metals, if we think
about what happened
last time,
all right, we had these big flush out
moves, these reversal flush out moves.
Boom, boom, boom, boom, boom. Based
settled. This was from October, really a
month, month and a half. All right,
before this sort of cup and handle
break, all right, momentum is still
bullish. If we still fail to follow
through in something like this, then
yeah, I think we can return back down to
these 50s. But it like if you
accumulated in here, I think you're good
to hold. But you you'd want to see a new
high or a base out. So you either want
to see this reclaim or a base out in
here. What you don't want to see is a
failure to follow through and this move
here, right? You don't want to be
holding through that.
But overall, macro environment wise, it
looks good. Like, is it overextended? I
mean, absolutely. We went over it
yesterday. It's well past two standard
deviations. I think it hit 2.6 standard
deviations on a daily. Well, well, well,
well past it.
Do you have a draw tool mapped to a
mouse button? I do not. I have to click
to it at the bottom.
Um,
no worries SG.
All right, folks. Uh, I'm out of here. I
stayed with you here much, much longer
um
than I anticipated. Nothing's really
happening here. Market's uh continuing
to rotate. All right, we came down to
this gray box, found a bid, we come back
up to previous day, value high, current
day, value high. Same thing. Rotation,
rotation, rotation, rotation. It's all
we're in. Don't be expecting too much
more than what you've had today. All
right, you volume's going to start
dissipating out. Um, as a reminder, um,
all the links are down below for my
recommended prop firms. I have put a
flash sale on for you guys who do want
to do the, uh, 20our beginner to advance
course, which comes with some flow zones
and it also comes with a discord. No
monthly membership, none of that stuff.
Onetime fee. Uh code 2026. That will
finish midnight on uh News Eve, right?
Midnight News Eve. I'll be back tomorrow
morning. Please trade safe, use hard
stops, all that good stuff. Be kind to
each other. Get off the screens if you
made your money or there's nothing here
you like. Remember, you trade for
freedom. That's financial freedom and
time. So, go and do something else with
your day. Peace and love, everyone. Take
care.