Morning.
Morning. Morning. How are we doing
everyone? Welcome back.
Welcome back. Hopefully some of you
here.
Hopefully you had a good uh good
Christmas holiday period. Uh markets are
moving this morning, so let's just focus
on that. So wishing you all fantastic
festive season. It's not over yet. So we
expect volume still to be light. All
right, we expect volume to be light. If
we focus on the daily chart. All right,
we can just have a look. Last week off
light volume. Uh you can see Monday,
Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday into Friday
just straight upside. Obviously we
missed uh the Thursday. There was no
Thursday, but straight upside on a light
volume drift. We're seeing that pullback
now. All right. So there was no recheck
of this area since that drift higher.
We're starting to see it into this low
volume node, right? So that's happening
overnight. So we're watching this. We've
got a cluster down here, 50-day, 20-day.
We've already let go of the 5day. So
we're back testing this. The question
really remains, are bulls able to hold
this area? We expected this pullback.
Unfortunately, it's happened without us.
It would have been nice to be involved
from this high volume node. You would
have seen we talked about this in the
newsletter, right? And in there, the old
point of control, two week balance range
in here. We're rejecting that old point
of control. We expect a pullback right
into this node. We've already done that.
So, the question now remains, do bulls
defend this for the move back up? Do we
go sideways or are we going to start
collapsing underneath this in the
market? And we can look for the hourly
for a few more clues into what's really
going on. So, let's have a look there.
Over into the hourly chart. Move this
one up for you. Make sure you can see it
all. All right. You can see here. Here's
the old balance range which we are
rejecting. All right, this looks a
little bit different because it's on the
new contract, but uh that old balance
range basically the point of control can
measure out here from the week uh going
back to Monday the 8th, right? Comes
right in at 9:22.
And you can see we hit highs just over
that 946. We peaked above an old balance
range inside last week's rotation.
Here's uh or last the Friday's rotation.
Friday's rotation. Old balance range was
actually 22s right here. All right,
we're starting to reject that point of
control. We lost previous day. We're
inside previous week. We're back down to
the bottom side of this profile from
previous week. So the question really is
very very simple. Do bids come back in
here? Remember this is a low volume node
on the daily? The daily profile from the
year looks something like this. Okay. So
do we protect in here? Do we project
against the previous week point of
control, the previous week's value? All
right, this is where bulls must come in
to defend this. If they're going to hold
dips, they really want to be holding
into the previous week's value into here
or a look below and fail and a reclaim
for a move back up. If they stay heavy,
all right, if there's increased pressure
on this market, we have that gap fill
potential, right, which we can think
about gap fill potential. If we lose
that, we're looking at the previous
week's value into 527 and then down into
the 33s.
Fact, I'm going to move this down right
here. 333s. [snorts] All right, so
that's what we're looking at. I want to
first think about dips.
All right, as we come into the other
side of range because this based on the
previous week is cheap. All right, this
is discount. [snorts] So, do we want to
trade inside? If we can't reclaim point
of control and we lose value, then I'll
be thinking about this into these levels
here. Very, very simple. I want to be
nimble today and careful with sizing and
positioning given that we're seeing
weakness in the market on a very very
low volume uh period. Okay, so don't
want to be overly aggressive and sized
in. You can see this move here on the
5minute chart. Really, really clean.
This was once we broke down. All right,
here's the rollover. Right. Peak above
that two week balance range. Peak above.
Peak above. Peak above. Fail. Fail
previous day. There comes the rotation.
Fail to get back above those 770s and
back into previous week point of
control. Previous week value area low
below us. All right, let's have a look
at the broader market because there are
lots of things moving right now.
Move you up here and go to five minute
and just focus on the spiders. All
right. spiders doing the same thing
here. Starting to see that rotation.
Okay, big highs here
and starting to see that pull back
inside into this kind of cliff shelf
into 85s I would say. So even on the
options I would say 85 is probably a big
level underneath that we know that it
was going to be the same as before 85s
82s 80s and you can see this old put
wall down here at 70s long long way away
but we want to see if uh there is some
response here into 85 on the spiders for
that move back up. I would be watching
in case we get that Q. Same kind of
story, right? Coming down. You can see
these key levels down here into well 20s
if we reclaim and then 17s below and 15s
below is what we're looking out for. Uh
the big movers are coming in the metals
though. So big gap up here in VIX. We're
still in the low teens. I want to be
aware of that. We're still in the low
teens gapping up into an area which we
have uh struggled at before. It's an old
pivot. So really the question is is uh
the VIX able to reclaim this? If the
answer is yes, then we might have
increased downside volatility coming in
this market this morning. Uh gold
leading actually probably copper leading
I would say. You can see bit of a
blowoff top here coming back into what
could be an RBS level. We can clean this
up. All right, this area here is an area
of interest. Right, if they're going to
hold dips on gold, I think we're
probably going to see a short-term
pullback and it might last a month or
two before we go again. Uh the main eyes
right now are on the liquidity or
potential liquidity issues uh over on
silver which you may have followed last
week which went on a ginormous pump over
[snorts] the Christmas period. All
right, was did another 25% last week.
We're seeing that kind of blowoff top.
You are going to see some short sellers
come into this market here trying to
capture some of the move as we see some
profit taking. So this is the failure to
follow through that we always talk
about. That's your first failure to
follow through coming back into range.
Um I would be interested this in a swing
short if we're going to come back down
into here and then see if they go over a
number of months of accumulation before
trying to have another run. The bigger
problems right now when we're looking at
stuff like that is the macro
environment. You know, is there going to
be a liquidity crisis in this market if
some banks start to uh forego closures?
Apple all right big gap down here. All
right, had a second attempt higher last
week.
gapping down coming under pressure but
coming into potential RBS zone remember
this is where we went sideways for a
long time so gap down on Apple let's go
across the mags gap down on Amazon here
right bid gap down on Amazon but again
can afford to come back down to the
bottom side of this range where it keeps
finding dips gapping down and actually
losing a bit of bid but you know this is
our structure that's the swing point do
we find a dip from here or are we going
back into range here. This is unhealthy
if we do that for the market in general.
Uh we were talking about that before the
Christmas period.
Meta, same kind of story back down into
the bottom side of its range right now.
Weakness in this market, gapping down.
Same story here on Microsoft. Uh this
doesn't look too good to be honest. Uh
right into the midpoint of the range.
That's the one that I'd probably leave
alone. Wait to see if either of these
come or a look below and fail or a look
above and fail. wouldn't really want to
be trading Microsoft right now, I don't
think. Nvidia, well, there's a blowoff.
All right, try to reclaim. You have to
think about where you are on a bigger
time frame, right? Coming right back
into this level of supply on Nvidia.
It's trying to get up there. Can it hold
a dip for that move? Failure to do so.
We've got this marked out. It's uh the
key level, which hasn't yet broken down
from. So, it still looks okay on Nvidia,
to be honest. Looks pretty good, but
gapping down today, but just not too bad
long term. Tesla just missed those uh
500s. All right, got pretty good close
99s. So, back into this shelf now. It's
a very volatile stock. Giving the whole
lot back and uh into the 66s. If we
start breaking down, staying heavy under
that, I would be very careful because
you're going to leave all this volume
trapped. So, either look below and fail
on Tesla. Otherwise, if we look below,
stay heavy. We're coming down into these
30s again. Market's got about five
minutes left here. Uh we can have a look
at some of the broader names. Expect
some of these look weak. That doesn't
look too bad over there on Oracle. Uh
can it hold a bid? I'd say versus 190 is
on Oracles. Have a look at some of the
chip names. AMD
not too bad. Let's have a quick look at
AVGO and then look at some of the beta
names.
Not too bad either. It needs to find a
hold a bid in here into the 40s.
>> [cough]
>> A quick scan through some of these sort
of gamma exposure names. RGTI. Expect
some of these to start collapsing soon.
IO and Q's already starting to do it.
MVTS probably starting to do it. Yeah.
There goes RTI. These are the ones
starting to collapse. It's a shame.
Would have loved a reshort opportunity
up here, but we will see. We will see
what we get. All right, folks. That
should have you prepared. You know what
we're looking for. Um, nice and easy
today. Don't go uh forcing big size. You
will not want to be forcing big size in
a market like this.
Make sure you understand where we are
placed on uh last week's value, etc.,
etc. And as long as you understand that,
you've uh make sure you're positioned
correctly for it.
[snorts] Uh won't get a chance to go
through all the good morning. So, you
want the volume up. Uh it can't go much
higher. Might have to turn it up your
end. There we I've pushed it a little
bit. Probably just need to
get closer into it. Do I trade silver?
Uh I don't actively trade silver, but I
need to be aware of what's going on in
silver. All right, so you big squeeze
out last week.
Uh the bigger problem is if uh there are
banks placed short positions on there,
margin requirements went up over the
weekend. shouldn't [snorts] really
affect the banks, but if anyone's been
silly and overpositioned into it and do
get start to get called out on margin,
we've had a pullback, so it shouldn't
affect them too much. If there's a
resqueeze,
I'll just be watching the knock-on
effect of that. You've got to understand
why silver and gold are going up. It is
the hedge against the dollar. All right,
it's been happening for years now. Uh
Asia coming out of backing the dollar,
going into a hedge in gold,
consequently, silver. copper is normally
the leader over in that market and then
if you look broader than that it's do we
have some liquidity issues starting to
happen with what's going on with the
bank of Japan etc etc so if you go into
a cascade effect of those uh metals
pumping and uh Japan forced to sell
their position in US uh
bigger issues ahead if that happens all
right here we go folks couple minutes
left just watching us we're balancing
right Now around the previous week point
of control, previous week's value area
low is this previous week low underneath
us. Yes, into sixes. Yeah, this previous
week low beneath us. Right. So, just
watching that. We do have a gap that
never quite got filled uh down into
these sixes as well. So, want to be
aware of that. But right now, starting
to sort of find a somewhat of a bid. So,
remember this is discount last week.
This is point of control list last week.
This is fair value. This is discount.
All right. This is minus D discount down
here. So, we don't really want to be
short down at these lows unless we're
going to start to roll over and lose a
bid underneath and migrate back down to
the week before its uh value. All right.
So, we're going to watch very very
carefully how we act here into the open.
One minute left. Morning everyone.
Morning. Morning. Morning. morning.
Uh, yes. Well, quite right, CC. I mean,
it's just a shortterm um position where
they're all down at the same time. It it
won't last long. Things will change.
Yeah, things will change. What you're
just seeing is some risk off across
every sector right now, but that that
will change and you'll probably go back
into some level of um
uh correlation.
Did everyone have a good Christmas
though? That's the most important thing.
Do you get time with your friends and
families? Market finding a bit of a bid
here as we expected early morning.
Here
we [snorts] go. Here's the open folks.
So, let's just see if they soak this off
any of these levels or this going to be
continued rejection down here.
Just going to give this a minute to
shake out, especially first day back.
Very, very thin on that open.
into these.
So, all of the mag red, all of those
beta names red other than Neo, the one
Chinese name I've got on my watch list.
[snorts]
Everything down other than gold. VIX up
over those 15. So, we've got our eye on
that. I want to see if VIX starts to
reclaim and base out or not as we trade
back into the low side of value. Spiders
into their 5day moving average or in and
around there. market trying to catch a
bit of a bid down here. Way too early
for me. Just gonna especially first day
back. Just let this settle down for a
minute.
Yeah, I think most mo most people missed
that drop. You would have done well to
uh to have got that. I would have said,
can we come back down to previous week
value area low, previous week low, or
they going to defend this with bids in
front of it? That's the question right
now.
New York open so far staying heavy. Mag
staying heavy. Yes, trying to find a
little bit of a bid here. Q's have
relative weakness right now. Apple's
gone red to green or at least it's
closed its gap.
They are trying to find some bids down
here at the moment. Come on. There we
go.
700's going to be key. and then New York
open. If they're going to hold bids down
here and get back above previous week
point control, they're going to have to
get back above these levels that we're
at now. [snorts]
[cough and clears throat]
Tesla losing I just got sorry
notification. Don't know why that came
up on my phone. Losing that 65. So big
level on Tesla if it stays heavy down
here. Here's the New York open drive.
All right. So they found bids here this
morning.
Maybe back up to test GlobeEx some of
these Globex levels now
into this shelf. All right, we can see
clear shelf here into 730 all the way up
to 770s.
So, can they reclaim that shelf at 730s?
If not, if there's a rejection there,
then we'd probably go and complete the
rotation to uh
uh previous value area low.
I'm just trying to let all this settle
down for a moment. Wonder if there's a
short opportunity up here on a drive up
if they trap bulls up here or if they're
just going to go reclaim and back into
value on a rotation from last week.
Remember that we can rotate all the way
back up to 820s. No problem. It's not a
huge move. 660s to 820s over the next
coming days. That's the rotation that
we're in right now. I would imagine up
here there might be a short between 730
and 770. We will have to see see what
they do. Just going to give it time.
Thank you, Kelvin. Yeah, well, you know,
market's been very thin the last few
days. I've barely watched it to be
honest. It's important that uh we
remember why we trade. It's for freedom
to spend time with our families. If
we're sat here over the Christmas and
holiday period, there's probably
something wrong with us. We don't want
to do too much of that.
Yeah, very possible, Josh. Very, very
possible.
Starting to get stuck here into 720s. I
want to see a retest up here in 730s if
possible. Uh, starting to see some
bullish action up here get trapped. So,
I am interested in the short up here if
we fail. Um, but trying to give this a
little bit of time to develop, but it's
starting to get close to those 730s.
Everything above 714 is aggressive
buyers not getting their way right now.
Right. point control in this session's
moved up to 714 7:15. So I'm looking to
see if we get up towards that 730 or 770
track buyers and see if some sellers
come back in market. Staying heavy
across the board right now. Where's
Tesla? Right back at that 65.
So I'm interested in what happens in
this sort of area here. Do buyers get
trapped somewhere in here? Do we reject
this? Do we reject this? If the answer
is no and we do this, then I'm not
really interested much at all. We will
see.
Still they push
more buyers getting uh piling in here
without the ability to move higher yet.
There's definitely some passive selling
up here. All very light.
Yes. Doing the same thing coming up to
this sort of shelf here into 57s. It's
got VWAP above 24hour VWOP into 61s. It
might want to fill. We're right the way
up here at 61s as well, interestingly.
So, both VWOPS at 61s. More buying
coming up here trying to force this
market higher. Mag staying red right
now.
ES could not get as ES VIX could not get
back above those 1508s.
So, some rejection there on ES. I'm
starting to get interested. This is the
kind of level that we talked about these
730s, right? 730s and above. We're
starting to see some reaction here.
Market really needs to close back
beneath 7:15 to leave any buyers
trapped. So, still not interested yet.
Just watching at these key levels.
Remember, if it wants to squeeze up to
770, if they just lift the offer, they
will let it through. That's fine. We can
uh watch higher, but I'm starting to get
interested in what's happening on the
tape here.
It might be that nothing comes at all.
These are the levels we're interested
in.
So, some of you I know were long out the
gate. I would be taking a partial into
here and then seeing holding a runner
just in case you get all the way up here
if you were long. I'm waiting to see if
there's a short opportunity which there
might not be. But uh here we go. So they
lifted and then we're going to come back
for this VWAP test now. And this is the
area of real interest and intent
is they've done a big old shove up.
How much more juice have they got? Some
clearly
still going
into this old pivot. Now we come. Maybe
they come and wash people out there. So
if you were long, you're looking good
into the 85. Big old squeeze. Apple
going green.
Tesla reclaiming that 65 level. Still
just watching here.
Very, very thin on this move. Maybe we
come up to this previous week value area
high in one push. Just do a full
rotation. Who knows? It's very thin. It
wouldn't take a lot to do anything into
these 800 tests.
Still no position for me. Just waiting
here to see how we are. Starting to get
my head around what this market wants to
do in this first session. Back up we go
into previous week value area high. Big
big big shove here. All right. So, we
expect sellers to come in and defend
this. We've just rotated
from uh previous week point of control.
Never came to value. We're coming right
back up to previous week value area
high. I would say around here because we
didn't because we didn't defend this.
You'd imagine around here there will be
some profit taking on this recent shove
up and then we see what's what 812 saw a
big seller step in there. Huge seller
is we're so thin. It would not take much
to move this market either way right
now. You can keep
shoving it around. No one's really at
the table yet. Nice full forward. Yeah,
I thought it was you that said you were
long premarket or just before the open.
Really nice. And just lock some in here
inside of value. So, we expect them to
protect value if we're going in a range
rotation.
It is very thin. Very, very thin.
Nice work, folks. All you that got long
for the move up. Really nice.
That runner work quick. You see how
quickly they lifted it from there to
there. Very, very quick. It's cuz we're
a very, very thin market right now.
Really will not take a lot to move this.
So, really bulls will want a pullback to
hold into this area here. They must hold
that area there. So there is some shorts
coming in here defending this level.
Point of control now move to 95. If they
lose that there is a possible pull back
into here and then we have to decide
what we do. All right. If they pull back
into here, remember this is basically
midpoint of this range. It's not ideal.
And then bulls can have another attempt
for this. You want to be careful of a
fail breakout over that. So if you're
bullish, you want to absorb dips here.
If they lose that, the full rotation can
happen.
And their target right now is to get to
previous week value area high. And then
this level up here 860s. This would be a
gap fill, right? This is gap fill.
Previous uh Friday's point of control,
Friday's value area low would be gap
fill. So if they can absorb on this
pullback, that's your only shot left to
go higher.
What is this blue level I've got marked
out here down?
We go.
Okay, some big sellers trying to step
in. Still being absorbed. So, I'm just
waiting for this tape to calm down.
Apple third of a percent up.
Tesla's lost that 65 again. It's not a
good sign for the broader market. If it
stays heavy under there, it's going to
be a problem. Starting to see this move
back towards this sort of gray box. All
right, this sort of area here in VWAP.
If they lose that, I'd be very, very
worried for those of you who are been
bullish.
Giant squeeze up here so far this
morning off very very thin volume.
somewhat of a messy date.
So, value low on this current session
all the way down at 716s.
We're right at point of control right
now. So, market's starting to sort of
calm down a bit.
Tesa reclaim 65 again. So, it's big over
under that level. Big big overunder.
Silver uh
not able to get back above
the previous lows here. keeps rejecting
72s.
Still weakness in silver.
Market getting a bit wonky here.
Remember, we've got news at 10:00 as
well, folks.
Doing on these spiders
rejecting that old low on the spiders as
well. Is that Friday's low? the uh
previous day low still being rejected on
Friday on spiders but still finding a
bid
off that 5day and VWAP. So market just
in a small rotation here while it makes
its mind starting to build a bit of
volume out in this area that we're at
right now. Dips so far holding not quite
coming to this level yet.
There are some buyers stuck above 14s on
this auction but not a lot but there
were some buyers. The sellers got
aggressive from twelves. They've tried
again to get aggressive at 94 and not
had success. So that's kind of the
rotation right now is sort of from 95 to
14s I would say and we can see if
there's fail follow through or buyers
succeed in getting back up to previous
week value area high and just see what
we get. Yeah, I want to do some
giveaways today. Not expecting too much
of a trading session, but yeah, smash
that like button. We give away some uh
Apex accounts and maybe some other stuff
later on.
stuck in balance right now in rotation.
It's definitely thin like at uh 94130 we
saw some big sellers step on the tape.
One, two, three, four of them in a row
just plummeting the market about 25
points and then it got absorbed off
pretty much nothing.
So, uh it is thin out here still.
We're starting to build out this range
here. We can put some volume on now.
been here a little while.
There we go. Thank you. Got it. So, you
can see this shelf starting to be built.
If we lose this shelf, we're very thin.
They don't catch a bid. If they don't do
the old bear trap in here, all right, if
they don't catch a bid, we're coming
right back down into this because we're
very thin. So, they need to catch a bid
here for the sort of bear trap kind of
look. Otherwise, if they uh start doing
something like this and collapsing,
we're going to come right back down.
Just watching this shelf as it starts to
build out a little bit here.
Here we go. Starting to leave this
shelf. So, if they don't find a bid
here, it will get very, very weak. It's
very, very thin. So, I'm watching this
carefully. Tape starting to get a bit
more aggressive. There's a bid down at
770. I want to see if we come into this
sort of 770 level. He's in my gray box.
VWAP's kind of around there just
underneath and he is bidding on this
tape here.
Is there much below? Yeah. So 75 down to
65 they're sort of bidding at right now.
Just waiting to see if we come down into
that and hold a bid or not.
Spy just found a bid at VWAP as well so
far.
Is that pre-market high on the cues? I
think it is. Yeah, it's basing over
pre-market high on the cues
this point of control around the 95s.
This is going to be key here.
Do we see a rejection? Here comes 9:45.
Opening range now set. See if we reject
this for this move into here. Here we
go. Starting to move down into it. Nice.
Okay.
Been shortening this now. And then let's
see. Covering some here. Let's see if
there's continuation here. But buyers
need to save this right here, right now.
Otherwise, we go wash all the way down.
Lovely.
Want to be very careful here. They're
starting to get aggressive on the sell.
Very aggressive. There's some absorption
here into 50s. If we let go of that,
we've got more room. More absorption
into 50s. They've tried twice now to get
through the 50s. Here they come. Really
nice. So, I'm going to leave this shelf
now
down to small size here because I'm
expecting a pullback at some point.
There's through the 50s into this buy
side imbalance which is down to 42.
Under here we go value area low on the
session to 30s.
Bit of a bid here in this old imbalance.
30s is the next stop. Moving my stop
kind of tight here out of this for the
first move. expecting a reprice here
back towards
65s to 70s and I can reload on the short
if they stay heavy there. So we're just
in a rotational market. We left this
shelf. Once we left that shelf I joined
in covered most into this sort of pocket
here. If we offer a reload here I'll be
looking for this. If we reclaim I won't
be looking at anything.
[snorts]
You took that Alex. I did it 736. So,
you took it long 736. Yeah, I I'm I'm
didn't take anything early in the
market. I just wanted to get my head
around what this market wanted to do.
I'm watching this now, this, and this
for a reload. Anything here is a reclaim
and go. So, I only want to be short if
they trap buyers on this next move up.
Remember, we got news at 10:00.
News at 10:00.
8:25. Where's that? [sighs and gasps]
Don't like that. They're not they're not
really defending in front of that right
now. So, we will see.
Back to VW up. ES holding it New York
open as well there.
Microsoft now gone red to green. Apple
gone red to green. I need to let this
shake out a little bit here. This is
kind of the area for the reshort. I just
don't feel fully comfortable with how
this tape's moving at the moment.
They are trying to resell. What's the
low of this auction? Looks okay.
Protecting value area low on this
session now then which is 46es. So value
for me 46es. This is now value. I'm
watching Ninja. So this is value now.
This is the rotation at the moment.
Okay. No rotation under here yet until
we successfully auction under. Watching
this carefully.
If we do let go, we're very very thin
down into 19s. So watching to see if
they bare flag this like we just talked
about
versus this gray area is looking bit
better.
Need to see a harsh snap here before I
add any size on. Here we come.
Sellers, are you going to come here? We
got to get through this imbalance.
I want to see a snap
edge of this imbalance. Looking better
now. Much better now. Can we complete
this rotation now?
Moving my stop.
Nice. Okay. Watching here into 30s. Want
to be careful at 30s. Then we're going
to go all the way back down to where we
found a bid this morning. So this node
here into 19s and 20s becomes important.
And if we snap that, we go lows. Really
good. We've seen lots of bids here on
the market into these 20s. So moving my
stop along with this now protecting
big level here at 30s.
Some sellers keep coming in here at 30s.
They're not able to move through. We can
see the bids down here. 25, 20s, and 10.
Do not want to see this reclaim value
now. I want really want 50s to stay
heavy. 50s have got to stay heavy now.
If we're going to complete the rotation
back down to here, as you can see,
squeeze up very very thin up.
Thin up. Built volume. Lost the volume.
Bare flag. Looking for a rotation into
here. Right. They might well protect
this when we might build out a D-shaped
profile for the day on low volume. I
don't know. If they let go of this,
then, you know, maybe we can complete
this move down here. Just trading what
I'm seeing folks in front of me on a low
volume day. Not going to uh over
overstay my welcome on anything. We're
within previous week's value right now.
There you go. to the bids. They're
trying to protect these 30s and 20s.
Yes, still holding that New York open,
right? Cannot get underneath that New
York open. You want to watch that New
York open there at 51s.
They keep bidding off it. I'm out of
this now. I can wait for a reload again
if I want to.
Lots of buyers trying to come in to
squeeze this up. Remember, we got news
in 10 minutes.
News in 10 minutes. So, same kind of
level. We're looking at this sort of
gray box and volume above 84s. So, all
the time
this level stays heavy. Shorts can maybe
get down into here. If they reclaim
this, then the long squeeze trigger is
on.
I'm flat now. So, I was short from this
break. We added some here and I'm flat
now. Just waiting to see what next. Just
being very, very careful. It's my first
day back. Not fully dialed in yet.
>> [snorts]
>> How do I see the bid bid is there?
Because I'm watching the level two.
Watching the tape. I'm watching beyond
just the candles. Candles show me the
structure. But level two order flow.
That's what showed me what's really
going on. Maybe they complete this now
into 20s. I'm out of it though. So on
chase now. Right. This is that bid. So
they're reloading the bid here at 30s.
It's the same player. They flush through
this. You should go 20 straight away.
Really? They're reloading this bid at 30
though. He's been it couple times this
morning.
And one more time. Do they flush through
him to 20? 30 is his level. And they
should come down. He's trying to offer
or bid some at 25. You should come 20
and then teens here if you're still in
this. You do not want it to reclaim 30s
now though, okay? Because he just came
in heavy to protect that and losing. So
you want him to stay out the money.
Here's the 20s.
You would need 30s to stay heavy here in
my mind.
Clear shelf there. Really good. Those of
you still in this looks good. There's
the 20s. Here comes the teens into the
10ens. This is New York open. Cover some
here, please, folks. Into this level.
And if we start losing previous week
point control, remember we expect buyers
to come back in here. They've shown this
morning that they're trying to defend
this level. Right. We squeezed out of
here. Let me draw it for you, are we? We
squeezed out on thin structure. We
trapped buyers at the highs. We came
back down. buyers might reload here. If
they fail to reload here, then these are
your targets for runners, right? Anyone
who took the short from here or reloaded
this, right? TP, these are the targets
[clears throat] for the runners here. We
expect buyers probably want to defend
this because this is where they showed
their hand earlier, right? This can be a
break and retest and a go if they really
want. Remember, news at 10. Really nice
trade.
[snorts]
There's no there's no special thing on
my bookmap, guys. There's there's it's
just standard. You don't need like some
crazy template or anything like that.
It's just standard, right? All you're
reading when you're looking at bookmap
is order flow. It's as simple as that. I
don't have any special indicators,
anything like that. Main thing I'm
looking at on bookmap is delta, right?
Buy aggressive buyers and sellers, which
are what you might call the bubbles, and
then the passive bids,
which the horizontal
Uh yes, in my orderflow course, right?
So if you go on my website,
flowzonetrader.com,
I think there's still a sale. Uh if you
use capitals launch, you'll get $100 off
that finishes in January.
Yeah, I go through bookmark, I go
through footprint, I go through track
participants, I go through delta, delta
divergence. Everything is in there,
folks. Okay, we're coming back down to
this New York open. You can see the bids
keep reloading here at 10 and 700s. EST
has uh found a little bit of a bid here
into that same level. The New York open
keeps trying to defend it.
Uh you can get a heat map on Ninja, but
I it would be an an extra thing, but I'm
watching bookmap.
Yeah. So, I'm watching bookmap. You can
see it just above me right on my screen
right here. This is what I'm watching.
All right, folks. This is what I'm
watching.
And then beyond that, I'm watching
footprints. Okay, which for you will be
here.
I'm watching footprints.
See, starting to find a bid. We might
come and fill some of these sellside
imbalances all the way up here if they
want.
Can't put everything on stream,
unfortunately. Uh not that I don't want
to. I just I don't have the room for
absolutely everything. [snorts]
It's bookmap above me is bookmap. It's
called bookmap.
Okay, that pop just failed. They just
came into 55s. ES rejecting VWAPs. There
are some buyers stuck here at 58.
Not sure this has finished the downside
auction yet. There's a big shelf there
that we built out at 14s, but that was
pretty clear sign that they're not done
with it yet.
VIX trading at the low of this range
which is not what you want to see. So
divergence across the board right now
settle down
news here in five minutes or four and a
half minutes folks.
Yeah, those buyers definitely just got a
little bit caught up there.
100% they got caught up there in that
last shove. But we developed pretty
thick shelf here in 13s. Value area low
for this current session is where we are
right now. You can use a New York open.
That blue line is your sentiment right
now.
We will see.
Tesla a dollar below that 65 level. Now
give you a readout on these. Tesla 2.33%
down. Nvidia 2.06% down. Microsoft 0.05%
down. Meta 0.83% down. Google over half
a percent down. Amazon 0.12% down. Apple
holding on 0.15%
green. All right. So they only won beta
names mixed bag. Most of them are down a
little bit. RGTI 1.30% down. MBTS 0.41%
down. And QQ quarter of a percent down.
IR 2.80% up. Uh yeah, most names across
the board sort of a little bit red right
now. What's that big winner I saw
earlier flash up my scan? I can't see it
now. Maybe it's gone. Maybe it was
wrong.
[snorts]
Might
have to wait for this news here. Might
have to wait for this news. But you can
see we're in a rotation. All right,
we're we're doing a rotation. We left
Friday, right? Friday was here. All
right, so we left that. We opened up
down here. Unfortunately, it would have
been nice if we didn't do that. But
there's previous week, previous week's
rotation's here. Friday's rotation was
above. We left Friday. We opened up. We
haven't actually retest previous week
value area low, but we held point of
control and we came back up to previous
week value area high just missing it.
Unfortunately, rotation is being built
out inside the previous week's value.
Remember, we are thin. We are thin until
we get to January. We're going to remain
thin, I would say, unless you know
there's a liquidity issue and everyone
runs to cover. Um, but we'll see.
Hi, Alex. In your course, where do I
find your TV setup? flow zone,
footprints, etc. Uh, if the footprint
setup, everything I go over footprint is
in the volume and order flow course. Uh,
the flow zones and stuff is in the
beginner to advance course.
If you do them both together, if you go
to to the checkout, it will give you a
discount if you want to do both of them.
I'm not sure. Maybe you're already in
them. [snorts]
News. Yeah, there is news coming today.
And I think it's just house sales, but
it's the only news we've got today. So,
you never [snorts] know. It might move
the market. And just make you guys
aware. Not red folder, but new home
sales, I think it is, which I can't
imagine are that good, even though they
have cut rates. Going to take a while to
see that start to affect anything.
Starting to build out a range here.
Yes, backing into this New York open
again.
see follow through. I don't think we
finished selling yet, but uh
we will see. These 700s look like they
want to be tagged. Here they go. They're
back into the shelf again. This guy
right here. If they lose that, it's the
New York open is the big over under.
Yes, it's under it right now. Sellers
coming in at those lows. Not seeing
follow through yet. I think 700s are
very, very possible here.
very aggressive here on the tape. There
they go. Here's the 700. So now back
into this New York open. What do they do
here is the question.
So if you're still in the short, you
look good. This New York open is your TP
somewhere around here. Sellers are
coming flying in here and starting to
get themselves bit aggressive at the
lows. So just TP some out. I'm not in
any of this now. Like I said, already
covered on that last move down to here.
This last one down here.
If we start collapsing this, you're
watching this previous week point
control this blue box. Do they find a
bid here? If they don't find a bid here,
we have clear targets. All right. If
they don't find a bid here, we have
clear targets. If they find a bid here,
rotation back up to here is possible.
This is our shelf now. So, we built one
shelf, two shelves. All right. How we
act here or here is possible for the
rest of the day or at least for the rest
of this session.
Where's my delta and everything gone?
There it is. There we go.
[snorts]
Right, back to these teens. Back to
these lows. Still in front of this New
York open. Big seller just came in here
into 25s. There's still bids on this
tape. Someone keeps reloading the bid
here at 15 and 10. Think he probably
gets swiped. It's It's a matter of time
till he gets swiped. He's been here a
lot here. He's going to get swiped.
There's your New York open. This is
sentiment. Now, what do they do with
this? If you come under New York open,
maybe previous weak point of control,
but you should have been covering some
into this move.
[snorts]
Here comes the news as well. then I
guess
so. New York open this blue line. You
can see they found a bid right on it.
It's New York open so far right on that
blue line.
[snorts]
Do I trade CFD or futures? I trade
futures. Why would you ever choose to
trade a CFD over future? If you can
trade a future, trade a centralized
exchange. Don't trade an exchange where
your broker can uh [\h__\h] you over. They
can slip you legally
retesting value area low. Now it looks
very different on mine here. So value
area low for me on Ninja is 27s. So do
they find a bid in front of that or not?
If they do, we can go back into rotation
inside value for the session, right? and
we can go right back up to this shelf.
So, I'm watching sort of 27 somewhere
around here. I'm not going to trade it.
If they hold this, all right, the
rotation is possible. If they let go of
this, I'm expecting, especially under
here, we have low hanging fruit if they
want to really go for it. At the moment,
we're just going into a rotational
market. My least favorite market to
trade, as you guys will well know.
How do I see it? Again, using orderflow,
guys. Using order flow, you won't see
the sellers and buyers unless you're
using some form of order flow, whether
that be footprint or
um
uh bookmap or watching the DOM.
Where this big seller came in is right
here where we are now. 165 lot came in
at 720 and below. So they need it back
below 720. These sellers if they don't
get it back below 720s they are going to
remain stuck down here. They need it
back below 720s for them to be back in
the money. So this is how it becomes
key. Now if buyers bid at 720s then the
sellers remain stuck. If buyers don't
bid at 720s, then sellers can come back
in, try and complete that rotation
underneath that New York open.
So, this is why 720s is starting to
become key here.
Yes, underneath that New York open or
sort of right at it. So, 720s becoming
key here. Do we start to stay heavy
underneath this and let these sellers in
the money? Here we go. So, big selling
came in at 13s. That's the next level
under 20s, 13s and then 10. And then
under there we're thin and we can look
at for expansion underneath that New
York open. So this kind of area here is
the key battle. Now this is where
sellers keep trying to get acceptance
lower at these lows and they're not able
to yet. We are seeing some form of
passive buying. Uh CBD looks absolutely
terrible in this session. I'll tell you
that much. Looks looks awful. It's
because there's not much volume.
[cough]
Big seller coming in again here at 15.
So here's the break, right? They need to
get under this New York open now. That's
what they're looking for. Still seeing
absorption down here again. So big
seller coming one, two, three times in
this area. They need that break lower
underneath this New York open. That's
where they're going to start feeling
comfortable. They're coming in
aggressive again here. really heavy here
selling big big seller down here.
Starting to reload in the 10s. He's
getting annoyed. He wants it underneath
this New York open. He's getting very
annoyed here. Still a bid. Once this bid
goes, you will see a flush probably to
690s from what I'm seeing on the tape.
Yeah, no position for me here, folks.
Here's the New York open again. They're
trying again here. Yes, doing the job.
It's actually underneath it.
So huge selling stepped in here now. I'd
say from sort of 15s down to where we
are now. They need a break lower. We
have a sellside imbalance as well up to
20 which we might go and tap into here.
We are not under that underneath that
New York open.
Tesla continuing to sell underneath
those 65s 465. So here's the imbalance
refilled. Still not breaking underneath
that New York open. All right. The
sellers cannot complete this rotation
that they're looking for. Not yet,
anyway. It might come, but not yet.
[sighs]
So, that open print still being held.
This blue line on your screen still
being held for now. And I'd say you're
starting to box in, right? You've got
like
this here.
All right. This is the build of
liquidity a bit like we had here. So a
break above this can come up to here. A
break below this can come down to here.
And you want to be careful of fail
breakouts either side.
Here's the New York open again. They're
attempting. Can they get a wash through
this New York open? There's a bid at 790
and underneath that. That underneath the
90 is previous week point of control,
remember? So here's New York open again.
Now they're starting to get really
aggressive on the tape here. They're
looking for 700s. Here's your 700s.
Through this, we go 90 and then 670.
There's your 90 tap straight away. So,
some covering happening there into
previous week point of control. Can we
get a continuation now lower? They are
looking to get underneath previous week
point of control. This red line to come
back down into the lows.
Still, there is some form of passive
buying down here. Sellers are in control
though of this market at the moment.
We're outside of value on the day. It's
just whether they can get underneath
this now. Right. So any of you who were
short from up here or reloaded here,
these were your covers. Next cover will
be low of day, previous week value area
low, previous week low, right? Any bid
over this.
You don't want to be holding above this.
Any of you who got short in here or
short up here, you can see clear shelf.
You are in control. This is your cover
point. And then down here for washes.
Looking better now for you. Just make
sure you're managing your risk on this
way down. It's looking better.
You should be down to some small size
here.
VIX really needs to get going here. So,
one thing that's putting me off what I'm
seeing at the moment is VIX just in the
midpoint of its range. Here's previous
week point of control. So, underneath
here, 670 big level.
There's some bids here. Previous week
point of control. 670 the next level.
[cough]
And if you are short, uh I think you
want 15s and 20s to be protected. All
right? So any pop-up, you want 15 and 20
to be protected. I personally would not
want to see it go over that if I was
short in this.
Nice, Jack. Nice work.
Still looks good. All the time you're
under that sort of
15s or 13s, 13s to 20s. all the time
you're under that, you look okay. I'
just be somewhat careful if they rip
through that level.
That's where they came in very, very
aggressively is that level. So, you want
to see continuation under that level.
Back to previous week point of control
here again.
Looking for acceptance underneath this
at the moment. They're trying to drive
price underneath this previous week
point of control at the moment. It's
what they're trying to do. Can they find
acceptance lower is the question. Can
they get back into 670? Can they get
back into this low of day 664? Can they
get under that into previous week value
area low? Right? So, what they're
looking to do right now is come under
here. What sellers are trying to do is
get under here to take these stops out
to get a wash into this and that would
be their cover point. They can't do
that. You want to be careful with this
move. which is why personally if I was
in this short any longer I would have
been trimming some into here and just
trying to let runners work now you're
comfortably in the money anyone who got
short from this uh volume shelf leave
right you're 100 points in the money
from here and on this push back in that
failed you're whatif well 70 points in
the money so you're good you should be
very comfortable in your position right
Now
[snorts]
I'd be watching this trigger point on
the queue. So 20day on the cues is into
this six 1920s.
What VIX has got to get going. I don't
like what I'm seeing here on the VIX. So
one thing makes me a little bit iffy.
You look good to keep holding but I
wouldn't be adding size. If VIX was
breaking out upside, I'd be willing to
add size into this short, but it's not.
So 670 is next level. Like I said,
that's where the bid is on the book.
Looks good here, folks. You look really,
really good here. Be looking for cover
points into some of these. And then down
here, this is the low hanging fruit.
Previous week value low, previous week
low. Looks fantastic. Big bar just came
in here and got absolutely hammered.
This is what you want to see. So you're
almost there. 670s. Do they take this
670 player out? He's reloaded twice now.
Here he comes. So, he's just been
absorbed. He's trying to absorb into
670s. So, be down to small size here.
And you're going to need this to stay
heavy on a retest previous weak point
control. Definitely, if you really want
to hold, you definitely got to stay
heavy up here into seven 710s, but most
of the damage now being done on that
drive. Very, very nice. Well done,
folks. Anyone who took that,
congratulations. Not a bad first trade
back. We'll take it. You had two
opportunities. the leaving of the shelf
or the pop back in.
Oh, don't worry. Don't worry, Jody. It's
still like, you know, I would say any
any money made on a first day back is uh
always very good. Here's a previous week
point control check here.
Open will be tested. Yeah, 707s may very
well be. It's where the sellers came in
heavy at 709 713 714s value area low
717s may very well be tested. We will
see. We will see. At the moment
aggressive sellers still trying to sell
these lows down here.
There is a bid down here at 660. They
still got unfinished business. It's just
whether they need to drift higher to
reload it or not. Here's the 74s again.
If they fail these, you'd imagine 660s
will come pretty quick. Here we go. So,
this is 70s. They're going to look 60s
here. They're going to look to take out
these uh stops here and then try and get
back down into value low. That's what
they're looking to do. Remember, if
you're a buyer here and you get stopped
out, you become a seller and that wash
into there then becomes possible, which
is what they're looking for.
[snorts]
I don't think so, Peter. I think you're
I think we're market starting to change
a little bit
and you're just in a rotation. I mean, I
wouldn't really call it a uh two leg
down yet. Say that pattern we made last
week on an hourly from Wednesday to
Friday.
The fact that we rejected the old twoe
balance range speaks a lot to me. Speaks
a lot to me right now.
I certainly wouldn't be a buyer of this
market long term. Not up here. I would
need to see like a a significant shove
back to 300 and really see a huge amount
of volume come in there. We have
divergence. Remember, most of the
markets took out their highs. Cues did
not. Um, if you go back to historical
patterns,
that divergence can often mark a top.
And the fact that we rejected a twoe
balance range point of control for me
does not bode well. But I'm trying not
to be too biased. We will see. Q1,
I think, is likely to uh shake a few
people. Let's say that much.
[snorts] We will see. We will see.
Thanks, brother. I got 402 from opening
line to short. 402s.
I don't know what you mean. 402s.
There they go. They're going to try and
sweep these stops out here. So, your
TPS, your next TPS might be hit there.
Big selling has come in at 72. So,
that's your overunder in this like
little shelf here. They've got to stay
heavy around here for that wash that
back down to uh value area low. I would
say if they can get there previous week
value area low which is into the 40s.
They're trying they're absolutely trying
to get it down there at the moment.
ES still not swept that low yet either.
42s is the pivot on ES spy pre-market
low for trading the spiders. 8670 is
kind of your pivot. Here it comes folks.
Here it comes. They're coming for it.
So, low of day coming in. Once they snap
these, I expect a wash down into this
area. You must be covering as you get
into this, folks. All right. Once we
snap these, you've got to be covering as
we uh if they stop run these and you get
sort of a volume spike. All right. If
they can get under here and you get a
volume spike down into here, you've got
to be covering into this move. All
right? You do not want to see it keep
absorbing here. You want to see a swipe
down for you to cover into. Use their
pain for your covers if it will offer
it. [snorts]
still learning from Indonesia.
Oh, so you made $42. Maybe that's what
you mean. I'm not I'm not sure what you
mean, but either way, thanks for
joining.
Overall on the daily, we are in a
rotation on the daily. Alex, yet to
determine the next direction. Right.
Let's have a look at the daily. How we
started the day. Uh yeah, so we're in
we're in that balance. Where are you
guys? Let me just get you over to this
daily.
All right, we're in that balance, aren't
we? If we think about what the market's
done
from swing to swing, right, there's your
61.
This is the old balance range. And this,
have we reclaimed it? No. All right,
there's the pullback. Did we make a
lower low?
No. All right, we're in a rotation from
here to here at the moment. If bulls
need to take control, they need to take
control of this and bid back over this.
And that will allow that new all-time
high. If they fail here, we probably
rotate back down to this. If they fail
this, we can come back down to this. If
they fail this, then we're going to have
a huge amount of volume built out
and that wash becomes more and more
probable. Right? if they cannot get back
above this
and remember we've seen divergence
remember ES uh RTY etc etc right taking
this out and pulling back so we just
need to give it a little bit of time at
the moment but yes like you can see this
low volume node is where we caught a bid
look at look at how condensed
even this is 50-day
20-day 5day contraction of Ballinger
bands that will change. I still think
this guy down here is looming for a
retest. When was the last retest of him?
May. Right. So, Mr. 200, I think, is
looming for a retest, but we're we're
just give it time. Remember, we're we're
not expecting much in this uh session
here.
Okay, there's your retest.
There's your retest.
So, I couldn't sweep this out. I only
swept the internal. Couldn't sweep this
out. That's pretty annoying, isn't it?
There we go. All right, back to the
open.
Back to uh
point of control.
ES trying to get back to its open. It's
back to its open now. It's got both VWs
above it as do we. And you can see
volume shifting, migrating now. Big old
Dshape, right? If we think about this so
far on this session,
not many nodes, big old Dshape. There's
your rotation.
So far in this session, we're coming
right to the midpoint of it. Fun, fun,
fun, fun, fun. That's why we have to be
taking profits down here. We didn't
never got that snap. Unfortunately, it
might come later. We might retest it and
stay heavy. We don't know. But, uh, this
is the level that we talked about
earlier where the sellers came flying
in. It's these teens. If they get stuck
here, there is a squeeze out probably
above 20s. The next level above being to
sort of 38ish, somewhere around that.
Sellers running out of bullets. I just
think we're in a rotation. We're just in
a rotation, right? We're guys, it's it's
7:18. We've been here 50 minutes on a
low volume day. I think lots of time
left, right? This can still be resold.
Think about this, right? If this is your
thin level where we got thin, where we
trapped buyers, where we sold down and
sold down, right? They can see still
resell this. I'll change my mind if we
start to do this, right? If we start to
build top side of here, this far too
early to say sellers are done. Far far
far too early. We're just in a balance.
Plenty of time left in this session.
and ES couldn't get back up to its speed
up there.
Well, VIX doesn't look good really,
Peter. It's drifting lower. I don't I
don't really like what I'm seeing on the
VIX right now.
It's uh it's it needs to get back above
1510. really above 1510 uh for a VIX
squeeze would be nice rather than
keeping rejecting the pivot up here.
Remember, we want VIX to do inverse of
what the market's doing. That's healthy
correlation.
[clears throat] All of the mag now red
again.
Tesla clawing back some, but all of the
mag red.
No, not in a trade right now. Joe, uh
took the short from the leave of this
shelf.
All right, for this leave and then added
back here
and covered and fully out. Didn't hold
for this.
I'm not fully sharp yet. And I' I've
sized down. When I'm not fully sharp,
you know, it's first day back. I will
tell you, I probably overindulged. I ate
lots of food. Didn't drink too much but
drank a decent amount for me and smoked
a few stogies and this is first day back
yesterday. Barely left the sofa. So
[laughter]
just gonna slowly get back into rhythm.
Right.
We're through the open already, folks.
We're through the open. There's a little
shelf here into 20s. Remember I said if
we get through 20s, they probably led it
to 36.
Lots of buyers coming in these last two
candles up here above sort of above the
15. So this is the big level, right? If
we look at I can take you over here.
We think about where big selling came
in. Look at this strong shift here where
these buyers last got caught. All right,
we went buy side shove up
into sort of here. Come on.
Right here. This is where the buyers
last got caught on the sell. We're
revisiting that level through here. This
is where strong selling took place. Look
at the delta. Big selling in this candle
here. All right. So, this 20 to 40s
becomes key as well. I was saying if
they get through 20s, they're probably
going to go 38s 40s.
All right. Just just based on what
actually occurred during this this sort
of time here. I'd say from 9:55 to
10:02, right? So, we're just watching
price revisit that area of let's just
call it of a battle of of a contestion.
Like sellers came in heavy at 720. We
know that to 707s on this breakdown,
right? This is where they came in heavy.
We're repricing them now. They're
starting to be out the money. Buyers
came in big at 37 to 40.
ES still cannot get through its New York
VWAP.
Apple gone red to green.
Gold down 5%. Yeah. 4.81%. I mean, it it
needs it. Silver down 8%. I mean, you
got to understand, folks, like it did
25%
up last week. You have to understand,
everyone, like this is cool. This is
your small cap, right? This is retail
buying. Don't be [\h__\h] stupid. All
right? Pardon my French, but this is
where you buy the accumulation. You
don't [\h__\h] buy up here, right?
Everyone's just found out, oh, silver's
on a flyer, right? from November, you're
up almost 100%. You're up, I don't know,
probably like 70% here. Don't be stupid
and buy here or buy this first dip.
Don't do that. You're going to see Think
about anyone who's been long. Most
institutions have been long, right, all
year for this breakout and this breakout
and adding here. They're not long up
here, right? They're going to you're
going to see some profit taking. Do not
be stupid and buy the high or buy the
first dip, right? You don't need to rush
into these positions, right? They take
time to develop. This could very, very
well come all the way back down to here
and see if it can find some
consolidation for a go back up. It might
find a bid before. It could also come up
here and find a failed follow through.
If enough retail get trapped here, this
will be the collapse of it. All right?
Don't be stupid and read the papers and
buy what they're saying. Oh, silver's
blah blah. Shut up. All right? Don't
listen to any of that bollocks. Follow
what's happened here. This is a low
volume squeeze up during Christmas. All
right, that's all it is. Let it come
back and settle. You don't need to be
the first to buy it on a dip. You guys
saying you're buying uh against this big
knife move. You don't need to. What you
need to do is wait and see if
institutional buying comes back in at a
key level, right? You don't want to buy
up there like absolute psychopath move.
Even if we go going to think about this
whole thing, right? 50% retracement. You
got to get back to 64 or right 61 in
this golden zone. You got to get back
into the 60s per ounce. It's got a long
way to go before I'd consider buying it.
Long, long way.
Don't get caught up with hysteria and
what
I don't know CNN and CBS and all these
people saying. They will get you caught.
All right? They don't know what they're
talking about. Do not get caught into
that trap.
Do not get caught into the trap.
Ask yourself, if you are up almost 100%
in a month, would you be buying or would
you be taking some profits, right? And
then times that by
billions and trillions of dollars. Okay,
we are due a pullback. Do I think it
would be rebid on? Yes, I do think it
would be rebid on early between Jan and
Mark.
But you're currently trying to buy a
pullback on 29th
after last week it went up over 25%. And
over the month it's gone up almost 100%.
Right? So you just don't do that. Make
that make sense to me. If Apple had
moved from 200 to 400 in a couple of
days in in a in a week or two weeks or
three weeks, would you be buying it? No,
you wouldn't. So don't do it with
anything else just cuz just cuz they're
talking about it. Understand the auction
theory.
Clearly, it can't find value up there.
Very, very clearly. It's moved from 30
an ounce to 80 an ounce. Like, just make
it make sense.
Can't do it forever. All right. Doesn't
mean it can't go back there and revisit
it. But why buy the first pullback,
folks? You're too smart to do that. All
right? You're far too smart to do that.
Why don't I use IB? I do use IB. Initial
balance hasn't come yet. It's not set
for another five minutes, four minutes.
There's no initial balance to trade yet,
my friend. It's the first hour of
trading. We've got to wait another four
minutes until it's set.
Absolutely. Use initial balance.
Okay, back in to this [clears throat]
top of value for this session. 750 on
here. What do I have it on? Ninja Trader
760. It's about 10 point uh kind of
discrepancy there but value area high on
this session up into here into this VW
up. All right, you can see this is the
D-shaped profile. It might well be that
they rotate from here. All right, if
they get acceptance through here or
they're going to get through this thin
structure, aren't they? So sellers will
want to come and defend this for the
rotation. Buyers will want to try and
force a squeeze here, force their hand
out to get back to these highs. We can
just wait. You've got four minutes until
a new 30 minute candle and 15 minute and
5 minute candle and IB is set.
I imagine the sellers will want to
defend here or hereabouts.
And if they don't, then we're going to
go back for that shelf that we first
shorted this morning.
What is IB? IB is initial balance. All
it is is the highest point and the
lowest point of the first hour of
trading in a current session. So
obviously we're trading New York. So
it's 9:30 to 10:30, right? 9:30 to
10:30. Everything's still being
absorbed. There's sellers here at 50,
55, 60. There was a seller at 80, but
he's left the building right now.
And where did that big buyer come in?
39. All right. So we've got delta,
positive delta above 39. They're trying
to hold above 39s right now. These
buyers
revisit towards an old imbalance and be
up here into 50.
There we go. Testing this seller up
here. This is that imbalance into around
the 50s and the value area high. So, do
sellers do a little look above? Do they
let them come above, do a look above and
fail,
or do they just defend this range and go
for rotation? We're about to find out.
So, this is the 40 where we have
positive delta above which they're
testing now. It's where the big buyer
came in
and big buyer still holding price there
right now. So 40 was the level. I can
see it on the tape. Right. So you also
have a little shelf here. I'm just
watching the delta on that tape at 40.
We had like an outside bar. It's
starting to be paired off a little bit
because we did have an aggressive seller
into it. This is a big level here. Here
they go. So here's the flush back down
into view up today. Absorb this. Now
remember, we are in a rotation. You can
see the D-shape. All right. We're in a
rotation day. There's your Dshape. All
right. No acceptance below. No
acceptance above this yet. Okay. I'd be
very careful about a look above and fail
on a rotation. If they look above and
hold, we know here is where we trapped
those buyers this morning. So buyers are
trying to get the market up to here so
they can get let out of the market.
Sellers, if I was a seller, I'd be
trying to encourage them to do this. All
right, a little look above into a low
volume and fail. That's the kind of move
if I was a seller and I enjoy trading
rotation, which I don't. But that's the
kind of thing that I'd be looking at. We
know 40 is a big level, right?
It's started to be paired off now, but
it was a very very big level.
I'd be same as orb today. Yeah, you
you're right. You're right. The uh
15minute drive if you're a 15-minute orb
trader. Yeah, absolutely right. Unless
uh we do a huge spike, but yeah, you can
see purple lines, these little dots
which start to get bigger and bigger.
Those are my initial balances. All
right. So, you're quite right. IB is the
same as orb today.
They are defending the edge of this
value area high on this session at the
moment.
Alex, would you be open to a trade in
gold futures in 2026? Uh more for a
swing position. Yes,
I'm open to a trade on uh
anything which is moving
well outside of where it should be in
2026. So, I'm open to gold and silver um
for swing positions.
I don't want to actively trade them, not
dayto-day.
I think the way they move, you're
better, you're almost better to be
positioned long-term in those.
If the 21 crosses VWAP with Momo, do you
scout counter long since it's above
value area high or is that probability?
If the TW Oh, since you you mean above
the current value area high. Well, you
got to remember where we are in
rotation.
This is the rotation.
This is the current rotation.
Any trade above here for me is kind of
dangerous. The maximum you get is that
relief to here, right? The better
rotation would be if it bases above or
if you catch the low. I wouldn't be uh
looking I'm I would not be playing this
move here. No, I would rather let that
fake out and die and play that move
there.
As most of you know, I don't love
playing rotation anyway. [snorts]
New York VW. Is that just anchored to
the New York session? Yes, correct. Just
a 9:30 open. All right. So it's a cash
print.
Yeah. It doesn't mean do you know when I
play that Otus is if there was plenty of
room above, right? If we were migrating
higher and there was room above for
sure. But we're not. We're not doing
that. So what you're actually doing is
you're saying, "Hey, I'm going to buy
the most expensive value price on the
day inside previous week hoping we can
revisit." And for me, that's a dangerous
buy. doesn't mean it doesn't do it, but
I'd need to I'd need to see a lot more
from buyers to convince me to take that
play.
I think there's a good chance the door
gets shut on them. [snorts]
You're short 25747.
I'd say you're a bit early based on
structure. the the area is not too bad,
but I want to I want to wait and see if
they do like a little look above and
fail. All right, that's what I'm looking
for. Can they do a look above and fail?
Because at the moment, buyers are just
stepping in here quite happily. What you
need to see is aggressive buyers chase
the market and get stuck. If you're
going to look for the rotation short
[snorts]
VIX new lower day, this is what's
concerning me is we have divergence here
on the VIX today. And that is a concern
for me because there's a new low day.
It's into its gap. If it wants to gap
fill, it's going to come down to 1440s
and below and well below. And that might
really let this market out for some
relief. I don't like seeing a market
which is in major divergence to the VIX.
There you go. Otus. Yeah, [laughter]
I'd say 45's become key now for buyers.
They've stepped in aggressively at 45s
numerous times. So that's their level
they want to hold above right now. 45s
is the level that they're looking to
hold.
I wouldn't mind seeing a little swipe up
and then buyers come in and see if
there's actually a passive seller still
here or not. We're just at the edge of
this current range. Maybe they expand up
into here. We don't know. It's not an
area I want to trade in right now. I
just want to wait and see. Let some
price action develop up here. Make a
decision after [snorts]
>> [snorts]
>> QQQ just above VWOP and it's not
indicated either way outside the 50
minute. Exactly. Rotational day. We're
in a rotational day. We're not outside
the orb. We're not outside previous
week's value. We're not outside anything
right now. We're in a rotation. We have
a D-shaped rotation, right into thin
volume. So, very, very possible they
come up here. But the question is, is
there a passive seller hanging out here
who traps buyers and does this move? I
don't know, which is why I'm just
waiting right now. [snorts]
Apple has found a bid.
Tesla's back inside of that 65 now
trading at 67. That's a good uh shove up
from Tesla reclaiming. So potentially a
look below and fail there under 465s on
Tesla. I think that was the level where
aggressive sellers came in at this
morning is sort of we have a 77 81 86 92
and sort of 95 stand out. They stand out
above. Remember volume today very very
thin not a lot of volume.
I might enter along. No, I would be more
interested if I see a passive seller
here uh absorb aggressive buyers and
close down back inside range for
rotation. I'm I'm
I would be careful about a long. All
right. All the time we've squeezed up
without building a base. All right. for
me. Squeeze, squeeze, squeeze, squeeze.
This is the look above kind of level we
just talked about. If there's a passive
seller here and we close in here, they
can go in rotation. If they do this and
then they start absorbing,
even then, I don't really like it in a
rotation, but we we're just we'll see.
We're starting to see that passive
seller up here. This is what I talked
about, the look above and fail above
value area high. This is what I'd be
more interested in playing. And we're
starting to see that. So, if they don't
bid here at VWAP, all right, if this is
a look above and fail, this can get
very, very aggressive to the downside.
Just watching carefully here to see what
happens.
So, I think Otus just asked this and we
talked about this move here. Be very
careful. This is the gray box. Remember,
if they fail this and they get back
under point of control on this session,
we will probably rotate lower because
this is the kind of trap at the edge. If
they can print above this, then their
their aim is to get back into this up
here. The sort of 94 iss
long up here. I think the the risk
parameter is not very good. You are
bidding at the one of the worst areas of
the day. Doesn't mean it can't move
higher, but remember when we assess
whether we're going to trade, we want
like pocket aces. Here's VWAP. So if
they don't bid this, you are going to
get more of a flush in this market.
[snorts]
Does that make sense, Otus? Because I
know you just you just you just asked
this exact question.
Yeah, hopefully that makes sense. So
this was value. This is Dshape. We want
to bid from here to here and sellers are
likely to sell this. Do you remember
what I said when I said what would I
like to see if I was a short seller and
I liked rotation? I'd like a failed
breakout.
You going back and remind what I said
into this low volume for aggressive
buyers to come back in and get met with
passive sellers and then get back under
here and we can rotate. You're starting
to see it all happen very very quickly.
All right. Hopefully that makes sense,
but just let me know in chat because I
tried to explain that to you before it
happened.
That's my dog. Hang on. Let me just open
this up. You all right, Luna?
What's up with you? Come here, Mr.
Hello.
Nana's going to take you. Don't worry.
Uh, I understand why you dislike
rotation now. Yeah, it's just not my
favorite trade. It's not my favorite
trade. Especially, you got to remember
we're inside the previous week, but
we're under the previous day and we're
now in a Dshape on the day. I mean, it's
just
nothing. I wouldn't say it's a high
probability day.
What's up?
Is there a VWAP indicator on Ninja
Trader? There is. Uh there's a free one
if you're using Orderflow and
there is one if you go to Ninja Trader
communities or whatever it's called.
Someone's built one. I think it's called
like VWAP X or something like that.
You played the fail breakout made 20
points. There you go, Gary. Nice,
nice, nice, nice. Yeah, for me I'm just
just flat. Just not uh this is not
something that's grabbing my attention.
But you can see this gray level came in
important. All right. Why? It's the same
level as earlier. All right. So, what
you've got to think about
at the start of the day, think about the
very very start of the day, we talked
about,
you hear my dog, she's not happy. We
talked about a drive up here being sold
into. They didn't. They got a what what
I would call almost like a blowoff top.
Buyers got trapped above this level. All
right. So, once we got back below this,
shorts took control. Shorts didn't
complete the rotation under here. They
wanted this, they didn't get it. So,
we've had relief all the way back and
they're stepping in at the same level.
Now, if we start just building liquidity
here, or even if we build liquidity
here, all right, we're just building
this out for the next leg, our
probability of a really good move
diminishes, especially given the type of
day it is. Remember, it's the 29th of
December. Not that many people at their
desks. Not that many people.
I would yes trader Rick I would agree
but just remember I wouldn't consider uh
the next two or this trading session to
necessarily be high probability plays uh
within value same as last week um just
because I think the volume's going to be
lower and I think big participants might
not sort of turn up. I'm more interested
in where we're at, you know, one two
weeks into January. But yes,
you know what happens? I would ask you,
we've left from the bigger context. I
wouldn't necessarily say all of the
context is bullish because if we come
down here,
right, this is what you need to
understand about the old balance range.
This old balance range,
we are not finding acceptance back in.
It's a two weeks balance range. We are
rejecting point of control from that old
range is two is 920s. All right, in here
we can't get back in inside of it. At
the moment, we keep rejecting this old
balance range, right? So maybe there's a
deeper pullback to be had. If we lose
previous week's value, maybe we pull
back into the weeks before I would say
down here, this old naked point of
control is an area I'm interested in.
buyers bid off that then you know that's
the kind of swing point where I think if
I was going to be very bullish in this
market if I was a perma bull right and
we'd done this and we'd rejected this
I'd be looking for a pullback into here
to bid off to go back to highs that's
what where my brain is right now and if
we lose that then I'd say well buyers
have just completely failed to hold the
rotation and new lows are probable so
this for me is the big level, right?
It's when we come back into here.
This is clear. We can't find acceptance
back in it. Not yet. Maybe we find
acceptance in the next few days, but
right now we can't. This is where I
think I will peique my interest of does
institutional buying take place there or
not.
At least that's how that's how my
brain's working, right? That's what I'm
seeing. Doesn't mean I'm right. It's
just how I'm viewing the market.
That's not necessarily true. It's back
to value from two week balance. So I
would say your idea is invalid. Well, I
don't think we are back there. We've
we've clearly rejected it. We we just
rejected point of control and we we're
back. This is what I'm saying. We're
back there on a low volume drift higher
week. All right. Where I don't think
many people were at the desk. And this
is what I'm saying. Like if this had
happened first week at January, I'd give
it more consideration. I'm not I'm I'm
not going to give it too much
consideration when we're low volume. But
like I said, I'm happy to be wrong and
that's okay. What I would say though is
VIX is continuing to fall into its gap
and this market might get going here.
do not like the divergence uh on the VIC
and the SP VIX and spiders right now.
VIX well into its gap.
Previous day high on the VIX will take
it back down to sort of 1430s.
Gap fill on the VIX is all the way down
into 1360s.
It is rejecting an old pivot into these
15s. It might well pull back into these
1430s, 1420s and see if it can find a
bid.
the law. Well, technically technically
it's between VIX and ES, not BNQ. But
yes, in in a healthy market, the
correlation is that they do the
opposite. But we've got VIX breaking
down underneath lows and spiders
midpoint of the range.
Market just gone still here and we're
developing a big fat node here as well.
Nice cyberpie. Welcome, welcome,
welcome,
welcome, welcome, welcome. 581 of you
here. I want to do some giveaways soon.
Make sure you smash that like button.
I'll be here today and tomorrow. Maybe
I'll be here Wednesday. I'll see. But
yeah, very light trading week.
Not expecting much at all.
bearish bull can't handle the pressure.
Well, you I would say you probably need
to size down if that's the case.
If your P&L swings too big, it's
probably stressing you out. Yeah, just
size down. You got to earn the right to
size up. You got to earn the right to
have bigger P&L swings. You got to get
comfortable with that slowly. You know,
the jump from one
micro to two micros is manageable, even
though it's a 100% jump. The jump from
one mini to two minis is probably not so
manageable. So, just size down, move to
micros, nice and slow, or don't even
trade cash, you know.
Don't trade cash.
All right, ES back into its VWOP. stuck
between 24hour VWOP
and then New York VW up on the ES Q's
balancing out at that same VWOP. Spiders
the same place. We're at this point of
control. You can see the rotation
starting to take place around here. This
is not a level that I want to be
participating in. All right. Not really
interested. Buyers will want to do this.
Sellers will want to complete this
rotation down here.
Buyers will want to try and let these
guys out. At the moment, they can't get
back back above value. that look above
and fail has played out.
They're trying to build out volume node
here. The question is, do they let this
go? Do they protect this again or do we
come into this or do buyers trap all
these sellers and complete this rotation
and let these buyers out?
Right now, I'd say sellers
in this node here have done a good job.
It's just whether they can leave this
volume trapped here and start to return
back down here would be my question
right now for these sellers.
They're trying. They're definitely
trying.
[cough]
It's crazy how gold always rejects the
20-day moving average in New York
session. Is that right? I mean, it's
mean reversion, right? 20 days your
mean.
I haven't checked the standard
deviations for gold, how far outside it
moves, but yeah, I mean, 20 days always
your mean.
So, starting to see this wash now. New
York open will be the next target for
these shorts. So that look above and
fail
above here like we talked about. There's
your lower high starting to leave this
volume, right? They want to try and get
back down into here if they can. That
would be their first cover point. If
they get acceptance under here, they
still have things to look for lower. MAG
all red other than uh Apple. Like I
said, I'm not going to trade the
rotation. Um well, if you give you a
readout, equally weighted. We're 0.72%
down today on the mags. Uh Tesla 1.85%
down, but has reclaimed that 65 level we
talked about. Nvidia 1.68% down.
Microsoft pretty much flat, 0.03% down.
Meta 0.77% down. Google 0.42% down.
Amazon 0.22% down. Apple 0.05% up.
There it is. Otus said, "Yeah, there.
There it is. There it goes.
>> [snorts]
>> There it goes.
So hopefully I kept kept you at least I
kept you out a bad trade, right? And
next time you see that setup and you
think about taking that long, you'll
think twice about it.
You'll be like, "Hey, I've seen this
before. Even if this goes higher, this
is not a great setup." There you go.
Here comes New York open.
So any of you that took this fail
breakout, all right, you want to be
taking a partial into this level here,
New York open. You want a partial
into this level here. This is your New
York open somewhere in this range here.
Hello. Let me teach, please. All right.
Partials here. Then runners are your low
of day. Remember, we didn't quite sweep
this. It might be that we don't sweep
this. But if we sweep this, all right,
then you're probably going to see a stop
run somewhere into here. And this is
your next TP. So, I'd be like TP1 to
protect TP2 down into this. All right.
Somewhere into here.
Really nice.
Augustine Da Vinci. What does that mean?
Paint my nails.
Nice. Otus. Nice. How was uh were you in
um Palm Springs over the break? How was
the flooding down there? I've been
hoping to get up on the mountain here,
but the roads have uh not in good not
been good here. Can't get up to Baldi
which has still been closed. Uh Mammoth,
there was an avalanche out. It's sort of
got my snowboard ready and snow on the
mountains and nothing to do. All right,
here's your previous week point control
is value. So the only thing left now I'd
be covering some here and then holding
to see if you get a further breakdown,
right? Holding to see if you get a
further breakdown at this point.
Yes, coming into that lower day. Massive
divergence here uh between ES and the
VIX today.
It's being a bit of a bugger.
It is being a bit of a bugger. There are
some cover points here. So, you should
be covering some into this folks
[snorts]
into this pivot here.
Clue's in the title there. Shouldn't
Shane, I have a hard time timing your
entry. You shouldn't be timing my entry.
You should be timing your entry. And uh
that's your clue there. Shouldn't be
following everyone. You should be using
me to understand what's happening in the
market. You should be using your model
and my teachings to trade. Not uh not
trying to copy me. If you copy me in,
you're going to be lagged anyway because
the stream unfortunately is six six
seconds behind. And I'm not in an entry,
right? I said very clearly, I'm not
going to trade this. But if I was going
to trade it, right, I'd be looking for a
fail breakout, failed follow through.
The gray box was there the whole time.
I'd be looking for a fail breakout into
low volume node and a rotation from one
side to the other. Right?
Gave you the teaching cuz I didn't even
trade it. So, if you're waiting for me
to say I'm in short, you're still
waiting cuz I'm not trading rotation.
[snorts]
What software creates the different
colored waves or the clouds? This is the
Flow Zone Pro, right?
This is my indicator.
Version of it comes with the course.
Everything's on my website,
flzontrader.com.
below 660. Don't see much support till
412. What do I think?
Um, no, I wouldn't necessarily agree
with that. Uh,
level we're at now is key from last
week. Um,
I'd say there is some volume at sort of
580 to 5 550s
uh if we get down there. But the moment
keeps finding finding a bid in this area
same as it did last week. If you look at
Monday last week, Tuesday last week
keeps finding a bid in this area. Uh if
we break those lows that there is a node
that's why I have this down here that
there's a node down here and then under
that the old value from the week before
will be down at 522s. uh once we start
letting go of that then I think there's
a wash into the 330s but you know they
keep buying dips down here we are just
in a rotational market please remember
that
why don't I use the bands and viewer
because I don't need them they're not
something I don't know that's a I don't
know how to answer that question because
they're not part of my strategy because
my strategy how I trade doesn't use them
that's why I don't use them. It's not
cuz they don't work. Everything works
once you build a system around it. It's
just they're not what I like to use.
Doesn't mean you shouldn't use them.
There's no right and wrongs.
Up 1k on 20 emails today. Nice, Tom.
Good work.
Nice, David.
I mean, it's not bad. Uh, this move
here. Yeah, potentially. Just remember
this. This is the big level from
previous week. So, it depends. Like, I'd
almost wait to see if they're willing to
rotate this. Just remember last week,
right, we found bids here. Um,
it's where we keep finding bids. Oh,
there we go. All right. Into this
structure here. You want to be careful,
right? The the buyers keep coming in
down here. So, I wouldn't be thinking
about getting too much today. All right.
This is the you're in the middle of the
profile. Any drift higher goes back into
the middle of the profile. We're just in
a rotation, folks. Don't look for trend
in a rotation. All right. Let it
develop. If you It's going to have to
really show you it wants to do it.
You're in a low volume week as well.
Like why why why why be like trying to
play trend and risk on and like why do
anything in a low volume week? Do you
know what I mean? Like we're in the
middle of a Dshape.
We're protecting edges.
I wouldn't really be doing much here.
Like maybe you wanted to take this,
maybe you took this this morning, but
like you're you're I would say we have
diminishing edge in this market right
now. How many times have I told you like
the VIX is diverging from everything?
like it doesn't look very good out here
right now in terms of like high
probability setups.
Thanks JJ or JJ A is that JJ A trading.
Yeah, just because I trade this way,
folks. Like I always say, there's no
right and wrongs. Like, um, I can't
remember who asked me about the VWAP
bands, but if they work for you, use
them, right? If they work for you, use
them. But if you've developed a strategy
around them, use them. It's not like I
think they don't work. It's just not
part of how I trade. That's all it is.
That's all it is.
I'm actually going to move remove this.
traded through it quite a few times now.
And this is like a base that they keep
bidding is more like this.
Keep holding
[snorts]
The volume is pitiful. I don't think it
was this low at any point last week. I
mean, it Yeah, it's going to be low,
guys. You got You got to understand
we're we're trading between Christmas
and and New Year's. I mean, anyone in
Discord will know I said, "Hey, we'll
get on stream. If there's something
there, we trade it. Otherwise, we'll
just have some fun together, right? You
don't need to trade every day. You don't
need to trade every session." Like, if
you're just clicking buttons for the
sake of clicking buttons, you need to
have a little word with yourself.
Yeah. Just need to have a word with
yourself. just you should be trading
setups if and when they set up and
that's the same every day. Um
for me there's there's no trade here. I
don't like trading rotations. Most of
you will know that. I made that always
made that clear. I will call them out
for you. But I don't like trading them.
Certainly not going to trade the
midpoint of a rotation.
[snorts]
You learned from me that key levels are
the key and you work with that. Yeah. I
mean you need to trade around key
levels. don't want to trade if you're
trading before a key level. It means
you're jumping the gun, right? Let it
come and test a key level. Let it and
not just like at the level like let it
show you what it wants to do at that
level. People that try and catch a knife
because they think, "Oh, there's good
structure down here." Like doesn't h you
have to remember the market doesn't have
to do anything. We can just build
thesis, it doesn't have to do anything.
What you need to do is have the levels
that you want to trade at and then wait
for your setup to present in and around
those levels. Don't jump the gun. You if
you're buying because you've got a blue
box on your screen, but the market's
tanking,
chances are just as much it's going to
slice through your blue box, right,
[snorts]
Alex? How does raising margin
requirements affect shorts in comparison
to longs? Uh you mean in in the metals?
Uh depends how if they're overlever if
they're overleveraged short side uh it
will force them to cover at least
especially if the margin requirements
are more overnight. It affects them both
the same way affects them both the same
way in the futures market. Doesn't
matter which side of that trade you
take. It's more about who's placed more
uh positions in the last 48 hours. Let's
say who's bought the highs or who
shorted the highs, what price has done
since. At the moment, uh price has
pulled about 8% since those highs. So,
anyone who took a short [snorts]
with high margin requirements
is comfortable. Any retail who bought
the high is absolutely pinned. Most
people will be up, you know, pro I would
say volume on silver is probably from
like 35s,
you know, it's they're they're up 100%.
They don't care about the margin. The
big money won't care about the margin
requirements. The big people who've been
long for, you know, all of this year and
even well before that accumulating
um won't care. It's more that's what's
happened in the last 48 hours. Who've
taken positions in the last 48 hours who
weren't prepared for that margin
requirement to change? Who's
overleveraged? [snorts]
Not new to trading. What's better, Apex
or Tradeify? That comes down to what
your ambitions are. Uh Apex, you get
more accounts. Tradeify, you don't have
to deal with trading trading draw down.
So if you don't like dealing with
trading trading draw down, probably go
with a tradeify account. If you just
want to scale and you're willing to be
patient and you want max profit,
probably go with Apex.
Yeah, exactly. Uh is it Virgil? Yeah,
stick with what I know. We went over
metals at the beginning of the day. I
think that there will be swing
opportunities coming both sides of that
trade. I'm not too fussed at the M
today. I think it'll be a crowded trade
both sides. Just let everyone else go
through hysteria. The the way I see it,
right, it's it's
this market and in general, this market
is feeling more and more like a small
cap, right? I don't want to take the
crowded trade. If if silver big if if
silver was going to go into a multimonth
multi-week fade, I won't need to be
shortening it today. I can let it build
out. Let it set a lower high. Let
everyone else [\h__\h] around and build the
volume for days, weeks, months, and I
can if I really think there's a mean
reversion or a bigger fade back to 30s,
for example, on silver, which I'm not
convinced there is, but if there was,
then I'll take that trade when it's not
so crowded, put some position on, and
just let it work. the same way smart
money got long in the 30s and let it
work for a long time. I don't feel the
need
to jump into the crowded trade. All
right, it's no different to GME. Look at
GME when everyone got the hysteria about
jumping into GME. Oh, going to get long
because everyone's told me to get long
and then they change the margin
requirements and then everyone's
smashing short. Okay, great. You got
loads of volatility. If you waited three
months and put a short position on and
closed your eyes for three or four
years, you're laughing, right? So, you
don't need to trade like the huge
volatility day one. That's what I'm
trying to say, I guess.
[snorts]
All right, [clears throat] back to
previous week point control.
Big if here, but if they do, if this is
a retracement that they do start to fade
and you get this breakdown, like I said,
there is still low hanging fruit. Those
of you who are short from up here, all
right, if you covered some here and
you're holding this, if you get this
stop run down here, I think there's low
hanging fruit to come and test. It's a
big if, but that's what I'd be looking
at.
Can you get acceptance lower in this
market? [snorts]
It's trying his value area low on the
day.
They're finding a bit of a bid here.
There are some buy side imbalances
underneath this right now.
at the point where we transitioned uh
delta on these candles down here. Big
sell delta went to big positive delta in
these candles down here. So just
watching how we act here at value area
low on the session here at 87s and point
previous week point control. We know
it's a big contested area.
I wouldn't be a new money short here.
But if you were short from those highs,
you can wait to see if they can complete
this rotation. ES starting to reject New
York open as well. Question is, can it
take out a pivot low? VIX just stuck
right now.
Here they come. So, into some of these
imbalances. Do they see follow through
now for you guys? Hopefully, you get
some follow through here, which would be
nice. Big seller coming in. You need to
get follow through here. You don't want
them to get stuck. These are where the
imbalances are.
They are attempting attempting
to move lower here.
86 86 and 93 are where big big strong
buying come in so far. Where's this big
one? 78 as well. Where's 78?
Might get a snap here. Hopefully you
guys get a snap here. Would be nice to
see them clean everything up.
Thanks, David. Very kind of you. Get my
coffee for me later.
So, yeah. I'm not sure if any of you I
think like Otus and some of you were
short here. It's cover here and wait and
see if this can break down. If you if
you run these stops,
all right, then these low hanging fruit
will get hit. If you keep if buyers keep
protecting this level, you just got to
be fully out. You can't just hold
forever because this is your Dshape,
right? This is why I keep telling you,
we don't expect trend day. It's a big if
button. Maybe if you're positioned short
here, you can afford to try and let this
work. But here is your rotation. You
don't want to be short at the lows of
this rotation. You do not want to be a
new money short down here. Even if it
breaks down, that's the same as trying
to be in new money long up here. This is
telling you what it's trying to do.
[snorts]
I'm going to get a refill of coffee here
and I want to do some Apex giveaways.
All right. When I'm back
Okay, into those imbalances. Still
protecting lower day, but you're looking
a bit better here. Is there any follow
through for you lot
versus previous week point of control?
Some bids are coming lower. It's just
whether they're willing that bid
starting to chase the market up here.
Someone's looking to cover cuz he didn't
get filled there. He's up at 80 now.
So, he was all the way down at 665 and
he's come up to 80 looking to get
filled.
Do I ever use the DOM? Yeah, you can see
it on your screen above you, right? It's
right above you or right above me right
here. Yes, I use the DOM. What's the
benefit? The benefit is to see real
price action. I want to see who's who's
bidding on the market, who's being
passive on a bid or a sell, who's being
aggressive, and where they're stuck. All
right? It's why I use bookmaps, why I
use footprints. Absolutely, I use it. I
don't watch it all the time. I watch it
because you will get exhausted.
Here's a little tip for you guys. Um,
if you watch every little move, you're
going to be exhausted. What you want to
do is once you learn to read orderflow,
you want to read what watch it when you
come into your key levels, when you're
at your key levels. All right? So, if
your key levels are 200 points apart,
it's like just set price alerts for when
you get close to a key level and then
zoom in and start watching it once you
get there. Otherwise, your brain will uh
or in my opinion, your brain will get
very very tired.
Very, very tired.
Who's this guy spamming non-stop? What's
he actually saying? Let me have a look.
There's no, everyone always asks that
there's no special settings on bookmap
guys. I don't change anything. There's
no like amazing setting. The only thing
I change is this DOM on the right hand
side. So I see delta first. That's all I
change guys. I I don't look at anything
else.
Nothing else.
All right. Thanks for forward.
Is top steps dom good enough? I don't
know. I've never used it, but not if
you're uh not paying for
um
uh data. You like if you're only seeing,
you know, four or five points outside of
where you're at, it's not going to be
very useful
on your volume profile. Is there any
reason you don't care to see up down?
What do you mean? I have it.
I see you just have the volume area. No,
it's here, my friend. It's here. You see
this gray part? You probably just maybe
can't see it. This and this. This is up
and down. Yeah. So, that's value on the
session. This is outside of value.
This is just based on New York session,
right? So, it's it's anchored to New
York session.
Yes, I do use it.
Alex, please authorize my use of EMA
Trend Fren Pro. Uh, Carol. Okay, let me
have a look. I only had two of those
come in. I've done everyone else's.
There's only so many I can do. Um,
did you fill the form in correctly and
put your uh name correctly there, Carol?
Right. Cuz I can see some here. One,
two, three, four, five that I need to do
after here. But uh I did everyone
yesterday.
Oh, I see what you're saying. Uh no, not
so outside of outside of value. What do
I care about if they've built a node?
Right. I don't really I'm not do too,
you know, if we got acceptance above
here, where are we going to go? All
right. Probably to this this node up
here. I'm not too bothered about this.
Right. There's not there's nothing
really taking place out there. So if you
think about areas I care about this
area, this area, this area, this area,
right? If shorts protect this, that's
the trap, right? Like we did here, like
we did here into thin areas.
So I do care about what happens outside
if they've built some actual liquidity.
If this was just like this, then that
just says to me, well, there's no build
out of liquidity there. Not it's not an
area of interest. [snorts]
Yes, I did. Well, I mean, okay, let me
have another look then, Carol, because I
can't uh
see it, but I'll have a look.
I'll just authorize everyone now. And if
you if you're not on there, it means you
haven't filled in your Trading View name
correctly. But I will do it now.
What's your actual name? Carol Wright.
Carol's Trading. I can see it there.
December 26th. Let's see if it's in
there or not.
Can you try now, Carol? See if that
worked.
I'll email you as well.
Apologies about that if it hadn't gone
through for whatever reason.
Should have just emailed you now. These
people, they type in things like they
put their name
and then it's not their username.
Let's try that one.
Give me a second here, folks, to just
make sure everyone's got this who
applied for it this morning.
It's another incorrect name.
Don Money. Let's try you.
There we go. He has one.
One sec, folks. I'll be right back with
you. Apologies. Make sure everyone's set
up here.
Audrey.
Alex Todd. That won't work. It's wrong
name. And AG1 I did yesterday. Okay.
Okay.
>> [snorts]
>> Okay, back to point control up here on
current session. All right, current
session P. This node here, previous week
P and this node here. This is the
rotation right now. Question is, do
sellers take control or is there squeeze
back up to 50s? That's we're in a
rotation, right? No acceptance above, no
acceptance below yet. Yet things can
change.
I just approved. Uh, everyone Don Trron
money. I just did that one, Don. Sorry,
I just see you now. I just emailed you
back. Should be there.
How do you apply for it? There's a free
video on my YouTube on uh Trend Friend
Pro. You just fill in the form. Okay,
big selling coming here. They're trying
to they're trying to get this breakdown.
VIX just still not really doing
anything. We're back down to previous
week point of control again. So sellers
are going to have one more go here. If
they cannot get back below this, they're
going to start getting stuck. Oh,
right. They are trying to get this
breakdown to come and clean out these
stops. And what they want to do is get
down into these 630s. That's what they
are attempting to do.
>> [snorts]
>> There's a buyer here at 680 again.
No worries, Carol. Yeah, sorry about
that. Not sure why you didn't get it.
They're trying to fill this buyer at
680. If they fill through this,
there's a bigger wash downside
available.
He has in the same kind of move. Vick's
just
stuck. Absolutely stuck.
Here
they come. I'm going to try and fill
this 680 guy. Here they here. He is just
underneath this. Some guys front running
him.
It is 680, right? Yeah. 680.75. He
should get filled here. And then let's
see if they go through this low volume
straight back down into this imbalance.
And 660 would be next level that they're
trying to fill. And they're offering 55s
or bidding 55s now. So this guy's still
not been filled into 680. 680. Yeah,
680. Still not been filled. So they're
front running it and we continue to
rotate from value area low. I'm
surprised they haven't filled this guy.
It might come back for him. And maybe
not. We will see.
Vic still in no man's land.
Uh,
I've added Trend Frame Pro to the
YouTube command list. A nice one.
Thanks, Adam.
To identify zones for your trading, are
you using one hours or you combine 1
hour, 4 hour? Uh, top down, man. Top
down. Weekly, daily, like we do at the
beginning of each show, weekly, daily,
hourlys,
right? So weekly, daily, hourlies,
and then once we get through that, we
can look at everything else like
previous days value areas, previous
week's value areas, where are the high
volume nodes, where is the SNR level,
does it match with a high volume node,
do we have an area of liquidity? Like
you got to just get through the process
of going through it every single day.
And it becomes easier and easier because
you know once you get through process of
doing it once all you're doing is moving
moving areas.
But 1 hour and 4 hour will work for you
Peter as long as you're zoomed out
enough. Right.
No worries Rosco.
You're long here, Trader Wick. Trader
Rick, sorry. Yeah,
we'll see, won't we? We'll see. It's I
mean, it's it's holding the bid very
very well here. There's cannot deny that
it's holding the bid very very well
here. I just think there's a huge amount
of liquidity or stops down here without
a full retest of this area. But you know
if they are going to bid up
I wouldn't be surprised to see it wash
down here first whether it's today
tomorrow uh Wednesday or next week I
wouldn't be surprised to see it come and
retest this first the way it's built
this out and on if it can hold a pivot
here and then do it then I think it's a
good area right personally
you know if you're looking for that
rotation off one go makes sense based on
what you're seeing here but I wouldn't
be surprised to see everyone get run out
first and then them try and do it. But
let we will just see. You've got to
trade what your setup is. Like I said,
it doesn't matter what I think. It only
matters what your setup is. If your
setup, if you've got proven track record
trading that setup, you should
absolutely be trading your setup. It
really doesn't matter what I think. I'm
just another guy on YouTube. The same
way I don't care what anyone else thinks
or what they do. I I have to trade my
edge.
I think that makes sense. Rick Rick
saying it's definitely a low volume week
so it's going to test my patience taking
small size given uh the weak backdrop. I
think that that is a wise and sensible
decision.
[snorts]
Yeah, exactly. Run run run the stops,
reclaim then go. That's that's where
what I would think is probable. But it
doesn't matter what I think. If your
system tells you that you need to be
bidding now, small size for a for a
bigger swing, then that's what you
should be doing. It doesn't matter what
I say, you should be doing what your
edge is, right? So like if that's what
your edge is right now and you're taking
that position, you're doing the right
thing. You can only trade your your
system in your edge. You're absolutely
doing the right thing if that's what it
says for you.
Newbie, thanks for the indicator. I
think I might be missing piece of my
trading being selective and
understanding trend, bias, momentum,
control, and condition. I know that
you've watched my video as your recent
video describes. Yes, I think it's a
good video. I think it's a good video. I
think it would help a lot of people
stay out of poor poor trades. That's
normally what lets people down. They can
spot good trades. They can't stay out of
poor trades.
What time frame am I watching? This is a
one minute. Um, I execute on a one
minute. I'll be honest with you. I'm
watching a five and a one. Right. So,
once I've done my top top down analysis,
I have a an hourly that I pay close
attention to and a five and a one.
Right? So when I'm looking when we come
into areas of interest, I'm looking to
see who's trapped and where they're
trapped on the volume uh on order flow
on footprint on bookmat using a five
minute and a one minute. That's that's
what I'm looking at. All right, that's
all I'm looking at. So like my five
minute right here,
right? So I've got my flow zones on here
on a fivem minute and I'm just looking
at where are shorts coming flying in.
Where did buyers get stuck this morning?
Where is value? Where are we migrating?
Where are their stops that we can
potentially run? And once we get into
those areas on a 5m minute, then maybe
I'm looking at a one minute being like,
okay, who can I see in a very low time
frame who's getting themselves caught?
I haven't tried deep charts. Uh there's
some guys in the in my group who have
used them, think they're very good, but
my what I'm using is very very similar
on Ninja Trader. very very similar.
Thank you, Rosco. Appreciate the kind
words. Yeah, if anyone hasn't watched
it, I dropped a new video at the
weekend. I'll post it in chat. Um, it's
probably useful to you guys about when
to get into a trade and why to get into
a trade and just building a very simple
system, right, to give you context of
what you're looking at on the day. And
if you just go through it over and over
and over again, if you get into it every
day, that video right there, I would
advise you guys go and watch it.
We're still just trading inside of the
orb, inside of the IB, inside of value
on the day. We're just rotating,
rotating, rotating, rotating. I tell you
what, if shorts don't get this breakdown
soon, uh Rick will get his play because
they will get themselves stuck. They
have tried here and here. And if they
don't get this move soon, you will have
a lot of shorts piled into this. And
Rick will probably get that squeeze up
to here. And if they get acceptance,
then they have the next node.
[cough]
[snorts]
Do I know if there's another way to see
delta levels on volume profile like on
deep charts? uh like this. This is what
I'm looking at. This is delta, right?
This is volume. This is delta. So, yes,
but you need third party apps to to do
it. But that's exactly what I have on
Ninja Trader.
Exactly what I'm looking at.
Or alternatively, if you're using BMAP,
where's you guys here? You can watch
this. This is your delta, right? This is
why I have it next to price. So we have
a big blue for me is positive delta red
is negative delta and we're looking for
outliers big outliers to see who's in
control right so that's why I also have
the level two up someone asked earlier
do I watch the domain the answer is yes
I have a video on how to set it up on a
5minute NT It's it's it isn't on NT.
Well, it is on NT mate, but you'll need
to I I'll send you a link afterwards.
It's uh it's called City Footprint.
You would have seen um me and Mo talk
about it in chat a few times in Discord.
Do I recommend some good orderflow
platforms that have everything you would
need in one platform like footprint,
heat map? Uh yeah I mean what I'm using
has all that right this is on ninja
trader using city right has all that
these are the big participants this is
delta this is volume profile this is uh
delta at the bottom as well like has all
that there's there's tons and tons and
tons it's just finding one that you like
at a price point that you're comfortable
with [snorts]
but we can go uh those in discord we can
go over this later I have emailed them
asking for a discount for students so
waiting to hear back it is Christmas
they are in Germany. They will be
celebrating. They'll probably won't I
probably won't get a response till
January.
Yeah, Mo. Mo is an expert. It's Mo that
helped me out and get into it. I mean,
we have slightly different setups, but
we're looking at the same stuff. Yeah,
like ask Mo in chat. Uh Mo in Discord,
guys. He's uh well versed in it.
Okay, coming back down. They're trying
to break down. They're going to try and
come for these lows again. All right,
again, this is where the big selling
keeps coming in at 90s. They are not
finding
good flush under 90s. What they're
trying to do, they're not getting it.
They're trying to get a good move under
90 to come and clean out these stops. So
80s, 82s and 80s is where I can see a
buyer on the tape right now trying to
absorb. The question is, do we run the
stops? Q's are just stuck between the
5day and the 20-day. If you look at QQQ
stuck right between the 5day and the
20-day today,
still no stop run of these lows. The
more they try and the more they don't
get it, the more annoyed they're going
to get. That bid just moved up from 80
to 87.
So, someone's been trying to cover down
there. He's starting to get upset he's
not getting filled and he's starting to
walk his bid up to try and get filled.
So, he's at 87s now.
Yes. Discord is for members only. Yeah,
people have done the 20our course. It's
no monthly fee. It's just a onetime fee
to do the course in Discord, which like
I said, guys, it's just to make sure
everyone's trading the same way.
How long can you leave the delay? I
think it's uh 48 hours, market stalker,
and don't quote me on that, but it used
to be 48 or 72 hours on Apex. Check the
check the FAQs, though.
The VIX looks absolutely
terrible. Absolutely terrible.
It's just stuck. Completely stuck. And
it's trading downside of anything.
Building liquidity to go lower on the
VIX. So, the opposite to what you'd want
to see if you were bearish on this tape.
Right now, you can see we're starting to
wedge in and someone is going to get
hurt soon. All right. starting to wedge
in. Sellers need this breakdown under
here to here and they are not getting
it. Buyers are going to look for a
squeeze above this into this. Right. And
this is the wedge building out,
liquidity building out. Someone's going
to get hurt. It's a matter of time.
Yeah. Well, we expected it, didn't we?
Low volume day. We We This is what we
expect. So this is absolutely what we
expect.
There you go. Market stalker. Someone
just answered you two days. So I said 48
72 hours here. So you have two days to
activate it. [snorts]
Okay. How many likes we got on stream?
Should we do some giveaways here? What
we up to?
Nowhere near enough, guys. We need 400
likes. 550 of you watching and we've
only had 250 likes. Smash that like
button. Let's get it up at least 350 and
we'll do an Apex giveaway. Maybe a
course.
At least 350. Just smash that like
button. Doesn't cost you anything.
Tape's gone a bit quiet here.
It's like it's stopped.
How much is the course? Uh, it's $6.49
for the 20our course with the flow zones
in Discord and it's $3.99 for the uh
volume and order flow course. There is a
discount on that course right now. If
you use uh
sorry, I'm just watching this buyer step
in. If you use uh code launch in
capitals, you'll get $100 off the volume
profile course.
Okay. Uh TJ, can you email me um so I
can check your email and I'll add it to
it if it's not there.
Oh, you did this morning. Okay, let me
As soon as I get off stream, mate, I'll
do it. Let me see.
I haven't seen your email. Hang on, let
me check my other account.
Maybe spam.
Did you email the right account?
I haven't had an email, bud.
Are you in Discord, TJ, or not? Shoot me
an email info@flowzonerader.com.
I'll get it fixed for you if it's not
there.
Okay, buyers looking to try and force
this squeeze up at the moment.
Sellers not getting that breakdown.
We are just stuck and sideways. I'd love
to do a giveaway here. Here's the New
York open.
Okay. Well, we're If you fill out the
the EMA form, I'll do it after the
stream. I can't can't do everything at
once, guys. cuz I can't drop everything
for for because one of you suddenly
filled out a form. All right, but what I
can do is definitely sort out TJ.
Just shoot me another email, TJ, cuz I I
haven't got it. I did just check spam as
well.
Okay, so buyers looking to try and
squeeze these shorts out here for
relief.
Yes, not through that New York open.
Market's gone to sleep here volumewise.
It's very very sleepy. It's gone too
sleep.
Gone to sleep. So sellers couldn't get
under these 90s. And uh buyers now if
they can hold anywhere in here, they
will try and complete this rotation up
into this. If they fail, it's still the
same thing, right? It's a buildout of
liquidity. Sellers need to complete this
rotation under here to here. And they've
failed so far. Buyers will need to get
relief into here. And if they can cause
a squeeze, good for them. But for me,
it's just a no trade. There's there's
just not enough here to trade with.
You're looking at like 20 points in here
right now. Edge to edge. Like, we'll
just wait and see. Okay, let's do some
giveaways.
Have you hit enough?
When will the volume be back to normal?
Well, have a guess. When everyone goes
back to work, which should be January,
right?
[snorts] Most people will take prolonged
holidays over this time.
10 more likes, folks. 10 more likes,
please. 350 minimum here.
[snorts] 350 minimum here.
Back down to the underside of this range
now. These guys cannot make up their
mind up what they want to do. And now
this bid has just fallen out bed at the
low side of this, which is hilarious.
And they're still not taking it out.
>> [snorts]
>> Yeah, it's an introductory course
though, guys. Don't get too excited.
You're not I'm not giving you the full
courses.
Same as always. It's the introduction
course. Okay, let's bring this up.
Uh,
right. Let's do Apex first. Code FCT get
you 90% off Apex right now. Just type
that in chat once and I'll give one of
you away, of course, of any size you
want.
So, just type it once. You don't need to
spam. If you spam, it will al auto
automatically pull you out. You only
need to type it once, folks.
Just type it once.
Be nice if they complete this rotation
one way or another. It might actually
set something up for the next day or
two. Give you guys a couple minutes to
do that.
Yes. Coming into its lows as well.
I say spy 685 is probably a big gamma
level. See if they can get there though.
They can't even break this IB low yet.
We are completely stuck. This market's
completely gone to sleep.
One more minute.
Ah, I think I just see you.
Ah, thanks, Todd. Okay, I see it.
Uh,
I'm going to get you set up now while
you guys are entering this.
Sorry folks, get out of here.
Should work now, Todd. That should be
fixed for you. Sorry about that, mate.
All right, let's pull a winner. Five,
four,
three,
two,
one.
Ransom Baggins 9301.
Are you here? Ransom Baggins. What a
name.
Let me know you're here. There you go.
All right. Ransom. Free Apex account on
the way to you. Copy your name so I
know. All you've got to do email me
info@flowzoneontenttrader.com.
Send me a screenshot of you logged into
your YouTube. So, I can see that you uh
own the account and I will sort you out
with a free Apex account of any size
that you want.
All right, congratulations.
Remember guys, Apex is on sale right
now. 90% off ends Jan 6. Code FCT will
get you 90% off. Let's give you guys uh
another giveaway here.
All right, we're going to do the
introduction course. Just type course
once in chat. You only need to type it
once.
Just try type course once in chat.
We're starting to see this breakdown
now.
I want to see if they can you want to
see if they can attack these stops down
here. All right. And if they do attack
these stops down here, I do think we
have unfinished business at the lows.
But it's it's a big if right now, folks.
I would say it's a very very big if.
Every time they've come down here,
they've been absorbed. There is a buyer
on the tape here. 370 lot. Let's see if
he's legit or not in front of 75.
Yes. About to take out that pivot, that
pre-market pivot 9:00 a.m. Can it do it
is the question. It's right into it
right now. Gone wick to wick. Does it
run the stops down here or not?
[snorts]
It's not really getting going yet. So,
we will see, folks. You will see.
So, uh, ES is already down here, right?
ES is already down here. That bid just
pulled. So, he's a spoof. Mr. Spoof on
the tape. Just be careful. Mr. spoof on
the tape.
Is there anyone lower? 667 657
630s. All right, 630s would be good.
That's basically into your previous week
value area low, which is what we're
talking about. That low hanging fruit if
we big if we can get there. If we can
get there,
is ES taking that liquidity? Yeah, it's
still not. It's coming though. Okay, ES
now about to take it. And if they flush
and recover, I'd be careful here on Q's.
It's gone tick for tick. You need a
flush here. And uh if you were short,
remember anything down here, you want to
be covering some of your position.
Yeah, it's not willing to willing to run
it out yet.
What indicators am I using, guys? It's
I'm using my flow zones, right? my
system and you get you get a version of
it with the course or you can upgrade to
the full version or you can buy it on my
website if you're interested. There's no
pressure to do that, but there you go.
All right, let's draw a winner of this.
5 4 3 2 1
Edward Ruxens. Are you here? Edward
Ruxens.
Edward Ruxens.
Making a note of your name.
Are you here, my friend?
There you are. All right, Edward. Same
thing for you, please. Right, take a
screenshot of you logged into YouTube.
Send it to me. info@flzonetrader.com.
of you logged in and I will sort you out
with a free introduction course.
And that will also mean you get um
$100 off uh if you ever want to do the
main course as well.
Nice. Thanks, ma'am. All right, so we
got 15 20 minutes left. Markets trying
to trade lower. Has ES wicked it yet?
Still not. So ES has gone wick to wick
with that pre-market low.
Looking to see if they uh flush that
level and run the stops at the moment.
They keep bidding off it.
You think volume profile is useless? Uh,
are you okay?
Really?
I don't think so.
It probably means you don't understand
how volume works cuz volume profile is
definitely not useless, is it? It's
clearly showing you that we're in a
rotational day. It's clearly showing you
that it's built out a node here. It's
clearly showing you that unfinished
business is down here if it can get it.
It's clearly showing you that it can't
find acceptance above here. But you know
what it must be that all the traders
around the world who use volume profile
must be uh must not know what they're
doing.
Motive wave. Yeah, I've heard motive
wave. Very good.
We are stuck. [sighs]
Market is asleep.
Market is asleep. Oh,
I don't think this is accurate because
you can see it's not giving you the good
zones to buy or sell. What the fudge are
you on about, mate? Um,
I'm going to ignore stuff like that. Uh,
it its job is to show you what is
happening based on volume. Um, it is
clearly showing you what is happening
based on volume. How you want to
interpret that is up to you.
Activation fee on 25K uh I think is 60
bucks right now. XB
95% of traders fail. So yeah, they don't
know what they're doing. Yeah. Uh 95% of
uh retail traders do not use volume.
Most of them use uh imagine imaginary
gaps, imaginary imaginary information.
>> [laughter]
>> It's funny how such a strong opinion
followed by thanks for the explanation.
That says everything you need to know
about retail right there. It doesn't
work. It doesn't work. It doesn't work.
It's not showing me what to do. It
doesn't work. It doesn't work. Oh,
thanks for explaining it. And that sums
up retail.
[laughter]
How about taking the time to learn
something first?
Have I heard of Patrick Wheeland? Yes,
I've of course I've heard heard of
Patty. Patty boy.
I'm long Bitcoin from 110. It's not
going higher. It doesn't work.
[sighs]
Oh god. I bought silver at alltime highs
because the market said it's going to go
higher. It's not working. Why isn't it
working? It's wrong.
Come on, guys.
Oh gosh.
Volume's literally gone to sleep, folks.
I literally watching a book. You got one
one player uh sort of pinning it every
now and again and pulling. There's
nothing else happening. It's completely
gone sleep. Everyone's left to take.
We've done two giveaways.
I'm I'm definitely not going full
Patrick this morning.
Definitely not.
You're welcome, man. You're welcome,
man. I'm definitely not going full Patty
this morning.
I haven't sworn at any of you. I haven't
screamed at any of you. I haven't shut
the chat down.
I'm just saying like don't you don't
comment on whether something works or
doesn't work if you don't know what
you're looking at. Right? It's like me.
I couldn't go and look at a car engine
and be like, "Oh, that's [\h__\h]
broken." I am I haven't got Scooby-Doo.
What's going on if I look at something
like that? Not yet. Yeah, not yet.
[laughter]
It's coming. The rant is coming. It's
definitely not coming, guys. I'm so
chill today.
[laughter]
Yeah. This is me being calm.
Okay. Still nothing happening here.
Divergence to ES. Did ES break down that
pre-market low? It didn't. It did sweep
the initial balance low though. All
right. If we want to have a look at ES,
we did see a sweep of the IB low right
here. We're not finding acceptance below
it though. Right now,
we can't find acceptance. We didn't
sweep premarket. That's what I was
looking to see if we would sweep it. And
you'll see some form of compression
here. Okay. If they don't fill their
obligation, if they cannot successfully
take out all these stops and shorts keep
piling in, at some point you might get
that short covering rally, which is what
uh I think Rick was looking for the
start of a short covering rally. Just
depends whether ENQ uh which is holding
up pretty well right now. Remember, we
haven't swept this low, but we are like
we talked about in this sort of zone
that we pivoted from this morning. So,
if we think about structure, there's
your pre-market flush. There's the
breakdown. There's a pivot off. There's
the first retest, and we're just
building out volume here. Remember,
we're in a rotational market. There's
your shape right now, condensing in
here. Longs look for are looking for a
break above the teens and 20s. Shorts
are looking for a continuation below the
80s and definitely below the 60s to get
down into these pockets here. This is
what shorts are trying to do. This is
where longs are trying to get back to.
All right. here and here. And that's it.
We are pinned right now on low volta.
You got what? 10 minutes left.
I'm just reading your comments, folks.
I'm not going to read them all out loud,
but
that's great to hear, Abby. That's
That's awesome to hear. Glad I'm glad
it's helping.
What do I think about gold after this
little crash? Um,
Looks fine.
What's the volume like
when I'd start getting concerned about
gold, right? I would like a bid will
probably come in around this shelf.
Maybe it comes in here. What I'd be
concerned about is if you get a failure
to follow through. If you push up and
you leave these guys trapped, one, two,
three, four, five days worth trapped and
a deeper pull back into here maybe. and
then if there's a continuation to the
bottom side of this range. But at the
moment it looks okay. I wouldn't be like
bidding on this market uh necessarily
like swing. But if you're swing long in
gold and have been you know since this
pullback remember the last time I played
gold was a short
here
right for this move. We've accumulated
since okay the pullback into this sort
of range here is what they're trying to
hold for a rep push higher. Okay. If you
start to see failures to reclaim and
start to go backside without the ability
to reclaim, that's when I'd be more
concerned about gold doing a bigger
pullback. But, you know, with what's
going on macrowise, I think it looks
okay right now.
Same in silver. I mean, if we look at
expansion of this range,
getting right up to the fours.
If we think about retracement
one pivot low,
right, it's still healthy. It's fine. It
hasn't even retraced 50%. Remember, we
talked about it. Like this move last
week was a 25% push up. You have to
understand how big a move this was on
low volume. Where's last week? Monday
almost 25%. Right. It's a big [\h__\h]
move. One, two, three, four days. It it
needed it needed and it needs a
pullback. Okay. What you don't want to
do is the guy who's like, "Oh, silver's
at all times and buying." Right? You're
becoming the liquidity for them to sell
into. You got to remember how an auction
works, right? They can't sell. They
market makers, institutions can't sell
to nobody. They need retail. All right?
They need retail the other side of the
trade. So, hysteria, gold, all silver at
all time highs. Hysteria. Hysteria. CNN,
CNBC, BBC, ITV, whatever. Oh, silver all
time highs. Great time to buy. All
right, you all go rush and buy it.
Institutions go, "Thanks. There's my
profit taking." Pair off the market.
Flushes back down. Retail starts to
panic. Sell, sell, sell, sell, sell. Oh
my god, I did the worst thing ever.
Sell, sell, sell, sell. Institutions bid
it back up. All right, you have to
understand how the auction works. It is
about buying low and selling high, but
it's about using the liquidity at those
levels to be able to get enough size on
to buy and sell where they want.
Did you just [\h__\h] call me Patrick? Am
I about to go absolutely mental here? My
name is not Patrick.
[laughter]
I execute on a one or a five minute, my
friend.
Correct. Correct. If it's in the news,
it's in the price, right? We're forward
looking in the market. We price in ahead
of the news, right? Ahead of the news.
It's why you often see like, you know,
big news events. It's already priced in.
The news event comes and you get the
dump. It's already priced in.
Some say that futures are such an
efficient market. It's difficult to find
edge. Have you used a variation of your
methodology on equities? Yeah, I would
agree with that. I think um futures are
very very efficient market. Doesn't mean
that there is an edge. You have to be
very very patient. But you're not or
you're it's not true always because
silver is a prime example. Okay? If you
if you've taken that short position on
silver overnight, it was very very
clearly needed that retracement. All
right? like I will show I'll I don't
even know but I can guarantee you it's
well outside the standard deviation. We
will just have a look. Right, let's go
to our daily.
All right, let's look at silver.
Okay, surprise surprise. We're outside a
standard deviation, right? We're well
over two standard deviations. In fact,
I'd say we're probably at three standard
deviations plus. Let me have a look on
the 20-day. There you go. So, uh two and
a half, just shy of three standard
deviations. We were 2.7 standard
deviations outside of the mean on
silver. Okay. So I already know markets
cannot live outside two standard
deviations. Almost all markets unless
you're talking about small cap and even
those traditionally can live outside
three. This all right is a fantastic
condition to be short on silver. All
right for a mean reversion trade where
we where's the first reversion? 5day
second reversion 20day. All right
outside of Ballinger band overextension.
So to say that there's no edge would be
incorrect. To say there's less edge I
would say is correct. Why? Because
you've got more vehicles to trade in
stocks. Okay. So if we think about
something equivalent of in stocks, I
don't know. Let's look at some of the
high gamma exposure names. RGTI for
example. Can we find that? RGTI.
Okay.
This right is very very clearly a short
squeeze on continuation on retail
getting trapped right
big move first condition second
condition there there's the trap that
fade from here back down to where it
came from is a highly probability trade
all right you're not going to see that
setting up on ENQ very regularly right
so when people say that about defining
edge and uh do stocks and single names
have more edge Yeah, frequently they do.
Um,
and if you think about you've got 500
stocks plus to look at and that's on the
S&P alone. If you want to include the
New York Stock Exchange even more, if
you want to include small caps even
more, right, then you have more
opportunities
in those names
to find
really what you're talking about is
finding participants offside. That's
really what we're talking about all the
time. When we talk about efficiency,
we're talking about finding participants
offside. So, I would agree with that to
an extent. But what I'd say is if you
learn to trade this market, whether it
be Q's, ES, gold, whatever, if you learn
the personalities, you will be able to
find some edge there. It's just very
much about being patient.
Where you based in the UK? I'm not I'm
based on Los Los Angeles. I'm from
London, but I'm based in LA.
What is my setup to take a trade? Uh my
favorite setup will be multi-time frame
trap participants. Okay, multi-time
frame trapped participants. So, if we
have left a volume shelf,
we've talked about this a few times last
week. Let's
think about it.
I can give you examples of trades I like
here.
This was a trade we participated in with
size, right? Because we left a twoe
balance range trapped. Fail breakout,
fail breakout, fail breakout. Everyone
who's long in there is caught. Fail to
re reclaim. That is a high probability
higher time frame short. So we look for
a lower time frame entry. Short short.
Here we traded the squeeze back up while
everyone else was looking short. This
was an old naked point of control on a
weekly chart. Once we hit this and we
started reclaiming, everyone was looking
for a continuation. Had not very many
reasons to go lower. This was a long
back up. I'd say this is an A trade.
This up here was an A+ scenario. These
fades here were A+. This is probably an
A setup. This right here is like a C
setup for me. It's like I don't really
want to trade inside these. I'm
interested above here or below here or
for a reclaim here. Right? So that
that's how I deem it. Easy way of
putting that I'm looking for a protrend.
I'm looking for alignment where what I'm
seeing on an intraday session aligns
with my thesis on a higher time frame
session and we're at a key area.
[snorts]
Just cuz I mean it doesn't have an
accent does it doesn't mean you live
there.
Maybe I've missed comments above. Yeah,
I'm from London guys, but I live in Los
Angeles.
How do I use IB for trading? Like you
look for breakout breakout failure
patterns for those levels or you just
use for reference. Yeah, absolutely. Uh
I use it to tell me what the condition
is.
Go and watch my video that I posted on
Friday or Saturday. Right. This is a
prime example. All right. Can we find
acceptance outside of value, outside of
initial balance? No. Are we outside of
current day's value? No. Are we outside
of previous week's value? No. Are we in
a low volume day? Yeah. So, what's my
expectation? Rotation. I'm not expecting
a trend. If we can't get outside of
anything here, this is screaming and we
just rotate and rotate and rotate and
rotate. And maybe like buyers can rotate
to here. Maybe they fell up here and
rotate down here. I'm not expecting a
trend. So, I This is telling me the
condition of the market.
All right. This is telling me the
condition of the market. Opening range.
Are we outside opening range? No. Are we
outside of value? No. Condition of the
market is to build liquidity right now.
We're in a liquidity building phase of
the market. We're not in a trending
phase of the market right now.
What's my soccer team? Arsenal.
How do I end up in LA? Uh, my wife took
a job, so we left. We left London.
you're going to enter a short now. What
do I think? Uh I don't think it's
particularly wise. But if that's your
setup, you go ahead. But I I don't think
I don't think I see uh market wanting to
do that.
Auditions. What do you mean auditions
for what?
I can't um I'll be a terrible actor. I
don't know what what could I What could
I audition for, JD?
Do I have math entry by like buy one or
buy three? No. That's called averaging
into a loser. It's the worst thing you
can do. No, no, no, no, no.
Uh, opening range, whatever you want it
to be. Initial balance is the first
hour. opening range. Most people would
play a 30-second, 5 minute or 15 minute
opening range.
Yeah, I'm [\h__\h] Goona. And guess what?
We are top of the league. Top in Europe,
top in Premiership. Don't want to hear
all that. That's where we are going into
the new year. Can we Can we get the job
done? We'll see if some [\h__\h] strikers
can start scoring. It'd be nice.
Shakespeare. Oh gosh, I've got nothing.
Yeah, exact. I'm with Adam here. Any
Arsenal slander, instant ban, you'll
never be welcome here again.
Once price breaks out of accumulation,
should we end wait for a retest of range
or enter immediately on the breakout?
That is down to you in your trading
style. Are you a breakout trader or or
are you a break and retest trader? Do
you like to play against volume that's
been built or not? I can't tell you the
answer to that. That's That's down to
you.
Nice one, Aaron. Hope you're good, mate.
City will catch us. I hope not.
I hope not. They look dangerous, though.
I mean, Haland's just I need him to be
injured or something.
Giraz is not a Howland right now. He's
not finishing like a Holland.
Right, we're into lunch here, folks.
We're into lunch.
Look, you can't do, guys, I'm going to
help you out here. I can tell it's from
you guys. You can't do a stop-loss based
on percentage. And you can't do well,
you can you can do what you want, but if
you're doing a stop-loss based on
percentage or a take profit based on
percentage, you are ignoring what the
charts are telling you. you are totally
ignoring it, right? You your stop needs
to be where your trade is no longer
valid. Your TP should be up to a level
if we're long up to a potential level of
resistance up to an area of liquidity
and then after that we're looking at the
next area. If you're just doing it based
on, well, this is what I want. Well, let
me tell you something. Market don't give
a flying f about what you want, right?
It doesn't care. So, you have to trade
what's in front of you. That is
structure. You have to trade the
structure in in front of you, right? If
I'm going to put my stop here, let's say
I'm long now and I put my stop here.
Well, market don't care about that,
right? Even under here, right? Maybe I
can be like, I'm hope the market
protects that or I hope the market
protects that. I hope the market
protects that. These are the swing
points that the market's going to look
to run. If I put my stop in front of
them and it's highly likely that I'm
going to get stopped out, isn't it?
It doesn't care about percentages,
right? It does not care about what you
think, what you want. take that out of
it. You have to play based on what the
market is showing you. Not what you
want, what it's showing you. [snorts]
Why the Man City blue candles are a fair
point, mate. I mean, a fair point there.
What shall I change them to?
Everyone's got a color. [laughter]
There you go. There you go. SFC. There
you go. [snorts]
All right, folks. I think I'm going to
get out of here. Um, just a reminder,
the sale for the volume uh profile and
orderflow course will end Jan 1st. Okay,
at Jan 1st that will end. So if you are
interested in doing it and you want $100
off, sale will end Jan 1st. Prices on uh
the mentorship, the 20our beginner to
advance course will be going up next
year.
Just do what you want. Like I always
say, go and what I do so many free
videos. Just go and do all those first.
You don't have to spend money, but if
you are interested, that is what's going
to happen. And um the sale on Apex, I
believe, is till
Jan 6th. you still have uh a sale on
most of the other sites right now if
you're interested. I did do a video on
my favorite ones right now. Uh please
don't trade with funding ticks, okay?
They will steal your money and they are
absolute [\h__\h] Don't trade with
them. Ones you need to be trading with
Lucid, Funded Next, Apex, Take Profit
Trader, Traderify. Um there are some
outside of those, but those would be my
top five for 2026. Okay? Please, please,
please, please, please do not trade with
funded ticks. Okay, they have uh
clearly they must have some liquidity
issues or something. Stay away from
them. They will take your money from
you. All right, if you've got accounts
with them, don't go and blow those
accounts up. But uh I wouldn't buy any
more accounts with them. All right.
Well, the thing is, Radical, a few
months ago, they were fine.
It's only become a problem in the last 5
days.
So, it wouldn't have made a difference
to you a few months ago. We were all
taking big fat payouts from them a few
months ago.
No, haven't traded with Funded Futures
Network. What happened with Funded
Ticks? I think they have some liquidity
issues. So, they retrospectively changed
all the rules. So, if you log into your
account, you'll probably see that you're
missing a decent chunk of profit.
They've changed the rules on uh how many
days you need to trade, what profit
targets you need to hit, how long you
need to hold trades for. Um they are
they will lose a well they already have
they've lost a ton of uh support now. So
just be careful. Normally if people are
doing retrospective um changes it's
because they have some liquidity issues
as in they're paying out too many
traders, they're losing money. They need
to stop.
All right,
but all the links and the codes for my
favorite prop firms, they're all down
below. So, obviously I do make
commission that, but if you want to use
the codes, they will always get you the
best uh best price code FCT for most
prop firms other than take profit, which
is flow zone, right?
Yeah, lots of you still made some
winning there, which is good.
Giant rider up 440 this morning. Thank
you for your insight and teaching.
You're welcome.
You're welcome, everyone. Thanks,
Jeremiah. Thanks everyone for joining.
Took a payout and done with funding
tics. Yeah, that's how I feel. I think I
took three or four payouts. Um,
no, they didn't even respond to me. Uh,
and they sent that email out the weekend
which is just utter bollocks. Just just
not good people.
Yeah. Every morning. Yeah. Anyone that's
new, I'm live here every morning. 9:15
Eastern time all the way until lunch.
Right? It's important that you show up
at 9:15 9, not 9:30
in my opinion because I go through the
pre-market and what I'm looking at. It's
there that you're going to learn what
we're looking at each day. The process
of where we are, where we're opening up,
what the potential trade setups are.
Remember, your profits come from
planning, right? The process, the
planning, that's what leads to the
profits, not just turning up and just
hitting buy or sell.
Okay? So, you're starting to see these
stops starting to get popped. So, this
is what I saying. If you put a stop loss
on based on percentage, it wouldn't have
helped you. We're going to start running
these out. All right, folks.
H that's awesome to hear. I'm glad,
Tommy. All right, guys. Back tomorrow
morning. All right, we'll be back
tomorrow morning. We'll go again. Make
sure you check out all those free videos
I posted at the weekend. I think you'll
find them useful. Peace and le love,
everyone. Use hard stops. Remember, it's
low volume. Don't be expecting too much.
And uh yeah, I'll see you all tomorrow.