Morning team. Morning team. How are we
doing? Last session before Christmas.
We're going to go over through uh go
going to go over all the higher time
frames. Look at what we might get.
Expecting a lower volume day. We have
had some news this morning moving the
market a bit, but uh a bit like
yesterday afternoon. Not expecting too
much today, but you never know. So,
we're going to turn up. Be here for it.
We're going to give away some courses
and uh Apex counts either way to make it
worthwhile for your time. So, as always,
starting on the daily chart. I'm a bit
bunged up, so if I sound funny, that'll
be why. All right. You can see we're
trading this low volume node. All right.
Right here. If you're wondering what
this profile is on the side of the
chart, this is the 2025 profile. All
right. This is all the volume we've had
for the whole of the year. And we are
trading right in a little node at the
moment where we might potentially catch
a bid. All right, if they use it as
support, if we get under it, we will
probably use it as resistance. All
right, what are we doing? We're trying
to close the gap right now. So, we can
see this Friday to Monday gap is right
here. We're trading inside of it for the
second time. Yesterday, we tapped into
it, found a bid. Today, we are trying to
uh close it by the looks of it. At the
moment, probably right into the middle
point of that gap. We have lost the
20-day, not by much. It's just above us,
maybe 10, 20 points above us. We've got
the 50-day below and the 5day way, way
down here. All right, so the
opportunities are still here, both sides
of the market. If we think about what we
did, we talked about this from the low
to here.
Alex's brain not in gear from the high
to here. All right, we drove up into the
golden zone. Can't get a close above the
786 right now. I'll keep rejecting into
this rebalance. Question is, do we find
a bid here, right, for the remainder of
the year? Is a bid found somewhere in
here to go and attack the highs or is
this just a little bull trap and we
collapse back down and we do something
like this? Time will tell. We don't know
right now. I'm definitely on low volume.
I'm not placing that bet. I'm not
looking for a big move out of this in
low volume. Okay, let's have a look into
the hourlys.
Make sure you guys can see this. All
right, this is where it gets a little
tricky right now. All right, because
we're leaving
or we're trading between two volume
areas.
So, yesterday
we had a big D-shaped profile right
here. You can see this is tight, right?
717s
to 75s. There's not a lot in that. 40
odd points. Okay, there's not a lot to
play with there. But this is where we
couldn't find acceptance above. We
didn't find acceptance below. We traded
sideways all day like we predicted but
we have now broken down away from it on
that news trading into the gap. So the
question is very simple. Are we going to
reject volume or value from yesterday?
Are we going to migrate value lower? Are
we going to come into here reject value
area lower in front of value area low
and close this gap if there's going to
be follow through? Are we going to get
down to previous day value area high?
All right with there is a node here
which is why I've marked it out. So, I'm
watching this to see, do we find a bid
in and around, let's just call it 580
down to 520. All right. So, if we're
going to have one more little drive
lower to fill the gap and maybe do some
more damage, then I'd be looking for
this move here. Some kind of bull trap
here and cover points would be here.
Three point three points really close
the gap little node previous week value
area high.
If we come down here on a morning flush,
all right, without giving the good sell
signal, I'll be ignoring the shorts and
I'll wait and see. Are we going to find
a bid here, here, or here to come back
up, right? So, I'm willing to play both
sides of this tape as long as we go to
an extreme. If we go up into previous
days value and there is no reaction,
right, and we do something like this,
then we're going to expect this, right?
We're going to expect move from lower
value to higher value. It's not a lot to
move from. So if you wanted to play that
and we reclaim it, you could look for
this move back to the top side of value
if you wanted to play inside of
yesterday's value.
If big big [clears throat] if here, but
if we lose previous week's value area
high,
the natural progression, if suddenly the
market got very very heavy, I'd find it
somewhat surprising on what I'm going to
consider a holiday session. Then you'd
be looking for a move down here, 400s,
440s, right into point of control. if it
really got a weak week all the way down
here. I find that move there
kind of hard to think about happening
today given the probability that not
many people are playing the market. But
you never know. You just never know. So,
I've got to prepare you for it. All
right. That's the we'll deal with that
as and when and if we get there. So, the
first moves we're looking for are a push
that fails, TP1, TP2, TP3, or a flush
that bids up.
Right? Those are your first
opportunities in the market. Your second
opportunity in the market will be if you
reclaim this to go from one side of
value to the other. And kind of the same
but on a weekly if you lose this
you lose this and stay heavy here will
be this move right
one of these options right so that's
that's to have you prepared for what
we're looking for if we move up here you
can just see we're trading right in the
middle of the gap it's the last place I
want to trade right now all right so um
we we don't want to trade right in the
middle we want to see this come back
here test some key level and fail if
we're going to go for downside. All
right, that's what we're going to look
for. Okay,
let's cycle through some of these names
quickly. A few to get through. ES over
the 900s, which is that key level I
probably say over under. Let's have a
little look. Yeah,
so relative strength here. Can ES find a
bid at 900 and continue that move up?
Otherwise, you're looking at 880s.
All right. So, I'd be looking to see can
it hold 900
whole number or 880s for that bid back
up to take out some of this liquidity.
That's the big question. It has relative
strength. It's possible. Um, if we look
at RTY, that was on a screamer
Sunday, come back down, big push
yesterday. Same kind of thing. Does it
find a bid here or do we see that
rotation in small caps at end of the
year start to come back into the bigger
names? Time will tell. tell. All right,
spiders
85 upside and then there's not really
much until 700. The the big gamma I had
a look last night is still up here. Um I
can't imagine we get there this side of
the year, but you just never know. All
right, so I'd be watching 85. That's
been a level for a few weeks as has 82
and 80s. All right, so 80s pull back
into 80s. If they hold a pull back into
80s, we can be bullish. 82s as well.
There was some exposure there, but not
very much. 85s is your top level. So
that's kind of potential rotation here
on an hourly while they build it out.
Cues, same kind of thing. This needs to
be blue.
And we can move this pivot up into
around here. All right. Watching 615s on
Q's if they flush down there and hold.
Um, same as like that uh move we were
looking for on NQ. And if they lose
that, then you can see it's back into
range. Some liquidity here we can aim
for. It all depends. Remember we got a
balance two weeks. This is two weeks
balance range ahead. Going to be tough
to get acceptance back into there, but
we will see. VIX continues or had
continued to drift lower.
Right, low 14s.
This starts to get into the area where
market just barely moves when we're down
here. You know, no volatility. This is
fear, greed, and volatility. This is how
I think about the VIX. So, uh, yeah, all
the time we're down into here, we're not
going to move too aggressively, but you
can see it's caught little bit of a bid
at 14. Um, we're going to have to watch
how it acts at 1490s, 15s. Does it
reclaim? If it reclaims, maybe we get a
bit of weakness in the market this
morning. Bitcoin, all right, reflushed a
little bit last night or the last few
sessions. You can see from Monday, bit
more of a selloff back into this range.
Those trading Bitcoin, there's your
range. Look below. Look above. It needs
to hold this and it's still got to
reclaim this area up here otherwise it's
still pretty bearish. Um, let's have a
look at the big names
opening up flat on Apple. Still in this
range, right, this is Friday, I think.
Thursday. All right, Thursday. Friday,
Monday, Tuesday. Still just boxed in
right now. Not a lot to do. That was It
had weakness yesterday. Did they hold
that pivot? Big question. We're going to
set price alert at this low just in
case.
>> [snorts]
>> Amazon
flat as well. Boxed in as well. You can
see you can see these boxes, folks. All
right. Little bit of an uptrend here. If
they start breaking below this, you'll
see weakness. Otherwise, this has
squeeze potential for a break. Look,
both are possible if buts and may.
That's the market we're in right now
because we don't have a too many
participants. So very similar here to
Google,
right? Strong trend starting to try and
break. There's the look below which bid.
They rebid it. Can they hold 309s? Now
if they lose 309's, are they going to go
backside
again? Open up slightly flat or slightly
weaker actually on Metal. Slightly
weaker as well. Slight gap down. Couple
bucks, not a lot. Um
yeah, Monday gave that whole drive back.
But look above and fail. Hold drive
back.
Zoom out of this. Yeah. Can it hold this
mid part or does we do we get weak into
there? Question marks over that
flat here on Microsoft.
Same thing guys. Boxed in look below
look above create liquidity. It's going
to be the story of the session by the
looks of it. All of them look very
similar.
Nvidia going to come back for these 180
checks or at least 50% or 61% to look
right. So look above here couldn't
regain it. Tried a few times yesterday
starting to lose the bid. So we could
think about this
either catches a bid here or here. And
if it doesn't catch a bid there,
you're going to see weakness.
How we doing for time? Not too bad.
Tesla
couldn't quite make it. Alltime highs
did come yesterday. All right, just shy
of that 500. They're all front running
that 500. It's such a magnet. You'd
expect it to get there, but uh we will
see. So, back down protecting
yesterday's low. Current week low,
previous day low. We've got some bids
down here where we absorbed. So, can
they hold this and have another shot at
it or are we just going to sort of sit
in here, which is very probable? Uh
let's just have a look at a couple
outside of this. So, I want to look at
Oracle. Oh my god, that's pissed me off.
So, I was bidding at 75. We had 78 gap
fill. I was bidding at 75, never got it.
Gh.
Sorry team in Discord. I don't know if
anyone took that swing off the gap fill.
That was really nice. It's worked really
well. AMD, all right, had a big shot
yesterday. They sold it. All right,
we've got trap participants above. And
they sold the 220s and right back down
into this ledge. Now, uh, another one I
want to look at is AVGO.
It's got a bit of a shelf it's been
building.
Yeah, still trying to fill the gap. So,
I'm going to leave
do some alerts down here.
These are just for potential swing
opportunities. That's all it is. All
right, that's us covered.
Back to the cues we go.
Don't be pushing too hard today, folks.
All right. Today is not a day to go
attacking the market with all your size
and pushing, right? Expect low volume.
Expect things like slow drifts and
things like that.
Morning. All just joined. Been trading
futures using supply and demand. Wanting
to learn how you guys trade. Ah, good
morning. Good morning.
Does it say the 22nd? Is that what it
says? Let's change that. Sorry,
it's the uh auto
change in OBS clearly. Maybe it's cuz I
set it live yesterday. That's probably
why. It's probably my fault. [snorts]
All right, here we go, folks. Open
coming up. What? just under one minute
away. How do you join Discord? You have
to do the 20our beginner to advance
course and it comes for free with that
and lifetime for free with that. That's
the course you've got to do if you want
the Discord.
Gold. Sorry. You want a gold? I mean,
you just be looking to see if there's an
all-time high continuation or not.
You've got some structure down here.
I think about these little nodes here.
Do you start holding bids, closing the
gap or not? If you don't close that, if
you don't lose that gap, you're coming
right back down. That's all I'd be
looking for this morning is that gap.
How do you act in that gap?
No, I do not wait 30 minutes. Trade
whatever the setup. If the setup
requires me to wait 30 minutes, I will
wait 30 minutes. If it does not require
me, I will not. So, here's the morning
drive. out. Here's a push into value.
Here's the question. How do we act here
at value? Lower time frame algo previous
week high. There's the tap of value. Do
they now sell this back down is the
question. So, watching this to see if we
get acceptance back into value or if
they're going to sell, right? Do we get
acceptance back into value or are we
going to sell? We find acceptance then
we're looking well you you guys who take
take rotations are looking at 94s and
715. So, straight into value. What a
load of [\h__\h] This is going to leave us
nothing to do today probably.
Don't see a huge driver though there.
We've got a mixed bag in the mag.
Amazon with a push this morning I guess.
And all the way back up to previous days
value area high off one push. Fantastic.
And this is what we call a thin market.
What a load of [\h__\h]
So we will see. Do they reject or they
going to now bid over value high and
keep going? I don't really fancy buying
up here off a move like that this
morning. Thank you very much, market.
They're still bidding this. This is on a
squeeze now.
Well, I'm sorry folks. There's nothing
we can do with that. When the morning
when the opening minute goes through all
the levels like that and keep squeezing.
Oh, I'm not touching it. Not with a
barge bowl. No chance.
No chance. So, protected the gap. No
reaction here. No reaction here. Slight
reaction at value area high. Uh but I'm
not bidding there. When we've gone
through it on one on a one minute
candle,
there is no way. Just no way you will
catch me doing that.
[laughter]
Holiday holiday candles.
Holiday candles.
Okay, let's see if they hold a bid here
or not. Are they going to come right
back down to uh point of control?
We're going to have to change this. I'm
going to get rid of this alto together
to be quite honest
and we're just going to watch
yesterday's levels now. Uh you you could
bid here. I will not be bidding here
because we just squeezed up. I don't
want to bid a squeeze up.
Let's have a look at how we look inside
of here. That was very aggressive for a
morning shove.
So back down towards point of control at
the moment
sevens.
Watching this PC down here. They're
trying to get aggressive here. If they
lose PC, then we're going to go right
back to the other side, you know.
Okay, back to you up.
Oh, you got to love a holiday session.
You got to love a holiday session.
That is funny.
That is funny. All right, I give you
give you We might just come right the
way back down here if we lose all this.
They don't bid here. We're going to come
right the way back down. I'll give you
give you a read out there. Tesla's just
gone green to red. All right, but it's
pretty much flat. Nvidia 0.13% up.
Microsoft 0.15% up. Meta 0.01% up.
Google 0.03% up. Uh Amazon's the strong
one today, 0.81% up. And uh Apple is a
third of a percent down.
spilling water everywhere.
Okay. Well, inside of yesterday's value,
this is not ideal. This was the last
thing I wanted, unfortunately, this in
the previous week. So, we'll just see
how we act here. If they find a bid
around here, it might be that we uh can
drive back up and take out some of those
edges yesterday at 39 and above, but uh
not convinced right now. Big shove up,
big pull back into previous day point of
control. or do they rebid? I have no
idea. If they can't rebid
um then back down to here and New York
open we go. So they basically their
opportunity now is to bid this and do
one of these. They lose this we'll come
to here. Here's the rotation. If we lose
that, we go back right back down to the
New York Open.
[cough]
[clears throat]
Let's see.
Yeah, this is probably like the worst
setup we could have um asked for if I'm
if I'm perfectly honest with you. The
last thing we wanted to do was drive
through all the levels in the opening
one minute and then in minute 3, four,
five, and six be right back stuck where
we were yesterday. That's that's not
that was not my uh if you ask me what my
A+ move was today, this was not would
not have been it. All right, but let's
see. It looks pretty bullish now. We're
starting to grab bids here. So, let's
see if they can bid above value and
start expanding maybe up to previous
days high if we got very lucky. That's
what they're attempting to do at the
moment.
Oh god. If it's going to be like
yesterday up here, there's not going to
be a lot we can do with it.
What's VWAP? Um, I think you might need
to uh do a little bit of research before
you trade if you don't know what VWAP
is. It's volume weighted average price.
Be slightly concerned.
You don't know what that is if I'm
honest.
Okay.
ES did tag previous day high
and GloEx already twice.
Starting to find a bid here. Here we go.
Let's see then. Can we get acceptance?
Looking for a squeeze up.
Current value area high is right here.
Don't want to give this much room, but I
am looking for a continuation squeeze.
Very light size, by the way, folks. Very
very very light size. Here we go.
Through value. Let's see if we can get
through to the 7 740s and above.
We get above here. If we c if we can get
above here, I'm going to peel some out
straight away. as soon as we get into
here. I want to see us hold these levels
and get into here. What I don't want is
us to get stuck. If we keep failing
above this, the danger is this rotation.
I do not want to play that rotation. I'm
trying to play for this at the moment.
Trying to position for that. I will cut
a VWAP if we can't
just get caught again above current
day's value, which is currently 26.
Let's get some volume on for you guys.
No, that's not what I want.
No, no, no. Come here.
There we go.
Okay,
they're trying to bid 10. It looks
sloppy and messy right now.
Yeah, 740 is GloEx highs. We haven't
taken it yet. That's what I was trying
to play up into.
If we get through that,
I don't want this to come back under VPO
here at 705s.
So, we've got some buyers trapped under
705. We need to use their pain to move
higher. So, I'm playing their pain point
at the moment. If we lose that pain
point, then I'll be flat
because if we lose 705s right here, all
right, there are sellers underneath who
are stuck. I will cut out because I do
not want to come back into this. I'll
just cut break even if we get back into
this, which I'm getting very close to
doing right now. It's be we're looking
for this. If they collapse this, then
this is possible. I don't want to trade
this part. I'll just leave it alone and
see if we find a bid here again or if we
collapse the whole thing.
very close to my stop here for BB be
705 is their pain point underneath that.
Okay, stopped out. So, a whole 17 bucks
I made there. Fantastic.
We'll wait back into value area low on
the session. Losing VWAP ES has relative
strength. Couldn't find a continuation
bids.
Going to leave this alone now because I
don't want to trade really inside of
what we created yesterday. This is my no
trade zone at the moment. I want to see
if we can do this or if we're going to
collapse this. Even that's going to be
ugly if we're going to do that. Unless
we trap a lot of volume up here.
It might be that we go to sleep again.
What do I think about the opening range
breakout strategy? I think it's a
legitimate strategy. It's about all I
can say on it.
Sometimes it will work, sometimes it
won't work like most strategies.
Okay, they caught a bid at VPO. Again,
this is not accurate. VPO for me is down
at 704 705 where my stop was.
I need to let this settle down. ES looks
really good like it wants to go. VIX is
trading back down at low of day.
Q's lagging again. Where's RTY? RTY pull
back today.
Tesla the weak one half a half a percent
down. Oracle as well 2.28% down. So we
do have some weakness in tech. Rest of
the market is trying to catch a bid by
the look of it. Amazon's caught big now
1% up. Google now 3/4 of a percent up.
Meta 0.15% up. Microsoft quarter of a
percent up. Nvidia third of up. Tesla
half% down. Oracle 2.16% down. Apple's
trying to close its gap. This thing
can't make it mind up what it wants to
do. Looks pretty bullish. Spies
definitely look bullish right now.
They're about to take out that high and
uh and Globeex,
but [clears throat] weakness in ES in ES
in Q's. God, I'm ready for that holiday
if I can't say the difference between
that.
so through back down into previous day
point of control. Now we might rotate
all the way down into value if they
can't find a bid at previous day point
of control. Value area low from
yesterday was set will be 677s.
This is my no trade zone at the moment.
Yes, rejecting uh GlobeEx there
into VWAP into flow zones.
Sellers coming in down here not getting
their way. So there is still absorption
around previous day point of control for
now. They're trying to reoffer 705.
Hasn't come up there for the reoffer. It
looks a bit thin now or it's already
gone to sleep.
Anything could happen very quick if a
big player comes in both sides.
There comes the bid
of previous day point of control. Now
they're going to try and get back up to
24s will be their job. Here's previous
day value high. I'm still willing to
play upside if we can find acceptance
above a key level. I don't want to play
inside of yesterday's value. Can we get
above previous day's value area high and
start squeezing? Come on, catch up,
please. So, here's the test of those
20s. 24s I think I said was the level.
There we go. Can we start squeezing now?
ES looking good.
Can't get through value high on the
current session. Want to see expansion
there for me to get in. Looking for us
to base above here for that move. Here
we go. So, here's 24's coming up. We
need to get through
20 in that candle that there 37. All
right. All the buyers got caught from
24s to 34s and the same from the candle
at 932. So, I'm watching those levels.
That's why I'm waiting to see if we can
find acceptance above there. We're
rotating into it. I need to see if we
can find acceptance above it.
Uh, very possible, Jour. Yeah, I mean,
we we do expect sideways no volume
today.
That that is our expectation is for
that.
They're
holding PC again.
No acceptance yet from ES on that drive
out.
I don't know, Carla. Couldn't tell you
why. Maybe you're measuring it
differently. Good morning, Bella. How's
it going?
Morning, Bella. Everyone say good
morning to Bella, our Apex Queen.
Yeah. No, no, no. Early Christmas
present. You're right. You are
definitely right. We're just stuck. We
are stuck.
It's trying. It keeps trying up here and
failing.
Every time buyers step in here, they're
getting hit with a passive seller, but
it it's trying. It is definitely trying
to get going here. It wants to get
through these value area highs from
previous day and current day. It's just
struggling a bit.
720 is the level. You can see every time
it's up there, there's uh some buyers
keep getting offside. If they get
comfortably through that, we'll squeeze.
Here we go. Can it get through it?
Just added more offside delta there.
There's sellers at 25s and 30s. We have
the chance to go here. I really think we
have the chance to go here on a squeeze.
So, can we find acceptance to squeeze
now?
Upside to 40s possible. Come on, market.
Someone just put their foot down on the
gas. There you go. All right. Here we
go, folks. Here we go. So, we're looking
for that upside target. ES starting to
go now as well. Can we get acceptance?
Here we go, folks. Here we go. Looking
for that move into 40s. take some
partials on the way because we're not uh
a big volume day. But once we get to 40s
and above, we might start squeezing.
Here we go. We've got some sellside
inefficiencies above into 45s. Here we
go. Partial into this. Thank you very
much. Took a minute to go there, didn't
you? And let's see if we get very lucky,
we get up here. But most of my money is
coming out here just in case because I'm
expecting range rotation.
And [snorts] we thinned out straight
away the bids. Where's Where's Mr. Mr.
Bidder can't see anyone. We're looking
at uh five lots on the tape here.
There there's Mr. Bidder. He's down at
17 and 20s now. So, they're going to
refresh down there if they get the
opportunity. No one with size up here
right now.
Man, I missed the short from previous
day. Val area low almost gap filled.
Missed the long from the current
session. This might be a no no day for
me. Oh, that's all right. I mean, you're
not missing lot a lot. Let's be honest.
You the range is pretty small. You're
not missing much. Okay, so here we go.
Back down into that bid we just talked
about. 20s and 17s filling this
imbalance. There's not many players on
the book today, folks. I'll tell you
that much. There are not many players on
the book. 20s is key. I'd say 21 and 20
and 19. Those all have over a 100 lot
buy side delta currently offside. So buy
uh sellers
will want to keep the will will want to
get back under those guys. That's where
they keep rebidding. Here we go again.
So that same level 17s and 20s.
Can we find acceptance? ES looks
fantastic.
ES looks fantastic. What's dragging us
down? It's Oracle right now. It's the
chips. Tesla quarter% down. It's trying
to play catch-up. Oracle just under 2%
down. AMD five uh half a percent down.
AVGO is trying to go red to green. And
then you've got those like gamma
exposure, what should we call them?
Quantum names. Um kind of just dithering
around today. So RGTI 1.60% down. Uh
MVTs third of a percent down. IQ's up on
the day. Uh it's looked good recently.
Half percent up. Nen 1% up.
It's an interesting one. Cavana, don't
say you've gone without me getting
involved short side yet. Don't don't
don't
you [\h__\h]
Oh,
well that pisses me off,
[\h__\h]
Okay, sorry for language. All right,
guys from Discord, you'll know that I
was looking at this. We mentioned it at
the weekend. Uh, [sighs] didn't get
filled yesterday. Got limits out here
hoping to get filled for this. At least
this gap though want to collapse. I
think this thing is dead in the water.
Honestly, it's way way overcooked it.
Okay, here comes a squeeze. So, can we
get up to previous days high now? Is the
question.
This is our next target. if we get
there. Already pulled most my money out.
Is there a giant wall at 783?
Um
I wouldn't say it's giant. There's a 89
lot in front of it.
Not giant, but there there are people
there. It might get thicker as we get
closer to it, but there's not much on
the tape today. Here we go. One more
squeeze attempt here. Let's go. Let's
go. Let's go. Let's go. See if we can
get up into 90s. Beautiful. Here we go.
Here we go, folks. So, just playing from
previous day value area high once we
held previous day point of control and
gap fill. Remember, we held that twice,
sellers tried once, sellers tried twice.
We play their pain partial into here.
And let's see if we can get up into that
if we get really lucky. And we want to
support the bid here. Now, we don't want
this bid to start losing up here, right?
Because we're in a squeeze now to move
higher. So, we want to try and support
the bid here. We do not want to lose
this level. If we lose this level, I'm
uninterested in this market, but we're
going to do that as great
[snorts]
anyway. Well, it wasn't what we wanted,
but we've made a little bit of money
today at least. Unfortunately, that
opening candle was an absolute ripper.
Can get involved in that. Didn't quite
fill the previous week gap.
and uh didn't
didn't offer any sell opportunity or any
buy opportunity. It was pretty naughty
actually. Dirty candle. Dirty candle.
All right, back into this gray box. My
stop is the bottom side of this gray
box. I want to see them support a bid.
I'm long from previous day value area
high here.
If we don't support a bid, then I will
give back on my runner up.
Buyers just got caught up here a couple
times. Want to be careful. They need to
get back above 45s here.
They definitely need to hold current
value area high,
which for me, what am I looking at is
32s. All right, around here.
Move this up a little bit. Somewhere
around here. We want to hold. They can't
hold this. I'll be I'll cut it, folks.
You're in both long. Nice. Nice, Jour.
All right, I'm out of this now, folks.
On the runner. Nice JSON. Yeah, I wanted
to be in both. Uh Oracle I really wanted
to be in. All right. When everyone was
calling for the end of the world on it,
I was like this is I mean the pullback
on it was so good. People don't
understand how how much we moved so
quickly.
We think about this. This is ridiculous.
O RC L sorry oh it changed here we go
48% pull back basically a 50% discount
yes please into structure here's the gap
fill
gap fill is right here
right so I was looking for longs I just
wanted a little dip into 75s and I was
looking for this retrace now you've got
a gap above into 216s I'll be selling
some into that I saw yesterday they said
that there's a they're looking for 50%
upside next year. So 50% upside so back
into that same level. I think they'll
way exceed that. But uh I'll be taking
partials off into that gap fill and then
just holding. And if we bid for the rest
of the year then it would be fantastic.
And if we lose it I'll cut it and I'd
reattack it down here. Yeah. So nice
play mate. Well done getting long in
that. We were looking for it in Discord.
I had my limits out.
It's
>> [snorts]
>> uh two things I've missed now,
unfortunately.
Is what it is. All right, I'm out of
this. All right, I got out of this on
this uh edge of this gray box. They're
still holding though,
but now flat. So, we're locked in 490
bucks. That is it for today so far.
long entry in case of a New York mid
open retra test. What you want a 50%
pullback off your open candle or I mean
I think it's probably given that that's
probably what that dip is. There's your
open.
That's that opening candle that.
So this was the 50% retrace into that
open candle.
If you're going for a whole session,
you're into these same lows. You're
basically into previous day point of
control current value area low. The only
thing I'd say, Peter, is if you come
down, if we build lots of liquidity here
and we come down into this level and we
don't reclaim, right, and they don't
bid, then we're going to use that and we
come right back down into here. This
this is where it gets a bit tricky.
Especially
on low volume. Remember, it wouldn't
take a lot for one player to just be
like, I'm done with this market for this
year and we we can close very quickly.
Right into point control for the current
session and VWAP range is very small
today, folks. All right. Might look big.
You might be like, we've got 113 point
range. We have, but uh most the range is
actually just in here. Uh you're playing
with 40 points, right? because looks
above have failed. Look below this has
failed and we started the day down here
and we've shown no signs of going back
there. So, we haven't got much to play
with.
[cough]
I say buyers are still in control of
this session right now, but we're just
testing previous days value high. So if
they don't find a bid here, we will
rotate to previous day point of control
previous day value very low. So don't
really want to play in this, right? So
if they don't find a bid here, they will
rotate to this. And if they lose this,
this if they lose this, this is
possible. Definitely this is possible,
but they might well just bid. This would
be like yesterday, right? Yesterday we
did this in here. Today we might well do
this in here again. Very, very possible,
folks. Right. They've lost value area
high
back into here. Now, if they lose this
back into here, then you have to ask, do
they bid off previous day value or was
this just a test of value and we're
going to lose it all? Come back down to
New York open gap fill. I don't know. I
really don't know, folks. They whatever
they want to do with it, they can. We'll
just try and follow as they go.
Tesla about to close its gap. So, whole
of markets trying to go green at the m
moment. Thank you.
Hold of the market's attempting to go
green at the moment. We are attempting
to hold current days value low, this
level here, and previous day point
control and the gap fill. Right. So, gap
fill.
This is previous day's closed, previous
days point control, current day value
area low. This is discount for the day.
If they can hold it, if they lose it,
then we're going to look for deeper
prices
here.
Here.
I have no bias here, folks. No bias.
Balls definitely came in this morning,
but I don't have too much bias.
Thoughts on Nvidia? Um, have a look. You
swing? You mean you bought the dip as in
you bought a swing dip?
I mean, you can see the levels I'm
looking at. You're just in a range on
Nvidia. I don't think anything more than
that, right? Bit of a blowoff up here.
Never able to reclaim. Right. So, you
got buyers trapped up there. If you
break down under this level, it's night
night. All right. So, I wouldn't be
holding on under here. You've had two
undercuts, two look belows which have
reclaimed. I just be very careful if you
lose 170 basically. But otherwise,
you're just going to trade between 85
and 70. If it gets through 85, squeeze
potential to 90. If it gets through
that, it's got bigger potential. That
That's my thoughts.
All right. So, back down to previous day
value area low. So, they lost value high
like we talked about. They're losing
previous day point of control. They're
coming back down into previous day value
low. Do they find a bid here? If they
can't find a bid here, they come right
back down to the New York open and the
old gap fill.
It is uh
not very fun out here.
Classic pump and dump. I wouldn't call
this a dump yet. It might look like a
dump, but uh I wouldn't actually call
this a dump yet. Right. It's a push,
a look above and fail. And we're just in
yesterday's range. There's no dump here,
guys. All right. Just be aware this is
tiny. This might look big because we're
in tiny range. This is [\h__\h] all.
Nothing's really happening here. All
right, fellas and ladies and gents,
let's say. All right, you're looking at
like 30 40 points in rotation. It's not
a dump, right? The dump will come if we
start losing, you know, some of these.
This is uh definitely not not a pump and
dump. Not right now. It's a push and a
look above and fail. I'll give you that
low hanging fruit. Push.
Pull back. low hanging fruit look above
and fail can't hold value back down to
other side of value but this is the
Dshape from yesterday right we have to
leave that for anything further to
happen in my mind
10:00 a.m. Please
[cough]
consumer confidence. Yeah. 10:00 a.m.
What's expected? 91 expected, 88
previous.
I would just try not to carry too much
of a bias today. That's all I would say.
Light volume, holiday day. We're here to
turn up and have some fun. If we get
anything else, it's a bonus.
Value area low, previous day high down
here. This is where they're going to
want to bid. If they lose the bid here,
New York open and uh new opening gap
potential potential, but you would
imagine they'll want to try and bid
here, but we will see.
Just remember, we're basically stuck
between yesterday's value and previous
week value. Bit like yesterday. It's a
little bit of no man's land. [snorts]
We've gone through gold a few times. I'm
sorry. I'm not going to keep clicking
over to gold.
You're short at 729.
That's nice. Once we left this gray box,
that's nice. Right. Look above. Left the
gray box. You're short. I'd be
partiallying into these. Right. Respect
these levels. Previous day point of
control. Previous day value low. Hold a
runner in case you get back to New York
open and close this gap. But expect this
to rotate. Yesterday we did this. It's
very possible they do this again. My
expectation
like defensively I'm thinking, okay,
we're likely to rotate there. And if we
don't and you get further move downside
for you, great. But make sure you're
paying yourself along the way. Looks
very very thin here.
came in at 89.1 versus 88.7 previously
and estimated at 91. So it came in
underestimate but better than last
month. I mean it
it means nothing.
It's a bit like the CPI print.
Oh, inflation's gone down, but we've
only included 20% of uh of inflationary
products. Oh, fantastic. So, so what
you're telling me is you're cooking the
books again.
All right. Value area low here previous
day. [snorts] There's some absorption
here. Down to 67s is where they keep
bidding down to at the moment. They've
just got passive orders out on the book.
Aggressive sellers keep stepping in at
67s. Looking for this wash. Here's
previous week high.
I'm not trading anything right now. One
and done so far for the day. Or it might
have been two attempts at it, but one
and done so far to the day the day. Uh
New York open down here. If we lose
that, we got the gap that we were in
before.
So it's not the sort your mag doing the
damage right now. It's those other names
we talked about. It's AMD, it's AVGO,
it's OCR, it's PayPal, it's Cavana, it's
Bull, it's Neo, it's IBITE, it's iron,
it's IQ,
MBTS, RGTI. It's the quantum names again
suddenly got hit. RGTI now almost 4%
down. MVTS 2.41% down. ONQ 1.41% down.
IN 1.57% down. Those names got hit. Neo
2% down. Bull 3.2% down. Cavana 1.19%
down. Oscar Health 1.90% down. AVGO now
half% down. AMD 1% down. So it's the
names outside of the MAG getting hit.
They are the ones where the profit
taking everyone's like get the [\h__\h] out
of this coming into end of year. Don't
want to hold. They're the ones getting
hit right now. Mag's not doing too bad.
Tesla's the weakest one. Half a percent
down. Everything else is green.
So just probably a rotation. We can have
a look at the breadth of the market.
Let's have a quick look.
Where are you?
I mean, it doesn't look too bad out
there still. This overview. Go away.
There we go. Doesn't look too bad. So
you can see the names getting hit. your
oracles, your softwares,
consumer defensive,
but the the mag's okay. It's outside of
the mag getting tagged right now. Okay,
down into the gap. This is previous day
load. It's green line. All right, down
into the gap, right, giving the whole
thing back.
Are we going to see follow through? I'm
just trying to look to see if we see a
rotation. And tests are starting to
really sell now.
Still weak on the spiders.
Watching this New York open. If they
reclaim this and revisit value area low,
I'll consider a reshort up here. I just
want to be careful because we're in
rotation. This is new week opening gap.
If they come back up back up here
ideally here, I'll consider that move
down.
Just don't if we do this, I don't want
to play it. They've had enough FAFS up
here for two days now. We're going to
continue. I need to see that or in front
of that also is okay.
And I'll tell you the big sellers came
in one block came in at 62 and the other
guys came in at 77.
One block came in at 62. The other guys
came in at 77.
So currently we tapped previous day low.
See if we can close below it. If they
can get aggressive
at New York, let's get rid of these on
the screen. New York open acting as
resistance right now. Let's see if we
can get and close this gap or not. Do
they get acceptance underneath previous
day low? So far, the low of the auction
is all selling. All right. So, it's all
sell side at 30. So, there's still some
bids down there. I want to see this pop
up first before I think about anything
else.
Yeah, gap feels possible. That would be
the edge of the gray box, right? The gap
fill. That's the edge of the gray box.
That's what we were looking at early
morning. Didn't expect them to do that
push quite so aggressively early
morning. I will be honest with you. I'm
looking to see if they drift this up and
resell it. We're a bit extended right
now. I got a nasty feeling that they're
just going to do it in one move like
they did earlier.
Lots of bids down here. 30s, 32s, 25s,
20s, 15s, 05s. Look at all this
liquidity below. So, ideally, they pop
this up for a resell and they don't
reclaim value. We do not want to. If
they reclaim value, I'm [\h__\h] not
touching it. If they're going to be
dirty dogs today, I'm not interested.
But if they pop up and sell like that,
even that last move wasn't too bad, then
we're interested, right? I am interested
in these pushes that start to fail,
especially if they start closing below
30s. If they start closing below 30s,
some buyers got caught there at 45s.
Bids here at 30s. Think we're going to
go now lower. Here's the 30s. They keep
bidding. I think we probably swipe all
these guys out for downside pressure.
Now here come 30s. Come and put that
catch up so I can see.
So they're bidding 30s, 25s, 20s. Ideal
scenario for me will be something
maybe to get over New York open a little
pop somewhere into this node or here
which is resold. Otherwise, they're
going to force me to play low of day
which is not ideal. Don't really want to
do that. But watching this here and this
here, right? So, do we reject this? Like
a look above here or do we come all the
way up here and reject this? Which will
be actually be better price-wise. Uh I
will not play if we get back inside
that. I'm not interested.
Not interested. Remember, we're
protecting the gap at the moment.
So, here over this little node. So
either they look above this and fail now
or they're going to squeeze all the way
back up to previous day value and
current day value area low.
This is where buying keeps coming in at
56s. They keep getting stuck here again.
They got stuck there at 56s. So this is
that like look above that node and fail
kind of move has potential here.
Lots of buyers got stuck in that last
wick. I'll tell you that now.
So, can we close back downside the
bottom side of this node and start
losing 33s? Now, if they rebid over 56s,
we probably go value area low. If they
stay heavy around 56s, we should be able
to look for a wash into new low of day.
Here we go. So, they're protecting it so
far.
They need to see follow through though.
Yeah, not much follow through here.
Hello, wakey wakey sellers. Come back in
please.
This New York Open sticky. They've got
to lose New York Open.
Come on. Here we go. Come on. Lose this.
Lose this. You've got to lose New York
Open. Please stop pissing about around
this.
There's a seller under New York Open.
Keeps getting stuck. Right at 43s. So,
the rotation right now is 56 to 43s.
Waiting for one side to win.
Sellers just want to keep uh these
buyers at 56 is stuck. If they can't
keep them stuck, we'll go previous day
value or low. Here we go. This is seller
coming back in again here at 42 is being
aggressive. We just need a close which
is heavy here.
Eyeing this up for a short
big block just came in. Can they see
follow through to 30s now?
What's this white line here? This is
just one I plotted on the chart.
Oh, this is the opening range. Jesus
Christ. Figure out what that was. Okay,
so still watching 56 is where the buyers
are stuck.
Still no position for me. Cleaning out
56s now. So either they retract buyers
now or we come right the way up to value
area low again. Still no position.
Waiting to see there if they were going
to trap with follow through.
And if we reclaim value, I will not
short this. All right. We reclaim
previous day value low. I'm not going to
play short because they're protecting
that gap. Yeah, I don't mind the long.
The long back up to here makes sense.
And then trim some. Right. If you're
playing this reclaim, I'd trim some
here. And if you get this, you get you
might come all the way back upside. It's
very possible because we've just
repriced this candle, right? We're
filling this imbalance. So if you got
long here, trim this. I'm waiting to see
if they want to reshort this back down.
If they don't, then your long is
possible to value area high and I will
just be no position at all. Okay, stop
talking. Start focusing, Alex.
There's a cell imbalance into 71. We
just tagged into
680 up here. Big block.
Nice J source. Yes. Nice. That's just
how you've got to trade in this market
right now. We're trapped between two
ranges, right? Previous week and um
previous day.
Oh, you [\h__\h] Don't tank this now.
Caught monologuing. Oh, you absolute
[\h__\h] whip. Got caught teaching.
Oh, too late now. I need to pull back
in.
Just getting heavy.
These are where the sellers keep coming
in though and getting stuck.
Think we're going to get expansion here.
Looking for the short now. Oh, I've
missed that attack up high I talked
about. Maybe we can come back up towards
60s. 50s, sorry, 650s. Let's see. Fill
some of this in.
New York open there.
Flush coming by the looks of it.
piling in here. Competitive price down
there. You can see all these orders
stacked down to 20s right now.
Yes. Going to lose a bid. I think the
flush is coming like I talked about.
It's getting very whippy around here.
Here we come. All right. Let's see then.
You got follow through. Can we get under
previous day low?
And can we close the gap will be the
next question. Sellers keep coming in
here and not getting their way. You can
see the book they're not very big. If
you look at bookmap these buyers are not
that big. 30 25 20s and then down to 10.
But they are absorbing down here. So far
I think they will get filled at some
point. I'm watching this New York open.
I really want to see if we can come up
to 50s and then reject 50s. Then I'll be
really interested in the cell.
Lots of selling down here without moving
lower.
I'd say everything is sellside 37 and
under without moving lower right now. So
any seller under 37's currently stuck. I
want to see this hit 50s. All right,
because I know that's where buyers came
in. I want to see if they stay stuck.
And we just trap more buyers in this
candle. This is such tiny range. It's
hard for me to uh get involved in at the
moment. Maybe if we get up to 50s.
Where's that imbalance? Imbalance 52s to
54s. Maybe I'll think about it. Maybe if
we do this,
I'll be interested now because I've
missed this. We were talking about this
move up into here to protect it. I've
missed it. Got caught teaching. This is
the one problem I have sometimes trying
to show you guys. I missed the actual
moves I want. [sighs]
Let's see. All right, here we go. Let's
see if we can fill this in just above
50s. That keeps breathing there.
Yeah, exactly. Both sides possible. I'm
trying to be flexible today. All right.
So I can show you my my my leaderboard,
let's call it. It's all I'm just trading
one account today. Up 710 on it. So we
will just see what we get.
Okay, here we go. Are we going to fill
this imbalance in into this little
level? That's all buyers getting trapped
there again. They were trapped at 51s
before. There's a little imbalance into
54 I'm looking at.
No one on the book above until 70s. It's
very thin book.
Here's that imbalance field.
They're supporting a bid now. Buyers are
coming in.
Well, it's now or never sellers. I would
say you have the chance now or never.
There's some bid support coming in.
They're interested in bidding this at
the moment.
[snorts]
Yes, back to its gap. Uh PDC
[clears throat] looks messy down here.
All I'd say right now is definitely
sellers are caught under 37s and we
might well test this val area low up
here. Now
we are seeing some bids come back in to
this market.
650 now being bid. He's walking up. He's
trying to push this market up right now.
He's rebid again. He's walking up and
again he's walked up into 55s now.
See if he's legit. And again, they're
getting aggressive there. Not touching
this. Too many games here. Way too many
games here for me.
Back to the 70s. If they go back inside
the range, there's nothing I'm going to
do. I'm not touching it up here. No way.
This is my no trade zone.
No way. We're going to have no
acceptance above, no acceptance below.
I'm not trading in 30 points, so I'm
good. Thanks. I'm absolutely good.
But yeah, you can see a buyer on the
tape. He started getting aggressive from
those 30s. He walked up to 40, 42, 45,
50, 52, 55. He's now pushing this market
up. He's literally [clears throat]
stairstepped up underneath. First time
we've seen it. Yeah. into this low
volume node yet, but we're into previous
day value low. We reclaim current value
on the day. If they don't reject here,
then we're going to go back inside value
and we're going to come up to previous
day point control and then up to
previous day value high. And it's it's
just going to be a no trade day for me
in that in that market in that area.
Yes, back to New York View.
Some those names are still rotating.
It's not the mag, guys. All right. It's
not the mag rotating. It's the sort of B
and C list names, let's call it. That's
what you're seeing. rotation in right
now the B and C list names I would call
it
RTI and NQ MBTS remember today's the
last balance day as well we rebalance
after today right on the on the ETFs I'm
pretty sure so AVGO goes uh into the
cues after today the rebalance day it's
their last it's their last chance to
position so that's probably what you've
got going on with the rotation in those
B and C list names it's their last
chance to reposition for the rebalance
on SPY and QQQ.
What was a rebalance day today? By the
end of day today, we kick a load of
names out of the cues and we bring a
load of names in. All right, so the
weakest names get pushed out and um
strong names that they want in go in.
That's why overall you want to be long,
right? And over why the market will
always go up long term. It is built to
go up. All right. So, it's like it's a
bit like a relegation. I don't know if
you have that in America, but for those
to give you Premier League t terms. All
right. The bottom three of the table,
they get relegated. They go into a lower
a lower division. That's actually what
you get in SPY and QQQ. So, we boot
names out which aren't performing well,
and we replace them with names which are
performing well. Every quarter they
rebalance.
So, that makes sure that the market
stays strong. So if you imagine you got
a stock which is doing [\h__\h] and is down
on the year and no one wants it anymore
and it's underperforming and they
replace it with a stock which is up 100%
of the year. Well, guess what? Brings
strength into the market. All right, so
that's what today's the last day to do
it this quarter. So that's probably why
you've got a lot of names,
you know, those big option names, those
big uh
uh quantum names. You're seeing some
weakness in some of them or they're
actually quite whippy like I I am very
whippy today. You're probably seeing
people reposition themselves for the
next quarter.
Just stuck here at previous day values.
Can't really do much at the moment.
Do I have a certain entry like a break
of a previous candle? Sometimes it can
be a previous candle. Uh normally it's a
break of an area where I think
participants are really really caught.
So I'll have an area I want to buy or
sell in and then I'll look for an entry
within that area based on what I'm
seeing on the tape more than anything.
Or or maybe it's even a reclaim of an
EMA. Like right now there's nothing for
me to do. We're going to go back into
range rotation. I'm [\h__\h] no way am I
playing range rotation today. No thank
you very much. I don't want to play in
the area we've been at all morning and
all of yesterday. I do not want to play
in here. It is a choice. All right.
Doesn't mean you guys can't play in
there, but I'm making the choice. I do
not want to play long in this. All
right. I don't want to play in this. We
either need strength or weakness or
nothing. That's how I'm treating this
market right now. I don't want to get
chopped up is the best way of putting
it.
Okay. So 85 86 is a big level. 86 has
positive delta c. 85 has negative delta.
So 85 sellers are still in control. 86
is still stuck. We get above that then
uh more squeeze potential possible based
on what I've seen on the book.
Do we need MBO to get the DOM? Um,
this is just uh I just pay for CME data
on here.
But you don't have to use this DOM. This
is just bookmap. This is Bootmaps DOM.
But you can use whatever you like.
You just want uh data beyond. I mean, I
never get people that look at they say,
"Oh, yeah, I trade the ladder." And then
they have no prices on the ladder other
than, you know, a ticky the side. You're
not trading a ladder.
You can't You're not trading a ladder if
you're seeing a tick either side of you
like what you would get for free from
Topep for example. You if you're
actually going to look at this data, you
need to pay for the data to see it all.
Okay. So, previous day point of control
now at 94s, you got both VWOPS 24hour
and cash VWOP up here. We're getting
stuck right now at previous day value
area low. So, maybe they drift in and
lose it. I don't know, folks. But it
doesn't look very pretty right now. It's
one thing. The one thing I do know is it
doesn't look very pretty.
So losing previous day value low. Value
area low on this current session is 66.
Don't want to say that out loud. It's
the sixes. All right. It's the sixes.
Not going to say that out loud. And we
have a shelf up here into 700. Okay. So,
this was the this was the level that
they broke down from.
All right. So, they're trying to catch a
bid here to complete this. And if they
get through this, they're going to try
and complete higher.
It's messy. It's messy. Messy.
Exactly, Mike. I'm with you.
You're amazing. saying your trading
style fights my style and I really
appreciate your style mentorship. Thus I
will join your channel and support you
your honesty and professionalism. Thank
you. Oh, thank you very much. Very kind.
Okay, into this imbalance above. So into
these two VWOPS previous day close,
previous day point of control.
Where's my mouse?
Might it might be a no trade day for
Alex. Big buyer coming in here. 192 lot
trying to force this squeeze higher
right now. He was a market buyer. He
came flying in at the 83s, right? Flying
in at 83s. That's big old size.
Mark open tomorrow. Uh I don't believe
so. You have Well, I mean some of the
futures will be open.
Not the whole day necessarily,
but just treat it as a holiday. I
wouldn't I would not bother.
You have jobless claims tomorrow
morning.
I will probably take tomorrow off. I'll
see. Maybe I'll come on for an hour. Uh
Thursday and Friday, you're off. Okay.
Thursday, Friday, you're off. And then
next week, you're back into it. Monday,
Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday, Friday. I
might trade
Monday, Tuesday next week.
I think stuff like this is I'm going to
I'm going to be honest with you. I think
this sums up the dirtiness of a
government. You're going to put initial
jobless claims out on Christmas Eve and
then you're going to put more jobless
claims out on New Year's Eve
when no when no one's here. You're just
going to hide it when no one's here. I
mean, it's
I just think that's that sums up the
government for me.
What? We've had no data for months and
months and months. And some of the
biggest data you're going to put out
when no one's there.
Good one.
You normally not trade previous day
value area. Uh because if if we've it
depends on what that value if this value
area was nice and big, I'd consider it.
But look how small this is. And look how
we've chopped this morning and chopped
here and chopped yesterday. I don't want
to chop in here. I don't want to play in
here. Right. This is bollocks in there.
I'm not interested in playing in there.
Think about you just bought the previous
day value long and you just got stopped
out. You going to have another go and
get stopped out again or you going to
fade this and maybe you come down to
here like
I don't think there's edge is the best
way of putting it. There's not edge in
that. When there's edge in previous
value areas is when there's something
like this, right? Nice big area.
All right. lose this. Yeah, I have room.
I have room. What the hell am I going to
do in previous days value right now? I
mean, there's just
from 15
to 80
35 points. That's as big as my stop is
normally.
New Year's market be quiet as well.
Very, very quiet. January be good.
Volatility in January is normally very
good. If we're going to see a sale, it's
going to come Jan. If big if, but if
we're going to see a sale, it's going to
come Jan. Just go back and have a look
at the last few years where we've done
the big pullbacks.
Take care, Ka.
Yeah, I don't trade for the views,
unfortunately. [snorts] All
>> [clears throat]
>> right, protecting this little shelf. You
can see we've developed like a bit of a
node here. This low volume node acting
as resistance right now, but if we get
through it, it will be just like knife
straight through volume today. Very,
very low.
Very, very low.
critique of government with words like
dirty equals a trap door on the thought
police in the UK right now. I know.
Well, thank God I don't live there.
You can't have an opinion unless it's
very very left in an agreement with
everything that they think.
Yes, Kia. I'll get on my knees for you,
Kia. Whatever you want, sir. Kia. I
should get rid of his sir for a start.
He's an absolute [\h__\h]
They are. Yeah. Sup. Yeah. They've been
arrested not even for posting, for
liking other people's posts. But, you
know, crime is at incredibly high
levels. And when they say, "Oh, crime
levels have gone down." Oh, have you
just suddenly not included knife crime
in that data? This is the thing people
don't understand. Um, not you guys,
because if you're trading, you're
probably smart, but I'll make you aware
of this. things like that CPI report
that came out which came in better than
expected didn't include like 80% of the
goods we'd normally include. Right? This
is what they do when they say, "Oh,
unemployment's uh better than expected."
They won't include some data. When they
say crimes down or violent crimes down,
they suddenly don't include like GBH and
ABH. You have to like really look at the
sort of asterisks at the bottom to see
what they've included. Okay. So,
couldn't get back in above this low
volume volume node. They're doing the
same here. And you can see the
rotational part is sort of here right
now. Right. No acceptance above, no
acceptance below. We have structure. We
can chop. I'm not really interested at
the moment. We have to leave areas for
me to really be interested.
Yeah. For liking posts. Fresh. Yeah.
People have been arrested for liking
other people's posts. They come to your
front door, knock on your door, and try
and arrest you. Even though, you know,
you've had a daughter that's been raped,
for example. that won't be looked at by
the UK police because they're too busy.
Yeah, it's uh it's in dire straits over
there right now, unfortunately. It's not
not somewhere I'm in a hurry to move
back to. Let's just put it that way.
It's the fall of a country. Can it be
fixed? Absolutely. But not with the
current leadership, I would say. Not
with any of the leaders who are trying
to get in at the moment either, I don't
think. So, you know,
I do worry about this isn't about the UK
or America. It's global thing. Where are
the young leaders, you know, who are
center, not far left, not far right,
bang in the middle, center, who can
drive a good economy and a good social
environment. Where are they? I'll tell
you where they are. Nowhere to be seen
because anyone with anyone at sense
doesn't want to be involved in politics
at all. And that's the problem we have
right now. It's why all the leaders,
they're either crooked or old.
Same stuff in Germany. Is that right,
Roman? That's a it's a shame. Where am I
from? I'm I'm originally from London,
but I live in in Los Angeles. Okay, so
they caught underneath this gray box.
You see this? No acceptance below. Low
volume node. Caught them. Come back to
the top side. If they hold the bid now,
they will try and drive higher through
this low volume node uh to the upside.
Now, if they can hold the bid, it's a
big if, but that's what they were trying
to do. Can they hold this now into sort
of 83s after doing the damage? So, they
caught shorts here. Can they hold this?
Can they find acceptance above and go
back into here? Now, that is the
question they're currently posing in the
market. I will not be trading this, but
you guys are welcome to trade it.
Showing you what what they're trying to
set up to happen. Volume point of
control now is down here. So, I know on
this chart is showing up here, but on my
chart, it's down here now. So, they're
trying to see if they can bid back above
VPO on the day and get back above PDC,
which is where they keep failing. 92s.
All the big selling came in into the
700s this morning.
It's just it is messy. You see this gray
box for the rotation for me. I would say
this is very very messy right now
moving towards anarchy. Yeah,
unfortunately I think you you could
potentially be right and it's going to
take something too uh drastic to change
the sort of trajectory mankind's on
right now. I'd say
anyway, I'll leave too much of my uh tin
hat thoughts to myself because you guys
will think I'm absolutely insane.
I'm trying to avoid consolidation, but
above and below consolidation, you've
got a big space Also, you didn't trade
here. I guess only on points with big
price movement, right? Yeah. I I just
the way I see it, um I need to see I
need to know that I've got room, right?
So, if I'm going to hit a I'm not
interested in five or 10 points, right?
So, I need to see that I've got room to
get to my target. And then I've got to
see that the risk profile makes sense to
get there. Um that's kind of how I see
trading. And if we don't have room and
if we're just light volume chopping
backwards and forwards, I have to ask
myself, is it worth my energy?
I would agree. Ch children need to be
nurtured. Yeah, absolutely.
I'm from the UK and I would say that's a
fair assessment, Alex. Yeah, it's it's
tough, man. It's tough. Like, all my
family live there and I keep saying to
them, I've got no interest in moving
back, you know? I'm
I'm a landlord back there. I'm very
close to selling up my home. People
don't understand this like attack on
what they consider rich. They don't
understand. If you get rid of the
private landlords, what you're going to
get is the big companies come in. If you
look at if I sell my house, it's going
to be bought by a company owned by Black
Rockck, right? And they're going to [\h__\h]
over uh UK citizens way more than anyone
else. And people don't really understand
that. So, they vote for this, you know,
agenda that the government put in like,
oh, landlords are terrible and blah,
blah, blah, and we're going to tax and
load. you're just going to replace it by
a very greedy um big company and that's
going to hurt people even more. It's
it's it's the lies that's the problem,
right? And and it's not people's fault
that a hardworking people, they are
getting screwed right now. There's no
doubt about it. But the lies that the
government tell is what's really
damaging. But you know, it's not just
this government. You know, it's not
about Labor or about conservatives.
They've all been terrible for ages, ages
and ages. I mean, historic, I'll be
honest with you, historically, I was a
conservative voter after the absolute
mess of what we saw in the pandemic.
There was no way I could vote for them
anymore. So, what I did was not vote at
all. Just like, [\h__\h] this. I can't vote
for Star, but I'm not voting for
Conservatives either because they're all
they're all scumbags. And that's the
same any country. Here's the squeeze
back higher now, folks. That's the same
for any country. You got to remember how
many uh how many governments actually um
actually deliver on their mandate?
Zero, right? Zero. Zero ever deliver on
their mandate. That's the that's the big
problem.
I wouldn't vote reform.
Not for me.
Fiscally, I'm conservative. socially I'm
uh
I'm more left of center. Not not left
but left to center. So I mean that's
kind of where I stand. I believe that
you know don't think you should punish
people for working hard. I think you
should incentivize people to work hard.
I think over the taxation that you're
seeing in the UK is absolutely savage.
Right? The I'll talk about me
personally. All right. I I own three
companies in the UK. I pay myself out of
the UK and I'm a landlord in the UK. I'm
getting [\h__\h] on every single way
going. I might as well just stop stop
all work. So what's going to happen?
Giving you me as an example. I'm going
to sell up and move everything I have to
a more taxefficient country. So let's
say I move to Texas next year. Well, UK
loses everything that I've just done.
Now multiply that by the millions of
people who will be use leaving the UK
for similar reasons. going to Dubai,
going to Portugal, going to more tax
efficient places. What do you then get
in the UK? Less job creation. People
like me employ people, whether that's
full-time or it's on contract work or
whatever, right? So, less job creation
equals what? More people with their
handout asking for money from the
government equals what? More stress on
the NHS. Less people in private health
insurance equals what? Government going,
"Oh, we need to get more money. Let's
tax more." Hey, guess what, guys? You've
been taxing more from the beginning of
time. Is it working? No. Maybe you need
to have a look at it. Right? So this is
this is the problem that you get in.
Right? So and the agenda of
the agenda that they have of like tax
the rich earning six figures a year is
not rich. I'm sorry it's not earning
eight. Sure. But how many people do you
know that ear earn eight figures? And
how many of those employ lots of people?
Probably lots. So, it's it's just like
it's just a for me I would just say it's
a bit of a mess. It's a bit of a mess.
Um I can't comment on I haven't been
there for a long time so I can't comment
on the border control. I think a lot of
that is um some of it's probably valid.
Do you have a lot of illegal immig
immigrants there? Yes. Does some of them
need help? Yes. Are some of them
violent? Yes. Are some of them great
people? Yes. Is the UK built on
immigration? Yes.
I mean, there's just so many ways to
look at it, right? So,
it's tough, guys. It's tough. I don't
have the answers. I I'm not a
politician. I don't have the answers. I
just want peace and fairness for
everyone, right? I think motivate people
to work.
I don't think we live in a day and age
right now where why do people not have
the ability to have a safe home and put
food on the table and clean water
anywhere in the world. There's no reason
for that nowadays. It's ridiculous that
we still live in a place of and I'm not
talking about the UK globally of famine
and stuff. There's absolutely no reason
for that. We need to do better as as
mankind. Um, we will be doing I tell you
what, we will be doing more charity work
here next year um on the channel. I'll
be doing some charity work. My Christmas
present from family this year is uh I
asked for a donate. I do it every year.
I've asked for a donation this year.
I've done it for Movember. As some of
you will know, I lost uh two friends to
suicide this year. Um so maybe we do
some Movember stuff. I'd like to do some
homeless stuff next year. We figure it
all out.
Okay, so reclaiming. So you can see
we're leaving the gray box. So they trap
shorts. We'll get back to talking about
the markets. Sorry folks. So we trap
shorts. They bid back up value, right?
Trapped shorts under here. They went
back into gray box. They did this move
here I talked about and their target now
is previous day value and current day
value. So if you're long, these are your
targets. Um just be careful because it's
so slow moving. Like this will feel big
but it's tiny, right? This will feel
big, but it's like 10 20 points, but
that's it's a very slow day, so this is
what we expect. Here we go. So, you
might get it now. Really nice.
There you go. So, almost there. Really
good. If any of you took it, congrats.
We talked about this uh when we were
here. There's the dip. So here's your 30
pointer and I'd be holding runners now.
If you can get through, you need to get
through this little level here and you'd
be looking at 37s and then highs and if
you get really lucky all the way back up
here again. There you go, folks. Off it
goes. Rotation, rebalance rotation. So
into value area high from yesterday.
That's why I said I try and avoid this
but called it for you.
Nice, nice work. Nice work there, buddy.
Nice work, Tyson. Yeah. So, just hold
now. See if you can get back through
this gray box. If you get acceptance
over 36s, I'd be looking for all the way
up here. If you can find acceptance over
36s, but as long as you protected those
profits,
really nice ES about to break out as
well. You look good. You look really
good.
And you'd want them to hold sort of 704
705s. really
really nice
really really nice guys. So let's just
see if they can hold 704s 705s. You've
just completed the rotation of
yesterday. Um I still think you've got a
chance to move higher. I'll be honest.
I'd be watching into 30s and then
through 30s obviously 50s and through
that. Uh maybe if you get lucky up
towards the high 700s.
As long as you protected in here.
Yeah, this one's very slow to move. Uh
on here I have volume point of control
down at 682 right now, mate. Down here,
right on Ninja Trader. It's just slower
on here to move, but my PC is down here
right now.
Right. So that was the hold of it and
then the rips while the gray box is
here.
So I'd say you'd want to protect this
for this move. If they lose this, you
come straight back down in and we're
just going to do this rotation here. If
they lose this, you want them to hold a
bid and do this right now. If you're if
you're already long, right? If you're
already long, wouldn't be joining now.
But that's what you want to see if
you're already long. [snorts]
95s. Okay, cool. Yeah, that works
underneath previous day point control be
up there. Low volume node. It's good
area. You've already paid yourself,
right, Tyson? So, you you got long from
85. You've paid yourself into 715.
You've got your 30 handles. Your stop's
10 points in the money on your runner.
And if you get going, fantastic.
Nice. Nice work, mate. Really nice.
He shifts because of market sentiment.
No, your point of control shifts because
of volume. All right. So, all point of
control is is the area where most volume
is traded. Not most buyers, not most
sellers, most volume. Most buyers and
sellers. So, if we when we pause in
areas like think about how much time we
spent here and here again, this is why
PC you get these nodes here.
This is PC for me down here right now.
Right. Trading View has it up here for
me. I have it down here right now.
I'm going to get a refill on this coffee
and I'll be back, folks.
I do have some good news as well. Um,
Funded Next have agreed to do
uh three giveaways a month over here on
this channel, which is fantastic. So,
we've got one that we're going to
announce today off for YouTube. You'd
have seen that post. So, starting in
2026,
we will do three funded next giveaways a
month. And we will try and do daily
giveaways on Apex if we can get a few
more codes,
which would be nice. And then we just
have to wait for Lucid. So, I'm trying
to trying to give back to you guys. The
bigger the channel gets, the easier it
is for me to get them to give us codes
for me to give you, right? So, it's
getting better, guys. A year ago, we
didn't do any. So, think about how how
quick it's going. And then we got like
one a week or one a month on Apex, one a
week, now one a day. Now some of the
other guys are going to join in, which
is awesome. Nice to see the community
growing. All the time it grows, it means
I can I can give you guys more and then
we can see if we can get some other fun
stuff. I'd love to do a deal with like a
tech company and be able to do, you
know, a giveaway every couple months
for, I don't know, a monitor or a
keyboard or some something like that
would be cool.
Okay, so the pullback here
back down to this same level we talked
about. You don't want to see it lose
these levels down here. And this is the
low volume node down here. You don't
want it to lose this this level. There's
a buyer at uh 762 lot that the bids are
so small both sides today.
Still deciding between
Apex and TPT.
Yeah, just all depends what type of
trader you are. I'd say if you if you're
consistent and you just want to go for
base hit, base hit base hit over
multiple count account accounts and
compound Apex. If you want to go for the
big wins, the big days and sit in a
trade set and forget TPT out of those
two. Yeah, those two. If you're a newer
trader, I would look at Lucid or Funded
Next. I think they're probably the
easiest to pass and easiest to get paid
from,
but maybe not quite as good for scaling.
No, no, it doesn't, which I didn't
realize. Uh, Lucid does not have a
monthly subscription charge. It's
onetime fee, I believe, on the on the
Flex accounts at least. Is that what
they're called?
Lucid Flex. That sounds right. On the
new whatever new accounts they launch,
there's no monthly charge.
Okay. So, for me, VPO just moved up here
now.
So, uh we're in control now around these
713s. So, for you buyers, you want price
to get back above 713s, back above 715s
and start squeezing for you guys. And
then you're going to be good. If you can
get back above here and squeeze up, it
would be ideal for you guys.
You don't want to keep losing. If you
build a shelf here and lose it, it's
going to get dangerous.
We're in rotation. You will watch ES.
See if you can get through initial
balance. Here's the squeeze. Really
nice. So, Tyson, hopefully you're still
in this. I think that might have got
close to your stop. But if we can
squeeze now, you've got these targets
above. So, oh, right. I'll be watching
this, this, and this.
Big ifs may, but you might have been
knocked out. I'm not sure.
Max payout on Lucid. Uh, oh, before they
move you live, you mean? I'd have to
check. Let me have a look.
Yeah, one time fee on lucid.
I will check.
It's trying to do it for you, Tyson.
Don't if their sight's down at the
moment. I can't get it open.
Anyone else having that issue?
There we go. It's open now. Uh let's
have a look.
Isn't ES absorbing above the wick? E ES
is doing pretty good, but it's got to
get back above its initial balance high.
So that high that it put in earlier at
948 is trying to get back above that.
Right. So at the moment we're still in a
rotational market.
So payout caps, profit splits after the
first 10,000. So for a 50k account, it's
1 and a half thousand first payouts, I
think. And then 2,000 pay out three and
four and then two and a half, five, and
six.
That's on a Lucid Pro. Let me check the
flex.
2,000 on the flex I think on a 50k until
you get to number six and then scale or
live. So kind of like Apex
in terms of like the money,
but you don't have the consistency
rules, right?
Yeah. I love TPT, man. I love TPT. I can
tell you this this month it's been my uh
and I've slowed right down now, but this
month's
been solid for me. on TPT. Where am I up
to?
I just requested again last night. So,
there's the 12th.
So 1,000 1 and a half th00and 2 and a
half th000 three and a half thousand and
I've barely traded this month. Daily
payouts
it's I think they're phenomenal.
Phenomenal.
And they're quick. Very quick. Only
takes a day a day one a day to you put
it in. They prove it. It takes a day to
land. I would say normally
I really like them. Only thing I think
they need to improve is their customer
service a little bit. Still looks good,
guys. You still look good for a drift
higher. You can see this node here. So,
all of you guys that were long off this
call here, right, that one there once
they failed this and did this. You look
good. It's trying to do this move now
for you. Some of you were long down
here, which was fantastic. I didn't have
the bollocks to take that and uh I told
myself I'm not going to trade in here
today. mainly because it's Christmas and
it's light as well. I don't want to do
something stupid. Remember my weakest
trade. You can see I've called this for
you. My weakest trade is in here. So, I
don't want to go into the Christmas
holidays doing something stupid.
[snorts]
Uh, what do I think about deep charts? I
haven't used deep charts. One of my
students likes them. Um, I trade on
Ninja with something that looks kind of
like them, but I think they're good. I
do think they're good. I think they're
quite expensive though from what um I
think it was Mo. Are you in chat? I
think it was Mo that was using them for
a bit.
Is there a video from the course
overview so I understand your style? Uh
yeah, there's like a couple advert
videos on my YouTube page if you go to
courses.
Do I need Ninja Trader account for
funded next? Uh no, no, no, no. You
trade on uh trade bait or what do they
offer? A few different things. Hang on.
Look. Yeah, you don't need NT.
They've got a deal on right now. You can
get 100K uh account for the price of a
50k account with code FCT right now.
Who do they work with?
Trade of eight and ninja. So anyone that
works with trade of eight. Anyone that
works with trade of eight will work. So
you could trade on trading view fine.
Yes. Trading draw downs f with your mind
feel the same. Yeah. The thing is with
those trading draw downs, guys, is not
to get too glued into it, right? If if
you're struggling,
if you're struggling with a trailing
draw down and apex, I would say either
two things. You're we probably oversized
because it shouldn't bother you, right?
So, you're probably oversized. And once
you get a This is the thing, and I'm
talking about I am someone that when
they changed those rules 18 months ago,
I got denied a five figure payout
because of uh what was it? you couldn't
they they wanted consistency on size and
all these things and they've sorted
their [\h__\h] out since then. I promise
you. And I'm someone that got denied
five figures and since then take five
figures out pretty much every month. Um
take your time if you get past the
buffer. Size down, get past the buffer.
If you're going to trade with Apex, once
you're past it, you trade it like
everyone else. Okay. The difference is
that you're going to have 20 accounts,
not three or five. And the payouts scale
fast once you do that. But you have to
watch the video I did at the weekend.
You have to take your time early on.
Yes, it's a pain, but don't don't hear
all the hysteria. Just trade the setup.
If the setup's good, you you trade it.
Setup's not good, you don't trade it
early on, you protect your profits,
right? That's that's all you have to do.
Don't try not to overthink it. But I if
it's not for you, totally understand.
Then look at some of the other accounts.
Remember TPT trading draw down as well
once you pass um and go in the pro
accounts for the first until you pass
the buffer. So, you're going to have to
if either of those two, you're going to
have to deal with it. If you don't like
that, Funded Next, Lucid, and um
Tradeify, right, that's it.
How long I've been trading? Well,
probably full-time, six, six or seven
years. And before that, I had a bit of a
hiatus, but I was swing trading. Um, and
I was almost did this as a job. So you
can watch some of the interviews with
me.
Alex, even though I don't trade the same
as you, more of a trend trader. Hey,
that's how I like to trade as trend. By
the way, really appreciate your
commentary and analysis every day. It's
definitely helped my trading. Merry
Christmas. Thank you very much. I I like
being a trend trader, mate. That's my
favorite trade. Um, it's just that we're
not in a trending market right now. Um,
but that's my favorite trade is a pro,
what I call a protrend. So, if the daily
wants to move higher, the hourly wants
to move higher, for example, I'm looking
for a pullback on a lower time frame
into a key level to trap lower time
frame traders to then move higher.
That's my favorite. That's my A+ trade.
Nice. Glad it was useful. Hello. I just
bought 50K trade of eight Apex and I'm
kind of nervous about that. I made 9K on
demo yesterday and now it feels so
different. Yeah. Well, that's why you
need to that's why prop firms are great,
right? Because demo you've got no
exposure to it at all, but on prop firm
you've got some exposure, but remember
your exposure is probably between 20 and
50 bucks. It's not a huge amount of
money. So, just trade it normally,
right? Don't worry about it. Here's the
squeeze. Tyson, you look really good. It
looks fantastic holding above this new
little level. Okay, watch to see if we
can find acceptance through this. I
think there's a chance to really start
getting up into here. Let me just do a
projection and see if that times out
with previous day high.
Yeah, I think we've got a shot at this,
folks. I think you've got a shot at
getting into 792s.
Let me just check these levels from
yesterday.
I'll mark this out. We We need to see
this. Here's a pivot from yesterday,
right? I'm going to pay attention to and
then the highs. So, yeah, this is this
is the target, folks. These are the
targets. I'm going to get rid of this.
I'm not worried about this. I think this
one and then up here. You look good.
Just manage the position. Move your stop
up. I wouldn't be a new money long.
Nice, Tyson. Great work.
Was I part of J Trader in the in the
past? No, I know Jay Trader and I used
to work with guys that originally
uh traded with him, but I was I never
learned with Jay and was never in his
room.
So, I'm close to payout right now. Two
PAs close to the buffer on day four.
It's the closest I've come to pay out
all year. Thank you, brother, for all
the support. I'm thrilled to be part of
this team. Hey Tyson,
nice man. That's your dedication and
hard work, dude. And and I think the
biggest thing for you was like opening
up because we've been able to start,
you know, turning your trading around by
you facing it head on, which like kudos
to you my friend. Really well done.
Divergence with ES. Yeah, ES has taken
out this IB high, but I think we're
still going. We still look good. Trend
looks good. Everything looks good right
now. Multi-time frame candles look good
right now. Delta looks good right now.
Buyers are in control. They came back in
control once we reclaimed previous day
value. All right, so they held this dip.
Thing about down here, sellers had the
opportunity is why I was annoyed. I got
caught monologuing here because the sell
opportunity was here. Couldn't break the
low. That's where they get stuck. All
right, that's the pivot. They held this
and the next chance is here and now
you're away. So now it's just holding
runners looking for the expansion up
into here. Now you look fantastic.
You look fantastic. Oh, don't move that.
We're going to need that. All right. So
here's current value high. I want to see
you expand Valeria high. Come and rip
these faces through 50s. We should run
the stops. So stops will be at 50s and
the top of this box 60s. All right. So
50s and 60s. And if we run all of those,
you I'd be moving my stop up and then
hoping you can get up here at that
point. It looks good.
What's your target on ES? Um, well, I'd
say definitely whole number of 50s
coming up. Let's have a look. Yeah, you
have a you have like a a big big level
at 47 and 50 if you get acceptance into
that 67. So 47 to 50 is a huge level on
ES and if you get acceptance through
that 66 and 70s
[snorts]
[groaning]
break I'm ready for January. That's how
I feel. I feel very much the same. Only
good riskreward
entry for new long would be previous day
point of control maybe in the afternoon.
Uh I would say it depends.
It depends if we've had the low hanging
fruit. Like it'd be an area of interest,
but you got to understand it depends
what this market looks like when we get
here. So let's say they fail this high
and they come down into here. But if
value is here on the day, you've got to
ask yourself why are you bidding at the
midpoint of the day, right? It's all
about context. All right. It's all about
context.
Is it a important level? Possibly. But
it depends what we've done before we get
to that level. Have we taken the low
hanging fruit? Is there anything else to
aim for? Has volume died right down? You
know, are we is does that previous day
point of control becoming the midpoint
of the current day's range? Do you want
to trade that then? Because you're at
one to one at each side. Do you know
what I mean? Like, so it's context. It
really depends.
I'm 500 away from getting a 50k funded
account. I hope I don't screw it up.
Hey, we'll just positive mental attitude
and just trade legit setups. Okay, no
forcing.
I've somehow been on the wrong side of
every trade the last two days. So, I'm
probably just going to wait till the new
year. I think that's a good idea to just
just wait now.
I'm long from 25714. Do you stop loss?
Are you targeting higher trades? 71
714. You're a little late. Um well, my
target would be up here. If you can get
up into searching here and it So, my
target would be depends how many you've
got on. If you've got multiple, I'd be
trimming some into 50.
What's this? Into 50. Into 60. and then
into 800. Basically, that would be my
target if I was you.
[snorts]
How close would I trail my stop? Uh,
well, I don't know where your entry is.
So, it really depends where your entry
is. Fresh. If you're like Tyson and your
entry is Tyson's long from 80s, all
right, then you can probably afford to
let it pull back if it really wanted to
into here. If you're just small size
left, all right, you could afford to let
it pull back into this kind of shelf
here and look for that. But if it does
this and it fails, you want to be out.
You don't want it to come back down and
retest. But it really depends where
you're long from, you know, because if
you're long from here, [laughter]
you can't you can't be risking down
here. So, I don't know where you're long
from. I need context.
Any experience with Borox? I do not.
I've never traded with them.
I've never traded with them. There are
guys in chat. I think Richard, if you're
here, Richard's traded with them quite a
lot,
but I don't trade with them, but I think
they're good from what I've heard.
What's the best way to trade multiple
accounts? Copy trade. I've heard
execution can be wonky. Also, different
size accounts. If you could shed some
light. Yeah. Uh, [gasps] copy trading is
risky. Obviously, it's risky because
you're using leverage, but um I use
affordable indicators um copier. That's
what I use. your biggest problem copy
trading um from what I can see if you go
over 20 accounts is the API issue when
it when you get through your orders. So
you got to be disciplined. Otherwise,
just do them in bundles. Three to fives.
You're going to copy trade.
Long from 668. Looks good. 668. You're
long from 668.
Yeah, very good in this in this fail
breakdown. Really nice. Fantastic. It's
a great trade. Almost 100 points.
Fantastic trade. All right, I want to
see you run these stops now. I think you
will do it. All right, so this these are
the stops from today. If you think about
where the shorts are, they've got
they're in from here and from yesterday
they're in from here and then if you get
that here. So hopefully, we don't know,
but hopefully you get something like
that that just runs them. Just be
mindful ES has already done that move.
What is that level on the Q's? 21s.
Okay,
[snorts]
long from 705. So, lots of you are are
long and strong. You look good. You look
good. Just manage it.
Just manage your position accordingly.
There you go. So the other Dave says,
"First time I traded 20 accounts
together, I blew them all up. Now I
won't trade more than five bundles at a
time." Yeah. See, I think that's wise.
[snorts]
Still holding value area high and GloEx
here. Still looks good.
All right. Still looks good. It could do
with like a little bit of sideways and
something like that would be really
nice, right? A little a little trap down
here. or your continuation trade higher.
Still looks good.
What I will tell you is buyers came in
at 40 here and held the bid and sellers
came in at 38 to 36 and just got
themselves caught.
If I tell if I see what I think is the
end of the auction, I will tell you. But
I think you look good. We're into a
sellside imbalance here at 46s. We
should we should
see if they can hold the bid here at 40s
and then have a resqueeze higher. They
are still offering 50 52 55 and 60s.
Those the levels that we're looking at
still looks good.
So there's a bid here at 40s. You want
to see if he holds.
Just manage manage this position you're
all longing. You look good. They're
going to attack these stops now.
And hopefully if there's enough stops up
here, you'll get a little swipe up,
which you know, if you're sized on, I
would be taking some profit into this
move, which is coming right now. So,
here comes current high of day. And then
the top of the gray box is a pivot from
yesterday. Okay. So, we know this is an
area shorts will want to protect. If we
get a run through it, then you want to
be selling into it. Right. While we talk
about this, I'm going to use the
bathroom. Just be smart.
All right, let's have a look. How's this
looking at the highs? Some buyers
definitely caught there a little bit.
Strong selling coming in here. You
definitely had some buyers caught as
soon as I left there. This transition
right here.
Yeah.
All right. So, you want to watch this.
If they resell this, I'd probably be
out. If they reclaim this, you're going
to be good. That's what I'd be watching
at.
There is an imbalance all the way down
here as well. So, sellers are starting
to come in here. It just all about
whether they can rebid. Like I said, I
wouldn't be a new money long up here,
but you can manage your positions. You
just want some of these shelves to hold
on. And you want to see like a little
trap and a reclaim.
But yeah, I'll be definitely watching
that 45. If you can't get back above 45,
then we're going to leave those buyers
stuck. I'm still bullish on this overall
for you guys managing your positions.
I'd still say there's a chance for this
to move higher, but 45 is absolutely
key. [snorts]
Yeah, exactly, Doie. It's why I'm
somewhat uninterested. You know, the ATR
is going to be low on these kind of
days. And it's the funny thing is it
only takes someone who's like, "Fuck, we
forgot to reposition this for this
client, right, cuz it's the last day to
do it." To come in and throw like a 500
lot in suddenly cuz they in urgency
forgot and is going to chomp up
everything on the book in one go. And
that's that's the other danger, right?
[snorts]
Yeah. Let's get the likes up, please.
Lots of you have been watching here this
morning. Smash that like button for me.
Let's try and get over 400 likes. So, I
want to give away like some courses and
I want to give it away some Apex stuff.
So, let's get these likes up.
Nice, Tyson. Great work, mate. Super
proud of you. Super proud of you. Let's
get you that payout. Let's get you that
payout early next year, if not before.
I need some merch. We can do some merch.
So, rejecting here to get above. All
right, it's starting to be a little bit
of an issue here. Right, you can see
where we just talked about those buyers
were stuck above 42s.
I hate it when it does this and I can't
teach this. Low volume node is starting
to be a problem. Buyers need to see
something like this. If they fail to do
that, you will see a trade back down to
value probably. So, you're starting to
see the shift now in sentiment. You can
see the delta starting to flip here.
And you could sort of watch ES. If
you're trading ES, you'd want that to
hold initial balance high right now.
Only my second stream, but you are doing
a great job analysis wise, bros. Keep it
up. Hey, thanks for joining. Second
stream. Thanks for joining. Hopefully
you join again. Maybe I'll be here a
couple days next week. Definitely from
uh New Year's. would be back 5 days a
week as normal.
How do you win? Yeah, we get those like
buttons up and then I'll run a
competition in in here shortly.
So, just stick around. We do
competitions once we get to uh midday.
So, 50 minutes. Maybe we'll do some
early today if it if it stays slow.
Thank you, Stash. I like the name Stash
Royale.
sound like a DJ.
That's DJ SKT's label stashed.
Alex, I'm a brand new green trader, but
I've built a double 9 figure company
from scratch. So, I'm a weirdo worker
focused like an eagle. What should I
begin trading to get my first 100 wins?
Oh my gosh. Uh, are you looking to trade
every day? futures lift or are you
looking to swing? Are you looking to
like if you're a busy person with
another company, are you looking to
position trade, get into positions and
let them work or are you looking to be
more active and trade like intraday in
and out? I think that would be my first
question is your time. If you haven't
got much time, like people think I I've
only got 30 minutes, I'm going to day
trade. I would do the opposite. If I've
only got 30 minutes, I'd be looking at
swing trading. I'll be looking at
positioning myself long-term.
Yes to which one of those? [laughter]
Thanks, Mr. Grant. Where am I based? Los
Angeles. Based in Los Angeles
every day. I'm not busy now. I'm here 8
to 10 hours a day. Okay, great. So, all
I'd say is don't focus on the money,
right? Because if you're new, you need
to clock up your 10,000 hours, right?
Same as you would for whatever your
other career was. You would have become
an expert in that to have a good
company. So, 10,000 hours times on the
charts. Uh, I would say ES is probably
the friendlier option if you're going to
trade futures. NQ is more violent, but
more will give you more money. I would
say pick one and learn it. Spend three
months on one of those and learn them
first.
Um, also time of day. If you're going to
trade Asia, I'd focus more on gold.
You're going to trade overnight. Yeah,
exactly. Use micros. All the stuff I
talk about, use micro. Start on sim.
Start on sim. You've got to learn
everything first. Learn the setups.
Learn to understand liquidity. Learn to
understand how the market acts, why it
acts that way. Then start to develop a
system. So, focus on one setup at a
time. Maybe an opening range break,
maybe initial balance trade, maybe a
range um mean reversion trade, maybe an
expansion trade. Understand the models
and why they work. Start there.
What markets am I trading? ENQ. You're
watching the ENQ, the NASDAQ. My trading
next week, I think Monday, Monday,
Tuesday. What did we say? Monday,
Tuesday next week. Let me check.
Monday the 29th, Tuesday the 30th.
Wednesday I'll be off. Thursday I'll be
off. Likely we'll have a hangover. I'll
think about the second and the third,
but we'll see. Um I want to like from
the fifth we're back at it, guys. Right.
So I will probably be here at least a
couple days next week, but from the
fifth we're back at it. That's when I
expect volume to come back to the
market.
I have four funded Apex funded 150K
right now. They are slightly in draw
down. I'm getting chopped up. I was
doing well the past month, but the last
few days have been rough. Feel like I
can't get in the sync with the market.
Well, Breezy, if it's the last few days,
I'd say it's probably because we've gone
into
Let me show you. This is why uh it's a
good hold here. This is if we reclaim
this is where shorts will need to defend
42s. If we reclaim this, those guys who
are already long from down here, you'll
get your squeeze. If we fail in here,
they will collapse this. All right. The
reason you're struggling this month or
this week, sorry, versus the last few
weeks, is the higher time frame. All
right, let me pull this up so you can
hear me properly. All right, it is the
higher time frame. If we zoom out, all
right, and think about what we had for
two weeks, we're in imbalance in a
balanced range, right? So, I didn't make
very much money in here for two weeks.
All right, we left that balance. So,
someone asked me about like trend
trading or protren. Once we left that, I
was short and I was short with size
here. We pulled back in, I was short
with size here. We pulled back in, I was
short with size here. All right, so
three big winning sessions, right?
Because we went protrend, leaving them
trapped. Once we got down here, this was
our target of the weekly newsletter,
which I sent out. It was a naked naked
point of control on a weekly chart,
right? Once we drifted under that, we
reclaimed it
and we expect what? All right, if this
is how the chart looks, if we've broken
under this, what do we expect? At least
a pullback. All right, so we were long
bias from here. Now, look at the
difference in the range. Look how much
range we've got to play with here. So,
we're long biased up here. Lots of
people wanted to get short here. And I
said, be very, very careful now because
we've done one, two, three. Bulls can
trap here. But we've hit the target.
This is the different lowhanging fruit
hit and we were actually bullish here
when everyone else was trying to get
bearish, right? And we started breaking
out. Now, why is it tricky this week?
Here, let me clean this up.
Where has volume been built out? This is
your previous week's volume.
This is two weeks prior's volume from a
few weeks ago.
Where are we? No man's land. Right. This
is why you're struggling, right? Because
in here, we had clear identity of what
kind of market was we were in. In here,
we know we're going to be choppy right
now. We are between the two. Have we
tested this this week? No. So, there's
been no weekly buyers able to take this
up. Have we tested it and failed? No.
So, there's been no weekly sellers able
to push it back down. Have we found
acceptance back into here? No. So,
there's no range rotation in here or
buyers looking for that trade up. And
have we done anything else other than
build liquidity? No. And what else do we
have? Low volume week, right? We're in a
holiday week. So, this is why you're
struggling this week because the
conditions are not protrend. They're not
rotation of big range. They're not
counter trend pullback. They're
liquidity build on a on a week where
we're going to have very low liquidity.
All right? So, the conditions are
probably not prime for what you are
looking for. They're not primed for
anyone, but for if you traded well two
weeks prior or last week or whatever you
were saying, I forget. Sorry. Then um
that's why it's conditions, right? It's
conditions. I talk about it all the
time. Understand,
how can I frame this? Understand what
trades you like taking and then
understand what environments they're
good in. I forget who was here earlier
and they said they like they're a trend
trader. They listen to my commentary,
but they like trading trend. And I said,
"Trend's my favorite." We're not in a
trending market, right? So, my favorite
conditions are a trending market, right?
Even if I'm going to play the a big
daily move back back up and it's counter
trend on the daily, but I know in that
day we're going to have a trend, I can
use participants at lows to pivot back
higher. I understand the conditions I
need. Okay, we're going to come and test
these 42s I talked about earlier. We'll
get back to this conversation in a
second. Just want to help you guys.
Right, so we're coming into this area
here. If we look at bookmap, this is
where the guys came flying in. All
right, these guys here might be about to
get stuck. This 187 lot, 130 lot, 123
lot. They're about to be stuck here. If
we hold the next pullback into 42s and
40s, then I expect new highs of day.
Right? If we hold the next pullback into
sort of 38 40 42, I expect a new high of
day here. These shorts didn't get their
way. They did not see these big
aggressive shorts. They didn't get the
breakdown underneath the last low. So
they are now caught any pullback which
ho hold holds around here if they hold
it I expect a new higher day
right so we get back to that
conversation
so
I just draw this out for you if longs
hold this I expect a new high of day if
you come under this you're going to get
the rotation so I'd be bullish on the
hold of this okay so yes understand what
trade setup is your favorite setup then
understand what conditions are
preferable for that setup and focus on
that setup in those conditions. Do not
focus on those that set up in subpar
conditions. Where people get stuck is
they look for things like
I don't know like a breakout trade in a
ranging market. A ranging market is not
going to give you a breakout trade,
right? A ranging market is going to give
you a failed breakout.
All right? So, if you're a trend trader,
let's just come up here a second.
All right. If we've done this and we've
created a range,
all right, if you try and take this
breakout, it's very likely that it's
going to come back into the range. If
you try and take this breakout, it's
very likely it's going to come back into
the range. These are going to be failed
breakouts. All right? If you just look
at WOFF, this is what we do. You want to
wait for an acceleration out of it and a
pullback and a hold when we're leaving a
ranging market. Right? When we're in a
trending market,
we're in a strong trending market and
you're early in the trend, pull back one
or pull back two, right? If you're not
going to trade longs from here, then you
can take a breakout here. It's much
safer to do. I wouldn't be doing it on
the third leg, right? Leg one and two.
So, that's a prime example of
understanding the conditions of the
market and what you're looking for.
JC, glad I found your channel. Thank you
for joining, my friend. Thank you for
joining.
Higher time frame is key. Look at uh the
4K with ES reversed. It's like cheating.
I was long on the ES for three days from
6775. There you go.
Exactly. That's why strategies don't
work in every situation. That's why as
you get better as a trader, you will
start sorry, you will start developing a
playbook that works for each strategy.
So, as you become more proficient, for
me, I'd say the easiest trade is a is a
trend trade, protrend, right? So, if
we're bullish, higher time frame, making
higher highs and higher lows on weekly,
monthly, weekly, dailies, right? Then
you're looking for a pullback on an
hourly to get long into. Simple, right?
It's the first trade I would I would
advise. Once you get good at that, then
maybe you can think about a range trade,
right? I still hate range trades. I will
take them when there's enough space in
the range, but I don't like them. Maybe
then you can take the range trade. Maybe
then you can look at a breakout trade to
move away from value. You can look at
that. Maybe then you can look at things
like if you want to get aggressive at
the open like a 30 second opening range
break, things like that. You can start
adding playbook, right? Think about any
skill that you add. Think of train
trading like a sport. You go and play,
I don't know, tennis for the first time.
You learn to just rally, right? Just hit
the ball over the net. Get good at just
hitting the ball over the net. Then
maybe you develop a top spin. And then
maybe you develop a back a backhand top
spin similar to the front hand top spin
but with your backhand. That could be
like your pull back long, pull back
short. Then you develop a slice backhand
slice. That could be like, I don't know,
your failed breakout or your mean
reversion short or your failure short.
And then you develop a slice on the
forehand. Then you develop your serve.
Maybe your serves, your A+ trade when
you know everything's going well. You're
looking for that big serve, right? Where
you size in. It's like that, guys. You
develop your playbook slowly over time.
You don't do it all at once.
Holiday is good to avoid. Yeah, I would
agree. Stashed. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Like
we said all all week we were here, we
were saying we don't expect much. We'll
be here in case we get something, but
we'll be here to hang out as much as
anything else and do some giveaways and
have some fun, right? Otherwise, trading
can be very boring. We didn't expect
much yesterday or today, but we made a
little bit of money. So,
he's very smart, guys. Follow him. Thank
you, Stash. That's very kind of you.
Range trader. I lit my lips when I see
in inside the daily range. There you go,
Julian. See, this is what I love about
trading. Everyone can like there's room
for everyone. Once you know what you're
looking for, like Tyson earlier has very
much this year, we got Tyson on track by
focusing on IB trades. So either
expansion outside IB or rotation
rotation inside IB. And you just heard
him say earlier like he's about to take
his payouts for the first time this year
because we got him on track by sticking
to a playbook, developing that playbook,
and slowly adding more plays to it.
catching up with chat here. Sorry guys.
I was kind of rushing the market the
last few days just trying to go small
base hits across multiple counts and one
at once and just think it was a bad
choice in hindsight trying to rush.
Yeah, definitely. No, there's ne
I will tell you now, all right, I've
been here a long time. There's never a
reason to rush. Never, ever, ever. You
you will see me miss trades on stream.
Most days I will miss trades on stream.
I'll be waiting to be picked up. it
won't pick me up. I'll get caught
teaching you guys and miss the trade.
What you won't get me doing is rushing
in afterwards. All right? Because I know
whether it's that session, the next
session, the next day, the next week,
the next month, the market's going to
give you opportunities. It's just about
being here for it. You never need to
chase it. It will come back to you. It
will come back to you. What about
reversals? Yeah, you can trade reversals
if that's part of your bread and butter.
Trade reversals. Just don't be the wrong
side of it. Don't be fighting a big
trend day. So many people look for
shorts on big trend days. It's where I
see most people fail.
If I was having a trend day, let's say
now, ignore all the levels. All right.
What would I look for? If I would look
for taking out some liquidity, trapping
buyers at the highs, coming down,
producing a lower high into a volume
shelf that I could rotate from. And I'd
need a clear target down here. So, let's
pretend the profile looks like that and
we could trade all the way down. That
would be a reversal. I would not be
short into these pushes. No way. That's
where most people get it wrong. But
yeah, reversals are legitimate
strategies. We play them all the time.
Green on the last four days of December
is not bad. I would say it's pretty
great. Green four days at all was pretty
good, mate. Well done. I've been
watching your lives the past four weeks.
Had no idea you were in LA. So am I. I
absolutely love your live sessions. You
give so much knowledge. A thanks
Jeremiah. That's really really kind of
you. Where in LA are you? We go over the
open
will do you mean will we go over the
open rate trade when it's good and when
it's not a good idea? Oh, when when's
the orb good and when's it not? I would
say when there's targets above. Right.
So right if we have a 15minute orb today
we this is our 15-minute orb. Right.
Today we traded inside, failed, traded
down, held, right? If if we break away
from it, let's say
we have key level here. Let's say we've
traded here, right? And if we break away
from it here and we have a level here
and we know buyers got trapped, then I
trade downside. Same the opposite way.
It's all about same when I trade the
open. Sometimes you'll see me trade the
open. All right. Yesterday, I think
yesterday or Friday, I traded the open
aggressively once I saw momentum come
in. If we see momentum come one
direction and there is a clear
lowhanging fruit to aim for, I will
trade that. So, if I'm going to trade a
break, I'll trade it. If momentum's on
my side and I know, okay, they're going
for that. I can see it's up there. I
know we want to go there. I'll trade it.
What I won't do is trade an orb inside a
range when there's nothing to do, right?
So let's say our orb is here and our
profile is here from the current day or
previous day or previous week, right?
Then what's likely to happen? Push fail,
drop, fail, right? Because we're pinned
in the ranging market. When's it going
to be good? The orbs here and we're
bullish higher time frame. Let's say
we're bullish higher time frame. We've
got level of liquidity here. We're going
to trade that break because it makes way
more sense then to go upside [snorts]
second day here while you really explain
the dynamics of a market in detail and
an understandable format. I've been
trading on and off since the mid 2000s
and I started trading prop in fair. Glad
glad I'm able to help you trader doc.
You were talking about the play about
playing golf with the eight iron to get
a good at that before switching clubs. I
like that one. Yeah, Breezy. That's out
of the book. Um, golf is not a game of
perfect. That's what I said. Someone
asked yesterday what's the best book to
read and I said the best non-trading
book to read I would say is golf is not
a game of perfect. Loads of other ones
like Atomic Habits and all those things
but you won't hear many people talk
about golf is not a game of perfect but
it's a good reminder about developing
your skill base slowly and being okay
with, you know, being okay with just
being good at one setup. You can be
profitable just being good at one setup.
The hard part is being disciplined. Only
taking that setup, right? [sighs]
Um,
holidays are for drinking. Hey, I agree.
I went and bought some more cigars
yesterday, so I'm going to have a sore
throat these holidays.
It's my third stream experience. I like
the way you explain things with zero
[\h__\h] focusing on trading arena
markets. I've canled my two streams and
concentrated the stream with you. Uh,
thanks for joining, Sam. Thanks for
joining. Thanks for the kind words. Look
forward to working with you, especially
next year. I remember not not here as
much until we get uh past the New
Year's, but back to normal from January.
We'll be doing 5 days a week.
Sell now. Now, I wouldn't say sell now.
Is still holding volume. You've taken
some liquidity. Your first level here
has been taken. Your second and third
levels are here. I would for me I'd need
to see you know a drastic drop and a
failure underneath volume right and then
the problem with your cell then is where
are you going to target I mean they can
trap in here and you can target here we
can have a look at what that looked like
in terms of uh the footprint inside this
you did catch a few buyers up here
versus 50s again
you still have a buying balance here
structurally you're still holding pretty
good.
Zoom out. Look at this on a 5m minute.
I can see some sellers came in here
earlier. So sellers need it underneath
these levels. This is where they came
flying in earlier and here, right? So
I'd say if you get a close under here
and you reject, then maybe, but I
personally wouldn't be picking tops up
here. Yes, you'd swept the liquidity,
but in terms of what I'm seeing,
technically speaking, it's still
bullish. You would need to leave it. For
me, I'd want to see it leave volume.
This is why I'm saying it's got to be
careful. Maybe some of you are trading
the IB trade back down and that's your
trade. You're focused on that specific
trade and you don't wait for
confirmation. You're looking for IB
close. Okay, go. Possible, right? I'd be
looking for that. And until I see that,
I wouldn't be convinced that it's a
short because we still have targets if
it wants to move higher. Okay, we still
have this and this. It wants to be
higher. So I would need to see strong
selling pull back in reject volume and
then you haven't got that far to aim for
really unfortunately you'd be looking at
sort of 30s to 15s and teens and maybe
if you got lucky down here. So you're
going to get 15 and 30 points if it
offers it at all. This is the problem
with days like today. The range is just
not there folks.
Sorry guys, having to scroll up here to
see you guys. Uh, I think I found my
main stream to watch. Hey, nice.
Welcome. Welcome. Thank you to I'm
speaking my mind. You're doing a good
job. You're welcome, dude. I've been
following you for almost two weeks. I've
learned more from watching you
than from the course I took. Thanks so
much. You're welcome, man. It's fairly
common. There's a lot of [\h__\h] courses
out there, unfortunately.
Absolutely. Hands down, one of the best
streams of ENQ. Thanks, Dave.
What are you trading? And does it come
what are you trading on and does it come
with such details? I'm not sure I
understand what you mean. Futures lift.
Um, I chart here on Trading View for
you. I execute on Ninja Trader.
Morning
SFC. How you doing? Welcome back again.
Hope you're good.
CCL is dropping like you said. There you
go.
Um
I play golf at university level. League.
Nice trader doc.
Inhale those cigars. No, no, no. In no
inhale of cigars. [laughter]
[sighs]
Uh, first week on your channel. You've
been awesome. I'm originally from New
York City. Living in in Atlanta,
Georgia. Go dogs. Getting ready to enjoy
Miami style Christmas at 75. Happy
holidays. Hey, happy holidays to you, my
friend. Happy holidays to everyone here.
Looking forward to ramping up in 2026.
Me, too. Me, too. The likes are low.
Yeah. How many likes we got? Can we get
these likes up, guys? Because I want to
do some giveaways for you. I'm feeling
generous. I want to give away. It's the
last one before Christmas. I'd like to
give away three Apex accounts and three
uh very beginner courses. So, I want to
get these likes nice and high if we're
going to do that. Where we at now? And
then I'll give you a target.
3009, guys. We can get to 400 500
easily. Let's get to 400 at least and
give away. We want to give away three
Apex accounts.
Eric, thank you. You're the best. You're
welcome. Love your stream. Thanks for
all you do. Thanks, Brock.
I got the funded trading 90% reversal. I
got sorry, I got all the funded trading
90% reversal and waited for clear lower
highs and a break of fair value gaps and
it was working. But for the past few
days, front running reversals,
I think I'm going to wait for Jan. Yeah,
exactly. Exactly, Breezy. Like if you're
playing that strategy, just understand
you've been in a range. So
you got to wait to trade trade the
edges.
Rumo says, "I'm short. NQ 25 743."
So you're playing in this edge. Just be
careful. You've not let go of anything
yet. All right. You've not let go of
anything yet. This is your pivot. This
is your high. Until you break down away
from this volume and do this, there's no
short in my mind. But look, if if you're
risking IB, I understand can be a legit
trade. If that's your strategy, IB to V
up, don't mind it. But I would say
structurally in terms of volume, you've
not left volume, you've not pivoted yet.
All right, so just be careful if you're
short in this already. Make sure you've
got your risk set to somewhere that you
feel that buyers are trapped. I would
say, all right, even on Bitmap, we can
see there's a big buyer got caught 302
lot at 751. So, as long as you're under
that, as long as they protect that, that
would I would use that as your risk for
those of you who are in it what I would
deem possibly a little bit early. 7:51.
You don't want it back over that.
What time will I trade till today? Uh,
another 25 minutes. We'll do giveaways
into the into the end of this stream.
really agree with you, but mentally I'm
stuck at 70%. I need to go back to
value. So, I'm always looking for
reversals into VA. So, it sounds like
that's your trade, though. So, if that's
your trade, that's that's what you're
looking for.
Short 732. Silly 732. Uh you're looking
for the breakaway short. I I would let
it die under there first. I wouldn't
short there because this is what
happens, right? Like I talked about, you
need it to trade down. I'd be very
careful with this node and you'd need it
to leave volume and then trade lower.
you are starting to see it potentially
leave volume. But I'd be looking for
this if they're not kind, right? Two
things are going to happen. They'll be
[\h__\h] and do this or they just do
that without offering this. Right? But I
would, for me personally, I'd be looking
for this to fade away. All right? And
then reject a key level and trade lower.
Until that point, personally, I wouldn't
be looking for a short. I'm not going to
trade it at all today. But I'd be very
careful. Like I said, the structure this
low created this high. This is a volume
buildout. You've not left this volume
yet, right? And you haven't even come
into this node yet. So, I'd be somewhat
careful. Doesn't mean it can't move
lower, folks. It can come up here and do
this and do this and do this. It can,
but it can also come up here, protect
this, and finish the rotation and
completion. ES is still above initial
balance high. VIX is still around low of
day, right? VIX currently trading at
1370, guys. All right. So 1370 you're
looking for a short while VIX is very
very low. And even on this last
pullback, let's look at the shorts that
got caught in this last pullback.
They're all caught offside.
Look at all these guys
right into this block we talked about
earlier. Remember 2 minutes ago we came
back to this. All right. These shorts
are piling in here twice. Now until you
get a break like this, these shorts can
be stuck. If they start rebidding over
here, the next target will be this. And
if they get through this, it's a
squeeze. So I would be very hesitant to
be too eager short in this right now.
Can I please show the footprint settings
if you can? Uh yeah, sure. These are
just how I use it. This is not might not
be how you want it. Right. So I have row
size, manual, ticks per row, two
display. I have it on profile delta um
is what I have for type and then I have
apply background and I have PC showing
and info uh summary box I have it set to
info. All right, that's it. Stat levels
actually I have imbalance 500% stat
levels four.
Right, I can't scroll down to show you
that. I don't know why it's it's all
stuck but hopefully that helps. Right,
these are the main ones you need. Row
size manual ticks per row two display
profile type delta. It's up to you
whether you have the gradient on or not,
but that's how I have it at the moment.
PC, I have it yellow so it stands out. I
can't show you that, but PC have it on
set to yellow. Under that s uh show
summary info, I have the info box.
That's it, folks.
You could put delta on as well. Where
would that be?
There you go. You could have table.
Let's do that. You could have table. I
would take volume off session CVD P open
interest. Just have delta. It would look
like this then. And then you've got your
delta. So you can see heavy delta in
this 5m minute bar. You've got 10
seconds left. Question mark. Are we
moving lower? No. Who's stuck? Sellers.
All right. They came flying in here and
they're not moving lower. Look at this
heavy delta. Are we moving lower? No.
So, we've got passive buying here, and
if they break, they're going to try and
take this out. Sellers need to come
under here. So, I'm saying I wouldn't be
early on the short yet, folks. They're
piling in here, and they're not breaking
lower, which means in here, you've got a
buyer absorbing the tape. So, sellers
are now caught in here. Sellers are
caught here. Buyers are caught here.
This is where the rotation is. Would I
meet be a new money long? Absolutely
not. But I wouldn't be early to the
short, right? You're not seeing a
breakaway and a rejection. And you're
seeing sellers get trapped in the same
level we talked about earlier.
Hopefully that makes sense to you guys.
And I can even show you the same thing
on bookmap. I'd be looking them just
gifting you some pretty big time
knowledge here. All right. Same thing
here. Look at these sellers at the end
of the auction down here. Selling
selling selling selling selling. If we
think about
these guys, they're offside. If we think
about the break,
everyone under there's now offside. And
if we let this buyer out, we're going to
go upside. And where's liquidity? It's
all resting above. Remember, the gray
box is a 60s. Look very bullish for me.
Tried to make I tried to I tried to warn
you there about being short early.
Hopefully, this is a good lesson for you
guys to see why you don't frontun
shorts. You do not front run shorts.
Alex, thanks for your time. Can Oh, I
just did that one. The footprint. Sorry,
guys. Still getting through these,
bro. Do I use instant funding prop? I do
not. I think uh I'll be honest with you.
Instant funding prop. What goes against
it? I'm assuming you mean like director
funding. Very expensive. Very very very
very expensive what it is. Uh secondly,
very bad rules. Normally it's like 20%
consistency or something on instant
funded. So you're paying to get direct
in funding, but you're limiting what
you're able to do. I think you're better
off to do something where you can pass
in a couple days. All right? Or even one
day and not have that 20% consistency.
That's what I would say. Instant
funding, it's not a scam because they
tell you what you're doing, but I I
would not advise it. Right? If there was
an instant funding without consistency,
for sure I'd do it. Save you loads of
time. But there isn't. Not that I know
of. Do I trade gold? No. Sometimes I
will be swinging gold, but I I don't in
day trade it.
How many subscriptions do I have? Uh
bookmap
trading view. That's it. I think I want
to get a good um
uh gamma reader for my Discord. Just
trying to find one that will uh give me
updated um Gex levels for Discord. I can
get it for myself for Ninja. I'm trying
to get it so I can have it uh maybe with
an API or something so it automatically
tells Discord. That's that's the next
one I'm trying to get at the moment.
What platform do you use for foot
footprint? Uh for me I use Ninja Trader
and Trading View.
Your My volume profile looks different.
What's your setting? Uh it would be the
same as I just had
on uh footprint, right? Ticks per row
two. That's it. That's the only thing I
change. Ticks per row two. You could
have it on columns at a th00and. It's
the other way I would have it.
Do you use volume profile starting at
the Asia session? No, I use it at RTH.
So, New York session. Sometimes if
Asia's had a big move, if there's been
some news overnight, I will mark out the
GlobeEx range, right? So, I'll go from
the the open of the new session right up
to 9:30. If it's had a big move, I'm
interested in that. But otherwise, no,
because there's no volume there, right?
So, if we look overnight, look at the
difference in volume. So, I'm not really
I'm not too bothered.
So, here's the push, guys. So, if you're
still long, top of the gray box is your
next TP and then all the way up here.
All right, this will be the third drive.
So, I'd be very cautious now. One, two,
three. All right, they need to get their
take profit here. All right, we're
starting to build this. This is not
bullish in terms of structure at this
point. I wouldn't be buying this move,
but I would be selling your bullish
plays. Remember those of you who are
long from down here, we sell in the top
of the gray box and up here. I would not
be getting bearish until you see
something like this. Okay, tried to make
that as clear as possible. And this
still just in that slow grind higher.
I found bookm but messy for NQ. You just
need to get used to reading it, man. It
just moves a bit quicker for NQ.
for footprint. Is it not better to see
on Quant to Tower than Ninja Trade TV?
Ninja and I see it on Quant to Ninja
Trading View based on how volume is
calculated. Yeah, it's probably a little
bit more accurate.
Nihal spot gamma is that is that a
website? I'll check it out.
How do you get footprint for Ninja
Trader? Um there's a video on it, but
what you want to do is uh open up
volumetric charts. Uh, I don't really
want to do it on here cuz I've got
another thing loading, but let me bring
this over. All right. I use a third
party app for it. But what you want to
do is come Where's your charts here? Is
this it?
No, you want to go to data. Sorry guys,
give me a second. Data
chart style. Here you go. Am I on the
right one? Chart style.
Uh,
oh my god. Why can't I remember this?
Let's stop using it.
Hang on, hang on, hang on. Properties.
Nope. I thought it was up here.
Why can't I remember this? Come on,
brain. getting gear.
Someone remind me. It's Volutric. I just
can't remember where to find it cuz uh
I'm using a third party now. I have it
on here. You see?
I'm going to find it for you. Give me a
second.
I can't find it.
Data series candle type. That's what I
just did. I couldn't see it. I gone mad.
Data series.
type. Aha, there it is. Well done. Thank
you. There you go. Type Voluttric. All
right. If you go to Volutric, that's uh
that's their in-house version. All
right. That's their in-house version of
footprint. That's what you want to go to
if you're using the free one. If you
want to get the data for that, um it is
free if you're using Trade of 8. any
prop on trade of eight. There's again
there's a video on my on my uh YouTube
for free which teaches you all that.
Okay, there's your swipe. So your TP
just got hit. The only thing left now is
up here. All right, but that was a good
stop run up there. If we look at bookmap
like we talked about, that's could well
be the end of the auction, right? It
could well be the end of the auction
now. So if we look at bookmap now, look
at this stop run up here. 22 31 33 112.
Right, so that's where they ran those
stops. They've got room higher if they
really want to go for my red line on the
chart. But again, I wouldn't be a new
money long. I'd be down to 5% of my
position here because they could easily
collapse it. And look at the book. It's
gone very, very thin all of a sudden.
Right? Very, very thin now. So hopefully
that made sense. Like even for you guys
that were short, all right, and you were
asking me, hopefully that made sense.
That will help you next time you're
thinking about front running and getting
short earlier, right? You have to ask
yourself, remember, ask yourself before
everything, is your location good? Your
location wasn't bad in this area. Was
momentum good? Location was okay. Was
momentum good? No. What was the
structure? Well, that was your swing
low. That was a swing high. Did you ever
get a change in character? No, you
didn't. All right. No change in
character. You held dips. Did you ever
break away and reject volume? No, you
didn't. Did you ever leave buyers
trapped? Well, you had a very small
amount up here, but you also had a lot
of sellers, like we talked about trapped
from here, right? When you use their
pain, now you're starting to run the
liquidity. So, hopefully it's a nice
little lesson here for you guys for next
time.
How you know this shorts just closed
longs. How did I
How you know if this shorts or just
closed longs? How do Oh, how do I know?
Why do I think that's stop run? You're
saying? Uh I I don't What I know is that
yesterday this was a pivot. Today this
was a pivot. So I all I know is that
there's market buy orders here. All
right. And those would be short stops.
Short stops and breakout
buyers. All right. Have their orders
here and here. And all I know is that
there's lots of buyers in here, right?
who are currently stuck because we're
not above their price because of how it
looks. I know that there probably stops.
All right. Doesn't mean we can't come up
here. They need they're going to need to
print and hold. They they look
aggressive right now. They look like
they want more.
Um
up just under 400 today. Alex, all
micros back to my new eval. Thanks for
everything. See you tomorrow. Nice.
Scott. Scotty. Catch you. Oh, I won't
see you tomorrow. I don't think or maybe
maybe I'll trade in the morning for an
hour or so. I'll see see how I feel.
Is just using an anchored volume profile
tool that's just as good as indicators.
Yeah, this is this is an anchored volume
profile. That's what this is. It's
exactly what it is.
I notice you turn off session CVD
because uh so I have I watch CVD if I'm
looking at CVD
I'm watching it here on a five minute
right looking for divergence right so I
don't want to I don't want another thing
up top there not just just another thing
to look at but it's only because I've
got it somewhere else on the chart
right how we doing for the likes guys we
got those likes up to do the giveaways
yet where we up
Guys, we need we need to get to 400
here. Let's get another
25 plus likes. I want to give away three
Apex accounts and three introduction
courses. These the courses are good for
people who've never traded before,
right? So, if you've traded before, you
might not want to do it. You can give it
to friends and family or we can just
reroll it.
Can I tell you why there is an auction
or resting order above or why you felt
the auction was done or dead around the
location? I felt like it could be done
because it was all buy side. The resting
orders above are all sellers up here.
So, they're probably buyers right off
the low looking to take profits. Uh the
auction could have been done
but isn't done because we had all buy
side delta in this candle here. big buy
sell delta big volume and we weren't
willing to trade above it but now we're
trading above it so it's it's irrelevant
at this point we didn't we had the
chance to come and do this but they
didn't they rebid IB right we're above
IB we're in technically and we're in
trend right now potentially up to there
as the target
will you trade during Asia Alex it's
very active I have to sleep at some
point. [laughter]
I got to get some sleep. So, no.
Brandon sold my QQQ calls 10 seconds too
early. E. Well, you should have made
money. Jumped another 20% on that daily.
Oh, man. I'm sorry. How do I enter the
giveaway? We I'll I'll tell you how to
enter in in 5 minutes time. We'll do it.
We'll do it all together. Don't worry.
Everyone on stream will have a chance of
winning.
How much is the intro course? 99 bucks.
Very very cheap. So if if you don't win
and you want to do the int intro course,
it's 99 bucks. It's only two hours long,
but then you get $99 off the beginner to
advanced course. All right. So you
basically get the intro course for free.
Best way of putting it.
Someone was asking, I'm not affiliated
with them. Peria instant has no
consistency after the first 10 days.
Then it's like, oh that's interesting.
never traded with them either.
Which course do you recommend for a
trader with three years experience
to learn to factor in volume profile
into their existing strategy? Um, just
do my uh the volume profile and
orderflow course. Go to my website
flowzonetrader.com
volume and order flow. that course right
there. It's uh
399. If you use code launch all
capitals, you'll get $100 off. That ends
in January 1st. All right. So, it's
trying to reach up here. It's getting
very squeezy right now. All right. This
is all just buy side pushing.
How did I get my next location up top?
This red line right here, previous day
high, right? So, anyone who is swing
short,
this is their location. This is where
their stop is. Right? So, if they're
swing short, this is where the stop is.
So, if we're going to hunt, we're going
to hunt 780
all the way up into 90s. Right? So, I'd
be watching this level here.
So, if I was long,
this would be a place to start taking
profit
right in there.
[sighs]
12-hour shift day. Good for you, man.
Good effort. Jeff Stewart W done for the
day. Have a great Christmas, Alex.
Congrats, Jeff. Nice win. Nice win.
All you guys who got long from this call
we made, where was that call we made?
All the way down here. Have we got 100
points now? It's a 100 point trade. We
called out. So from here,
this was the call right here. There's
the signal. But here was the call that
dip inside that held TP1,
TP2, TP3, and this would be TP4. If we
hit that, you've hit all your targets.
Anything above that is a bonus, folks,
as a 100 point winner if you took that.
while I've been sat on my hands.
That's nice. Did any Are any of you
still in it from down there? I know
Tyson got out of his position. Are any
of you still in it?
It's a nice move.
Why did I not take that? Cuz I just told
myself I wasn't going to trade mid-range
today.
uh it was highly probable, but I just
don't like I said, I just don't want to
trade in here today. So, I was I'm happy
on effectively the last half decent day
before Christmas to just relax. Do you
know what I mean? Like, I've already
locked in some money this morning. I
don't feel the need to um
I don't feel the need to trade and I
missed my core entry which I forget
where it was when we were I missed that
short back down and then we talked about
that long but I'm just trying not to
trade inside that range. It's worked
really nicely for you guys though. It's
been very very nice.
Still long but only two micros left. Two
micros over 100 points. That's $400.
That's It's great, man. It's great. Does
my work indicator work on higher time
frames for swings? Yep. Exactly the same
rules for it.
Yes, I think uh Trader 8 does. I don't
trade on them, but I'm pretty sure it
does. I think the footprint charts are
pretty good on Trader 8 as well from
what I understand. Just be careful here
as you're building out a little shelf
here.
Still bullish on this, but we are
building out a bit of a shelf here.
I'm going to get rid of this now as
well, folks. Okay, because we've gone
through it. You're extended here. So,
this is the three drive. They had to
successfully beat this drive. They did.
And you're technically in a trend day
over this.
They can afford to come down here. If
they hit that, maybe they come down.
Maybe they come down early and have
another attempt. I don't know. But uh
this is very bullish right now. It's in
a squeeze.
Do I only trade futures? Do I trade
individual stocks? I swing I used to
trade individual stocks a lot. I swing
individual stocks. So I'm a swing trader
on ETFs and individual stocks. I don't
really day trade them. vote. [sighs] I
just don't have the time to do this with
you guys and teach in my Discord and
provide a course and try and trade
futures and then do individual stocks.
Although I think there's so much edge in
individual stocks, but
my brain just it will run out of space,
you know.
I've only got so much RAM. I made $200
on each account earlier. I'm just
hanging out and learning. Nice, Richard.
That's good work. Another payout coming
your way soon. That means
I'm down $10 today. I was up over $700.
No more trades for me. Sorry to hear
that. Yeah, just walk away. $10 is
nothing to be down. Just scratch it off.
Scratch it off.
Out of ENQ long GC on the pullback.
Okay, nice. Dave,
what is the time frame of your TV
footprint chart? That was on a 5m minute
we were looking on just then uh a couple
minutes ago. I just found your live
trading yesterday for the last hour.
I've been on all day today. Best live I
found. Great teachings. Thanks. Hey,
welcome. Thanks for joining. Thanks for
the positive energy.
Nice work those who stayed long. My
rules no trade after 11:30. Yeah, great
work those who stayed long. They look
good. It still looks good. It looks
good. Very, very squeezy right now. VIX
has found a little bit of a bid at these
lows. So, I'd just be somewhat cautious.
But we have a clear target above that
it's clearly aiming for right now.
What's the time here? Here's the 9:00
candle. All right. So, into lunch. We're
going to do these giveaways now.
Brandon, you're just in options.
Is Discord free? No, unfortunately not,
my friend. Okay, so those of you who are
new, Discord is just for people who do
the 20 20our course, the beginner to
advanced course. So with that course 20
hours you get a version of these flow
zones. All right my indicator you get a
version of this included in the course
and you get discord for life and in
discord I often do like group coaching
and teachings. It's all included.
There's no like um monthly fee. The
reason I do that to be clear why it's
only available on that course is because
I want students in the room who trade
the same way who are looking at the same
things. I think it builds like a better
working environment. Let's say if
everyone's looking at the same thing, it
means they can call out trades which
they're seeing and other traders can be
like, "Yeah, I like that." Or, "Uh, have
you thought about this?" Because they've
all done the same course. I think
Discords fail when they're free or
they're monthly with no indic uh
education. You get everyone trading in a
completely different way, arguing and
bitching with each other, and it causes
a nightmare. That's me talking from
personal experience. I've been part of
other Discords as a student, part of
other Discords as a mentor. And the best
way to do it is to have
just everyone on the same page. That's
my feeling. So that that's why, okay,
folks, it's not about the money. It's
that I need everyone to be trading the
same way. It also means when I'm not
there, there are guys who can step up
and say, "Hey, this is what we're
looking at today because they understand
the process, right? That's not to say my
process is the right way. There's tons
of processes. There's tons of way to
trade one ways of trading. But when I've
got 200 plus people all trading the same
way, it creates a very healthy
environment." All right. So, that's the
only reason, guys. All right. Let's do
How do we find out if you're on
tomorrow? I will if I if I'm going to be
on tomorrow, I will post a live stream.
Okay. Um, you're getting a bit wiggly
here. So, there's the move into the low
volume node, which they just caught and
trapped and they've instantly reclaimed
here. So, buyers are still in control.
This little trap here into this low
volume node into the flow zones. Buyers
are still in control. This is where they
want. They clearly want up here. is
absolutely clear as day. This is where
they want. So if you are a buyer, I
would just be you probably not got much
left. Just sell into this push into
here. All right, you can hold like a
tiny bit just in case we go all the way
up into the nines, but I would be
selling into that move. Right, there's
big big buyers trapped there yesterday.
Right at the high day yesterday, we had
a huge buyer trapped offside.
There's a lot of good information in the
Discord, private lessons, and a live
chat Saturday morning. Yeah, we do a
live uh Coupoops runs a live room every
Saturday morning where everyone reviews
the trades and ideas. I try trying to do
more weeklies definitely bi-weeklys um
lessons so we can go anyone that has
questions we do lessons all together. Um
it's like my call center 10 coaches are
all roleplaying the same way with their
team of agents. Alex, you have a serious
business. Oh, thank you. Thank you,
ma'am. It's very kind. All right, let's
go. Let's Let's do these giveaways. I
want to I want to give back to you guys.
You guys have been really good. First
thing, have we got enough likes on the
stream? Are we at 400 yet? We are. Thank
you, folks. Fantastic. Okay, giveaways
coming your way. Let me just
set some of these up. So, don't do
anything yet, folks. Don't do anything
yet because I want you all to have a
chance of winning.
Right, let's do
Apex first. So, just type FZT in chat.
You only need to type it once. If you
type it more than once, they will pull
you out the giveaway for spamming. So,
just type it once. We're going to give
away three
uh Apex accounts. Any size account, any
type of account you want. So, if you
want to do 300K, it would be free. We're
going to pick three winners for those.
All right? Because it's Christmas.
Normally we do one one a day, but this
is the Christmas giveaway, folks. All
right, let me do a nice
nice giveaway for you guys. I'll give
you guys a couple minutes.
We all done folks? Give you guys 15 more
seconds. Just type it once in chat and
then we're going to pick three winners.
[cough]
Okay. Five 4
one. There's still lots of you flying
in. Here we go. Here comes the winner.
Winner number one. TPT Trader
J3C, are you here? TPT Trader J3C, just
let me know on stream that you're here,
please.
Just let me know that you're here.
Nice. Okay.
All you need to do send me an email uh
with a screenshot of you logged in to
your YouTube so I know it's you. All
right, info@flowzonerader.com
and I will sort you out with a free Apex
account. Okay, I'll get give you a code
and you can use it for any size Apex
account that you want. All right, so
info@flowzonerader.com.
Just send me a picture of you logged in
so I know that it's you. All right,
let's do the second winner.
So, all you guys have just re-entered.
No worries. 5 4 3 2 1.
Comish 77. Right. You don't need to type
it again, guys. Don't worry. Just Just
those ones who thought they'd missed it.
Comish 77,
are you here? Comish.
Yeah. All right. Same thing for you,
Kish. All right. Just send me a
screenshot of you logged in to your
YouTube so I know it's you. I've made a
note of your name.
info@flowzonerader.com.
All right. Info@flowzonerader.com.
I will sort you out.
Okay, we'll do one more Apex giveaway.
Sergio, that's a regular. I recognize
that name. Sergio, are you here? Sergio.
[snorts]
Yeah. Awesome, Sergia. All right. Same
thing for you, Sergio. Okay.
info@flowzontenttrader.com.
Send me a screenshot of you logged in.
All right. And we're going to sort you
out some Apex accounts. All right. So,
the three of you all win an Apex
account. Congratulations everyone and do
a course giveaway now for you guys. I've
been trading 5 years but recently added
map and volume profile to my toolbox.
Can you give me a quick rundown of your
strategy with it? I'm looking to have
more precise entries. Uh Sean, uh I
would say go and go and rewind this.
We're coming to the end of the video now
where I'm doing some giveaways. But
there's tons there's tons on my YouTube
for free, mate. Go and have a look at
that. But what I'd be looking at right
now, target is up here for runners. If
they're going to leave this volume
trapped, then they're going to wash down
to here. But right now, we're very, very
bullish. But I use volume as an
indication of where we build liquidity
and I use it to exit that liquidity and
look for the next level. And I use
bookmap or footprints to see trap
traders. As simple as that. Okay. But
yes, and normally I'd explain more, but
you've come right in at the uh end of
the stream where we're doing some
giveaways. Sorry, bud.
Okay, so I want to give away some
introduction courses, right? So, these
are good just to explain these are good
for people who have never ever ever
traded or looked at a chart before. If
you know what you're doing, this course
is probably going to be way too easy for
you. So, you can do it because if you do
this course, you do get $99 off the
20hour course. All right. So, it is
useful, but if you want to give it to
someone for Christmas or something like
that, you can also do that. All right.
Okay. So, let's go. Type course in chat.
You just need to type it once.
And we're going to do three of these
away for Christmas as well. We give
three of these away at Christmas.
[snorts]
Still holding this volume shelf up here.
Still with a target above right now.
Still with that target above. Where are
the spiders? 87s.
Yes, got stuck at those 950s right now.
Still holding volume.
You guys maybe another 30 seconds or so.
Lots of you in here.
Oh, Marashion, you've just been uh
pulled out of it, unfortunately. You've
typed it about five times. So, uh
I did warn you guys, don't spam it. This
is what happens.
Yeah, no worries, Sean. I I totally get
it. Uh if you if you come back here in
uh January, I I can go over it, but
there's um there's a t there's tons on
my YouTube. I do have a course, but you
know, if it's your first time here,
don't do the course. You want to make
sure that you can uh you like how I
teach. All right? So, that's the most
important thing, the pedagogy. So, I
would say just go on my YouTube, check
out all the free stuff on my YouTube
first.
Okay? Here we go. Three, two, one. First
winner is
I like the name Krypton
FTZone.
It's like it's close to mine. Krypton,
are you here?
Krypton FTZone, are you here?
Give you a second to make yourself
known, otherwise we will reroll it.
[laughter]
Bearish bull. But he said to give it to
me, did he really?
Okay, I'm going to give you 10 more
seconds, Krypton. Otherwise, we're going
to roll. So, you need to say that you're
here in chat, otherwise we're rerolling
this.
Is CVD showing divergence? Uh, yes, it
is starting to show some divergence
indeed. You're not seeing bullish
aggression at the highs.
Definitely is. be watching this volume
like I talked about. I I'd be watching
this. There you are. All right. If you
do this
this trade down to here, I'd be watching
this if they let go of this this trade
down to here. Just know there's a low
hanging fruit up here still. Not until
that. Okay, Krypton. I'm going to make
note of your name. Right. Just shoot me
an email. Same thing all the time, guys.
When you win, I'm going to make a note
of your name here. You win the course.
All right. Shoot me an email.
info@flowzontrader.com.
All right. Uh, I need a screenshot of
you logged into YouTube so I know it's
you. All right. Two more winners coming
right up.
Futures lift. There we go. Futures lift
been nice and active today. Futures
lift. Um,
do you want the course? Futures lift.
It's an intro course. I can't remember
if you've done a lot before,
but I can sort you out.
Oh, you here. Can you hear me? Future's
lift [laughter]
perishable.
He was definitely here. He just said
something. Future's lift. You just won
the course. Are you still here, my
friend?
Are you still here, my friend? Just let
me know in chat you're still here. Be a
shame if you've left because you've been
here all day.
Give you 10 more seconds as well.
Last chance. Futures lift are you here?
Yeah, there we go. Just in time.
Awesome.
Awesome. So, it's the introduction
course. I will sort you out as well.
Just uh email me
info@flowzonetrader.com.
All right. Info@flowzonerader.com.
I've made a note of your name. Just send
me a screenshot of you logged into your
YouTube. Okay. Okay, we're going to do
one more winner today. One more winner
now. Jeremiah White. Jeremiah White.
Nice features lift. Oh, I'm glad. I'm
glad, mate.
Are you here, Jeremiah?
Jeremiah was here yesterday. There he
is. Awesome. All right, buddy. Same
thing for you, mate. So, welcome to do
that course. If if you've done other
courses before or you know what you're
doing, it will seem very very light for
you. So, you can always give it to
someone for Christmas. All right. But,
uh it is a two-hour course, introduction
to investing and trading. And uh you
also get a discount code when you
complete that course for the main
course.
uh info@flowzonerader.com.
Email me, send me a screenshot of you
guys uh of you logged in. Sorry, you
guys. Of you logged in so I can see it.
All right, it's all you need to do. Um I
saw someone asking, was there going to
be a Christmas sale for the beginner to
advance course? I haven't I hadn't done
one because we just did a Black Friday
sale. Um
h let's see if I do a flash sale for two
days for you guys. How many of you
actually want this beginner to advance
course if I do a flash sale for two
days?
We did just do a massive sale. So it
won't be as big if we do it.
You didn't get it. Black Friday. Yeah,
we did do a big Black Friday sale. Okay.
All right. If I do it, it's going to be
a flash one. So, let's have a look. See,
we can email
my dev about this. Give me a second
then. Give me a second.
I will limit the run because we just did
a massive sale. So, it' be first come,
first served. We do this.
Yeah, that's what we're talking about.
The 20our one.
Um,
give me a second.
Where is he? Trying to see if he's
online so I can email him now.
One second team. Right. You're starting
to leave this volume up above trap. Just
be careful. Those of you who are
bullish, you should have been down to
tiny size. You are starting to leave
that volume. Be very very careful.
Okay.
What do we have here?
I'm setting this up for you guys,
right? It will end Christmas Day at
midnight. It's going to be a flash sale,
folks. And it's going to be first come,
first served. And I'm not going to
announce it. So, it's just going to be
for you guys on YouTube who are here.
One per customer.
All
right. Flash sale, guys.
Only on the beginner to advanced course
is one per customer, 20% off. Code XMAS.
All right.
So, XMass. I'm going to post it in chat
so that you guys can see it. All right.
I'm not going to announce this. It's
just for you guys in YouTube. Simple as
that. So, because there's enough of you
here that were asking for it, I will
look after you.
So, it's for
this course here.
Tell I'm feeling jealous generous doing
this. All right.
20%
flash sale.
ends
Christmas day
code.
Oh,
there you go, guys. All right, so that
stuff's there. I'll pin it to your chat
now.
You can replace the old pinned one.
Right. It ends Christmas Day. I'm not
going to announce it. So, it's just
going to be for you. For you guys. It is
first come, first served. All right.
I've done it as a limited number because
it's just too good value. I can't just
keep giving it away. Secret Santa. Yeah,
I think that's I think that's quite
kind. I done we've done three Apex
accounts. We've done three introduction
like to trading foundations of tra
trading and and investing. Uh we're
giving away a I'm going to announce
today the winner of uh the funded next
as we're going to pick that off YouTube
today and then we've just done a 20%
sale for you guys for the um beginner to
advanced course.
Does it include the orderflow content?
No, that's that's a separate one, but
there's still there's still 100 bucks
off that right now.
Yeah, I think that's fair. I think
that's pretty fair. I think that's
pretty fair. I think that's me getting
in the Christmas spirit, right?
Hopefully you guys are happy with that.
It's only fair. All right, ES is
starting to break out. I'll sit here
with you for a little bit longer. ES is
starting to break out. You left the
volume there. You haven't rejected the
volume there. So, like if you were going
to be short, you've probably already
stopped out. It needs to leave this. All
right. It needs to do this if you're
going to leave. We're building a new
little base hit. It has got a target
above and ES is still going. All right.
So, the strength on ES is still there.
What just happened there? The strength
on ES is still there. Um,
I would say your point of control just
shifted up as well. So, if you start to
leave this, there is a drift down into
these, right? I wouldn't be bearish
underneath that unless you really build
out. You're starting to see this this
gray box. They probably wicked you out.
All right. So, if you were short here
risking the other side of that, you
probably just got wicked out. It's
possible that you can have another go if
they if they let it go. They're being a
bit dirty today on ENQ, but it's
probably because it's very low on volume
and liquidity, and there's still a
target above. So, I'd be super careful
about being bearish up here, right?
Super careful.
Yes, the 20our course comes with Discord
full forward. Yeah, it's included. So,
this is the course that has uh a version
of the flow zones and discord all
included in it.
Yeah. Merry Christmas to all of you.
Tell me again which profile you have on
the right of the ch uh chart. This is
anchored, right? This is anchored volume
profile, right? So, if you want to get
that, you need to come into here. Is it
this one or is it this one? I always get
confused. This one. Okay. Okay. So, 1 2
3 4 5 down into here into projections
anchored volume profile. And I just had
that anchored from 9:30. All right. So,
what you're looking at is what I call
cash. The reason I call it cash is it's
the cash market. So, from the New York
open, this is looks like a very good
trend day right now. But this is thin in
here. If you leave this, the only short
opportunity right now is here. Just know
that they haven't taken this liquidity
yet. I'd say the only short opportunity
is down into there. If you get a
collapse under here, maybe you get very
lucky and get into this. Um, but they
can. Any short today is counter trend. I
want to make that clear. All right. You
are above initial balance. You are above
opening range. You are above this level
here. It's counter trend. So, if you're
going to be adamant on taking this, it's
counter trend. You better be aggressive
with your stops because this is where
they want to come. They are trying to
get up into there. It all depends. Do
they trap too many buyers here? Leave
them and do this move. I don't know.
you're on a low volume day. It's
actually been a that move I said I
refuse to take but call it for you. Um
is gonna might it might just haunt me,
you know.
Might just haunt me. There we go.
[laughter]
H
Oh, nice forward. Nice. Today marks two
months of trading and following your
Apex system. I'll be getting my first
payout across four accounts in two days.
Thanks to your help, man. Hey, high
flipping five. That's all I care about
is you guys making money and getting
paid following your system. Well done.
Well done. That's awesome.
The coupon code for the 20% flash sale
on the 20our course is Xmas. So, all
capitals. I think it's all capitals. Let
me just check.
Let me just check. Have I done that
wrong?
Yes. All capitals. Xmas capitals. X MAS.
All capitals. The code for the uh $100
off the volume profile course is all
capitals launch. All right. That ends
Jan 1st. That stops Jan 1.
looking for your email address on the
website. However, I can't find it. Oh,
info infojeremiahflowzonerader.com.
Info and then just my website
info@flowzontrader.com.
My live tomorrow maybe. I wasn't
planning on it, but there is news in the
morning. Maybe. You'll know, guys,
because I will, if I'm going to go live,
I'll probably set uh um I'll set it up
ahead of time, right? So you'll see
I've been using rolling fib 9 EMA. It's
pretty nice. Yeah, rolling fibs, man.
It's what the flow zones are. Rolling
fibs. They're useful.
The chat slacks.
Oh, it's uh delayed, is it? Yeah. I
didn't know how much by. Hopefully not
too much.
No worries, Jeremiah. Right. So these
are the only players I would not be a
new money long, right? So you're either
long from all the way down here that we
talked about. Some of you took this
long. I mean, this was a fantastic long
on the reclaim. That's the best long of
the day. The next best long of the day
was this in here that we called out. You
don't want to be long up here. All
right? You do not want to be long up
here. You want to be selling your
profits. And you can only exit. You can
only look for a short if we're going to
do this or if you see something where we
do some kind of blowoff, right? where we
do something like maybe we run this and
trap more up here and then you'd have to
cover into this and this. You have to
respect the nodes, right? You have to
expect all of these to hold. Traps can
live in here, but if they die, then I
expect to come down to this point.
That would be some decent relief because
this is quite a big swing. 100 plus
points and it'll be a third of a relief,
which is somewhat warranted right now. I
would say
the markets have been so unkind this
month. I don't know what to believe
anymore. Shorting or longing? Now, you
need to think about both, right? When
we're in balance, you need to be
prepared to not have too much of a bias
and be willing to play both.
What course platform do I use?
Think thick or smart? Uh neither. I use
uh I just moved to go high level. Before
that, I was at Teachable. Everything I
do is at goh high level now. So it's all
in one place. So
all in profile settings. Yeah. Right
here.
There we go.
Ticks per row. Two ticks per row. I
leave everything else. Everything else
is the same. And then I just place it on
the right. Right. Anchored volume
profile. Everything else is the same,
guys. This is all I change. Ticks per
row. If you want to do numbers of rows,
I would just do it to a th00and. You are
starting to see a bit of a rejection of
this volume up here. This gray box. They
are struggling to get back through this.
What time is that?
Is Luna walked? Is it raining?
Okay. Yeah. [\h__\h]
We got the Apparently LA is going to be
the wetest place in the world over
Christmas. The good news is it means
it's snowing in the mountains. So, we
will go snowboarding.
You still have four hours. Yeah, you've
got plenty of time. I I I'm going to get
off though very very shortly, folks.
Just hanging out with you for now. But
uh
it's gray outside. I'm going to go and
use the gym. I need to wrap some
presents,
write some cards,
all that good stuff.
Be a husband, be a good dog dad, all
that stuff. Back into this gray box
again. ES is still going. New high
coming here on ES. Relative strength
over there.
Yeah, go high level is really good, man.
It took me a while to move, but um
you're obviously into this stuff. Future
if basically I had all my stuff split
between loads of different um platforms.
Um so it's still I'm learning it, but
it's really good because they can host
websites. They do all your CRM. It's
like the funnels are strong on it. Um
I'm barely I've barely scratched the
surface with it, but it's pretty good.
Long to 27800. That's your final target.
Yeah, your final basically this area
here is where bulls were trapped
yesterday, right? So this is your final
target on your long. So if you were long
from
what was the entry we get this morning?
If you were long from this entry here,
all right, this is your final target.
You should be down to 5 to 10% I would
say, right? Because you probably sold
some, sold some, sold some, you're into
a runner now. If it gets up there,
great. But we it doesn't have to get up
there. And I wouldn't be long up here. I
you do not want to as in you don't want
to start a new entry here. The entry was
down here or even better
this failure to break lower. Okay? But
that was the first entry since your
entry is down in this region. You don't
want to be getting long here. If it goes
higher, then it goes higher. It is what
it is. But this is a poor entry for a
long. Very poor entry for a long up
here. Even if it goes higher without
you, just be okay with that. You stick
to the process.
I try. [laughter]
I try. Sometimes I'm I'm good. Sometimes
I feel like I get it wrong. There you
go. Rejection of volume. So this is the
gray box. First time now. Going to
repric some of this thin volume. We can
have a look on footprint where we might
price to.
Okay. So first imbalance here right. So
how we act here becomes key and if we
get through this right if we reject this
this is possible
and we got buyers trapped up here. So
this move here. So remember we're
counter trend. If you're going to be
short here you're counter trend. This is
the gray box. If you're short here
you're counter trend. So you're partial
partial because you don't know when
buyers come in because the main trend is
up. So if you're counter trend, you are
taking money off the table or at least
you're moving your stops. We can see
this node right here that we've
identified here is now starting to act
as resistance. They've had few attempts
to break through
this trade into here. I would be partial
one into this wick
and partial two into here, partial three
into here. And if you got very lucky,
you come all the way down. I would find
that unlikely, but you know, you don't
know.
Happy
happy I guess that's happy holidays.
Happy holidays to all. Close your
charts. Enjoy the time with families.
Quite right, Green Otter. Quite right,
my friend. And same to you, too. I hope
all of you have a fantastic holiday
break. Um, just remember guys, it's only
trading, right? It's it's just a job.
It's just a it's a job. It's not your
life. Your life should be what you do
the next two, three days, right? Spend
it with people you love, whether that's
with your family or with your friends. I
don't have any family here, so I've made
my own family in LA. And we will be
spending Christmas together. All right.
Nice close group [clears throat] of
friends. Have some fun. No doubt you've
worked bloody hard this year. It's not
been an easy market, especially for you
guys who who are new. It's been very
volatile. You've had to deal with so
much insane news. All right, we've had
war news. We've had oil news. We've had
tariff news. We've had inflation news.
We've had the government shutdown. We've
had just about everything you can
imagine, right? It's been insane. Give
yourself permission to have a break.
Right? Please give yourself permission
to have a break and go and relax. It's
really important you recharge your
batteries because I think opportunities
next year are going to be massive. We're
going to continue to be volatile. We're
going to have some big opportunities.
You want to be dialed and ready for it.
And that means relaxing off the charts,
right? Means relaxing off the charts. I
can't read what you guys are saying. So,
we'll read this now and then I'm going
to sign off. I think you mentioned
earlier,
sorry, do you mostly look at your
footprints on five minute? Yeah, between
a five minute and a one minute. I flip
between the two. Once I'm dialing into
entry, I will go into a one minute. Same
same as how I treat all my charts. I'm
mainly looking at like a daily, an
hourly, and a five minute. Once we get
to a level of interest, all right, once
we get to a level of interest, I'll look
at a one minute. Here's your here's your
takeprofit here, folks. So, your next
TP, anyone who took this, this is your
TP into here and then down here and then
down here if you get lucky.
So, someone asked, "How do I use volume
profile?" And I said, "I'll have to
teach you next time." Well, here's a
good example, right? We're leaving trap
volume. We're trading. We're prot,
right? Because we don't expect it to
completely collapse. They might very
well bid off value and have another
attempt, right? So, you have to be
proactive. If you're playing counter
trend short, you proactive.
Um,
today I'm in a loss of $970. Should I
have to wait and
trade next day or shut down my MAC?
Trade next trade? I would shut down your
MAC, right? The opportunities today are
few and far between. Best moves have
gone. FC Mike, thanks Alex. You're
welcome. Otus W again today. Thanks,
Alex. Praying for the FCT family. Have a
blessed time with the families. Much
love, everybody. Much love to you, my
friend. You and your loved ones. SFC.
Thanks, Alex. Uh, Richard, Alex, do you
know how to set up volume profile in NT
to look like the one in Trading View you
use? If so, catch. Yeah, we can have a
chat in in Discord later, Richard. Um,
I'm doing it, but I'm using a different
platform for it.
Good entry for short. You've probably
missed it. It was probably in in here.
If I took this, I'd have I'll be honest.
I would have got short here and got
knocked out. And I've got short again
and this one would have worked. And now
you have to see if this holds.
All right. You could be short now and
you wouldn't want buyers to take back
control of 72. So you could think about
if you're really adamant on playing
this, I'd be very cautious because we've
come down to a key level. But you could
think about a short here. But uh I don't
like what I'm seeing here. I'd probably
leave this alone at this point. it. You
should have been short in that first
attempt at the gray box. You could
consider this for this move. It's not
out the question, but uh it's not as
pretty, right? It's basically the same
thing. It's repricing this.
You'd want this to hold now. I'd be
short here looking for that. But again,
if they don't break underneath this,
this is going to be very bullish now
because this remember the protrend is
up. So what's if we think about the
legs, this is all this is right with
this potential move. So when we trade
these shorts for these counter trends
where we trap volume, we cover into
these because the protrend will want to
go up. We don't know if we've timed
that, right? We don't know. We know we
cover some, we can hold some. If we get
lucky, we get this. But if they go back
protrend, well, that's the move because
this is the lowh hanging fruit that I
always talk about, right? This is where
buyers are trying to go. So, would I
reshort this? Personally, probably not.
Could it go? It could work, right? If
they repric this and stay heavy, yes.
But just the counter trend and I think
it's had the opportunity to do it.
You've washed this, you've protected
this, ES still looks very strong. I'd be
somewhat wary about having a new short
up here.
I go grocery shopping and we only have
seven likes but 250 comments. No, we
have like over 400 400 likes.
I'm excited to get through your beginner
course. Follow along your guidance next
year and see what it holds. Nice SFC.
Looking forward to trading with you.
Happy holidays to you Christie and you
Jeremiah. Thank you everyone. Supertoy,
thank you everyone. Merry Christmas.
short Q2 bouncing around my entry a bit.
Still holding with a bit of green. See
if it dumps or stops me. I just be
careful. Yes, it's trying to break out.
So, you need to protect this gray box if
you're short. Uh Joe Bag, that that
that's the area, right? So, that gray
box needs to stay heavy for you. That's
what I would say.
Really keen to get started. How do you
get in the Discord? Uh Tony topic, go to
the very bottom of the course. Uh
there's like a module right at the
bottom on um joining the discord. It
will tell you how to do it.
QQ highly at GEX target 622 spike QQQ
622. Yeah, I mean that's the pre that's
just just above previous day high,
right? So if you look at the cues 62163
previous day high 62 if that's the GEX
level. The only thing is the way we've
built structure into 620 62030s is
pretty good. So, you know, any bearish
move is likely to be absorbed there
until they let go of that. That's the
one thing I'd be careful of th those of
you trading zero DTE or anything on the
cues right now. Exactly. Go Gunners.
Let's go Arsenal. Top of the league.
Where do I leave my keys? Top of the
table. Top of the table. All right,
folks. Love you all. Trade safe. Be
smart this afternoon. Okay. Like I said,
don't forget today's the last day they
can rebalance.
Sometimes it gets a little wonky into
close. If if if there's a fund who need
to move something like they need to get
into AVGO right now, then they will they
will not miss the opportunity. They will
do it. And if they've got a ton to do,
they will do it instantly. So, just be
smart. Maybe I'll see you guys tomorrow.
If not, have a great Christmas. Um and
I'll see you next Monday. Next Monday, I
think. All right. Peace and love and
take care. Use hard stops.