Morning everyone.
Back at it. Back at it. Two more days
left. Two more days left until the
holidays. Right. So today it means we're
probably expecting some lighter volume
the next few days. Uh last time we had
this, we obviously had a drift up for oh
quite a few days really when we think
about what we did over the holiday
season in November. One, two, three,
four, five, five days straight up and
then a little bit more of a drift after.
So be careful. Be careful with this
light volume. All right, you want to be
careful with your position sizing and
your risk tolerance. Might see just slow
drift. Might see the odd flush. Uh let's
just refresh this while uh trading
restarts the day. Going mental.
Still doesn't like it. Anyway, starting
off on the daily. Okay, you can see nice
big gap up today right over uh Friday's
close. We're importantly over this low
volume node. That's the one important
thing that bulls needed to try and do um
early which they've done. Why is that
important? Well, we can use this now as
potentially support. All right, so we've
got 20-day and 50-day there. Any
pullback into there, we want to see, do
buyers come in somewhere in this area
and try and get back into this balance.
All right, this is what we've been
talking about for a while. Notice uh the
daily Ballinger bands, right? We talked
about this as well. They're starting to
contract, right? We're starting to see
contraction as we get the moving
averages tight. It means that probably
probably more likely into next year, but
we'll see. We're going to see something
like this. Something drastic is going to
happen. We cannot stay pinned in for too
long. We have lots of highs up here to
run. If bulls do manage to hold a
pullback, build liquidity, and go again.
If we get that rally, whether it's this
side of the year or ne next side of the
year, we have liquidity to aim for, but
they're going to have to get back above
this. If this is nothing more than a
failed push, then we're going to expect
sellers to defend this range, right? So,
it's interesting that we're doing it
this type of this time of year because
there might be that there's less
participants up there, but we will see.
So, initially,
um, momentum pretty bullish off the back
of last week, off the close of last
week. We just need to think about the
range that we're starting to get into
right here. You can see we're we're
starting to lose location. It's swing
bulls that have the most fun right here.
And uh even something like this if we
just wanted to measure out Monday.
Let's just do that whole balance.
Okay, there you go. So this is like a
two week balance. Um what contract is
this? NQ1. So it should have it all.
Just be careful by the way folks if
you're measuring balance on the new
contract up here. You're probably going
to get incorrect uh figures because
obviously when we were trading the new
contract, we weren't trading up here. We
hadn't rolled over. So it' be very light
volume. So it might give you odd prints.
So just be aware of that. You need to be
measuring out the old contract. [sighs]
Okay. So that's the range we're looking
at. Um can we hold acceptance into 700s
and 600s? Can we get up into this old
point of control in towards the 900s?
How do we react when we get there?
That's the big question this morning. So
is it a push and fail for a pullback and
we hold this old rotation? Is it a
morning flush which gets absorbed? Or is
it neither of those and just a slow
grind and and drift higher? We will see.
Time will tell. But those are all
possible today. [snorts] Moving into
the higher well the the hourly. We can
have a look at what we looked at what we
saw on the hourly. Let me just make this
a bit bigger for you and pull this down.
I hate it when the trading view mouse
mouse does this. Very annoying. Right.
So you can see old week's value. Um
probably need to take that off
extending. There we go. And let's pull
that
into Friday.
There we go. All right. Old week's value
left below. So, we're gapping up over uh
previous week, which is strong, but
we're coming into that two week balance
range. All right. So, remember this. So,
we've effectively got balance in here,
point of control, an old PC around uh
what did we just say it was? Let me just
check that. Lost it. I think it's about
just inside of 900. One second. So,
let's just get this on to make sure when
we go from Monday to Friday
923. And if we extend that to a two week
balance,
yeah, 9 uh 8
8.90 to 923. So, we're just going to
mark that out really quickly in here.
8.90 to 923.
somewhere in here, right? Is an old PC
naked,
right? Since we left it. So, we're
watching that, right? Gapping up over
the previous week, which is strong,
drifting higher. Tech's had a pretty
good start to the session. Uh you would
have seen uh well, the curve in Japan
doesn't look good, but hey, but we're
not reacting to it. Like I said, it
might be a very, very crowded trade that
takes a while to set up. It has
historically taken a while to set up. It
doesn't always happen straight out the
boat, especially when we're expecting
it. So, let's see if price drifts into
here. All right, let's see if price
drifts in. Let's see if we pop and fail
this morning, come back and test old
value. If we do fail without a pop,
let's see if we hold value and then try
and go higher. And that will be the same
for the next few days, unless we close
well outside. All right, so that's what
I'm watching at. Do we hold value for a
drive higher? Do we reject the old
balance? All right, a push in which
failed backto back test the old value or
are we just going to drift in here?
Right. Are we going to drift in here and
just do nothing? Also very possible.
It's what we did before. It's what we
could do again. All right, let's have a
look at overnight. You can see what's
happened here. Here's the cash gap right
all the way down here. Nice big gap up
and just a drift higher. We haven't
washed anyone out. I'd be slightly
concerned about that. It's not an
automatically short, but we are somewhat
extended. All right, we're trying to
drive into here, but uh you know all
these players, anyone who was long
Thursday, Friday, last week swing.
Anyone who bought the open of the new
session, anyone who has bought in Asia
or in London has been left in the money.
We have not washed anyone out. Doesn't
mean we have to do it today. Maybe we do
it tomorrow. Maybe we save all of that
for post Christmas. I don't know. Maybe
this is the Santa rally. We will see,
folks. Time will tell, but all I can say
is we are drifting higher right now.
Right, let's go and have a look at
what's going on in some of the other
indexes.
Same story on the ES right now. You can
see drive and back up. It's already into
that old range. All right, so that's the
divergence strength in the ES. It's
already into this old range into it's
finding acceptance back into here. That
should look above um crucially above the
900s, I would say. So big big level
there at 900s. Let's have a look at the
spiders.
All right, that gamma level, that huge
level we had last week, never even quite
got down to it. The 70s, it's reclaimed
the 80s. Remember 70s, 75, 80s, and 82s
have all been big level. Now, I assume
will be 85s
on the spy. So, watching to see if we
get reaction there. We have got
liquidity above and then all the way at
90s. Uh, last time I checked, 700 was a
massive level. I very much doubt we do
that in two days, but strange things
have happened, right? Strange of things
have happened. All right, Q's, same
story. All right, we've pivoted back
above again that gamma level uh was
bought up. All right, we couldn't get
through it. So 600 held, reclaimed uh 10
and now 15s and now 20s. So it's on a
flyer. It just depends. Can we get back
into this old range? Remember the thick
old range here, thick balance here. Do
we reject that and find a bid here to
get back in or do we drift in and chop?
Just want to have a quick look at the
VIX. All right, slow drift down.
Remember, the lower we go, the more slow
drift higher we are likely to see. All
right, and we're now sub 15s that is in
uh volatility will be very low if it
stays down here. It just be a slow
grindy kind of session, but we will see.
Let's have a look at the mag.
Okay, failed look down here on Apple.
Range is still above yet to reclaim.
This is like it needs to get back above
76s. All right, so still lower high
break down higher low but hasn't taken
out this 76s. So maybe builds out
liquidity here. If it reclaims 76s,
that's a strong sign that it's been
bought back up. I'm still long Apple
from uh 202s or whatever it was. Um
Amazon,
that's looking much better. All right,
that is looking much better. I'm still
again swinging long Amazon. No reason to
sell yet. There's your double bottom.
There's the hold and they've got a qu
clear clear target, a queer target.
They've got a clear target to aim up for
into the 232s right now. So, if we can
get it going on Amazon, we're going to
try and get upside. If they can hold as
long as they hold dips into sort of 27
26s and 27s, they look good. As long as
they can hold dips. Google again, same
story. Look at that. We talked about
this for a while. Big channel down. All
right,
there's the look below. So, it tried
once, tried again, and then reclaimed,
and now we're drifting upside. And very
similar to this market, needs to get
back in this old range. Can it find
acceptance back into that old range for
a sign of strength?
Meta
again, still just a starter long on this
from 580s. Still not added or sold
anything.
Could argue maybe I should have added,
but we haven't pulled back down into
here yet for me. Um, it's looking pretty
good. I'll be honest with you, that's
looking pretty good. That is I'm long
for 580. So, somewhere around here. All
right. That's a good hold, a good push,
a pullback, which has held that range.
It's probably like a 30 to 50% pullback
and it's question is can they break out.
I was actually looking to see if we come
back down into here for a rebid. So a
two leg but we will see. At the moment
it looks pretty strong. So so far all of
the mag looking pretty good.
Uh gapping up all that uh Microsoft
got here five minutes. Another gap up on
Microsoft right not by a lot but it is
into a two-day balance. All right. So
it's one question here on Microsoft.
We're into a two-day balance, right?
Kind of get out of that balance for a
rebid up. And you can see the level up
here we've got marked out for a break.
And then Nvidia, this is the big one.
This was the big driver last week, uh,
back end of last week, right? We came
down, held this pivot. That's what's
key. That white dotted line, we still
have a price. We broke this, but we
could not flush underneath. We held,
reclaimed, and we've gone right back to
the upside. So, basically, no acceptance
outside of 74. 10 points higher. And if
we zoom out now, it will want to attack
85s and then 91s. All right, so if we
get back above, let's just mark some of
these out because we're going to want to
know if Tesla's
going to go mental today. All right,
let's mark 86s and then 91 break.
All right, can it find acceptance above
those or a drive out above those? If it
does, uh, the squeeze is on. All right,
if it does, the squeeze is on. Until
this point, technically, this is a big
look above and another look above into
range and a look below and fail. And
this can just do this for a little bit.
But if we start breaking through here,
expect some stops to start to be popped.
And then Tesla
still has been very bullish. Uh
just zoom out this minute. Yeah, it's
still holding really well. Um, but you
wonder how much juice it's got left.
Hasn't quite got to those 500s yet,
which is where it wants to go.
Day is this Wednesday. So, we can watch
Wednesday's high and low. All right,
we're trading in a range within that.
Once it breaks out, either side of that,
we will probably either get a breakout
or fail breakout. So, again, I can set
price alerts.
Uh
previous week high breakout and do one
of the low.
Okay.
[snorts] Uh Oracle rebounding. I'm
absolutely gutted it didn't get filled
on that. All right. As soon as it filled
that gap at 78 we talked about for about
a month plus. Uh filled it. Didn't quite
fill me. I mean, I just was looking for
one little wash here to pick me up.
Didn't quite fill me. And uh we've gone
now. So, I don't want to chase that now
cuz it's already
it's already looking good. It's already
20 $20. GH how annoying. But there we
go. It's what happens sometimes. All
right, folks.
That's kind of us. We are ready,
right? Go nice and easy next few days.
I'm already on holiday mode. had a few
drinks at the weekend. Had a big cigar.
Had a gummy last night. All right. I'm
on holiday mode, so it's just nice and
light for the next few sessions. Not
looking to uh do anything stupid. If
there's volume there, if there's some
setups there, we will be playing them.
If not, then we'll just have some fun on
stream and do some giveaways. All right,
we're going to refill this. Oh, already
refilled it. Good news. Uh, good morning
to everyone in stream. Thank you for
joining. Smash that like button nice and
early. All right, let's get up to sort
of 300 plus likes today. We'll do some
giveaways
and just over a minute here till the
open. So, we're going to look to see if
they do that morning drive up and if
they find acceptance or if they sell it.
All right, they find acceptance into
that gray box and the old point of
control, the red box above. Do they sell
it or do they just hold price up there?
If we get the morning flush,
right, then I'm going to look to see if
we wash out any of this sort of trend
line liquidity. Do we come back down
into GlobeEx and previous day high into
this blue blocks or even into previous
day value area high would be fantastic.
But uh it's a long way down. So we will
see. We will see.
Yeah, gold's going. I mean,
[sighs]
it's mad to see that breakout
uh over in the Asian markets
in the yields and we're not really
reacting off it. So, uh I think it might
just be very crowded, but we will see.
Like I said, sometimes these these
things can take a while to play out.
I'm definitely watching move into 930s.
Okay, here's the morning open. Instant
sell.
All of them are green other than Apple,
folks.
Instant sell here. And do they bid this
back up?
We can afford to come a long way down.
Zoom this out.
This
very steep.
Let's see if they come down or not. At
the moment, they're just absorbing the
tape at the lows.
Bit of a choppy start here.
[snorts]
How old am I? I'm 40.
I have a very healthy hairline for my
age. It's uh I don't have the bald gene
clearly. Unfortunately, a lot of my
mates have already lost everything.
It happens. It's called aging. Unless
you want to go to Turkey and get a funny
turkey job.
All right, just chopping around here.
So, very slow open so far.
But uh buyers are trying to come in and
expand this higher. We can go to that
gray box above potentially. There's the
New York open. So tapping into that New
York open at the moment if they want to
get going, but I'd much rather see them
come down and offer some dips this
morning. But maybe that was it and
they're going to look for it. We will
see. Like I said, light volume today.
Not expecting too much. Okay, so here's
the drive towards 800. ES coming up to
an old level of 930. There's liquidity
sat there.
Yeah, absolutely. Yeah, seeing
divergence there. But all of the Mad
Green, I'll give you a readout. Tesla 2
over two and a half% up. Nvidia 1.15%
up. Microsoft over half% up. Meta 1.15%
up. Google 0.17% up. Amazon a third of a
percent up. Apple's trying to go red to
green. It did flutter red to green for a
minute.
And Tesla crossing that alert already.
So that thing is going for it right now
through the 9550s.
So bids holding so far on that New York
open. I just want to let this settle
down. All right. That wasn't a deep
enough pullback for me to get long into.
We didn't get rid of every anything. We
did go wick to wick. Just think. Just
let this settle down, guys. We are we're
gapping up over 200. Well, we've driven
over 200 points with a big gap up. Just
don't really want to buy the highs until
I see a nice retest somewhere.
Am I bullish? I'm I'm bullish if we hold
pullbacks. All right. I'm bullish if we
hold pullbacks. But you got to think,
all right, understand where value is.
This was premium on Friday. This was
premium last week. We're gapping up over
it, which is good. But here's your gap.
All right. Here's what we've done
overnight. I'm not going to buy up
there. I want to see if we come down
into this or even gap fill and bid off
that. Right.
I'm bullish if we can hold pullbacks
into big levels. Otherwise, I'm not
buying all the way up here, right? We
we've talked about this where we are in
the range where we are near supply. What
kind can happen? All right. What can
happen washing out all those players
overnight who've been bidding all night
long and been absolutely fine? Is the
move into VWAP. So, do they bid off VWAP
now is the question.
ES couldn't get through. Can take that
liquidity at the 30s. Pulling back as
well. There's your first bid. Little
minor reaction off VW up so far. Apple,
Amazon, Google, and Microsoft all gone
red on the session here. Can we get back
into previous week high into
670s? This blue box down here. Right.
This is the trend line. I'd like to see
this just crack and come down at this
point and offer us a really good value
buy if if they can bid down here. Right?
I'm not bidding against I'm not just
going to bid against momentum. But if we
come down here and do something like
this, I'm interested. If they don't
don't hold this level, they can come all
the way down here. Previous uh highs gap
fill previous day value area high. We
can come and fill this. Remember this is
all overnight. We can come and do this
and then bid back off. So that would be
either one of these blue blue boxes
would be uh the most ideal location.
[snorts]
Excel coming in here getting himself a
little caught if they reclaim VWAP. This
is going to be interesting little battle
here starting to develop.
Huge delta came in at 704 sellside side
and got themselves caught here. So I'm
interested if they hold reclaims not
otherwise.
Yeah, still not down to its VWAP either.
There's the reclaim of VWAP. So sellers
are stuck on the 705s. Interested in
feathering in here little piece. Another
sellers come in at 27s there. So new
range being developed here at between 27
and 705. If they pop through 27, there's
a potential drift. If they hold uh 704s,
they're just going to keep all 705s are
going to keep going in rotation. I
really want to be a buyer down here.
Let me see. Get this on. There we go.
All right. So, you can see the low
volume load there. So, sellers
protecting that. They are still stuck at
these 704s. Now, they're getting
acceptance lower. Okay. So, my
expectation is that they should drive
down into this blue box. Now, I'm going
to get rid of this because we've broken
it. Here we go. Nice.
[snorts]
Okay, that's getting close to view up as
well. Where's the spiders? Underneath
its view up right now. We're going to
wash out lots of these guys. I want to
see this lower at this point into this
blue box. And then I can think about a
buy if we start to see absorption or
traps. If we don't hold this blue box,
then I'll be watching the next blue box.
Do not expect uh like nice smooth
conditions here this morning. All right,
we're going to come back and test this
seller at 704 705 again by the looks of
it. Can we get back through him or not?
And then do we get back above this 727
pivot?
Man, if they stop short here, it's going
to be a little annoying to size into.
Reclaiming Vpo now. They're going to
test VW up now. Let's see.
They're right on where those big sellers
came in. They're repricing it. Where was
this guy here?
716 710 somewhere around there. That's
that's where the sellers came flying in
on that last little move around that
Vpo.
Get into this blue box. Come on. One of
these two blue boxes are hurt my
interest. [snorts]
How much we got below 660s. So, coming
into some thicker areas here. Yeah,
buyers are they're just front running
this at the moment. They're front
running this level here right now.
I just want to see a wash either. What
I'm looking for is buying opportunities
here. So, some kind of trap down. Either
something like this would be nice or the
same kind of thing down here. So, I
don't want to just like bid against it
because we might just flush. I'm looking
to see if they get trapped down here or
not.
Back to VWAP. ES still hasn't got to V
up. That's one thing to consider.
Where's the VIX right now?
Sub 15 still
and Q's. Yeah, they're coming into that
pin high 1840s to 1760s
on the Q's. So, starting to see some
shorts covering here. Some bids coming
in. Got lots of liquidity here on the
book. You can see it just stacked up.
85s, 80s, 75s, 60s. Come on, flush down
because we need to trap some shorts down
there. You need to break lower first.
Don't bid before you got to be up on the
Yes, please.
Just hanging around these sellers
average that we kept talking about that
big seller that came in at 0405s. Want
him to keep this heavy. It's not that
I'm looking to sell. I just want this to
come a little bit lower and him to get
his exit and maybe some shorts to chase
in an ideal world. Okay, ES has now hit
V up. That's a good sign.
Maybe we can get one more little flush
here to trap some more shorts. If we get
very lucky, we're just in this little
range here
and see developed some volume. If we
start to see acceptance over 28s, then
we can go 50s.
Buyers getting trapped up there on that
last little shaft. Very messy here this
morning in this little range.
[snorts] Apple third of down now. Google
third of down. Microsoft just under
half% down. Rest of the market's green.
A mixed bag here this morning.
[sighs and clears throat]
They're trying to sell this. Another big
seller coming in here at the volume
point of control. Currently on a
session, we're not seeing follow through
downside. So there is some absorption
going on for sure.
Yes, back to VWOP again.
Definite absorption we're seeing here.
Back to VWOP on Q's. All right. Are we
going to start ripping? If we're going
to start breaking out through here, I'm
interested.
The sell is defending that uh low volume
node right now. But if we're going to
start breaking out through it, I'm
interested. I would have rather we got
into this blue box if I'm honest. I'd
rather we get into here first before I
do anything. But I will consider if we
break above and start holding above 28.
Let's call it 30s. I'll consider it.
Otherwise, I'm looking for that move to
previous week high and see if they trap
sellers down there.
Are they going to test previous day
value high? They very well could. Yeah,
this other blue box. So, it's either
this one or this one where I'm
potentially interested in bidding off if
they can trap.
Yes, still absorbing into view up right
now. No break below. Spies under it. Q's
are under it. VIX is trying to sort of
get back towards the 15s right now. It's
not there yet.
Okay, please come into this blue box and
then let's see what happens.
some buying here. 680 675 670 all
stacked up.
Come on.
It might well get it anyhow, but I don't
think it would be huge. If you do get
it, I think it'd be 1020 to any point
little run
unless we get down to previous day value
high, which would be mega. But uh we we
will see.
We will see. Right into this blue box or
close
into this previous week high, this red
line and orange line is GloEx low.
We started to develop some volume up
here now,
which they can lean on.
build those last lot buyers. So, passive
buyers now sat down at 70s and 60s
and we're going to come down for them.
Yep. There we go. Into the 70s. Can they
fill this guy? 70s and 60s. They're not
big. They're not big bids right now.
It's trying to get up to previous day
low. So, we're coming into very
interesting pop points here. It's all
depends if the market is able to trap
around here or not. I would say starting
to find some bids around here. At the
moment, we're probably a little bit
early. Just want to see us flush into
here, trap some shorts, and then if we
can do that, I'll think about going the
other way. Starting to get interesting
here. here. Some shorts just got caught.
Maybe not enough for me. Back to point
of control on the day again.
So this is the box right here. Above
this there is squeeze potential right
above this. There's squeeze potential.
And this is the blue box of interest.
Here we go. Bidding in. So 705s is that
same level where that huge seller came
in earlier. They don't defend that. We
will start squeezing. We got to watch
these VWAPs here as well.
that big big seller at 705.
Don't like the bottom of this auction.
I'm going to be honest
to bid off. Not yet.
There's a buyer down there. I want to
see a big seller down there being
absorbed. Not a big buyer, but we will
see.
Tricky, tricky. Might just be the lack
of volume today.
It's five minute
little look. See, one minute until the
opening range is set, folks.
Yeah, I don't like the bottom of this
auction. It might well hold, but I don't
love the way it looks at the moment at
the low of this auction. There's not
enough sellers caught down here for me.
Not yet. But uh if we start moving away
from this gray box to the upside, then
I'm going to have to be willing to do
something.
There's point of control is gray box.
Are they going to start breaking
through? Here's VWAP.
Big buyers coming in here. They're being
absorbed right now by seller still. So
this 705 is still the level there or
thereabouts where that huge seller came
in earlier about I don't know what
candle was that 9:36 this morning that I
called out. That's still the level. 936
and then 926 still being defended. Still
waiting here.
Still just don't like the low of the
auction right now. There's not enough
sellers caught that low of auction for
me at the moment. It's the only thing
stopping me doing much else.
If we had lots of sellers down here, I'd
be more inclined to think that this is
going to bid back up. But at the moment,
don't see that many. There is a bid
starting to come onto the tape, though.
He's moved from 70 to 80 to 90. He's
going to get filled at 90 here. There we
go. He just got filled
and he's reloaded at 87s
and at 85s. He's trying to soak the soak
it all up here on the bid. There you go.
He's coming again.
There's a bid here for sure. There's a
bid here. Yes. Still holding V up. This
might start going. I'm want to wait to
see if we can get above this gray level
cuz at the moment I know that that big
seller keeps coming back in there at
05s.
There he is again. That seller at 05. So
we've got someone bidding the tape up
and we've got a seller at 05. So, we've
got two two-sided tape at the moment.
They're stuck between each other. Not
one of them is winning.
Value very high in this se session now.
720 actually on the day somewhere up
here.
[snorts] We're just stuck in value.
There we go. Going to test 705s again.
I'm ready. I'm ready. If we're going to
go, I want to get in. If we're gonna go,
I want to be part of this. Watching this
New York view up here.
Passive selling up here again. Oh, I
don't like what I'm seeing. This is uh
iffy iffy iffy tape.
Iffy tape. Big buyers coming in here.
Can they see any aggression? No. Still
passive seller up here. So, still no
close and hold above gray box. They're
going to trade back into it. Maybe if
they bid off PC.
I try a little piece here. It's the
question.
at the bottom of that auction right now.
That dip held. Okay,
that dip held.
It just held 05s held PC's.
There they go.
Do they hold 05s again? What was that
point of control now? 97s.
If this next dip in starts to hold, I'll
consider it long.
It's not an A+ setup. I'm considering
this. They're starting to see a bid
here. They're bidding all the way down
to say 700 at the moment.
ES is trapped between the two VWs. Here
we go. Right. Small size. Then here we
go. Let's see if we can return up
through value. seller coming on here.
He's probably going to get squeezed out
to 45s now.
Come on, buyers. Stops already moving
up. I don't like this tape.
[laughter] How aggressive do I get when
I stop here? We should come and feel an
imbalance here. 37 and 45. I'm going
want to partial out into that. There's
35. Can we get a bit higher into 37 38?
You going to miss me?
like to see a bid move higher than 10
here. It's just sat at 10. Don't like
that. Do not like him sat there at 10.
He's got to move up.
I need ES to get back through New York
view up. That's better. Come on. Get
back through. Help us out here. If we
don't get acceptance over value high,
it's going to be a problem. We need to
move value up on the day, which is
currently at 21.
I'm going to fill this guy at 10 because
he hasn't walked up. They're going to
fill the guy at 10. All right,
small piece for that.
There's two guys having fun today by the
looks of it.
They are holding that 10. Well, they
didn't even fill him yet. He's reloaded
here in 15s now.
Mate, if you're going to send it, can
you please start walking up? Can you do
not just sit still because you're going
to make it impossible to trade if you're
just going to sit still like this all
day.
Walk up, mate. Get involved if you're
going to do it. Otherwise, just [\h__\h]
off.
Okay, rotation's 20 to 10 now. Now it's
20. Now we might go 38 through this
imbalance. Come on, mate.
Come on.
I want to see them lift this into 38 and
45s. I do do not want to see this come
back into the range at this point.
They've had enough fafing here. They
should just lift it into 38 and 45s if
they're going to do it. Big if
we're getting stuck up here. Back into
range we go. Is this guy at 10? Has
he left now? He got filled or not?
Back to gray box. [sighs] Do they hold
gray box for a bid? I'll still consider
this if they hold gray box on a bid. If
they lose it, then we're going to go
back into the blue box below because the
end the bottom of the auction is not
that great. All right, we're holding
gray box. That's a good sign. We got to
bid through this now. We got to go 38s.
And here we go. All right, come on then.
Come on then. Go, go, go, go, go, go,
go, go, go. Let's go. Finally, you've
turned up, mate. Finally.
All right, beautiful. Into these
imbalances. So, I'm going to partial
some out here into 40 and 45s.
I want to be careful. So, we're just
playing this imbalance. You can see how
thin we got here. And if we get
acceptance through 55s, we can think
about higher day, but we're already
taking some off. ES into New York open.
What a tricky bugger. this, but it's
it's actually not a seller on the tape
that's being a pain. It's actually the
buyer
when he should show that impetus and go.
He's he's he's pulling his bids lower
instead of chasing up. So, I want to be
a little bit careful. I've already
partialed some out into these 45s. Now,
that gray box held though. All right.
So, we flipped this gray box. We came
into the blue. This wasn't the best low
of auction. Going to be honest. I would
have liked to seen more sellers trapped
down there. Got above gray. Hell gray
into this imbalance. All right. We're
selling most of our money now. And let's
see if we can get up into this for an
extension today. But the move was highly
probable to come and fill this once we
held this. I don't know what happens
now, folks. It depends on this guy on
the tape if he wants to play ball. Mag's
looking good. Microsoft and Apple red.
The rest of the mag green now. How much
aggression have they got? Probably not a
lot in a holiday week, but uh there we
go.
left without you, Raph. Yeah, it was
tricky. It was tricky. I almost cut it
the second time round. I'll be honest. I
was had my stop just under PC. Okay,
I'll cut this if it can't hold. I didn't
read add heavy because I don't like this
buy on the tape. You can see now like
he's juggling. Don't like what he's
doing.
When I say he's juggling, what I mean is
he puts a firm level in and when he
should move up and support the bid, he's
actually moving down and then when it
comes down, then he's getting aggressive
and then he's pulling and then he's
getting aggressive. So, he's like moving
in and out pretty quickly rather than
putting his flag in the ground and
saying, "Hey, I'm holding this and I'm
going to start bidding above this
aggressively to get to where I want to
go." He's not I'm not seeing that kind
of aggression. And the one thing I'd say
the low of day I it's not shorts trapped
at the low of day right we've got shorts
trapped from sort of 97 to 92 and then a
little bit at 703 but a low of the day
it's very they are there but it's very
light you know from 75 to 72 it's light
you can see the transition in tape but
it's not like we we've got a lot caught
down there is the only
>> [snorts]
[sighs]
>> But hey, even if you took gray box,
maybe some of you feathered it blue, but
even if you took this here, it's not
huge, but you know, it's 30, 40 points
to start the day on a light week. Here
we go. Can we see any more upside?
Can you guys get back through to the
upside? Can you get back over the New
York open?
There's uh the last big seller above us
was at 760. So just be careful in case
he reloads at 760. [snorts]
Here we go. All right, let's see if we
can get to 60 and then through that
we're going to see if we can get to 80.
And then through that, we're going to
see if we can get a high day.
Like I said, wanted to be bullish today
on dips. Blue box was the area. Didn't
love the end of the auction down there.
It's a shame we didn't dip a little bit
lower, but there we go.
We look good here. Buyers just got
caught in that last little push. I want
to see push through now because they all
know there's a big seller who's been up
there at 60. Buyers just got a little
bit stuck here at 50s. Come on. You got
to reload and push 60. Come on. Come on.
Don't get stuck up here.
I need to see acceleration. I need to
see it now into this 60, please. And
then get through to 80s. They're
reloading 60s, these sellers. Okay, so
60 is definitely a level. We got to get
back over 60s now. Definitely a level.
We got to get over 60s up into 80s. ES
looking good. And once we do that, we
can look for this New York open 80s and
then high of day. Battle here though.
Definitely sellers coming in in front of
60s right now. I think if we get through
that there's a squeeze otherwise there
there's a pullback due here into this
probably into this kind of shelf here
into 30s. So we got to try and get
through 60s basically here there was a
big seller. All right when we broke down
from here he's still here at the moment
being protected. So maybe this happens
maybe they squeeze through. So I'm still
bullish.
I don't want them to pull back too far.
Just I'd love a rip. I would just love a
straight rip. But at the moment, I'd say
buyers over 54s keep getting stuck.
We might need a pullback here
and then see if they reabsorb the
pullback that comes.
You'd really want pullbacks to hold 30s.
Wouldn't want it under 30s.
Nice. Pass pasta on this.
Congratulations.
Here we come. Can we hold ideally 30s?
That kind of level. We've got a pretty
good shelf here around there. Somewhere
around here would be good for a
pullback. We just need to be careful
because if they sell back under here,
right? If they do something like this,
I'd become uninterested, especially
because of this low of day is not the
best low of day I've ever seen.
If I was a seller, I'd be reselling
this.
If I was a seller, I would be trying to
resell this in fairness. I think about
how we opened, flush, built liquidity,
but I think there's a chance to move
higher today. So, that's why I'm trying
to play that side rather than the
counter trend at the moment. Here they
go. So, I'm going to test these buyers
at 50. What was that level? 54s. They
keep getting trapped at 54s. If we get
over 54s, we should go 60s. We get over
60s, we go 80s. We get over 80s, we go
high day. And then we can think about
this gray box above, right? Just manage
manage the trade that you're currently
in. You should be sort of managing this
trade right now. Again, I don't think
you want it back below 30s, 25s and 30s.
You don't want it back into there. You
need to see them absorb that level.
Nice. I think we're going to go here. ES
is starting to try and go. It's got to
get through 25s.
Where are we looking on the ETFs? Got to
watch 85 here on the spiders. It's
probably a gamma level. His
buy is juggling up here again.
That's his fault cuz he didn't support
40s.
[snorts]
Yep. Still managing the trade at the
moment, but down to tiny size, right?
Down to tiny size. Still managing the
trade. [snorts]
But I'm going to need to see them hold
here into these 30s otherwise I'm out
because the only thing I'd say I'm not
convinced the lower day is in. It might
it might be but I don't like what I saw
at this lower day. There's not enough
selling down here with excess at the
moment. I would have liked to see them
poke into this and leave excess but I'm
still going to manage this trade because
it wants to move higher. I will still
sit in it. But we've got to we've got to
come and break uh 54s here. It's where
the buyers keep getting trapped. We
break that, we go 60s, we break that, we
should we should really get up towards
the highs at that point. So it's 55
where these buyers keep getting stuck.
We want to see acceleration through here
in 60 now.
Come on, Mr. Tape.
Keep getting caught at these 55s. We're
going to have another go at 55s. Passive
selling up here between 55 and 60.
Buyers are trying. And they are
attempting. They just need one big
squeeze out here. You need to see
someone massive just step on the book.
They're having another go. So you can
see 5455. They keep getting stuck.
Passive seller still reloading up there.
He's still reloading. Passive seller up
here. So these buyers keep getting
caught up here. The longer we're caught
up here without moving higher will be a
problem. We've developed another little
shelf here into 50 now as well.
And we have an imbalance all the way
down to 37 which I'm also aware of. We
might need to come and fill.
Don't like what I'm seeing here. These
buyers got to step in and step in soon.
They're having another go up here. Are
they into these 55s and 60s again? Can
we see acceleration through 55s and 60s?
Getting ready to sell if we can't
because there's a refresh seller up here
into 55 again.
Can't keep getting trapped up here
without a move higher. We will get
stuck. If they keep getting trapped up
here without that acceleration, we're
going to get stuck.
There's the cell starting to get sucked.
So, into this imbalance, this imbalance
is down to 37s. If they don't absorb 30s
amounts, like I said, if they don't
absorb around 30's amount, here's the
cell. Here's the last chance for them to
absorb. Otherwise, I'm out.
Back to view up on New York. View up on
the S and the spiders. Now and ever. Now
and ever. I'm out. Don't like what I'm
seeing. Cut. There we go. They have the
chance. Can always get back in. Can
always get back in.
So all that was was buyers getting stuck
up here. That 55s and 60s. I kept
talking about 60s was the level we built
this sort of shelf out. 60 was the old
level where there was a big seller right
where we broke down from and they kept
trying. These buyers kept trying up
here. This is what we didn't see up
here. Buyers kept trying up here failed.
So, we've returned back in. Might come
all the way down now. So, flat on this
now and now we just wait.
The only thing I'd say the low of day,
like I said, doesn't feel uh
don't feel too good to me.
Don't think there's much excess down
there.
Just want to have a quick look at the
mag here. What's going on?
Video active view up.
cell. Looks good. Google not too good.
Not too good.
Good.
I can't fill that. That looks bad. Okay.
Mix bag out there right now.
All
right, view up holding there.
I'd say more buyers got stuck at this uh
little pivot high we've had than sellers
at the low. So,
we might just get stuck here for a
while.
Yeah, I'm try. Yeah, sorry. I just see
your message there. Yes, I execute on
Ninja Trader, right? Excute on Ninja
Trader. Maybe you're new to the channel.
I don't execute on Trading View, but I
can't teach on Ninja Trader. The drawing
tools are nowhere near as good and I
can't flick around through the ETFs or
through the uh stocks on Ninja Trader.
All right, so we are holding VW up.
We're going to come and test value area
high probably around 30 35. That was the
overunder before on the way down. So the
question is, can they uh reclaim that or
not?
Would I consider entering a buy again?
Yeah, if it I consider doing anything if
it sets up. But right now, you know,
what do we have? Buyers caught the
highest. Could we find acceptance back
into here? No. So, what are we doing?
Buyers caught rotation. Maybe they come
and resell this. Do I like this low of
day? Like I said, no. I don't think it's
a good low of day. So, I'm not going to
bid on this in the midpoint of the
range. If I see sellers come in here and
get stuck, then we can think about it.
You know, we're not going to buy for no
reason. Look at the flow zones. They're
all flattened. They have the chance to
hold and absorb. They had the chance to
hold the upside of this and absorb.
They're not doing it right. So, no
random setups. We trade actual setups.
There's no setup right now to trade.
And we couldn't even get up to the New
York open. So weakness actually in the
cues. Actual weakness. And I wouldn't be
surprised if they put in a new low of
day because that low of day, like I
said, I don't like the low of the
auction. It doesn't look very good to me
down there, which is why I wasn't like
heavy heavy in size this morning.
Point control going to be tested here.
And if they get under that, probably a
new low day, but we will see.
Micro shelf here at 20s again.
Oh, might be a tough few days if they're
going to do this with these like
stacking these bids and then pulling
them. But we will see.
We thought it would be light. So, we're
getting what we expected.
That 30 level is big old level right
now.
It's where the buyers just got stuck
because they had the chance to hold it
on the dip back in and they didn't. So,
sell side is basically from 15 down to
94s. Buy side is basically from 20s up
to 33s. So,
we're right in the middle of that
balance now.
Look at this buying on the tape. It's
awful. It's awful what they're doing.
They're [\h__\h] about this morning.
[snorts]
They are [\h__\h] around.
You're only looking for a previous day
value area high test. I mean, it would
be a great level to bid off if we get
there. be fantastic level to bid off at
if we get there. But uh at the moment,
you know, you're going to have to need
it to get under previous week close,
previous day close. GlobeEx,
it's quite it's quite a big ask at the
moment, but you know, maybe if we start
getting stuck.
Oh, don't do that. Maybe you get it. You
know, if we start getting stuck down
here and too many pile in, maybe you get
something like that. I mean, that would
be a great area to bid off. I'm with I'm
with you. It's why it's highlighted, but
I'm not convinced we get down there if
I'm honest. It would be great if we did.
Be great if we did, but the mag's
holding up well. It's a good It's a good
gap up. We're into like a volume week.
You just wonder like are there going to
be any bears to sell it down that far?
It' be nice if there was. I would love
to bid back off there with you as well.
It's why it's highlighted. It's
definitely a level of interest.
>> [clears throat]
>> back to these 30s probably towards these
30s where these buyers have been getting
stuck. We if we reclaim that we're going
to go. So, it's just it's a little bit
messy at the moment on the tape. Right.
The tape is a little bit messy.
Yeah, look at these buyers down below
like pulling constantly, mate.
Puts me off trading when it's like this,
honestly.
Test these 30s and 35s again. Are they?
I still hear these sellers. They're
stacked against where those buyers are
caught. So, I think two things have
happened today. We passively sold uh 45s
and above. We're now passively selling
25s and above. There are buyers on the
tape, but they keep pulling their
orders. So, they're filling lower and
lower because they're just yanking their
orders, running away right now. So,
sellers, I'd say, at the moment, um
since this little pivot, are in control.
The buyers are the ones that got stuck
up here. and buyers got stuck up here.
And so until we reclaim those levels, I
don't think there's much to do.
I don't think there's much to do here.
The range isn't that big either, folks.
Smaller range today as expected.
Back to these sevens. Look at all these
buyers down below. Keep they keep
pulling and then uh moving down. So 700
95 90s 82s right now.
And the upside again 20s and 30s is
what's key on the upside. That's where
the battle is. So you got sort of buyers
stuck. Show you on it. Probably get it
up on here. Maybe you get lucky.
All right. So we can see these buyers
kept trying up in around here. They got
stuck. They just tried again here. So
buyers got stuck here. These guys tried
again here. Got stuck again. The problem
I don't like, I don't think there's
enough excess down here. There could be,
but for me that's pretty small excess
wise.
Back into this gray box, which can
probably be removed right now to be
honest. We've moved it up a little bit.
[snorts]
stuck between New York VW up and 24-hour
view up on the ES.
We are not stuck between those on the
cues, but we are on the ES
seller up now trying to defend 20.
seller from 20 just moved to 10.
Market slowed right down.
Oh, we're going to make a new low.
Probably should.
Probably [snorts]
should.
Uh, I can see a few of you have emailed
me. Um,
what's this about? I'll get back to you
as long as it's not urgent,
Gonzalo. I'll get back to you as soon as
we finish the stream. Okay, here we go.
So, maybe a new low now. Like we said,
it wouldn't surprise me. That lower day
was not particularly good. like we
talked about early in the morning.
[cough]
Can still taste
cigars on my breath two days ago now.
[snorts]
[laughter]
Uh well, it's a third party, so I can't
can't really share it on a third party.
Um
I'm using uh what's this thing called? I
always forget what it's called. using
city footprint.
Scrub my tongue. Yeah, trust me. I have
I enjoy I like I enjoyed it, but uh I
always felt awful like a few days after.
All right, back into here. If we fail
this previous week high here in GlobeEx
then maybe I can't remember who said
that they're looking to bid previous day
value area high possible.
Can't rule it out. Cannot rule it out.
New lower day made on uh ES. By the way,
we're going to bid off this now.
And it' be dirty if they do this without
a sweep underneath. It will be not very
nice.
[clears throat]
sellers coming back in there at 92s. I'm
just waiting now at this point.
Arguably could have flipped short here
when I said those buyers were getting
stuck. But uh I just want to focus on
the longs either from here or here. So
that's uh what I'm trying to do at the
moment is just remain focused on the
side of the market I'm looking for.
Short was clean. Yeah, it was clean once
they got stuck up there. It was it was
clean up there. I'm not going to argue
with that. Even here once they started
reloading. I just don't want to flip my
bias when No, I'm up. Nice. Been looking
for one clean thing. I'm going to stay
looking for that all the time. We're
above value. We are starting to expand
value area low. So, you know, if you are
short, if you took where the buyers were
trapped or faded this back in, your
cover points are now and then down here.
It very might well might keep going for
you, which would be great.
It's just not the trade I'm looking for
today. But it looks pretty good. These
buyers up here are the ones that got
caught here in what did we say? 30s.
Those are the two levels
right now where they definitely got
caught. They're in 30s.
So, previous week high coming up here.
This blue box.
They bid off this low again.
How are they not going to take out this
load? Come on, market. Surely you going
to take out this load. There's not that
much excess down here at all.
a little bit, but uh you'd like to see
nice strong sellers call if you're going
to think about long. I'm not seeing
that. I haven't seen that all morning
down here.
And they held. They're going to come
back for point control check. Here's
point control check right now.
Oh,
[sighs]
so sorry folks on the trading view it's
not moved as quick but P I have PC here
right now 97s. Okay, that's why I just
said that. if you like. I can't see
that. It's just cuz it's different on
Ninja Trader is moving quicker based on
tick data. [snorts]
97s.
Spiders running a beard, man.
Messy messy. We expect this this sort of
time of year, though. I'm still not
convinced. Lower days in. There is there
are some sellers stuck down there, but
it's so light. Um, but we keep tapping
into this PC. I would like to see one
more flush lower first.
Yes, GG. I I do agree with you there.
If PC check again here and if they lift
through this, they're probably going to
check VWAP. And if they lift through
that, they're going to check value.
This is where the sellers last came in.
705. So 705. 715s is where the big
sellers come in. Buyers are sort of
stuck from 7:15 to 7:30. So if that gets
refreshed on the sell side, we might
break lower.
All right. So basically, what am I
trying to say? I can draw it out for you
here. Sellers came in 7:15 to 7:30.
7:15. So buyers came in here and
couldn't hold, right? They kept trying
to fight here. So buyers are stuck here
and here. So all the time they sell
against this, we can break lower. I
don't think there's enough excess down
here still. So, I'm going to repeat that
structure-wise. Buyers got caught.
There's your lower low. You know, maybe
we get one of these I'll be interested
in. Maybe we do that here. I'll be
interested in. If we go back in here, I
won't be interested in anything at all.
We're trying to lead long bias because
we're gapping up over value. I just
didn't want to buy up here. It's too uh
too close to that two week balance
range. But I'm interested here and here
as the levels
for anyone joining a bit later.
Okay, so they're still defending point
control. Sellers still attacking this.
I'll give you a little readout on the
map. Tesla 1.21% up. Nvidia 1.14% up.
Meta 1% up. Amazon just about green. And
then you've got Microsoft 0.22% down.
Google 0.15% down. Apple 0.58% down.
So, let's get starting to build at these
lows without breaking lower. All right.
I want to see a break lower be absorbed.
That's what I would would like to see.
There is some absorption down here from
buyers, but I'd actually like to see
just a little break lower and it be
absorbed. But we just had a big lock
come flying on the tape here sell side.
And again here. Who's this guy?
115 lots. So they're defending. What's
his average here? 87s,
84s, and he's going to try again here at
90s. And if he doesn't get his way,
we're going to lift to 700 and go point
of control. There we go. Lifting to 700.
He's not getting his way. So was
aggressive selling down there being
absorbed on the tape. So we're starting
to see some bulls try and absorb the
tape at these lows right now. So perking
my interest as we go back to point of
control. I'm watching to see if we go up
to 15s now.
So, I'd say 15s to 30s is the level
where buyers got trapped. Right. 15s to
30s is the level that sellers will need
to defend. So, it might be a rotation
from here to there. It's not a lot, is
it? It's like 15 to 30 points, but
that's the rotation at the moment. Well,
at the moment, we're just sat at P at
these 700s. There's a micro shelf at
705. So if we go through 705s, I think
we probably get 1520s and then through
their 30s. But we can still build this
out and roll. But right now, there are
sellers down here who are caught
underneath. What was this guy's level?
87s.
Okay, here we go.
All right, so let's see then. Let's see
then, folks.
attacking this long now
into these 30s. 15s to 30s is where
sellers will want to defend. If they
can't defend that, we will rotate
aggressively higher. Taking some profit
here
from PC. It's only a 15 point trade.
Let's see if we can get back above 20s
and 30s. And I'll reload if we can.
Lots of sellers stacking up here. So, we
know 15 to 30s is where the buyers got
stuck. So this is where sellers, you can
see them on the tape are trying to
defend, right? We just went over this.
If we get back above that squeeze is on.
This is where strong selling came in now
and where buyers got trapped is just
above up to 30. So sellers need to
defend this level here. It's why I've
taken profit here.
Let's
see if they resupport the bid at 700.
It' be a good sign if we support the bid
at 7 or above seven here. It' be a good
sign that we're going to leave those
sellers on that last leg trapped at the
lows. They got to support PC, which is
basically 700.
Otherwise, I'll probably cut Slow
[clears throat]
day today.
Are they going to support the bid here?
There's P check coming up here into
sevens. There's the P check.
And do they hold this or not now is the
question. If not, we go back down to
lower day. If we get absorption here,
then they got a break back above 15s.
Bu's just left. Now the book's thinned
out.
What is going on?
Anyone want to play today at all or is
volume just going to completely
dissipate at this point?
There's literally no bid now on my book.
It's like completely gone to sleep.
Very slow. Yeah, very slow. It's okay
though.
It's easy to read because it's slow. I
just don't get what this buyer is doing.
This guy here, I don't know if you can
see where my mouse is. It keeps coming
on and off, on and off, on and off, on
and off all morning. Okay, no bid then.
So back down to value area low on the
day which is 82s. That's where the
sellers last got stuck is there and
under. They just got stuck again there
at 89s.
The rotations are so small here folks is
why I'm not trying to read too much.
Relative weakness is uh
is also on cues today. Be aware of that.
Eval pass. Not bad for a slow holiday.
Yeah. Nice for a slow Monday. Nice work.
Nice work.
We're just in rotation now. So if you
look at today, all right, this is value
for this current session. We can't get
above. We're not getting below. If we
look at previous day, we were down here.
All right, so we're gapping up. We're
holding a key level. If we break this
key level, we're going to come down into
here or unless we do a look below and
reclaim. Right? So I want to be bullish
because we're gapping up. I don't want
to be bullish here. I want to be bullish
on this pullback either into here or to
here. If we lose this, then we're going
to rotation. Technically, you could be
bearish in that rotation. I'm not going
to be not not on a holiday volume all
the time. I'm holding this. I'd rather
think about bullish moves. I know flow
zones are flat to negative, which is why
got to be bit careful in the rotation.
So, PC reclaimed again 700. They're
going to have another attempt here. So,
this is a higher low. This is a fail
break lower here from bears, right? They
just failed to break lower. We have to
say what we're seeing here. Bears failed
to break lower. They're now stuck. We're
probably going to come and test 715s,
720, 730. 730s is the level. Uh 715s to
730s is where buyers last got stuck. If
we get through there, then I expect the
market to lift.
Watching this now.
Nice from ES. Relative strength there.
Can the cues join in? So 7:15 to 7:30 is
where those buyers kept getting stuck.
Is my wife going to wake up and make me
a coffee today? That's the That's the
other question.
I might have to wake up in a bit. She's
got work.
Poor woman's very tired right now. All
right. 700 recheck again for point of
control. Do they hold this or not?
Market does not know what it wants to
do. Stuck between two very small ranges
here. Good hold there. Right, they got
to break back above 15s.
ES can't get it back above its New York
open right now.
I want to do a couple giveaways this
week. So, make sure you smash that like
button. Let's get those likes right up.
Testing, testing, testing, testing,
testing these 715s. Can we lift into
these 715s? And then how do we act into
30? Here we go. Here we go.
Can you lift through these 15s? Still a
passive seller here on the book here in
20 and 25. He's still sat there. I want
to see him filled and move. [snorts]
ES testing New York open. That's going
to be key. If ES starts busting through
New York open, dragging the market up,
maybe we get going.
Can't get through these 15s right now.
Are there any limits? What do you mean?
Vicks to 10. VIX ain't going to 10,
mate.
The market would never move ever if the
VIX went to 10. We've got too much news
right now circulating the world for VIX
to ever go to 10.
Oh,
this market's stuck. Market is stuck.
Can't get above V up. Can't break below
previous week high. It is stuck.
Stuck in like 30 point range.
Apple selling. Rest of rest of the
market's looking all right. Apple is uh
dragging this market down right now.
Weakest one today, 0.76%
down, followed by Microsoft, a third of
a percent down.
Amazon's gone green. Google's gone
green. Meta's now 0.77% up. Nvidia 1.41%
up. Tesla 1.50% up. Oracle 2.76% up. AMD
third of up. AVGO flat on the day. sort
of uh these gamma exposure, beta names
all look good. OCR 2% up, PayPal's up,
Bull's up, NEO's up, IBIT's up, N's up,
all those sort of AI exposure names.
OQ's up, MBTS is up, RTI is up.
It's just that we're stuck.
Up 500 today, shorting Tesla. I wish I
went full size, but hey, this week's
important to be cautious. Yeah, very
important to be cautious this week.
RTY has had a boost, hasn't it? So, that
rotation into small cap still there then
1.28% up and ES is going to have another
go here at breaking out through New York
open.
So, ES, it's a weird one. It made a
lower low today and it's now trying to
bust through New York open. So basically
ES has done this this swept and this is
right back up here and it's trying to
bust through this pivot which is next to
this. It cannot get through that New
York open right now on ES. That's its
big problem.
[sighs]
Sorry. Market's not moving, so I'm just
tired and still. No, no position now.
Certainly not. Nothing to do here, man.
Nothing to do. We're just trading in
here. All right. Until we get back above
this level, even that's a bit dangerous
now. But if we get bid above this,
especially if ES gets above New York
open, potentially be interested, but I'm
not bidding against this. No way. No
way. not going to c get caught in a
mess.
And a book's slow. Like if you're
watching the book, like there's guys
pulling orders or I reckon there's one
buyer being a bit of a knob today. And
and sellers, you would say like from
this pivot, if we think about what we
saw this morning, this is where buyers
got stuck and the next level they got
stuck at was 20s or 15s to 30s. All
right, so this is supply right now here
and here. So until we get back above
that or unless we wash and trap sellers
at the lows, right, those are our only
long opportunities. Either we get above
or we trap lower. Otherwise,
not really much we can do.
Yes, having another go at that New York
open.
It's through it now. Now, can it close
above and can it sweep out all that
liquidity? No is the answer right now.
Poked through it and got smacked.
Yeah, the volume's get guys, the
volume's going to be,
we did talk about this, volume's going
to be very low today, even lower
tomorrow. I didn't, like I said at the
beginning of stream, maybe we get a
trade, maybe we don't. If we don't, we
can just do some education and giveaways
the next few days. All right, I'll be
here no matter what. But don't be
forcing, right, on a low volume day.
There's the break. Okay. Can we actually
do something now? Then
sellers are getting caught here but
still it looks like we want to move
lower be honest looks like we want to
move lower at the moment first ES is
doing so well by comparison right we
caught some shorts there 74 down to 68 I
need I'm going to give this a bit more
time to figure itself out definitely
caught some shorts there
but they keep stacking these bids lower
we just got to Wait and see.
I said those shorts have been in control
so far this morning.
I should also tell you because they did
message me this morning. There is a new
sale on on funded next.
Uh
what is it here? 100k. Get 100k uh
account now for the price of a 50k. All
right. So, a legacy account $149 right
now. Um ends December 26th with code FCT
for those of you who are interested
on funded next. It is in my top five
prop firms for 2026.
You might have seen that video went out
at the weekend telling you which ones
I'm going to trade and why and which
ones might be good for you.
more shorts. Got trapped down here
again, but I'm still not convinced yet.
So low on volume, it's hard to be
convinced of anything right now, I
think.
[cough]
Huh?
Where's that delta 80s?
Hi, I passed 20 Apex. Hi, I passed 20
Apex accounts. Tomorrow I get P account.
Any advice for me? Yeah, leave it alone.
If you're just passing 20 p getting 20p
accounts, don't be using tomorrow as
your first day. Or if you really want to
get a micro and flip it so you have a
trading day, but don't
don't do probably one of the lowest
volume days of the year as your first
day to trade.
I mean top set funded, but definitely
think about funded yet next year. Have a
look on my video that I posted over the
weekend. I talk about which one's good
and why here. Stick it in the chat for
you guys
if Trading View is going to wake up.
Come on, YouTube.
Oh my god. My computer about to crash?
Feels like it.
Okay, breaking lower. So, let's watch
here. Watching to see if they trap here
or if we're going to move down to value.
Are we going to close the gap? Lots of
selling coming in here now.
So, 40s is a big bid. 60s, 50s, and 40s.
Vick's finding a bit of a bid here.
This is GlobeEx right here into 53 and
then we go
next level will be 30s.
Okay, I should mark this out. This was
Sunday open. Important to mark out. So
gap is in here.
Those gaps there.
Here's GloEx.
What's this level? 35s. Sorry, almost
forgot there. So gap fill is possible or
maybe just top of the gap. We're about
to find out.
And whoever was waiting for value area,
you might get it. You might just be
about to get it.
You might just be about to get it. Into
the gap. Thank you.
Into the gap we go.
Lots of shorts have come flying in here.
Just tapped into that gap.
tapped into that gap.
Are we going to go for the fill and
previous day value very high? Yes,
breaking lower now. A little bit messy
out here. Look at the mag. Apple,
Amazon, Google, Microsoft, all just
flipped red.
Just waiting now to see are we going to
come down here or we going to do a
reclaim. And if we come down here and we
don't hold, then I'm not going to trade.
I don't want to trade in previous days
value.
Not on light volume. Too risky playing
rotation.
Going
to test 50s here. If they get through
50s, I'm going to squeeze to 60 is where
the sellers last came.
Watching
on any reclaims here. Here's Globeex
test.
Uh I execute on a one minute but I don't
like strictly trade off a one minute
like these levels are are big daily and
hourly levels. I execute lower time
frame once I see participants trapped at
a level of interest for me.
[clears throat] I open a reverse
position on Apex for only a few seconds
by mistake. Will this harm my account in
the funded? Uh as long as you closed it
quick enough, you you'd be fine.
As long as you didn't hold on to it. W
on the short. Yeah, nice. Uh Henrik, did
you take it from up here or here? One of
these two. It's nice. You might want to
hold a runner in case you get into this
this gap to be quite honest.
I mean,
is it
I wouldn't I wouldn't say that's really
going or that really going. I wouldn't
say that's really going. Hasn't
reclaimed anything. It's in a downtrend
off the morning open.
I don't know what really going means on
Bitcoin to you, but I I wouldn't look
that and saying it's really doing
anything.
Okay,
shorts currently came in at these lows
at 40. I'm watching previous week high
to see if we start getting back above
that and back into value area low on the
session. So, do we start going do we do
a initial balance break into gap and
reclaim or are we going to resell these
levels? All right. So, the trades I'm
again, I'm not going to focus on the
short. It might very well play out back
down to here. I'm going to either look
for this
or something like this. Those are the
only two things I'm looking at today on
low volume. I don't I don't want to
touch anything else.
Really nice. Nice work, Tyson. What did
you play? The IB break.
IB breakdown.
Yes, already in back inside it I beach
trying to reclaim Globeex. Not there
yet.
[snorts]
>> [laughter]
>> Let's see. Let's see.
Sellers came in again at the low of this
candle. Sellers really need this back
below 40. If buyers start reclaiming 50,
there's probably a little move up to 75.
But sellers need this back below 40
because they've come in sellside heavy
under 40 right now.
It just feels so like slow.
I've been trading 17 years. You're one
of the best live streams I've landed on.
You're intelligent, responsible, and
seem to really know how the market
moves. Oh, thank you.
Thank you. Thank you. What's the
difference between futures and CFDs?
Futures are regulated. They're on a
central exchange. CFDs is a well argue
it's a regulated market but it's not in
a central exchange so that they can
do whatever they want in terms of
liquidity and your stops.
You'll notice all those big YouTubers
who make millions of dollars trade on
CFDs because they're not [\h__\h] trading
bollocks.
Very very easy to uh lie and manipulate
on CFDs. Here
we see. Okay, so they're starting to try
and go for the reclaim. Watching IB now.
Can we get going back through value?
Lots of buyers have come in here.
They're going to look for 80s if they
can get up there or 77ish.
And if we get inside that, this will be
a look below in fail. But I wouldn't
bank on that.
Not yet.
ES to VWAP already. Jesus Christ.
Big divergence between all these
watching value area low here into 675s
and do bears come in and reject that
would be my question I would be posing
at the moment.
and right into 75 here.
If we get acceptance back inside,
initial balance, then the IB2V up trade
is possible. I'd be watching this node
here at 92,
right? So, if we're going to trade
upside, I'd be watching this and this.
If they find acceptance, otherwise back
downside, we will come. Buyers keep
attempting up here and getting a little
bit caught up here at the highs right
now. So, I'm going to wait a little bit
longer. It's good defense from bears
there. So I'd say buyers now they need
to hold above 50s and definitely above
40s.
Big divergence to ES.
Big big divergence to ES here which is
all the way back at VWAP. So we are
around this initial balance. Can we see
a drive back through it now up into this
gray box and potentially VWAP? Here we
go. Have we got anything here?
the seller here at 80 keeps reloading 75
and 80.
They're trying to defend it.
I want to see if pullbacks get absorbed
here.
It's nice. Is 80. They got to get
through 80. This re refresh seller here.
They get through that then I'll be
watching for 93 and 97 [clears throat]
on a pop.
Come on. You got to get through 80. If
you can't get through 80, we can't do
bugger all. means you got no juice. He's
only a 33 lot. Come on.
Come on, Mark. Are you that weak?
Yes. Flying right through it. View up.
Ink. You got no juice here. Come on,
Apple. Catch a bid. Get through 80. Get
through 80. Get through 80. You got
nothing.
He's refreshing tiny size and we can't
get through it. It's not very strong
here yet from the bulls.
Where's Delta? 80 86 93. Is it going to
have another go at 80?
Still refreshed selling here. He's still
refreshed. He's still not moved. They
haven't chopped them all up yet. They're
going to have another go at him. He's
still refreshed. Another go. And he's
still refreshed. Right. He's selling 80.
He's got inventory to unload here. Once
that moves, there might be a squeeze,
but until that moves, he's refreshed
again with more size there. He's holding
very firm here at 80, this seller. It's
impressive.
And we have imbalances all the way down
to 60.
So that that seller is still on the tape
up pit, passively selling into every
push into him.
I'm going to come feel this imbalance.
ES looking very strong here back to its
New York open. It's still in a range,
but it's much much stronger than NQDs.
There's the 80 break. So, can they find
a bid over this now? Yep. Okay. So, can
we get to V Park, which would be sort of
97ish,
or is this going to be a look into the
above 80s and slammed?
Oh, we're going to reload 80. Buyers
need to step back in 80 because they
just loaded there. So really would want
to step back in there and then not. So
value area low again here in 275s and we
still have those imbalances down to 60s
I talked about
PC and fail. Yeah, it didn't even make
it. Didn't even make it yet. The problem
is now it's quite messy. So if we look
at the auction at the low, where is it?
Right. This is this is nice excess. This
is what we didn't have earlier. Remember
the earlier lower day I said there's no
excess. This is nice. All right. Sellers
are caught here for sure. And we have a
buying balance down here.
So, if buyers are going to hold this, it
looks good. It's just like a little bit
messy because you got IB uh what else
you got? Is this uh imb um uh orb
and IBL and then balance down here,
which they need to absorb off. So, they
might absorb higher first. But the the
lower day actually looks good now. That
looks good. Didn't look good earlier.
That looks like a better low day in my
mind and it's coming to the gap. All
right. So, it looks better.
So, I'm interested, but we've got to
show some sort of uh strength on
reclaims and stuff, you know,
and I'm also [clears throat] in my head
like smaller size, smaller range day,
lower volume day. Do you need to trade?
Can just be here? You've made some
money. Is it a big, you know, like
narrative in my head? I can show you
like I flipped a few accounts and then
I've traded a couple with a bit more
size. So 141 and one down here, 603 and
191. I don't know why these are
negative. I can trade copious being
annoying. But the others look are fine.
Others are just flip. I'm just flipping.
Wait, wait for them for next year.
[snorts]
[clears throat]
Sorry, folks. All right. maybe into
these imbalances like we just talked
about. Then in in this blue box there's
some imbalances down there. It would be
fun if they came down there and hold it.
ES is right back to New York open,
right? So it still can't get through the
open. We are in a
much much slower, smaller day.
22 points uh range today, folks. That's
what we've got.
122 points. Lower volume. Just be smart.
We're going to have some fun here. If
not, we can do a lesson if this slows
right down. We can do a lesson for you
guys or and we're going to do some Apex
giveaways. Uh I'll put the link in chat
for the funded next giveaway which will
be hopefully announced tomorrow. And
then hopefully that I I will just need
your email to give to them. I'll loop
you in with them and they will uh give
you a free account.
Still not filled these imbalances.
Market's going to sleep.
Bids are trying to come back in here. We
are still just hanging around. Previous
week high, value area low, initial
balance low. Uh sellers are caught
beneath us right now. Underneath 50
sellers are caught. Definitely
underneath 40 sellers are caught. A
flush that holds into 60. All right,
would be a sign that buyers are going to
leave those sellers caught. If we start
closing underneath 60, then
who knows?
Okay, here we come. 66es. Are we going
to start filling some of these?
Yes. We've tapped one of them. The next
one is into 61ish.
And then do they hold versus 50? That
would be the question. They hold versus
50 or are we going to go into expansion?
This is a twole and expansion lower. So
then buyers wanted to step in versus 50
here.
Some aggressive selling here.
And you can see the bid is at 50. It's
only 29 lot, man. So, they are trying to
absorb this.
Market really doesn't know what it wants
to do. I keep like having a quick look
over at the mag and everything's dancing
red to green. All right. It's good. Good
absorption into those 60s.
So, they're trying to find a bid here.
And if we find a bid here, it's possible
to point to control and VWAP. All right.
So, the IB trade will be from here to
point control and VW up if they can find
a bid. They got to get back through the
80s. Remember
that was the sort of line in the sand?
Did I reply to you, Joe? Did I not reply
to you? Maybe I missed it. Um, can you
send it again if I haven't replied to
you, Joe? I'm really sorry. Maybe I
missed that. Maybe it went to spam. Let
me check.
Can't see it. Hopefully I'll reply to
you, Joe. Thought I did, but if not,
please just send it again, my friend. In
info@flowzonerader.com.
It's starting to look a bit better.
Yeah, those shorts just c remember we
just said the there's an imbalance down
here. I'm starting to like look at
feathering into this long.
These imbalances down here just held. We
just talked about it on this chart,
didn't we? These imbalances getting
absorbed into starting to look a little
bit better, but they will need to hold.
What you need to be careful of is this
two leg. This needs to hold and your TPS
are here. Above that, it's a bonus, but
we're in a rotation day, maybe you get
up to here. Below this, below 50, it's
no good. All right, below 50, it's no
good. But what they're setting up is
tricky. the way they've set it up versus
IB and Orb and these 80s are way these
buyers keep trying to come in and not
finding that move higher right now
and ES can't get through that New York
open right so if you have a quick look
at ES
line you'll see it on the chart keeps
banging into it all right that's it's a
big level supply they cannot get over
this New York open base above that
potential squeeze out they can help drag
this market
resent. Thanks, Joe. Sorry, mate. Let me
check now. Oh, hey, I see it. I see it.
I see it, my friend. Okay, as soon as we
get off stream, I'll sort you out.
Really sorry about that, buddy. Don't
know where it went. Maybe it went to
spam. I'm sorry, but that one definitely
didn't. I can see it.
>> [snorts]
>> Yeah, still not through that New York
open. We are just testing the lower side
of this value in IBL.
A bit of a sleepy market here, folks.
Have I taken a trade yet? I'm waiting
now. I'm not in this long yet.
Letting this develop a minute. So, I'm
not seeing strength. What I'm seeing is
all right buyers keep coming in over 78
and there is a passive seller up there.
If we start if we start holding this
right here right now at 73s and
absorbing I'm interested.
I'm looking for like some momentum
someone on the tape to come in someone
to say hey we want this higher like I'm
not seeing ES do it. We're starting to
see it now. It's trying now. Is the 80s
again? Can we see acceleration?
Just waiting to see like some volume
come in. Someone saying I don't want
this lower. We're going to rotate to
point of control on VWAP. And even then,
like how many points am I really playing
for?
20 to 30 points. It's not a lot for me
to play for. You know what I'm like? I
like 50 to 100 point trades I can sit
in.
Now I'm developing a bit of this shelf
here. So level here.
We keep holding dips. there. I am
interested for sure. It's a big if at
the moment.
It's trying. It is try trying. I can see
them trying to be aggressive here. Here
we go. Here's the 80s and still
passively sold. So, still someone
selling everything above 78 at the
moment.
They are trying to step on the tape. ES
still not through that New York open.
Yeah, they're going to have another go
and reload 80s, are they? So, they're
bidding 775
67s and they're selling every pop into
and above 80 right now.
Very tight range. I'm going to use a
bathroom while this does whatever it
needs to do. Let me just see if
a few things out here just in case.
Just in case. All right, be right back.
Okay, it's trying, folks. It's trying,
folks.
Look at ES in that New York open. That
is massive level. Where's Spy? It's not
even at the 85s.
Is there gamma at 84? Can anyone tell
me? Is there some form of put wall at
84? Why are we struggling up there so
much?
We should be going here.
We should be going here. We should try
and get it through. This spy is causing
the bigger issue. If if spy just starts
driving through 84, I think we get a
squeeze out here into VPO and VWOP and
then maybe if we get lucky
into value area high
84 and 85. Yeah, knew it. Knew it. We
keep getting stuck up there. Has to be
some put wall up there.
Still stuck up there again.
We've got imbalances now. 83 down to 78.
Going to come fill and then it's going
to have to hold that value area low
again. So, still no acceptance on SPY
above 84.
Uh, no acceptance underneath this. Do we
have any more imbalances to fill lower?
I mean, yes,
we could, but uh
I'm becoming less and less interested in
this by the minute at the moment,
unfortunately.
Always no reply. What you saying? Let me
scroll up. Bro, I just came to your
second time on stream. When you trade
long or short, do you add P&L onto the
screen with stop- loss and TP? No. Do
you want me? Like, like I say, I give
you the levels. I tell you everything
I'm looking at beforehand. It is your
job to trade your account. All right?
Don't come here for signals. Come here
to learn. Come here to give get the
levels. Come here to understand all the
flow, all those things. But you have to
trade your account. I'm not going to
trade it for you. Same way. I'm not
going to go to the toilet with you and
hold your dick. All right? So, you're a
big boy and big girls learn to trade
your accounts effectively.
I'll teach you everything you need. I'll
give you all the levels. I'll give you
all the setups. I'll tell you even when
I'm looking to enter and what I'm
looking for well ahead of time
beforehand, but I'm not going to give
you a [\h__\h] gift on the screen so you
can just signal bot. Go and pay someone
stupid money to do that.
You're never going to learn if you're
looking for signals. If you're jumping
stream to stream, you're never going to
learn. All right, good hold of value
there again. And IB again waiting now.
Can we get acceptance back through all
these buyers keep coming in here? It's
not that good. All right. What I'm
seeing here on the tape, this is a
problem right now. All right. Say from
sort of here and above is all buy side
and there's someone absorbing. All
right. Some seller is passively sat
here. Once he moves,
we're going to see the expansion up into
point of control and VWOP. All right. Up
into these.
Just want to see this seller like [\h__\h]
off. And I'm not seeing that at the
moment. I'm see every pot is absorbing
and absorbing and absorbing.
[laughter]
It's a very English thing to say. That
might sound rude, but it's the only way
I can make it clear.
Okay, back to value again. Value area
low again. Initial balance low again. No
acceptance inside of range yet. No
acceptance outside of range. We're just
stuck. We are stuck. What's up, Otus?
Hope you're good, buddy.
[snorts]
Still that seller up there
above 80s. Once he moves, I'm
interested. Either that or I want to see
a swipe lower and sellers get stuck in
absorption underneath and be like,
"Okay, we're going to go buy side here."
Also, I need to see SPY get back above
these levels. This 84, they keep selling
84s. is absolutely key. We talked about
that New York open,
these 84s. You can see this blue line.
You can see it cannot get above this.
It's clearly gamma, right? They're just
saying no. So, we're pinned eight this
trade here. And if you want to see that
on the spiders,
where are we?
Right. Same level 84s
to basically 83s. You got a onepoint
range here. No acceptance above, no
acceptance below. They've pinned it.
They've absolutely pinned the market
right now.
I would love to see some kind of trap um
to offer this trade here.
I really want to see sort of this trade
here,
here, here, and here if we get lucky,
and here if we get really lucky. That's
what I'd love to see. But I need to see
[snorts]
some kind of a participant trap shorts.
They did it here, but we've not seen the
drive out.
They might need to do it one more time.
Get [snorts] rid of that node.
less important. I'm just building out a
Dshape here in balance. Here we go.
Okay. Are we going to see this guy lift
out the way?
Do we give this a shot? Long here,
folks. This what? One, two, three
attempts up into 85s now.
What you saying? SPX
call volume 69. Yeah, it's currently
trading 68 67. So, it's got room.
I really want to get long in this, but
uh I'm not seeing
a bit a good move here. I'm just seeing
sellers just sit like this. Like every
pop, they're just selling. They're just
sat there selling it.
I do want to get long if we give me the
opportunity.
Especially if SP Okay, SPY is interested
in me now. If this can close above, I'm
gonna think about getting long on spy.
How long we got left? 44 seconds with
this candle. [snorts]
How this closes, I think, is going to be
important.
Well, if we go sideways the rest of day,
we'll just do some giveaways and we do a
lesson.
No, it won't be too late because I I
want confirmation. So, I want a pop
above and a hold or a dip below and a
trap or I don't want to enter is in the
middle of this like sort of choppy range
that we've developed.
Right? So, I either want this to see
them retract shorts down here and go
again or I want to see this and hold and
leave these guys here stuck. What I
don't want to do is enter in the middle
of that.
I did just try and tra they tried to
trap short. So, it's not moved low
enough. The the volatility is getting
smaller and smaller as well.
Back to these 85s again. Where's that
seller? He is at 85. 104 lot.
Spy. See spy on that last 5 minute
couldn't close over over it again over
that 84 684 looking for spy to close
over it. Exactly. ES needs we'd like to
see ES above that New York open. It's
trying but it's uh it's clearly a cool
wall level on the spy which is 684 which
they keep selling
long target. Uh if I get if I get long,
it's just a trade from IB to here. So
PC's now shifted as well. Interesting.
Let's see if they hold PC. Now on the
other chart, it's still at 97.
There's 97. So here it's gray box
basically.
85s again.
We're going to go. We're going to go. ES
is going. Okay.
Come on, ES.
All right, let's try it. Let's try it
then. If I get slammed, dual slam on my
face. I'm small size. Let's try it.
Let's see if we get Bpock here. Yes,
looks good.
The chat buys again. I do not like what
I'm seeing up here with the passive
selling. Oh, am I going to live to
regret this? Might live to regret this,
folks.
We need to get back over 86s and drive
over 86s otherwise I'm not interested.
Don't want that flush to 70s which they
can't do. ES looks fantastic. Come on
ENQ. You're such a piece of [\h__\h] today.
Go.
Piece of crap. I'm tempted to take this
off and reload lower.
Especially if ES goes and takes out IB
and we don't move.
No. Off. Can reload.
[sighs]
It's too slow, man.
I will reload if they offer it. There's
just no forward side momentum here. ES
looked really good there. Oh, we're
going to go now. You [\h__\h]
How much size did you just have there,
mate?
This guy.
Let's just hold that close.
I think it's going to go, but
Yeah, I'm kind of with you. Is it worth
it, Carla?
It should. ES is absolutely running. We
should We should should should get back
into here
and then here. That's what I'm was
playing for.
Holding this under here. No trade unless
they retrap and reclaim. But uh we
should
just want to see just a big buyer step
on the tape because we can swipe. Yes.
Is going looks so good now.
There's someone is passively selling
every little pop. Like they are just
nonstop selling the pops here, but we're
not moving lower. So we're like we're
pinned like this. So they're absorbing
the lows and they're absorbing the highs
in this little range. So like there's a
buyer hanging out here and there's a
seller hanging out from basically 85s
here.
And so this is the range.
There's just nothing.
But it feels if we have a look over
here, why I wanted to play that long is
that move once we broke. The problem is
Oh, this is going to go. This looks so
good. Look at that. Really nice break.
taking this liquidity. Gunning for IB
higher. We're going to go now on accuse.
You [\h__\h] are, aren't you? You
absolute
[\h__\h] Okay, into gray box, which was
first target because that was old PC.
And then next target was 704s
if they run it.
Big if, but that's what I'd be looking
at if they run it. And then 710s. I
think they're going to do it now, folks.
Here we go. They're going to squeeze
this now. There's a seller here, but
they want to run through him.
They want to fill all these orders. ES
wants that IB high and ES has unfinished
business up at 930s
which means what? Spy 685 is the next
level is it? So Spy Spy needs to hold
684 and trade 685s basically.
Here we go. All right. Come on then.
Come on then. Come sevens. There we go.
Lovely. All right. VWOP.
Second time's a charm. Can we go VWAP?
And then can we go value area high? So
726es. Here comes VWAP. Come on. You
better [\h__\h] film me. Don't you dare.
Don't you dare. ES. I'm watching ES to
IB High. As soon as it takes IB high,
I'm going to trim. If it takes IB high
before we take V up, I'm trimming.
Yeah. Don't people that teach that. Uh
Kevin or Kelvin, it's [\h__\h] nonsense,
mate. All the orders above it has to go
there. But it it doesn't like that's
nonsense. Absolute nonsense when people
say that. That's not how you use
bookmap. Concentrate what it's doing
now. Those are passive orders above.
Yes, it would be nice to go and fill
them. It definitely doesn't have to go
and do that. Not that you said it had to
do that, but the amount of people I see
saying that it just doesn't. It never it
doesn't have to do anything. Always
remember that market will do whatever it
wants. They can put the orders up there
and pull them all. Here we go. Give me
my fill at VWAP.
O,
come on.
Come on. I want to get this off. Come
on. Come on. Come on. Watching ES into
that IB high. Come on.
Ah, so close. I'm trying to
Okay, good. All right, runners now
holding in case we complete rotation up
here to the 28s and then if we get
really lucky expansion, but already
locked most in here into VWAP because ES
is coming to IB high. So, it's a
rotational day. So, we're going to lock
in. Remember the trade is from IB low to
VWAP. All right. So, we looked below
guys like Tyson, this is your bread and
butter. We looked below IB. We came in
to remember the gap. We trapped shorts
down here. It's the first time I've seen
the end of the auction look good. This
is a little bit gross, unfortunately.
Took two attempts, but the trade IB to
VW up above here, we're looking at
value. And if we get above there, well,
we've got the New York open and IB high
to aim for, but we do have relative
weakness in NQ today. So, it might be
that it doesn't do it. ES is looking
absolutely fantastic. Right. I was
trying to time this with this. There you
go. So, there was the break. That was
the gamma break. There's the IB high.
This is the unfinished business into
9:30. All right. So, I'm still long a
little piece and we'll see. We will just
see now. Why am I doing NQZ? I need NQ.
Okay. [sighs]
All right. So, it took a couple attempts
here. Sorry, folks. ENQ's being a little
bit of a [\h__\h] today, but we're down to
tiny size now because we can reject this
if we want. But if we can get up to
here, it'd be fantastic. And if we get
up to here, it' be a monster trade.
Just a little piece left now from the
80s. Here we go. All right, let's see.
Can we get some acceleration here?
ES now taken.
Take an eye behind. So you want to be
careful and a failed look above and fail
on ES.
point controls moved up to here to 700
now. So we really we want to hold 96s.
Don't I don't really want to see it come
back down into like those 80s and 90s. I
want to hit see it hold 96s and
accelerate here.
Still long.
What triggered me to enter there? Uh
trap volume underneath, right? Blue blue
box, remember, was where I potentially
wanted to buy off. We trapped
underneath. We tapped the gap. We held
higher low. We did all this nonsense and
then we saw ES starting to go, the mag
starting to rotate back to green and uh
buyer starting to get a bit more
aggressive. Remember the seller kept
reloading at 80s and 85. So, he was here
from 10:46 to He was there for like
basically 20 30 minutes. He He's run out
of uh stuff inventory to sell. So, now
I'm looking for that rotation
and just want to see if we can get a
little bit more here. I'm trying to hold
the runner for current value area high.
And if we get lucky, if we get lucky
above value area high, which is GlobeEx,
then we get up here. But I really like I
will move my stop up as as we get into
this
ES about to finish that unfinished
business we talked about as well.
Remember 9:30 unfinished business on ES.
That's a big level uh through that. I'm
watching SPY 85685.
So we were right to be bullish. We just
had to wait a couple goes today. But
we're nice and green. You can see here
the one that I'm in 580 left. Right.
Just waiting to see how far up we go.
[snorts]
Keep getting stuck here at 10 [sighs]
lower time frame algo here. Want to get
back through this. This is where the
sellers came in and earlier in the day.
Remember this is kind of the level that
sellers came in earlier at the earlier
in the day
and say delta wise in here. Right. You
can see buyers got stuck here earlier.
Big selling above. If we get back
through that and looking to get back
into value to the top side of value.
Looking good. Looking really good. Now,
this runner might do the job for us.
Let's just hope
we can get up here. I'll move my stop.
I'm not going to take profit up here
because I've only got one left. But, uh,
I will move my stop up as we get into
this. But, you never know. We might come
for all this liquidity up here if we get
really, really lucky.
So, unfinished business now taken ES.
So, be very careful here. Here we go,
folks. We're looking fantastic.
So, you can trim some as we get into
value area high. The only reason I'm not
is I only got one left. All right. But
you can trim some as we get into these
value area highs. You do not want this
to come back beneath point of control
700s. You want all dips there to be
absorbed. But ES did just take that big
level I talked about. All right. It just
absor just just swiped that and it's
come back down inside. So that could be
the end of it for the day. We will see.
So I'm going to manage this no matter
what.
You never know. So I've got my stop now
underneath point of control. I don't
want it to come under 96. So we've got a
little low volume node. Move my stop up
to 94s here. And I want that to be
protected on the next squeeze up. If we
get a next squeeze up, I'll move my stop
up.
They need to make a new high here in my
opinion here.
[snorts]
stuck here a little bit. I want to give
this too much room at the moment.
Risking 20 points
up 750. Nice mate. Good work. So you got
long with me.
Good work.
want ES ES has got to get back above
930s, right? 6930s. Got to get back
above that in base. I'm playing ENQ,
right? I'm playing ENQ. My stop's
currently at 9425. I'm long from 81.
I've already trimmed a few off.
I know technically I could uh give this
more room, but I want it to hold VWAP
and this little low volume shelf, which
is not there on this, but they've got
one at 94s here. So, I'm looking for
this to hold and base. All right. If I'm
going to get my move, it needs to hold
this kind of level here into here and
then above that if I get really lucky.
It's what I'm looking for on the runner.
Right. If we collapse under here, I'm
not interested because this can be a
peak out. Right. If we're going to go
into rotation,
we're going to go into rotation. This
can be a sweep and a peak and a move
back down. And what I'm very aware of is
what the ES has done because it's just
taken out this big key level. All right.
So,
ES needs to hold above this now.
Definitely wants to hold IB. Look at the
difference. So good. So that was what we
took really with the long. The break for
this squeeze on ES helped us get long in
ENQ because this just looked so good on
ES. We just knew once it got through
this 694 positive gamma up into the
highs into this level. This was the
unfinished business which is why we
trimmed into it.
So, this is how I trade them together.
And then we just sit and hopefully we
can get going here.
Yeah. W's in chat if you got any of
this. Not sure you get any. Sloth got
it. Inferris. Got it. Holding runner.
Yeah, nice. Same as me, mate. Just in a
runner. Here we go, folks. Almost at
that value area high. So, if you haven't
trimmed some, you want to trim some. Uh
you can trim anywhere from now really
into this. There is a little shelf here.
So I'd say anywhere from uh 20s to 26s
is a partial if you haven't taken it.
And if we get lucky, we get this and
these if we get lucky.
So in the mag Apple the only one now
red. So we're seeing rotation in the
mag. We got a passive seller here. 20
25s. Is there anyone about 30s and then
50s and then there is some more
liquidity starting to be added onto the
tape higher. So we look good. We are a
little bit extended, so we might get a
pullback at some point. So, just make
sure you're paying yourself. This is
fantastic, guys. Basically into your
target now. Your TP's just been hit
here.
Another green day on stream. Let's hope
we get another one tomorrow. And then
really nice way to go into Christmas. I
didn't think we'd get much today, but
you know, the blue box was the level we
talked about. Two blue boxes I wanted to
buy off. This one and this one. We
tapped the gap. We reclaimed the blue
box. This is what we always look for.
This kind of move with excess big down
candle riced higher low. This was the
dip in when we had the buy side
imbalance and that was the signal. Took
me two attempts here, folks. All right.
Like I said, I will happily cut when I
feel unsure about it. I'd rather be out
of a trade than in a tra in a trade I
don't like. So I think I had a go here,
didn't really like it and then had
another go and we went.
So failing in front of value high this
little shelf I just talked about this
shelf here being important [snorts] 21s.
We fail that. This is where they're
trying to protect right now. You can see
clear rotation.
This shelf right here. Look how sharp
that is. All right, they are selling
against that right now. So buyers have
got to get back above 21s.
I'm not going to read into this.
Tempted to move at my stop up. It's
still at 94s
30 points. O
thing is because we've squeezed we can
offer quite a big snap. We can we can do
something like this if we're going to go
and we can also do this and then I'll
give the whole thing back is this is
always where it's tricky when we're in a
rotation. I'm going to try and give it a
bit more room.
But the moment I see big selling coming
in and weakness and no buyers like now
we're starting to see stronger selling.
If I don't see a buyer step up, I'll
probably cut early. Watch this into VW
up. Watch ES into IB.
Point of control still at 700. So, I'm
still underneath that. And this is a big
D-shape.
All right. So, we're just in a rotation.
I'd love to see this accelerate now.
Would make me feel a bit more confident
if we can get over 21 about holding this
last runner.
We're still in it. You can see it here.
All right. 702. Up 72 in this. Just
looking to see if we can expand a little
bit higher.
Do I think it would go New York open or
open high? Uh, I don't know, mate. Like,
it
I can't predict. All I know is right
now, this is a big level. If we get
through this level and base above, we've
got an imbalance here to fill. This is
thin. All right, we might want to attack
this. Right, so one thing at a time,
right? Let's try and get through this
first. see how we act here. If we take
this liquidity here, yeah, then I think
we are. But right now, I know that we're
into a very big level. If I was train a
range rotator trader, I'd be trying to
sell this or this move back here, right?
So, I I don't want to predict whether
we're coming here or not yet, right?
Because this could be the end the end of
the move where we're into at the moment.
[snorts]
Uh, finally in the black, Mel with a W.
Congratulations. Tried twice at 680s.
Finally got the third one, so I'm
slightly positive. Thank you for your
analysis. You're welcome. Waiting for
the dip now. Not chasing.
Um I made 550 today. Not too much, but I
can't complain for a low volume day. 550
is good money. It's good money. Adds up
very, very quickly. Six figure year. 550
every day. Scout my way to a decent W.
Thank you. Nice work.
Thank you for the stream. Great stuff.
You're welcome. Thanks as always, Cap
says. Thank you, Alex. Have a wonderful
holiday. You too, Mel. Um, newbie, what
percentage do you risk per trade? What
percent do you risk? Uh, depends on the
account I'm playing, mate, and the
setup.
Win for the day. Thanks for the streams
and teaching Alex. Have a merry
Christmas. Happy New Year. Looking
forward to joining your stream again
2026. Yeah, looking forward to it.
Looking forward to trading with you.
Close to golden pocket. Yeah, we will be
probably a bit more left I would have
thought of current day.
Golden pocket, I would imagine.
Yeah, 50%. If we go from swing to swing,
we're definitely being it. Yeah,
we're right on the edge. ES starting to
come back to IB. If ES loses IB, I will
cut this early
cuz it's taking its low hanging through.
At the moment, it's okay.
Golden Pocket, it's just a fib
retracement. All right. When if anyone
says golden pocket, right, they're
talking about the fib, right? Into I
would call it the 618 to 786. Some
people call it the 05 to 61, but really
the 61 is what you want to look at,
right? 61. When we come to these, all
right, these are normally good areas to
sell in based on fibs. All right? But if
you're going to do I'm going from higher
day to lower day. If we come from here,
we're already into it. If we come from
swing to swing, we're already into it.
But my bias is not lower today. Right?
My bias, if you we're here for the
pre-market show, my bias was to
potentially come up into here, but we're
not buying the highs. So, this is why
the blue boxes, if you ever see a blue
box on my screen, it's an area of
interest for me to buy at. It's probably
an RBS zone. We keep failing up here,
not going to hold this much longer.
They've just developed another little
node here.
Very tempted to take my profit here. I'm
trying not to, but this is uh
tempted to take what I've got. Don't
want to give too much back. Strong
selling coming up here.
Right. If ES loses IB or we lose VWOP or
VPO. In fact, I'm going to move my stop
up a little bit cuz someone can't give
[\h__\h] 30 40 points back. So, let's
see. I want to see VWOP defended. I want
to see point control defended. Uh point
control is not here, folks. Where it
thinks it is. It's at 700. All right.
So, your point control right now is
here. So basically this area needs to be
defended,
right? Or I'm cutting the trade. This is
my area. Bulls defend that or I'm out.
Remember I'm long from 800 from 80s. I'm
just want to see this area here defended
for a drive higher. If it isn't, I'm
out.
Um, [sighs]
new follower, subscriber, do you trade
live every day? Yes, I do. From what
I've watched, your style matches what
I'm trying to do and implement. Yeah.
Live here every day. 9:15 Eastern time.
Every day, Monday to Friday, we trade
into lunch. It's really important you
guys try and get here at 9:15. Like 9:15
to 9:30 is when I tell you what I'm
looking at and why. And it's important
we do that analysis. So, so when I'm not
here, you'll be able to do the same
thing for yourself because we do the
same thing every day. It's habits which
are going to make you profitable, right?
Good process, good habits. ES right into
this IB.
I want to give this too much more time.
That's fine. There new 30 minute, 15
minute, 5 minute bar coming in about 90
seconds.
The problem is ES can swipe down from
that squeeze up and that will drag us.
So let's see.
Let's see.
See that transition here? Where are the
shorts stuck? They're not really stuck,
these shorts until we get to 700 to 94.
So, if we bust through this, we're going
to go. But we got to I don't want to
really risk. I'm not risking below this.
So, basically, I need these guys to stay
in pain. These guys here need to stay in
pain. All right. If we're going to get
this otherwise this snap here, I'm not
going to hold beyond that.
E starting to develop bit here. Come on
market, please. Let's do one more shove.
Don't want ES to fail these 30s now. All
right, because it's looked above, come
back underneath. I want ES to flag and
go. Otherwise, I might cut this a little
bit early. I'm trying to give it room,
but I don't on a day where there's not a
huge amount of volatility, I don't want
to give too much back.
Spider's trying to hold it. ES trying to
hold it, but it's can't get back through
those 30s at the moment.
Slightly concerned about a look above
and fail because it was the low hanging
fruit trade on ES which we've taken. So,
I I will be honest. I'm slightly
concerned about a look above and fail
there on the ES. Okay, last chance
saloon for this market to hold on this
dip. Otherwise, I'm out on the runner.
This is that new 5 minute, 15 minute, 30
minute bar we just talked about. This is
increased volatility just for this next
minute or two.
Yes, holding well. Can I get back
through 9:30? Now or never, ES, you got
to get back over that this 9:30. Good,
good, good. Go on then. Up you go. ES,
help me. Help me. Help me.
[snorts]
Come on. Yes. I'm not going to give this
much more room. You're making me
Not very happy here.
I'm going to move my stop right up now
because I don't like what I'm seeing
there. Can always get back in, but hands
are off the mouse. Let it let it do what
it's got to do.
Uh, mate, you're the only one doing
lives that explains everything what is
happening. I know. It's cuz most don't
know what they're talking about. Need a
bunch more green day to have money for
the course. But so far, compared to
others I see online, you're amazing
explaining. Thank you, mate. All right,
I'm out of this. Don't like that
rejection. It might hold VPO, but I'm
done. I don't want to give too much back
on this. We've seen strong sellers and
they can wash down to 90s. I just can't
give too much back. Gray is the area of
control for these buyers that they need
to hold at. All right, so this is the
area that buyers will want to absorb
this gray box. But I just can't I cannot
justify this is just justification of
the trade. I can't justify trading from
here partial partial and giving the
whole thing back into here. All right.
So I cut I moved it tighter and tighter
and tighter. I got a bit impatient but
it's mainly due to ES again. This is why
I watched multiple charts. ES starting
to reject this red level. All right. So
they look above and fail and it's
starting to reject that. My danger is if
they lose this, we come right the way
back down to 84 gamma on the spy. So
I've cut this now. I'm just being honest
with you.
Might be that it still goes for you, but
I have cut this at this point. Why have
we lost in Q?
There we go. Nice trade nonetheless. We
traded uh what we could get out of it.
So, the max we got was from 80. It's a
shame we couldn't hold that first
attempt or whatever it was. 80 to 20 40
points. I don't think that's too bad in
the range that we've got today.
Yeah, I would agree, Joe. I mean, SPY
looks better. What Spy is trying to do
is just hold its initial balance high.
All right, it's trying to hold its IB
high and it's trying to, if you look at
the morning drive, Joe on spy, you look
at a fiveminute chart in spy, look at
the 9:30 high where we've created that
IB high, right? It's trying to hold
that. The problem, right, for those who
are new joining, is that we've taken
lowhanging fruit on SPY. So, if Spy is
going to help us find a bid today,
right, then we're going to struggle now
because we've taken low hanging fruit.
And you know my rules. Once low hanging
fruit goes, I become far less interested
in the market. I'm always looking for
that lowhanging fruit trade.
Dean says, "I'm getting a lot of value
from your channel, Alex. Your knowledge
seems very advanced. Are you
selftaught?" Yeah, selftaught. Self
taught. That's not to say I haven't done
other courses, but most of what I did
was uh a lot of bollocks, waste of
money. Like I'm sure a lot of you guys
have done. Most courses you will do out
there are absolute shite. Um so I've
I've done lots of them
over my lifetime.
Hi, I'm I'm a new follower. Next year
I'm in. Hey, looking forward to trading
with you, ma'am. How many setups do I
have? Uh, that's a good question.
Well, most of it depends on liquidity.
So, opening drive, if I if if I know one
side's trapped, opening drive, uh,
initial balance, uh, expansion, initial
balance rotation,
uh, trend day setup, if we're looking
for dips and flow zones on trend day,
and I would say like value, value
migrating higher, value migrating lower.
Um, the setup that I don't take, which
people here probably take and I don't
take, is I don't take a rotation, right?
I try and avoid a rotation. You can
argue today I've taken a rotation. You
can argue that, right? You can argue
I've taken this rotation, but what I'm
trying to say is I won't sell that. All
right, back down. It's a legit setup,
but I won't sell that back down on a
rotation. That's the trade I try and
avoid. Um, my favorite favorite favorite
favorite favorite trade A+ trade is when
we're leaving higher time frame volume
trapped. All right, you would have seen
we did it a few times last week. The
break lower two weeks ago was that
trade, right? That's my A+ trade. If
we're leaving higher time frame volume
trapped, that's when I like attacking
the market with more size.
Um, do I think we go back and fill the
gap?
I don't know. Not Not at the moment.
Like I said, I don't I don't think we
need to do that. All right. If we just
trade take the indicators off,
I'm just going to take everything off
for a second and just look at what we've
got. Right. Let's just let's just think
about migration of value. Let's think
about what we're seeing. Remember, we
traded long last week when lots of
people were trying to trade short. So at
these lows, let's just think what about
I'm going to move to like a five minute
chart. Make this make sense. Let's think
about what we've had develop over the
last few weeks and think about where we
are. Right? This is a twoe balance
range.
This we traded short aggressively. Okay.
This we traded short aggressively. Why?
These are the A+ trades I just went
over. Leaving two weeks trapped. We're
going to use their pain trade lower.
Right. This we avoided if everyone can
remember this and this I said is
probably likely to be a bull trap which
is sold. This we traded short. Right.
Because why? This is a two-leg into trap
players. You got trap buyers here. We
trade short. Trap buyers here. We trade
short. First attempt back in off a
two-leg. We trade short. This down here
was an old naked point of control. Those
who have been here the last two weeks
will know that we were looking for that.
It's in the free newsletter. All right.
This is your overunder. So they wash
underneath. They find a bid over. They
hold it. Now what we going to do? Trade
long to where this this pain point,
right? Because this move here is a 61 on
a daily and weekly. This is a the golden
zone on the daily and weekly. So we bid
up here. The same thing. We bid up. But
here we don't want to bid up in this
part in this part. Remember the ma main
money long was made here and here. We're
breaking out of this cycle, this
downtrend. But we don't want to be a new
money long up here. So, we want to play
dips back down. So, I remove all this,
then we can think about what's happened
last week and where we're trading from.
So, if we draw out last week's value,
previous week value area high, previous
week value area low is here.
Friday
is here.
Gap is this gray box. So, if we're
opening higher,
who's trapped right now, right? Who's
trapped from the previous week? Well, if
you were short here or here or here,
you're out the money, right? So, the
participant who's trapped right now is a
seller. So, we want to bid up. The
problem is if we look left, the
participant who's trapped in here is a
buyer. So, our range we need to respect
this this week's value or last week's
value
to this week's value. We're trading in
between this. Does that make sense? This
is buyers stuck. This is seller stuck.
This is where we are. So, we don't want
to buy up here and we don't want to sell
down here. So, we want to buy the dips
for this move up. And you want to sell
if you're really bearish the move back
down from here where they're stuck back
down. I don't want to take that move in
in a holiday session especially, okay?
Unless things change. So that's why we
were biased to the upside today and it's
also why we didn't buy the open because
we're too close to this box where those
participants who are buyers are trapped.
So we wanted to buy two possible levels.
One level is here and one level is here.
All right. So we want to buy for this
move. We want to buy for this move. Now,
if they collapse this, right, once we
hit this, I'm taking my profit. Now, if
they want to sell that back down, then I
will participate. All right, once we get
up into this old point of control, if
they want to do something like this,
right, then I'll sell back down. That
becomes the protren. And that would be a
bull trap, something we can go over
maybe next week or whenever we're back
in the market. If we collapse this now
and come back into previous days value
and previous week's value, previous days
value and previous week's value, right?
Do I want to buy it? I'm happy to buy
all the time we're holding, but if we
come back in here, these are the trades
I try and avoid. I don't want to trade
in previous week's value, right? I
really don't. I I want to see us bid up
or I want to sell high for the trade
back down into there and hold runners. I
don't want to participate in value. for
me. That's for me. That's my setup. I
choose to try and avoid that because I
hate trading rotations. I hate it. So,
if I can avoid trading it, you'll find
my P&L factor goes up. So, hopefully
that makes sense to you guys. There's a
little lesson there on why. See, this
gray box is still holding. I said buyers
will want to hold that. It's just based
on volume.
Um, [sighs]
ever tried ICT? I've looked at it, man.
But it's
look,
[laughter] there are some useful
teachings there, all right? But they are
not his teachings and they lack real
detail and
um
well, I'm just going to avoid saying any
more than that. There are people that
make a lot of money from it. Um
but I think they make money because
they're good traders. And I think you
find they use lots of other tools that
they don't talk about. Um,
can I re recommend some resources? What
do you want the on what, Jacks? If you
let me know on what, then I will give
you some resources. I've taken the
previous course. It was like an intro
course. Way overpriced.
Which course? You think the $649
20our course is overpriced
with the flow zones with Discord for
life? Or did you do the $99 which most
of the time is on sale for $49 which is
a complete introduction for someone
who's never touched anything ever ever
ever ever ever ever before. $99 bucks to
get two hours and you get $99 off the
next course is overpriced. You, my
friend, are a bit of a knobbyby.
If you think that's overpriced.
Jeez, my god. Um,
how do I get the indicators and where do
I go? They're all they're all on my
website or you get them in the courses.
flowzonerader.com.
What fruit am I talking about? Uh,
lowhanging fruit. Those are like what we
call easy trades. Low hanging fruit. So,
previous week high, previous week low,
previous day high, previous day low. Low
hanging fruit trades.
New subscriber here. Have you post any
videos on your setup indicators? Yeah,
like every there's a whole section on my
YouTube, guys. Whole section on learning
to trade
volume on order flow. Uh, I've got like
there's a shelf on my YouTube which is
all on volume. I haven't done the
orderflow ones yet, but there's a whole
shelf there for that.
Yeah, like you could anyone who said
that's clearly just [\h__\h] mental,
mate. And I give I give the the full
introduction courses. I give them away
on here most days on stream. It's if 99
bucks is a lot for a twohour course. If
you've never done anything ever before
in your life and you not willing to
spend 99 bucks, which I give back to you
to do the 20our course. So you basically
do two hours of education for free and
get a $100 gift voucher off the 20hour
course with Discord for lifetime and the
indicators. then you have no business
trading ever, ever, ever, ever. You're
never going to make it cuz you're not
committed.
What that basically means is you get
about 24 hours of education and the
indicators and Discord for $549
and that's too much for you. Get out of
here.
Yes, I trade in Discord in the
afternoons.
Yeah, I agree, Joe.
Yeah, full for like you don't need to do
it. I can already tell that you trade
order flow well. Like you're always
looking at the same stuff like and
there's never any pressure to do it
anyway.
Never any pressure to do it. Like I'm
here Monday to Friday, right? Doesn't
cost you guys anything to be here Monday
to Friday. [snorts]
Would my system work without bookmap?
Yeah, it would absolutely work without
bookmap. But I would feel like I'm
trading blind, right? Because most my
setups come from seeing trap
participants.
Yeah. So if you want this is the
difference between trading candlesticks
and trading order flow. Trading
candlesticks like
you might say okay this is a downtrend
we might still go lower right? Trading
order flow I know that sellers got
trapped here and we have an imbalance
here and if we hold this we're going to
come back up. That's the difference. I
can see what's going on inside of all
this whether it's whether you use
bookmap or footprint or whatever else
works for you. I need to know what's
really going on. And most most trades in
the market come from trap traders. Where
are trap traders? Edge of auction,
right? The last seller sold here. Why
did he sell there? Well, he got stuck
trying to think we were going to close
this gap. So, he tra he sold the gap
fill. Well, he got stuck. So, whose pain
do we use? His. Where do we go? This
way. Remember earlier in the day I said,
I don't like this low. I don't think
that's the edge of auction because there
were not enough sellers caught down
here. Here, there were enough sellers
caught. Right. said it doesn't mean you
have to use bookmap or order flow or any
of those things. Do what suits you. Like
if you're a beginner trader, I would not
advise you look at bookmap and
footprints. [snorts] You need to learn
like
basic principles. Like the biggest thing
that I
I want to be really careful how I phrase
this. The biggest mistake I see newer
traders make, especially like if you're
young and you're like, "Oh, I'm watching
ICT and
Guys, you don't know how the market
works. You literally, you don't. If
you're watching a guy like that, you do
not understand the mechanics of a mar
market. You don't understand the
auction. You don't understand why it
moves and how it moves. Forget the
charts. Understand why markets move.
Understand what supply is, what demand
is, what wales are doing, how they need
to get in and out of positions. Once you
understand that, once you understand
that and market structure and all these
other sentiment changes, then you can
look at trading. But so many just jump
on the charts and they're like, "Oh,
break structure, change cap." You don't
understand. You don't understand why.
So, it's never going to make sense to
you, which is why I try and explain it
here.
[snorts]
Yeah. All I'd say, F SFC, you're saying
you're interested in doing the course.
All I'd say is there's Make sure you
like how I teach. Go on my YouTube
channel. There's honestly there's
probably hundreds of hours of education
for free on my YouTube channel. Go and
do all that first. Make sure you like
how I teach. Say every day when people
are interested. Make sure you like how I
teach.
Do you do you think ICT invented
divergence in the market?
Do you do you actually think SMT is a
saying and that he invented divergence
in the market? You think that is his
concept?
Do you think an imbalance
seen on order flow here which he would
call a fair value gap which I can see as
a legitimate imbalance here which he
would not be able to see is an ICT
concept. You are kidding yourself. You
are kidding yourself. Do you think that
the algo that runs the market is an ICT
concept or is it WOFF theory and he's
changed the word the man for the algo?
Do you understand what I'm saying? Like
it's not his dude, it's just rebranded,
right? I'm not using his concepts.
I'm trading
I'm trading the market in all concepts
of auction theory and how price moves
that have ever existed which he does not
own. Regardless of what you think,
[laughter]
you can buy the indicators on my
website, mate. If you just want the
indicators, you can buy them.
No, the 90 the the only course it does
is the full course. But I'll tell you
now, random guy. If you do the course
for $99, if you've already traded for a
long time, it it is only for people who
are brand new who have never ever put
money in the market. But if you do the
course for $99 and you complete it, you
get a $100 gift voucher off the 20hour
course. So you get the beginner course
and you get beginner to advance then for
$549, right? So
trading psychology books. Uh yeah. Um
I gave my list.
One second.
Market stopped moving guys which is why
we can have a chat about all this stuff.
Okay, what would I listen to?
Where's my library?
Um,
well, it depends how hip you want to go.
Breaking the habit of being yourself,
Joe Despensza.
Um,
best loser wins, Tom Hogard.
Mental game of trading, Jared Teddler.
Um, trading in the zone, Mark Douglas,
Outliers, Malcolm Gladwell, that will
help you for black swan events. And then
the one I love the most, which I always
talk about, which is not a trading book.
It's a bit of a laugh. It's three hours
long, but it will help your trading, is
golf is not a game of perfect. I think
that is probably the best non-trading
trading book ever written.
So simple. Okay, they've held this gray
box. You can see they've held this
shelf. They're trying to find a bid to
move higher. So shorts fail to get the
rotation there. All right. So they tried
they've tried to break here. They've
tried once, twice. If they start seeing
absorption here, this is going to happen
through this. I'm not playing anymore,
folks. I've lost interest.
Candlesticks are confirmation for order
flow. Yeah, I mean like I said, look,
you can you don't have to use orderflow.
You don't like it's not for everyone,
but like I would advise you at least use
volume. It's the easiest thing to use on
a chart is a profile. This is telling
you where we're finding acceptance.
We're not finding acceptance under,
we're not finding acceptance over. We're
rotating in here. This is fair value for
the day. I don't like trading around
fair value for the day. I try and avoid
trading around fair value. Why? because
it's going to be the most competitive
price. If we're going to start moving
away, there's a trade there. We start
moving below, there's a trade there, but
there's only a trade to these levels
until we prove otherwise. So, at least
put profile on your chart. Only the
second streamer that you've seen that
has ads turned off. Yeah, I always have
them turned off. I put them back. I put
them on once I finished the stream.
How would you know traders are trapped
without order flow? Well, you wouldn't
really. you'd be having to think about
uh like wicks on candles, right? So, you
would have to make assumptions
and that's really what you're making.
You're making an assumption in here. All
right, that shorts are trapped and if we
don't come back down to this level that
they remain trapped and the same for
here.
So for example um this ICT concept which
is not his concept but this ICT concept
down to 53. You all went oh the
imbalance is down there. No it wasn't.
If you remember I can specifically
remember saying it's to 60. Well that's
the imbalance. There actually is not an
imbalance down here but you would all
think there is one if you're not using
orderflow. The imbalance was to 60s.
So that's the advantage. It's accuracy.
Yes, absolutely. GG.
Market slowly going to watch more.
Market slow. I'm going to watch more of
your videos. See you tomorrow. See you
tomorrow, bud. Yeah. Yeah. See you
tomorrow. [snorts] Unfortunately, my
first trading course with with Ross
Cameron, not Cameron Ross. Ross Cameron.
I know you mean. Yeah. Well, I tell you
something, Ar King. I almost did that
once in the day.
Um,
yeah. How to buy the high on small caps
by Ross Cameron should be what it's
called. Momentum trading. How to buy the
high on small caps. How to buy high and
hope we go higher by Ross Cameron.
How to buy high, hope we go higher, hope
your students will buy even higher than
you, and sell into your students by Ross
Cameron. I don't know if any of you
listen to my podcast with Austin Silver,
you will know I used to be in a small
cap room. We paid for Ross Cameron on
live stream and we used to take the
opposite side of it.
But I feel for you, Ar King.
I feel for you.
He charges an extortionate amount of
money, $3,500
to learn how to try and trade a squeeze
without understanding structure
properly.
Alex Berlin, I just started my fourth
eval on Apex, I think you're saying.
Good luck.
>> [laughter]
>> Exactly. Full forward. Exactly. Full
forward. It It's all It's all white.
It's all white.
You guys know you guys have been around
long enough know
it doesn't. You're right, Alchemist. It
doesn't matter what you use, but what's
incorrect is to say that someone owns
something when they don't. All right?
It's it's straight up [\h__\h]
plagiarism.
Let's just call it what it is. If you
did a dissertation and you just copied
someone else's thing and you know, I
write a novel and I I changed the word
Dave for Alex is plagiarism. Plain plain
and simple. Put a guy in a court of law.
Let's see if he's plagiarized. put on a
lie detector test, see if he's
plagiarized.
I know the answer. Everyone knows the
answer, right? So, it it doesn't mean
his teachings aren't good. He's found a
language of explaining the market to
people. It's fantastic. The more people
that understand the market, the better,
but it's not his. And that's the bug. I
don't own order flow. It's not mine.
never claimed to own order flow or
volume profile or an imbalance or the
EMAs. Might call them flow zones, but
they're rolling fibs if anyone asks me.
I'm not like they're special. They're
just rolling fibs. That's all they are,
right? So, that's that's my only like
thing I'm saying there.
Uh, can the indicators be bought
directly through Trading View? Yep,
they're on my website. You can buy them
directly for Trading View, but they're
on my website, flowzonetrader.com. All
the links down below.
What my thoughts on options trading? Um,
yeah, do it. My advice would be like if
you're going to do it, do leaps. You
know, time's our greatest commodity. I
would avoid zero DTE or, you know, I'd
look at leaps, especially if you're
starting. Giving yourself time in the
market is the best thing possible.
Honestly, if you can b yourself time
investing possible.
There you go. Random guy. Yeah.
[laughter]
Shouldn't shouldn't be shouldn't be
trading without knowing anything.
[laughter]
Oh, Alchemist, you're welcome to leave
at any time you want, mate. I'm not
talking about [\h__\h] about him. If you
can't handle the truth, I'm sorry. I'm
sorry, mate. If you can't handle the
truth, like I said, his teachings have
helped people, but they're not [\h__\h]
his. So, don't sit on my stream saying
that I'm trading how he trades because
of S&T. SMT is divergence. It's not his,
mate. It's been around since the
beginning of [\h__\h] time. All right?
Don't sit here and try and tell me. Just
don't because you're going to lose.
Yep. You can buy the indicators on the
website. Yes, golf is not a game of
perfect.
The links are all down below, guys. or
or just it's being posted in in chat by
Nightbot.
Did Ross Cameron get sued? He did get
sued. Yeah. Well, I think he settled
out, of course.
Is CVD on Trading View good enough? Uh
yeah, I use it. I use it on a five
minute. Yeah, I I use CBD on five
minute,
but yeah, it's fine.
Currently, it's uh it's dead. [laughter]
Absolutely dead currently.
Just not moving, no volume, nothing
being done on CBD. [snorts]
Can I look at gold? I can look at gold
for you.
Looks fantastic. We talked about this
last week.
If we base out, we have the ability to
go. Look at that. All right. So, those I
don't know if it was you asking last
week, but we talked about all the time.
Gold holds this range,
right? Looks really good.
developed this range, attracted more
shorts in here, and it's the catch-up
trade to silver, and we're just going to
keep expanding. And now you can do
projections based on this last pullback.
All right, so you can look at
7 700s, 750s, and then really 5,000s.
5,000s really. All right, here goes the
market. I'm just having another go.
Gold looks great. That's going to keep
happening all the time. time you're
having these pressures in uh Japan,
you're going to see, you know, they
might be positioning gold before they're
positioning or or or
removing their positions, I should say,
from the US markets, but we'll see. We
we'll have to deal with that in January.
Is the volume profile indicator you're
using native to TV1? Yeah. Yeah. This is
all native. This is all free. This is
just uh anchored Right. If you just come
here to this one down here, volume base
anchor volume profile and then I just
have it set up like this. Two ticks and
position to the right. That's it. These
are all native, guys. The the only thing
not native uh is uh the VWAP and uh the
New York VWAP, which someone in my
community kindly made, and the flow
zones. Everything else is native, guys.
Yeah,
that's it. That's it. I'm still a
student of the market. Markets are
forever trading uh changing as well. We
need to be adaptive.
How often do I follow the indicators
that pop up? That pop up. You mean this?
I mean, this was a good buy signal,
right? We bought in here at the same
time, right? But the best time to trade
flow zones are really when we're in a
trend day. So, a trend day would be
outside of initial balance technically
where we have strong trend developing
outside of liquidity being built. Those
are the best times to use it. So when we
go into trend days, you know, let's say
today for example was above the IB.
Let's pretend we didn't have supply up
here and we built lots of volume out and
the profile, you know, maybe looked
something a bit more like this and this
and this. This is like a typical trend
day profile. And this and every dip's
getting bought. Then we'd use flow zones
for dips, right? It just shows you good
good areas that you might be interested
in buying off. Yeah, we're going to do
give. Yeah, we do giveaways. I didn't
realize 9:00 already.
Why did market stop moving this early?
Which no one's You got to think, guys,
like everyone's probably feeling like
me. It's been a decent year. We've had
big moves this year. Last week we did
that rebalance higher um or rebalance
back into range.
Most people were shutting it down for
Christmas and holiday season, right? So,
even for me, I don't I rarely drink.
Saturday I got well stuck in champagne
for breakfast. I got stuck in at lunch.
I had a cigar. Anyone who's following me
would have seen big fat cigar and a lot
of whiskey yesterday. I'm going to be
honest with you. I took big fat gummy so
that I could sleep well. Woke up this
morning thinking I can't really be
bothered to trade, but if it sets up, it
sets up. Most people are like that, but
they're dealing with probably two or
three rugrats running around their house
right now with a killer hangover and
can't be [\h__\h] to turn up at their
trading desk, as in at the banks and
stuff. So you're going to see lower
liquidity. You're not going to see lots
of liquidity probably return until
January. All right. The volume's going
to be down. So that's why [snorts] the
market's gone to sleep.
The funding next account 100k draw down
is 3K and the profit target is 6K
compared to 50K. I think that's right.
Yeah, it's on sale right now for 50k
price, but you know, you're only getting
$500 extra of draw.
Yeah, exactly. Troy said it best. The
Robins Cup, in fact, the Robins Cup in
every single trading competition ever,
including real traders trading market
every day, is won by orderflow traders
says everything because you need to see
what's actually happening.
Um, I've been full-time since I started
a long time ago. You go and watch all
the interviews. I won't explain it, but
I I was going to do this for a job and
then I had a rather good career and came
back to it. I was investing in
16, 17, 18, even in private equity
before then and then came back to the
charts full-time uh maybe six, seven
years ago.
Do I ever use TPO? Uh, occasionally I'll
look at it uh for single prints, but
normally I can kind of see those areas
as low volume nodes anyway. So, but you
can use them. Again, there's videos on
my channel for free learning how to do
that.
ICT said before December 31st we're
going to alltime highs. I mean,
you never know, but you know, he also
said he was kidnapped, put in a van, and
taught how the market works. And he
created the algo. So,
Did I trade yesterday? No. You mean
Sunday night? No, I didn't. I didn't. I
don't trade overnights.
[laughter]
Uh, is that is that your is that your
choice there, Matt?
>> I do like nice Montristo. What did I
smoke at the weekend? I smoke
hea blue at the weekend. It was nice.
And uh what do I drink? Blue label.
Blue label. Um do I know why Trader does
not provide auto stop when trading multi
account? Seems very unfair and
manipulative. Is this common? What do
you mean, Greg? Doesn't provide auto
stop.
Do you mean like a max loss on a day or
an ATM kind of strategy? I don't trade
on trade of eight, so I I'm not sure.
So, I've never really used it.
Good for you. I think that's going to be
a w Kelvin. It's going to be a wise
choice for you moving to Lucid.
Do you like a an
volume price analysis book? I have not
read it. Not read it.
I saw an OG trader 30 years saying that
futures isn't the same anymore. Gamma
OT. Yeah, I I saw that video and I saw
people saying like, "Oh, he needs to get
over it." Um he he is he is right. He is
right and I've maintained that and
that's why I've like started paying more
attention to it. You have to understand
right zero DTE changed everything in the
markets. You have to understand that uh
because until when did they come in like
three years ago. The extra liquidity
created by those is massive. It is like
a gambler's addiction and they can move
the markets fast. Right. So, he is right
to an extent. It doesn't mean there's no
edge. Um,
do futures have the most edge? No. I'm
going to be honest with you. The futures
market does not have the most edge. Uh,
the biggest edge probably comes in small
caps if I'm honest. Um, that's where
most edge is in the market because
really your edge is created where
opportunity is. And opportunity comes
where people get offside. Now, you can
see that's how we trade in this market
every day. Okay, we're looking for
offside traders. The biggest offside
traders will come in small caps because
they are the most manipulated market
going, right? You're talking about [\h__\h]
stocks with [\h__\h] all PE with no cash on
hand that need to like constantly cycle
money to pay themselves. That's the the
best edge will be there. And a lot of
those small caps won't have zero DTE
either. So, you've got like a guy on the
book pumping pumping pumping and pumping
looking for his exit. That's that's
probably like once you understand the
markets, it's probably one of the best
markets to trade, but they've been very
sleepy for a few years. So, we'll see.
Um,
sorry guys, there's so many messages
here. I'm trying to read through them
all. A+ setup. Uh, like we talked about
it earlier, maybe you weren't here. when
we leave higher time f higher time frame
volume trapped happens fairly regularly
especially in this market when we've
developed a big range and we leave or
where we've done an overextended one
move one way or the other and then we
leave that volume that's my A+ uh we had
a few we had one last week off the lows
we had two last week off the highs so we
had three in the last week which is
fantastic
you get volume profile on trade of eight
I believe so Yes. Do you generally enter
trades with limit prices or market? Uh
but I always try and get in on a limit
if possible. I want my price on a uh to
get in on a limit if I'm forced to chase
a little bit. And I don't mean like 40
50 60 points after. But if I've got a
limit dangling and I can't get filled, I
will take a market break if I have to.
If I know if I'm if it's very high
probability that we're going one
direction, then I'd rather be in than
not be in. But I'll obviously have to
size down a bit if I'm forfeiting
optimal price.
Um,
what's my opinion on the orb strategy?
No opinion. I It can work. There's
nothing wrong with the opening range.
Some people trade 30 secondond opening
ranges. Um, as long as it works for you,
it's all that matters. I've got videos
on it.
I take one receiver in my first two
picks.
Okay. I don't I don't know. We're not
talking about football here, I don't
think. Um,
can he glick trade small caps? I have
not. Guys I used to watch uh were like
uh Nate Investors Underground. Um Ricky
Analog,
um
God,
my brain's so fried. Let me get up. Um,
I have all the old courses and guys I
used to trade with.
Uh, Steven Ducks,
they all trade the same way. It's all
it's it's all trap trap people at the
highest with failed follow through, but
none none of them use like advanced
techniques. Interestingly, well, none of
them teach it.
Trade of eight states market bracket
orders are not supported on group mode.
Is that right? That's terrible. That's
terrible. I'm sorry to hear that. Well,
then what you want to do is just put
your limit in and um put your first
order in and put your uh stop in
straight away as soon as possible. I'm
on top step and having no issues. Well,
makes a change. Alex, done for the day.
Green every account without a copier.
Really appreciate your help. Awesome
work. Do you ever have a person an
in-person mentor? Did you learn all of
my stuff online and through learn learn
experiences was the best experience for
me. Uh I'll tell you what, most my
learnings came from what not to do from
people that I would join and follow and
um you know more of what not to do than
what to do I would say is what I
learned. Um
or works well with volume. Yeah. in can
be.
Uh, yes, I'm in LA for the holidays, my
friend. Not going anywhere. Not back to
Europe. I'm not a fan of Black Label.
Oh, or even the Blu-ray label. I was at
my house, but I was at I can show you.
I've got quite quite a big collection
here, but uh it was it was I was not
hosting. I was drinking. Back to Blue
Zone again. Um yeah, we're just you can
see you can see this node we're
developing guys. We're we're inside
this. Okay. And this has become your
shelf and here
and it's starting to get a little bit
messy in here. Right. This is why I've
like become less interested. I think we
got probably the best trades. You could
have argued if we drove out higher I
would have been willing to play that
down this morning like we talked about
in Discord.
Um no trades. Lots of you saying no
trades. Say that's right.
was in the long trade on ES at 10:38. Is
that an A+? Let me have a look. Probably
not an A+, but it's probably a good
intraday trade. 10:38.
I would say that's an A trade for me.
Yeah. So, you have the look below. It's
really nice. It's very similar to this.
Um,
the only thing I'd say is we didn't The
difference is right, ES didn't sweep all
of this. Remember on ENQ we swept all of
this.
So, oh, the S the SMT just the
divergence was that NQ swept this. All
right. So, you had three drive attempts
lower on ES. Let's think about what
you've done on ES. Three attempts lower.
One, two, three. All right. We pin.
There's your initial balance. Okay. And
we cannot
sustain the auction lower. So what are
we looking? Market's looking for value.
So it thinks we're too expensive. So it
comes down. It's like, well, is this too
cheap? The answer is yes. You trade up,
you reclaim, and you go back to the
upside. And then you've got lots of
people to aim for, haven't you? This is
your gamma level. And once you get
through that here, and this was the
lowhanging fruit previous week high,
which we're now at. All right. So the
the trade's gone. This is why I saying
the lowh hanging fruit trade was from
here to here and here. This is the move,
right? That's the move. It's been and
gone. Can it go higher? Yeah. Can it
come back down? Yeah. But the a the a
trade is there. So, it's a great trade.
38s.
Um I mean, we can even have a look to
see
what happened at the lows.
load my template. No,
you're not going to give me a template
here.
You're not fantastic.
All
right. And look at the low at that low
that we just talked about. Right at the
low, you had 179 sellers caught offside.
Right. So that was your clue that you
trapped the sellers there and then even
the candle before. So where was sellers
coming in late like we talked about
underneath initial balance. All right.
So that's the look below initial balance
and fail. It's a fantastic trade.
Whoever just asked was that A+. I
wouldn't necessarily say it's A+, but
it's an it's a a an Agrade setup. A+ on
the day, but we're not leaving higher
time frame, but it's a great setup.
[snorts]
Alex, squat, bench, or deadlift? What's
my favorite to lift? Uh, when my
shoulder's not hurting, uh, probably
deadlift and then and then back and
then, uh, bench. Squat I hate, but have
to do it.
Ever checked out another Brit running
trader reality with colorcoded? Ever
trade up another Brit running trader
reality?
No idea. No idea, man.
How do I think Asia will act? No idea
either.
What's the toughest part in starting the
40 accounts? Uh, well, getting them
pasted and then the first couple months.
And then the other thing you got to be
careful was like even I had it today
like surprise surprise the accounts
which went a little bit wonky today even
when I was just like flipping them was
my Lucid accounts.
So you need to be careful. Sometimes the
data can go a bit funny. So it's it's
making sure you're managing those
properly.
Thank you so much, man. I couldn't make
more sense. That couldn't make more
sense. What? No. No. What not to do? Am
I wrong here? You can't expect
consistent profits from an inconsistent
market. Instead, maybe six days, no
money on the last 10k. Yeah, I'd say
that's pretty fair, Matt. Um,
and a lot of that will come down to you
understanding like what conditions you
trade well in. So, if if you trade if
there are certain conditions you trade
really well in, then those are the
conditions you should focus on. For
example, uh many who have been here a
long time will know that in here I was
going crazy. I was like I really can we
please I was saying prayers to the
market god saying please can we leave
this range this twoe balance. I really
don't want to be in here. This is I
don't like trading rotation. So look at
look above and fell above and fell look
below fell look below fell. Look below
fell. So in here it was see money take
money. Hardly made any money for two
weeks. And then in here
it was two and 300 point bangers on
stream. All right. As soon as we left
that, these are the markets I like.
Boom, boom, boom. And then here, boom,
boom, boom. All right. Brilliant. And in
here, no. And that's just me. That's
that's just how I like to trade. It
might be the opposite to you, but I
think if you know your data where you
trade well, like I always talk about and
this is why golf is not a game perfect
is a good book, right?
Basically, the sentiment of that whole
book is if you are starting to play
golf, you want to start using like an
eight iron or something. And if you're
good with the eight iron, get used to
going around 18 holes or nine holes,
whatever it is, with that eight iron as
much as possible. You are much better on
like a par four or par five to play your
eight iron and finish that as three over
than you are to get a driver out and you
know spoof the f first one put it in the
bunker then put it in the pond and then
you know you're 10 over on that hole.
That would be the equivalent to taking a
setup which is not your best setup.
Right? You will make more money by
avoiding setups which you do not like
and just trading setups you you will
like than just clicking trying to trade
every setup.
What are you using to copy trade with
Ninja? Uh I use affordable indicators
trade copier.
Yep, that order flow is on uh is on
Trading View. Yeah, if you got a pro
account, you can get it.
All right. Should we do some giveaways,
folks?
No, not a new record. Last week was was
record. [snorts] Last week was amazing.
I think one day we had 800 viewers and
incredible,
right? Smash that like button for me and
uh let's do an Apex giveaway.
Maybe we give away some other stuff as
well.
I'm feeling kind today.
Uh,
yes. Affordable indicators trade copy.
That's right. SFC.
Yeah, it's good. It's good. My advice is
not to use web- based platforms, I
think, you know, because you can have
API and web issues.
Um,
can I show how to set up? Yeah, I'm
going to do a video on it, but just so
you know quickly, up here in the candles
where you have your candles,
you want to come down and on there you
want to click volume footprint.
Volume footprint and that will bring it
up. That's all you need to do.
I'll [snorts] do a video on how to set
it up. Okay, let's first of all give
away an Apex account. So, just type FZT
in chat. You only need to type it once,
folks. Don't spam, otherwise it will
pull you out of the competition. Just
type FCT once in chat. We'll give you
guys a couple minutes to do that. While
that's happening, I'm going to get a
refill on my coffee stick here and we're
going to pull winner. Maybe maybe we
give away some fun stuff today. Let's
see. Let's see.
All right, you guys done?
Give you guys like 15 more seconds or
something.
Okay. Five.
3 Don't spam it. Two.
One.
Braveheart 180.
Are you here? Braveheart 180.
Yeah. Congratulations, Braveheart. All
right. All I want you to do
Shoot me an email. Send me an email. I'm
going to make a list of you. Got to come
back to Joe as well. All right.
Braveheart
180. All right. info@flowzonerader.com.
I want you to send me a screenshot
of you logged into your YouTube so I
know it's you and I will sort you out
with a free Apex uh course course code.
Gosh.
info@flowzonerader.com.
All right. What's my preferred prop
firm? Um, SFC. I literally just did a
video on my top five for the year. It It
all depends on you and I go over
everything in that video. Literally went
live yesterday. It's worth watching.
It's probably 20 minutes long, but I
gave you my top five firms and who who
they're good for and why for all of
those. Okay, let's
set this up again.
Okay, type course in chat. We're going
to give away the introduction course.
So, these are good for people who have
never traded before. Okay. So, if you've
traded before
and you don't want to do the course, you
can give it to a friend or family
member, or you can just say in chat,
we'll reroll it. Um, I'm feeling kind.
So, I'm going to give three of these
away today. Christmas. I'm feeling kind.
You guys have been great. So, we give
three away. Give you a couple minutes to
do this.
Man, it is amazing. I'm on like a lot of
Zillow lists for um houses down in Palm
Springs and they are just balling in
price.
Getting tempting. It's getting tempting.
All right, 10 more seconds, folks.
Sip of this coffee and then we'll pull
the winners and do one at a time.
All right, winner number one for the
introduction course. Oh, there we go.
SFC.
Um, I know you're here, SFC. Do you want
the course or do you want me to reroll
it? Are you experienced or you want to
give it to a fam family member?
Totally up to you. Just let me know in
chat if you want me to roll it for
someone else or if you want to use it or
give it to a family member or a friend
or whatever you want to do.
You'll take it. Awesome. Okay. Again,
just same thing. Shoot me uh an email,
please. info@flowzonerader.com.
All right, and then I'll sort you out
with the course.
Okay, we're going to we're going to do
two more giveaways of this introduction
course. Remember, it's just a two-hour
course. It's great for people who've
never traded before who don't understand
anything. Right, you don't need to type
it again, guys. Don't don't type it
again. Don't type it again. Right,
everyone's already in. We're going to do
a roll now.
Fall forward. Well, full forward
definitely doesn't need it. He's
definitely knows how to trade order
flow. But do you want it full forward?
Do you want to give it to someone or
you keeping it as well?
Roll it. You want me to roll it? That's
very kind of you. Are you sure? Okay,
cool. Well, everyone say thank you to
Fall Forward. That's very kind of him.
We're going to roll it then. New winner
coming. Three, two, one.
Juan Cavallio. Juan Cavalio.
Are you here? Juan Cavallio.
No, SSC doesn't need You just need to
email me with a screenshot of you logged
in to YouTube so I can just check. I'll
double cross your username. Yeah, just
so I know it's you. Congratulations,
Juan Cavallio. First time in. Nice. All
right, dude. So, if you just do the same
thing, I just need you to email me
info@flowzontenttrader.com
with you logged in. Just a screenshot of
you logged into YouTube and you're going
to get a free course as well.
Introduction course.
Yeah, exactly. Full forward saying he
wants commissions on the payout. Quite
right, mate. Quite right.
[laughter]
Okay, one more reroll.
Three,
two, one, let's go.
Rya, I don't know how to say that. Ray
Amaranti. Maybe I've said it wrong. If
I've butchered that, I'm terribly sorry.
Ray Amaranti, are you here? Ray. Ray
Amaranti 4768. I hope I'm saying that
right.
Making a list of everyone's names here.
Are you here? Ray, you got to speak up.
So, R A Y A M A. There you are. There
you are. Awesome. Do you want the
course, Ray? It's an introduction
course. It's two hours long. It's very,
very beginner, but if you want it,
you're welcome to have it.
I'm assuming you want it. Okay. Same
thing. So, just shoot me an email. Just
email me info@flowzoneontrader.com.
I need a screenshot of you logged into
the YouTube. All right. send me a
picture screenshot of you logged into
your YouTube. I've taken a note of
everyone's names here. So, I've got Joe
that I need to reply to. Braveheart 180
for uh
the uh Apex code,
SFC for the course, Juan Cavalio for the
course, and Ray for the course.
Congratulations everyone. We'll do the
same tomorrow. I'll give I'll give away
uh some more Apex codes tomorrow as
well.
All right, you can see guys, the market
has absolutely gone to sleep here. All
right, the market's gone to sleep. This
is what this was our expectation for the
day. You'll have to see what happens. ES
is holding initial balance really,
really well in creating a new range. Um,
a lot of this is going to be down to
Apple. Can Apple find a bid? If we look
at the MAG, I'll give you a readout
before we leave for the day. All right,
Tesla 2.84% 84% up. Nvidia 1.15% up.
Microsoft basically flat. Meta basically
flat. Google 3/4 of a percent up. Amazon
a third of a percent up. But Apple 0.61%
down today. I think there was uh more
pressure on them over some court cases
in Europe this morning. Please can I
type the email? Yes, I will type the
email in chat here. Type it in chat for
you.
info.
Can I tell you the issues with the rules
at funding tics? Uh, yeah, I can. For
anyone that's not been here for the last
week, all right, I'm going to stop my
partnership with them. Um they haven't
replied to a few things but they put in
some new rules which are um
well they're retroactive so they're
doing it over profits that you've
already secured. So any trade which
lasts less than one minute they're
wiping those profits. You can't take a
trade for less than one minute. Uh
they're moving to an 8020 split. You
would have seen at the weekend they're
now including weekends and the days that
you must trade even when the market's
closed. Those guys in Discord will see
that I lost an account this weekend
because I didn't trade on a Saturday.
Are you [\h__\h] kidding me? So, these
guys can go to hell. Um, the CEO is not
replying to people right now. I have
sent him a couple of emails last week.
I've been trying to avoid bashing them.
I never want to bash someone online. I
give someone always a chance. But, uh,
there you go. There you go. Radical
saying they took $3,500 out of his
rewards. I mean, this this is the issue,
right? it it's it's an issue over there.
Um I can't deny it. I'm I've been trying
to give them a chance to come back and
answer it. And I think a lot of guys
that traded with them who probably have
more influence than I do have been doing
the same thing, trying to give them a
chance to come back and be like, "We
shouldn't have done that. We're going to
we're going to change it." They're not.
The guy's gone [\h__\h] missing, guys.
We're not getting any response at all.
Um we're talking about funding ticks.
Funding ticks, right? So, unfortunately,
I have taken some nice payouts from
them. Um, but you would have seen
they're not in my top five. They're not
going to be in my top 50 if they're
going to act like this.
Oh, exactly, Richard. I mean, it's an
absolute joke. It is an absolute joke.
They might fold. I doubt they're going
to fold, guys. Um, I think it's more
that they're probably having to pay out
too much and they've just made sure that
they don't have to pay out. I doubt they
fold. Funding pips is pretty big. Um, so
I don't think they're fold, but
it's up to you, Neil. It's just you've
got to be aware of the new rules. Uh,
for me, I don't want to promote them on
stream, right? Like,
I [\h__\h] love JD. Oh, I'd love a bear
with you one day, JD. You're funny.
[laughter]
Oh god, it's so good.
I have my own account, mate. Um, but I I
mainly use it for swings swings and
ETFs.
No, they're they're the only one.
They're the only one right now. So,
I'll put a video up, guys. There's my
top five. Let me find it for you guys.
There's a top five. um
firms that I think you should be using
for next year and and why. The important
thing is to understand why which which
one's good for you and why because
everyone's different. Um let me put put
this in chat.
All right. Watch this video. If you're
thinking about getting funded next year,
you want to go for like 40 accounts and
roll them together. Watch that video.
[snorts]
Um let's answer the last few of these.
currently with TPT. I like TPT, but I
lost an account because I held a
position past 2:00 Pacific.
Re what? They didn't just close you out,
SFC.
And that's new news to me. I've never I
mean I've never been in that situation,
but
that's uh
I'm surprised there's not an auto
liquidation there. Have you emailed
them? I would email them about that.
Uh it you're welcome to like him. It's
it's because someone was getting very
funny about it earlier. So the you
always get a Marmite or we call a
Marmite Marmite person. and Marmite
situation. I don't know what you call
Marmite in the US. I don't know if you
even have it, but something that some
people really like and some people
really don't like, right? One of those
characters. I've got no problem with his
teachings. My problem is when people
think they're his teachings. That's the
difference.
I'm really sorry to hear that about TPT.
I've never had it happen to me because
I've never been in that position, but
I'm That's a shame. It's a shame they
don't autoquidate.
Um, it might be worth you can probably
put something in uh like Ninja Trader or
uh a copier to auto liquidate you at
certain time to stop that ever
happening.
Marmite uh Marmite is like it's like a
salted spread that you put on toast and
some people love it and some people hate
it. So if you have something that like
if you have some a piece of art for
example and you don't know if people
like it, you'd be like, "Oh, it's a
Marmite thing." Some people love it,
some people hate it. Very English. Very
English of me.
There you go. Yeah. See, like there's
nothing wrong with it. They work. They
work. I'm not going to say like fair
value gaps aren't a thing or OBS isn't a
thing. OBS is it's a break and retest,
right? These are all But it's My problem
is not that. It's when you get defensive
people saying he invented it and don't
this and he didn't invent it. He didn't
invent it but his teachings can work.
It's a big difference. The same way I
didn't invent volume profile or order
flow but my teachings can work but I
didn't invent it.
There you go. So info says anyone using
Sierra they have an auto liquidate on a
specific time. They probably have it on
most platforms. You just have to uh have
to dig in and find how to do it.
How was my morning? Yeah, it was all
right. Um most of them I flipped. I can
show you.
These are my accounts. So most of them I
flipped and then
one, two, traded three accounts with
size. And then these ones dragged. There
you go. That's that's me for the day.
Yeah. So these are all flipped. This
one, even the ones that are red, these
should all be eight bucks. But this what
I'm saying like you have to be careful
when you link them all together. Some of
them get a bit of a lag on it. Well, at
least that's what I experience fairly
commonly. And you got to be careful with
the APIs, right? Especially on trade of
eight. Once you move into uh linking
accounts together, you can get some
issues.
There you go, Mike. Yeah, it's a good
example. It's a good example.
Oh, that's weird. SFC, that's annoying,
bro. Just one thing. Do we need to buy
tools to trade the way you trade? No,
you don't need to buy tools. Uh th this
is this is free. Orderflow. Um I don't
know what package you have on um Trading
View. If you're trading on Trading View,
it it is free. Orderflow is free if
you're trading with Trader of even on a
prop firm. So if you're trading with the
trade of eight package, order flow is
free on trader trade ovate. It will be
free on ninja trader. Again, there's a
video on my YouTube how to get it for
free for trading on there. So no, you
don't need to pay for anything
additional if you don't want to. Um,
fair value gap is just a guide of
confirmation. That's it. There you go.
There you go, Mike. All we need is for
you to move the market. So I'm not
moving anything. We're about to leave
this volume here. So, we could come
right down into here if we if if they
start to not bid this. You can see we
built all these buyers can potentially
get trapped there. If they reject this,
we can come all the way back down to
here because they built out this shelf.
All right. And if they do this and
reclaim and they go back to the upside,
but I'm not going to trade this anymore.
I'm done for the day for sure.
I'm only planning to scale up to about
six to eight accounts on trade of eight
and I cannot copy trade if I want to
utilize my ATMs. That would be your
recommendation how to handle that. Three
to four. You don't want to copy trade or
sorry let me read that again. I'm only
planning on scaling up to six to eight
accounts on trade. Okay. And I cannot
copy trade if I want to utilize the
ATMs. Okay. Understood.
What would be your recommendation on how
to handle that three to four screens? I
would just I wouldn't I would just go
one one at a time. If you if you're not
going to copy trade you to an ATM, trade
one at a time or move to a system that
you can copy trade on like Ninja so you
can have your ATMs do auto.
You want to learn for free first. Can I
quote any good sources? Uh,
check my channel out. Uh, to start,
honestly, there's so much there for
free. Start there. Um, Hassan, there's a
ton on this channel for free. There's
there'll be tons on the whole of
YouTube. Just just
um yeah, there'll be tons of [\h__\h] as
well. But I stand by everything that I
put on this channel. So, just start
there for free.
Thoughts on Replicanser? I used to use
them SFC and I've stopped using them
because uh they're trying to change to a
subscription model. And I also think
genuinely think that AI um AI affordable
god affordable indicators is a superior
cop
cuz you can have your max profit. You
can literally put in all right this is
the max profit I want on this account.
This is the max draw down I want on this
account. This is the max size I want to
use. I want to trade mini mini and micro
micro on that. Like the the amount that
you can do on it is so good. So if
you're trading lots of prop firms, it's
really good. Like if you have a trading
draw down one, like I could get long.
Let's say I have like TPT,
Lucid, Funded Next, uh and Apex and um
what's the other one? Tradeify all
linked. I could have it so it takes my
Apex as soon as they hit $300, for
example, because they've got a trailing
draw down. So, I just want to lock in
and let the other ones work. So, that's
why I really like it.
Why was I put in timeout for speaking?
Asking which prop firm? I didn't put you
in timeout, mate. It might have been
Nightbot.
I'm sorry.
But yeah, all the prop firms I use,
there's a video just went live. Just
read that.
All right, let's let's make a let's make
a deal here. No more ICT chat. All
right, I stay here 5 minutes longer. We
can have a laugh, but no more ICT chat.
Let's just leave that word and that
person, all of that stuff alone.
[snorts]
looking like shorts might be the move.
Um, if they need to leave this, so they
tried to leave it and they're already
back there. If they keep rejecting PC,
but I don't want to trade this area.
Look how long we've traded this area
for,
right? So, you need to see an aggressive
leave and a resell. And then you got to
ask where we reselling to. still seeing
strength in ES above
um initial balance, but just based at
previous week, I just don't think
there's a a good setup here at the
moment, guys. I'm going to be honest
with you. Like, this is a buildout
liquidity. Can they do this? Yes. Can
they do this? Yes. It's a flip of a coin
right now. There's your profile for the
day. Look,
you want to trade in here? I don't want
to trade in here.
>> [snorts]
>> Uh, I'm not sure, Noah. Actually, uh, I
would, yeah, I would assume so, but
check on their website. I don't like I
don't want to tell you something that's
wrong.
Do I have any vids on order flow using
Trading View Charts? Uh, they're all in
the course at the moment. Unfortunately,
I haven't done any uh free vids. It's on
my list to do next year. But yeah,
everything
if you want to learn order flow um
there is a I'll show you because I do
have a sale running for you guys until
Jan, right? If you want to learn order
flow and how to do it,
use it in trading view and stuff. If you
come here, volume order flow, this only
went live last week. You can do this
course. This is everything that's
covered in the course. au auction theory
volume profile profile types developing
profile delta bookmap footprints
playbooks and repeatable setups and I'm
adding stuff to it all the time which
you will always have access to you click
buy now come down to here and type in
launch
in capitals all right you will get 100
bucks off right now $299 that's going to
be the cheapest it ever is right and
prices will go up next year but this
launch price will last until January So,
you've got like what, a week or two left
to do to do at that price. So, if you do
want to learn that stuff, it's all on
there. Everything is in there for you
guys. [snorts]
No pressure, but that's the only place
where I've got all my order flow stuff
at the moment.
We have a volume channel, right? I'm now
looking for TQQQ.
Does that affect your trade? I'm looking
at that. You're looking for T. No,
you're just playing the trips. So is the
you're you're just playing a triple
leverage. TQQQ
is exactly the same. You're just triple
leveraged versus QQQ, right? So you're
playing the long triple leverage QS. If
you want to play the short, you play
SQQ.
Oh, sorry. Okay, Evan, mate, I'm really
sorry. I don't know why that happened.
Let me tell you. Uh, Funding Tix is the
one doing the nonsense, Evan. That
That's who you want to avoid at the
moment. Okay. Funding Tick. If it booted
you out for whatever reason, it would
just be Nightbot being annoying. I'm
really sorry about that. It's It's It
happens sometimes.
No, the Ninja Trader um NT discount
ended, all that stuff.
Uh yeah, so the course you just won's
like a very introduction course SSC.
It's for people who've like never really
traded before. But if you do that
course, you get money off the beginner
to advance course. That course I just
showed you there is brand new. It's just
on order flow. It's way way way more
advanced. I would say do the do the
20our course first. If you're if you're
interested, say do the 20our course
first because you'll understand how I
view the markets. And then like a top up
to that would be the volume and order
flow if you're interested in that stuff.
Again, no zero pressure
volume channel looks off. What? Compared
to TQ's, is that what you're saying? Let
me have a look.
thinks the same to me. Just might be
that there's less volume traded on this
because this is uh has to include
options. It's the same, mate. It's
exactly the same. You're just stuck in
the same range there or thereabouts.
So, your high is basically this pivot
from
1120 and your low is this pivot from IB
and you're stuck in this pivot into and
around here. Let's go back.
Yeah, it's basically exactly the same.
There's no difference. It's the same
FCT. Since you work with TPT, let the
people here know that they have to close
their positions manually so you don't
get effed over by this in my opinion
stupid rule. Well, we we just talked
about it. I mean, I Yeah, we just talked
about putting stuff in place so that you
are protected against that. I've never
had that problem because I I don't trade
past 4:00. But uh
yeah, it's important to put what you
want to do is put as many tools in place
to prevent issues. So you want auto
liquidation, max stop-loss, max loss on
the day, max trades on the day, like max
number of um like contracts traded, all
these things, max like end of time, all
these things you want to put in auto as
much as possible.
Are you going to try Tradeify Daily
Payout accounts, Alex, or stick with
TPT? I'm going to stick with TPT. I
might do their 5day uh flex accounts
because they've removed the consistency.
Um, yeah, that's what I'm thinking about
going for.
You lost 4K today. How have you lost 4K
today? Sorry to hear that.
Okay, here goes ES trying to break out.
Q's are trying to go with it and if they
do,
they're going to look to come up to this
value error high again. They're going to
look to test this if they can.
So, the rotation still happening. Oh my
god. Let me draw it. This rotation still
happening here to here. Shorts tried to
come in under here. Couldn't get follow
through. Reclaimed instantly. Now we're
going to go back to this side and
they're going to see is there follow
through here or we just going to do this
dance or are we actually going to do
this? ES is breaking out though. Q's
can't move. Apple has been weak. It's
one of the big problems.
All right, guys. I think we're done.
Decent day. Locked in some nice profits
early. Um, I would just watch the
rotations for the remainder of the day
if I was you. What? Just let me check
the volume which came in. VPO is at 700.
Bang in the middle. Is that the same
here? Yeah.
Just check this.
90s.
Yeah, it looks like it wants to go.
You're going to test value area high.
Now, if you find a bid above this, I'd
watch this imbalance. 33 to 39.
Where did the sellers last come in?
Right here. So, I'll be watching 33 to
39 if you get through the current value
high. And then 75s. Just check this here
as well.
Where is this 720s?
Is there buyers stuck in there? It's a
good transition.
All right.
Yeah. So, all this is is a rotation till
you find acceptance. So, you're pinned
from here to here right now. This is the
current rotation. If you find acceptance
over this, like those levels I just
talked about up into here to repric, if
they really want to squeeze, you got to
take this out to get it back up to the
New York high. And in here, I would
leave alone. All right. In this level
here, I'd leave alone. You need to see
if we find acceptance or not. But we're
in a fairly standard bell curve. So, I'd
be somewhat careful about buying much
above here, unless it really shows
itself and they build out like a new
shelf here. I'd be very very careful
because it's very possible we do
something like this and then just come
straight back down inside which is why
I'm going to try and avoid it.
But we will see. ES is uh is starting to
get going for you guys now. But that's
that's going to be it for me. I'm going
to lot this up for the day. We'll come
back tomorrow. Last day tomorrow before
Christmas um that we're going to trade.
We'll see what we'll get. Again, very
light in volume. We'll do some more
educational stuff tomorrow. We'll do
some more giveaways. Where's the VIX
coming into here? Let me just check
this. This is a big level. But where's
it from? This is a long time ago.
September 18.
Okay. I just watch VIX once we move from
1430s down to 1440s. Uh we've never
really been able to move under that. So
you might find that they hedge a bit on
the VIX as we get into that. So just be
cautious.
Wait, can I ask you one more question?
No worries. If not, it just came back to
stream. I can wait. Yeah, just ask. Ask
Matt. Ask now,
what do you mean by an an order of
priority? Pat, everything's higher time
frame for me. So,
weekly, daily, 4 hour, hour. The higher
it is, the more powerful it is for me.
on the point of knowing what not to do.
In the last two months, I've been up 14K
and cashed out 10K, but I lost all of it
both times
by going back
in after the market closed. Is that one
of your rules? After the market closes,
it seems to plateau, but I get excited
and go back in. Yeah, there's no The
only time I would trade outside of New
York hours. All right. The only time is
if there's a reason. You've got to
understand volume is king. So, let's
just show you what happens in the after
hours.
Look at the difference in volume.
Pre-market, New York open, after hours.
Right. All of this is after hours,
market open. Right. We're going to
respect. It's funny you say that. We did
a lesson on it last week. We're going to
respect levels way more in the New York
session because there's volume being
traded there, not past volume, current
order book. Remember, when we get into
after hours, there's no one on the book
or it's much much thinner on the book.
So, we can skip around. Your spread can
open up. Um, it doesn't mean there
aren't good trades to be had there, but
you're going to have to be very accurate
on when and why you're getting in. If
you're just clicking buttons cuz you
want to be here in the after hours, then
yeah, you're going to give your money
back. All right,
UIX. I mean, in the NE, it's a funny
one, isn't it? Like
[sighs] over a holiday season. No, but I
think in January probably
RTH, mate. Yeah, RTH. The one on the
right side, RTH. Right. developing
volume RTH
pat I meant as far as looking at QZS VIX
and spy. Oh, okay. Um I don't give one
prefer. It's not like I give one more
validity than the other. So why would I
look at VI VIX? The relationship between
Vix and Spy. If we're getting divergence
where Vix and Spy are going the same
way, it's like a leave alone time for
me, right? So if Vix is starting to push
and Spy is still pushing, I'm like, well
that's not healthy. something's going to
go wrong there. When looking at SPY or
ES versus the Q's, right, we're all
we're looking for there is relative
strength. All we're really looking to
understand is what is the market
breadth, right? Because spy the breadth
would be bigger, more less waiting into
tech, more looking at like energy and
the finances. So, if we got a good
breath day
like we've probably got today, if I go
on Finn Viz and I have a look at the
breadth, I would imagine everything
really is pretty green. There we go. So
if we think about what the weakest thing
is
right now, all right, it's Apple. All
right, it's Apple that's holding cues
down. We look at finances, they look
good. Healthcare pretty good. All right,
Eli and Lily, not the best, but it's not
too bad. Most things are green, right?
So tech lagging a little bit from Apple,
but the breadth is good, which is why
you've got ES making bigger moves.
There's GlobeEx, so it's starting to go
now. It is such a shame they took so
long, but maybe could have traded that
reclaimer so low on volume. It's not
worth it over lunch in my opinion.
Trade the highest liquidity, highest
volume parts of the day and be done. I
agree. Once you truly learn what's going
on, you will realize all you need is
three to five good trades per week to
make great money. Yeah, even less, man.
One really banger of a trade a week or a
month, make all your money. I mean, if
you've read Market Wizards, you will
know all those guys who made mega mega
money. Market Wizards, very rarely are
they scalpers. They're position traders.
Um, right from the 80s up to now,
they're positioned and they're looking
for one big setup to come into their
life that they position for and that's
where they make the big big money.
Everything in between is pretty much
break even. Win some, lose some, win
some, lose some, win some, lose some,
and then boom, there's your big boy. All
right, peace and love everyone. That was
a nice little chat for an extra hour
here while we just hung out over
Christmas. Um, I will see you tomorrow
morning. I will be back here tomorrow
morning. Don't forget if you want to
support the stream. The links are down
below. I do get commissions when you use
code FCT or code flow zone on TPT. And
that money goes back into the stream. It
helps me provide this for free and
upgrade things like the lights and
everything else. Anyway, hope you
hopefully you enjoyed today, made some
money, or if not, hopefully I kept you
safe and you learned something. I'll be
back tomorrow morning. Trade safe this
afternoon. Don't expect big volume to
come back, right? You might just see a
very sleepy market. If you get a sleepy
grind higher market, do not try and fade
it. All right? If you get a sleepy grind
higher market, don't try and fade it.
Either be in it for the grind higher or
be flat. All right? Peace and love.