Morning everyone.
Good morning. Hope you're doing well.
Hope you had a good afternoon. If you
continued to trade that range rotation
yesterday, if you are a range trader,
well, last couple of days, definitely
yesterday was your market. That was your
time to shine with 200 points rotations
happening many, many times over. Okay,
we're going to start as always in the
daily chart. So let's just zoom into
here. The first thing I want to point
out is we are developing quite a thick
profile in here. And it's not really
surprising, is it? Because we were here
in September, we were here in October,
we were here in November, and we're here
in December. All right. So we've spent
now a good portion of four months in
this range. And you can see the edges
are starting to develop and build out.
All right. So we know we're in a thick
profile, which means in here we will
normally rotate. All right. And when we
leave the profile, we can be drastic,
but right now probably going to be a bit
like what we saw over here until we
prove otherwise. If we zoom into what
we've had this current week, right,
we're into Friday. We have to think
about this current week. Here is Monday,
Tuesday,
Wednesday, and Wednesday is the bar
right now, which is kind of setting the
tone for the week. So Thursday, like we
talked about yesterday, was highly
likely to be inside of Wednesday. We
currently have Friday inside of Thursday
and inside of Wednesday. All right, so
this is the rotation. You can see every
time we've poked up into here, we found
sellers. All right, we found sellers
here on Tuesday and Wednesday and
Thursday. Has this supply been chewed
through enough or is it time for a bit
of a bigger push? Time will tell. Um,
we're going to talk about these bowls.
All right, they're starting to come into
compression. So the longer we sit here,
the more these bowls are going to start
joining. So you might see by next week
it's going to be a light trading week,
but maybe by next week we end up being
somewhere like this. So we have
compression in the Ballingers and then
they will start to open up once we break
either side of it. So everything's
starting to coil and tighten up in this
market.
Um things to be aware of today. All
right, it is uh rollover triple
witching. All right, historically quad
but triple now. Right, so you've got all
contracts rolling over today. It's
expiry day
for your dailies because now we have
dailies, your dailies, your weeklies,
your monthlies, your yearlies, and uh
also for uh futures. All right, there
are over $7 trillion at play right now
expiring today in the options market. So
don't be surprised to see some wonky
moves. All right. Some pushes that fail,
some dips that rip. Like it all depends
where these funds need to pin price or
if they need to pin price. It is indeed
I just see someone say that apparently
the largest ever. It is indeed the
largest ever options expiry. Options uh
markets getting bigger and bigger mainly
due to the zero DTE. There's been a lot
of hedging taking place over the last uh
couple weeks definitely if not months.
All right. And it has been a bit bit
heavier than recent than um in recent
times on the put ratio. Okay. Okay,
let's move into the hourly chart. We'll
go over the current week, right? So, you
can see current week's profile,
developing profile, nice big D-shape. No
acceptance below, no acceptance above.
All right, this is a rotational market
in the current week. Profiles telling
you the current week is in a rotational
market. If we look at the previous day
value, well, it's right here. All right,
so the only people that are stuck right
now are these shorts from Wednesday.
This is why we played long off their
pain point yesterday. So every pain
point into here, we were long back up
inside. You can see no breakout of the
top side. Why? Because we're in range.
Nothing's changed. All right. So those
that were here yesterday, nothing's
changed. We are in exactly the same
situation. Literally, quite literally,
absolutely nothing has changed. We might
be opening up, well, open up almost
identical to yesterday. So what are the
plays? You need to be very aware of
breakouts and failed breakouts today.
All right. If we're in a range and
they're going to keep us in a range,
failures are often how we're going to
play it. It doesn't have to do that. All
right. The hard thing right now is we
are quite clearly in a strong downtrend.
All right. You got a series of lower
highs and lower lows and lower highs and
lower lows and lower highs and lower
lows. But this is where it gets tricky.
If we think about this rotation,
because if you zoom right out,
we hit the 61,
right? And we bid off it. If we think
about this rotation,
we're into golden zone and we're
starting to hold. This is where it gets
tricky. If bulls are going to do
something here, all right, if they're
going to try and be like, we want the
end to this, right? then they need to
hold this range here and try and and try
and cause a squeeze out right. They
might be better letting it come back
down into here trapping bears and
reclaiming to do it. So that's one thing
I'm very very aware of. Um they will
want the break of fours or whatever it
was yesterday. 410 was where those big
players were. Right? If they can get
through 410, 430, 440 to 500, that's the
big level, right? If they can get here,
then we wait and see how they act. Are
they then able to cause a squeeze up
into sort of 480s, 600s? Does that right
is 500 or even 410 or 600 used as a big
bull trap that bears come down and say
no, no, no, no, no. Back into range you
go. Very, very possible. All right.
Very, very, very possible. So, you have
to be flexible today and willing to be
to play both sides. If you're going to
play, I would say size down. Whatever
contract size you're thinking of using,
half it because uh today could get a
little bit wild, especially as we get
closer into the close. These are
historically days that I don't trade
aggressively, if at all. So, breakout,
fail, breakout,
breakout,
fail, breakout. All right, I'm watching
those. Uh, do I really want to play in
here? What do you reckon? All right,
look what happened earlier in the week.
Look what happened yesterday. Do you
think I want to play in this? No, not
really. Not really. I don't really want
to be participating in there. Um
overnight, we can also talk about uh
Bank of Japan quarter point hike up to
0.75 now. Uh biggest they've had in over
a decade. Okay. But quite possibly, like
I said, crowded trade. Everyone was
calling for the big end of the market
causing the flush. It can take a while.
If you go back and historically look, it
can take a while for that to take
effect. they're really going to start
unwinding. Um, but probably the dramatic
part was priced in which is why when the
announcement came out, we actually saw
relief right in Asia
we come to here. What was it? 11:00 I
think it hit or maybe it was here. There
you go. 10:00 it came early. Right. We
saw relief in the market where everyone
was thinking, "Oh, we're going to die."
Well, we're above the 200. We're above
the 5day. We've already priced it in.
We're seeing relief and relief. All
right. So that's the one thing to be
aware of and you're seeing it now
continuation to drive up. So overnight
we really we saw relief but it's inside
of yesterday's range right GlobeEx Asia
higher uh London higher and then it hit
the big wall came back down found a
rebid and we're going to go up and visit
it again. So this would be one two three
fourth time up here. Just be aware of
that. Eventually you wonder if there's
any sellers left up there. They're going
to start to exhaust themselves.
All right, let's go over some of the
other charts.
We can have a look at ES relative
strength over here. This looks messy
down. Get rid of that all together to be
quite honest. Uh still maintains in that
downtrend. Very similar, right? Strong
downtrend, but the same kind of thing.
hit a big pivot
is trying to form one of these to get
back up into here. That's the change in
tone. Six uh 6,900. I very much doubt we
get through that today. I would imagine
there's monster monster cool walls up
there, but that's what they are trying
to do, but same kind of thing. Have a
look at the spy. All right, you can see
that put wall. We never got into it
earlier in the week. We got close and
everyone covered into it. Um what did I
say yesterday evening? I did put the
gamma in. Let me just have a look
just a second.
600 QQQ to 615 are the big expiry walls
today on Q's. So 600. There you go.
Didn't hit it to 615.
Right. See a big expiry is up here. If
we get over 6 615, we will go into
positive gamma and put potential
squeezes on. So that would be your 500
pivot basically on the ENQ, right? So
nice and easy um in terms of numbers to
think about. Let's look at the VIX.
Probably still dancing in range. Why
does it ruin these every day?
All right, still just in a range. We
just zoom out here. Nothing's changing
for a second. Right? You can just see
we're going pivot pivot pivot pivot.
Right? It can't find acceptance below.
It can't find acceptance above 1750 to
let's just call it 16 or 1550.
That's the rotation. That's the chop.
That's why we're getting this sort of
sloppy.
I wouldn't know what to call it really.
Aggressive aggressive slop. Aggressive
slop maybe is what we call it. Uh let's
just have a look quickly here. Okay.
Still fading back in. Still holding
this. Still haven't broken out of this
is where disaster strikes in my mind.
So, still got price alerts. Oh, maybe I
just deleted that. Still got price
alerts up here. Let's put that back on.
All right, let's have a look at the mag.
Most of them opening up flat, I think.
Yeah. So, slight gap down. I'm just
going to call it flat in Apple. Uh if we
zoom out, it's into this key chop. If it
holds this, we've got that same kind of
downtrend. Relief will be there. It
doesn't have to come today. Might not
come at all, but that's where the relief
will come. Amazon, that looks a bit
stronger than the others right now. So,
we've got that sort of W shape double
bottom holding a possible higher low.
It's looking for relief out. That looks
better. GooG,
not great. inside the range still, but
it's trying. It's gonna have an attempt
to get into this, but you got lots of
stuck buyers up there right now. Uh Meta
being aggressive.
That's a good hold. Still inside
yesterday's range, but that's a good
hold. Uh so all the time Meta's holding
above 660, you look okay for relief.
Microsoft, same kind of story here.
You're seeing the same pattern here set
up over and over and over again. All
right, they've all a lot of these have
sort of feel like they might have
bottomed out. They yesterday they start
to get a run up as long as they can hold
a base. They've got a chance to come and
test the top side of these ranges. This
is the equivalent of the 500 level that
we're looking at in the cues, right? So,
all depends if all the market wants to
move up to supply and what happens when
we get up there. Uh, well, it's back
inside of 75ish
and that's where it needs to stay on
Nvidia. All right. Needs to stay inside
of this to see relief and needs to get
over 78. Right. Over 78. Let's set
another alert there. Over 78.
It's got a chance.
Got four minutes over 78. It's got a
chance. Tesla looks really good. Really,
really, really good. All right. That
one's 500. It is as simple as that.
Breaking out on all time frames. Uh
liquidity built here. If this can get
going, 500's the level. Um that's where
it wants to go. Big big number. Have
they built that in with this now?
Where have my extensions gone? There
they are. Okay. 12s. All right. So, it's
got a chance. Uh Oracle found a bid
yesterday. I'm absolutely fuming about
this. Uh didn't get filled. Remember
those who've been here the last week? We
were looking for the gap for into 78 and
I had some orders just sat down here for
a flush to pick up and uh well we went
in after hours yesterday so maybe we
still get it but that was really nice
gap fill on the daily and 10point ripper
more than 10point ripper and they have
to see if it holds a pullback now for a
continuation or if they just get melted
back down. So I've deleted
uh
my sort of wish orders that I looking to
pick up long. They've gone now. Okay,
let's share the stream. I actually
forgot to share it today. Oops.
Should have done that.
How long we got here? A couple minutes,
folks. Did any of you trade last night?
I'll be interested.
All right.
So, currently holding over previous
day's value area high into this open. We
got a couple minutes left. Morning
everyone. Not going to get a chance to
uh go through all the names, but good
morning.
Good morning. Good morning. Good
morning. Um yes,
the only VRP um
volume I use on that setting VRP uh VP
is on a 30 minute. Everything else um
I'm using anchored or fixed range.
Everything else I'm using anchored or
fixed range. Thank you, John Dennis with
the $20 tip on a Friday for my coffee
and bagel. I appreciate you. Thank you
so much my friend. Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you. Morning all.
So just waiting for us to get into the
open here. We are currently holding
previous day's value. So you know if we
hold a bid here it means they will look
to try and expand yesterday's value.
We've got all this supply overhead that
we got stuck at yesterday and this is
the current week value. Just think about
that.
Yes, exactly the same. We're looking at
exactly the same kind of thing. Is it
going to hold previous day value? Can it
hold the PDC
uh 830s and reach up into 855s and
potentially 870s? That's what it's
trying to do. Whether it can do it or
not is a whole different thing. Getting
a bit whippy here into the open as we
reach up into this supply block above
and GlobeEx and we just see what we get.
All depends if we're going to hold above
value or we're going to go back inside
previous days value. We're already
inside the current week value.
Splash that water my glasses to start
the open. All right. All of the mag
opening up green.
Uh Amazon and Apple flicking green to
red, red to green. Same with Google, but
most of them opening up green. The big
winner this morning, Tesla and Nvidia,
they had a big gapping up and Oracle
obviously almost 5% up. So into this
sort of supply block we got stuck at
yesterday.
Um, we just want to see if we're going
to hold bids this morning for a drive up
or not. Uh, that's what the market
probably wants to do if it's going to
find relief.
It's going to have to hold bids for
drives up if it's going to uh find
relief today. Remember 410 big level
yesterday where we had that trap bar
yesterday. If we start getting through
that, this is value area high on the
current week 30s and then we can think
about um 500s. But yesterday we could
not get through this block here. This
was constantly being faded. So be aware
of that.
If we start holding prints above it, it
is possible that we're going to go. All
right. So next level, if we can hold
prints above 410, we're looking at 30s.
So watching this now into the 10. Are we
going to get an early morning squeeze up
into 30s is the question.
Big buying coming up here. Big seller
just got stuck here. Can they hold above
16s? That's his print there.
16s is the level now. Looking for 30s.
So in this
trimming some here and if we get through
30s, we're going to look for more
upside.
Really nice into 30s. This is current
week. So trimming some here. And if we
drop below 16, I'm out. I'm out now.
Just a little squeeze here to start the
day. Just on one account.
Now we'll just wait. So, we hit current
uh value area high on the week. So, the
trade was just like an early squeeze up
into this. We might well get stuck here
and rotate all the way back down. If we
find acceptance here, then we're going
to think about a move into 500s, but
it's going to become very tricky to buy
up here. Now, I was just playing the
tape there. What I saw back into 30s.
You can see how big this level is at
30s. They keep reacting here. That blue
line across your uh screen right now is
value area high on the current week. If
we get through this and base, we're
going to go for 500s. Um, unfortunately
got knocked out of this, but locked in
some money there
into the 50s. Offside delta here at 50s.
Getting crushed here. Let's go then.
Love a dip now. Mother pluckers.
Always very careful if I do trade the
opening drive.
wasn't planning on doing it, but that
was a bit too obvious today to not take.
So, I'd say TW those 20s are now the
level. Uh buyers will need to hold above
20s
down here just based on footprint,
right? Just based on who got stuck
there. You might not see it in here.
Let's go to a one minute.
All right. Just these lot here. They got
stuck and this guy here. So, we're
getting stuck above 50s. Buyers will
need to hold these 20s, otherwise it's
going to be a problem. They're going to
search for for 500s if they can. At 500,
I would not be surprised to see a fail
breakout, honestly. Uh, Apple's still
dancing red to green. It's currently
red. Amazon's gone red on the day.
Microsoft's gone red on the day just
about. Big winner here. Nvidia right up
to 78 looks slightly. Wasn't that the
level that we just called for a squee
called for a squeeze out over?
Am I getting confused? Almost there.
Almost there. That's the squeeze out
level if it can get above and base above
that on Nvidia. So that's driving the
market up right now. But remember today
would not be surprised to see look above
and fail. It just depends what depends
where they're going to do that. Is it
over yesterday's level which we've just
done or is it over the 500s?
Back down towards these 20s. Remember,
this is where the sellers got stuck. And
if we get under that, we're probably
going to wash back down to the open. If
they hold above that, and those sellers
are going to remain stuck in this market
this morning,
come back down to test them. Buyers
still stepping in there.
Seller still remaining stuck under 20s.
A big buyer got caught earlier up here.
He's come back in at 40s. Reloaded.
Question now is really, do we break out
or is it a fail breakout? We've got
sellers stuck under 20s. A huge buyer
just came in at 43s. So, he's going to
need a breakout otherwise he's going to
get himself caught offside.
He's going to need a breakout otherwise
he's going to get caught offside.
He's trying. He's really trying. He's
coming in aggressively again. And here
we go.
Big buyer got caught there at 60s. It's
getting a little bit messy up here. I'll
be honest, folks. It's moving very, very
quick with some decent size. See,
biggest buyer on the day right now is
40. He came flying in at 40 all the
time. We're above that. He's
comfortable. If we get below that, I'm
telling you, he was massive size. He
came flying in 373 lot in one go. So, we
need to hold price above him for more
upside. Otherwise,
down. All right. If we start getting
underneath his entry point, we're going
to see weakness. Seller just tried to
come in here to force us back under his
points. So, we're going to come and test
him by the looks of it. Where did I say
it was? 45. 4325 is where he actually
is.
It looks like it wants upside. It's just
a bit frothy here. I've had a couple
goes at it. Locked in some good money,
but I want to be careful. Telling
myself, come on, mate. Don't be buying
too late in the day. We can play the
pain point but not beyond that.
Uh from uh Sunday open current weeks
from Sunday open. Lots of buyers just
caught got caught there at 55s. I'm
going to let this shake out for a
minute. We're back down to this big
buyers entry point. He's 42s
and he's pulled his bid. There you go.
So he's out
back down to value area low. This is
starting to look more and more messy by
the minute. So not surprising with OPEX.
So we're going to test this entry point
at 42s again and see if this is a trap.
And if not, sellers should sell through
now.
If they can stay underneath 42s,
that's their job at the moment.
And if we start coming back under VWAP
from previous day high, then you know
this will be the look above and fail
that we talked about. This red box
should become support. So if this does
not become support, all right, then this
will be the look above we talked about
this morning. This will be the look
above and fail if we start seeing one of
these. All right, which is why I wanted
to be very careful trimming my profits,
hoping we got all the way up to 500. We
didn't. The shift in the tape started to
come.
It just depends if we see this. Oh, I
just thought I just turned that. If we
see this become support now or not. Can
they offer this as a support range?
sure it's correct.
All right. So, do they hold dips into
these levels? Now, that is your
question.
And if not, it's the look above and bel
we're buying very high right now. If you
if you are participating upside, if you
look at the swing leg, remember 500 is
the upside swing leg. Uh 4890 is the
downside swing leg. So, we're buying
right at the top of the swing leg. All I
was doing is trying to play some
momentum of their pain and I will just
wait now. Let it develop. We're only uh
what 7 minutes into the day. Plenty of
time ahead, folks.
How do I know there was a 373 lot buyer?
Because I can literally see him on
either footprint or on bookmap. Right.
I'm watching level two data. I'm just I
don't just trade candles. I want to know
who's actually playing and where they're
playing.
Sellers just got caught there at 12. All
right, we're coming back up to that same
little spot. 35 and 42. That's where the
big buyers came in. If we start
repricing through that again, they're
going to take control. So sellers are
back letting this be back tested now.
They need to sell it here. If they
don't, we're going to see a squeeze.
There is a bit of a shelf starting to be
developed above. Let me get this on for
you guys. We're moving pretty quick here
this morning, folks. Sorry.
Where's 30? There we go. So, a bit of a
shelf up here. And if we get through
54s, we're going to really rip some
faces to the upside. So, I'm trying to
join this long now.
Are you going to let me get in?
We just got caught all those sellers.
previous week closed by the way at 70
470.
So we're getting stuck up there waiting
to see if we dip back down into sort of
40s and I can see a buyer on the buyer
here at 50s in front of 50s. This is the
same guy that's been spoofing though by
the looks of it. So trust him yet
they're going to come down to 40s. Let's
see if these sellers get stuck in this
little block between 43 and 35.
Hands are off the mouse. I'm just
waiting. Missed that little squeeze out
unfortunately. Was really good. Saw the
sellers get caught maybe a nanocond too
late to play that. But that blue block
held. So if any of you were buying that
dip into that blue block, it held
nicely. You should have partial out into
this high and then you're looking for
acceleration now. And I'd be looking for
470 and 500 if I was you, if you got any
of it. So you should have partial out
already. If you bought down here, you
should be partial out. And you're
looking for this little dotted line.
This is your previous week close. If you
get above that, you get lucky. Get all
the way into there. But you should have
been paying yourself if you bought that
blue block at the bottom.
They're refreshing up here in front of
470. They don't want it over previous
week close right now. ES a little bit
weak up here as well. Nvidia just got
through that squeeze level
and got hit straight away. So, it tried
and they sold it straight away.
So, let's see if it can base above. I
had it at 7842s,
currently trading at 7832s, 7820s. So
they obviously tapped into it and found
those sellers. So it might be look above
and fell on uh Nvidia there. All right,
this is your your point down here. 42s
to 35s needs to be soaked by buyers and
if it's not rotation back down to that
blue box.
So no re-entry for me. I missed this
here by a nanocond unfortunately.
It's whippy. It's whippy.
currently just trading in current uh
sessions rotation 60 to I don't know 20
60 to 25s your rotation right now 40
points
where's previous week value area low um
all the way up here mate 700s 700s
They're trying to squeeze. They want to
go. They These guys want to go. They
just keep getting caught up here. These
buyers, they're not finding acceleration
through. They got to get through the
70s. Once they get through 70s, they're
over previous week close. They've got a
legit shot at 500. But you can see every
time they're popping into 70s, they're
getting hit. Passive seller up here.
Reloading, reloading, reloading,
reloading. If he leaves, you've got a
chance. But you can see how quickly it's
moving in, move away, moving in, moving
away. It's just a passive seller set up
here right now. It keeps refreshing into
70. So you can see that white line on
the chart. Once you get through that 500
is possible for you guys who are already
long. I would not be buying up here. By
the way, I be your your dips were down
here or even into this into VWAP. You
should be selling profits into this. Be
aware that today failed breakouts can
happen either in front of this or above
this. They can fail or they can fail.
All right. So we do not get long right
at the tops.
The squeeze is on here. There's through
the 70s. Now you're going to get 500s.
There you go. So, congrats to you guys
who got it. Congratulations. Make sure
you're selling into this. We're into a
major higher time frame pivot here,
okay? Major major higher time frame
pivot here.
Really nice. There's your 90s. Don't be
a dick for 10 ticks. All right. Make
sure you're paying yourself. And once we
get a breakout over 510 to 520, we have
some imbalance above to fill up to uh
580s. So 510 to 520, that can be the
look above and fail. If we hold above
that, 580s is possible. I'm very jealous
now. God damn it.
There you go. There's your five. Really
nice. Congrats everyone who took that.
God damn it. God damn it. Missed my
reload.
Shouldn't complain. Four figure day and
I'm pissed off I'm not in the squeeze.
But there we go. All right. Please do
not join this late. All right. Please do
not join this late. This is can easily
be a fail breakout up here. If you get
lucky, this is the next block. All
right. In here, we've we lack structure.
All right. In this in this area here, we
can slice straight through it. We lack
structure, but we can they can also
reject it fast. So just manage your
runners now and this is your target if
you can get up there.
Really nice seeing bid support trying to
step on now. Look at all these guys,
these buyers stepping in trying to push
push price up. We're much better. This
is what I would have liked to have seen
earlier down here.
Really, really good. So yeah, W's in
chat. If you caught this, you you should
still be long. Those of you who are in
it, you should still be long. Big seller
just came in at 530. So, I'd say you'd
want price to stay above 530 to keep him
stuck. And you're looking for 580s now.
So, here we go into some old imbalances.
First imbalance tag. Second imbalance is
70. Then, uh, sorry, then 55, and then
last one will be 80. Hopefully, you can
get up to 85. You guys in the runners
make, please, you should be down to like
10 20% here. This is very squeezy. They
can drop this straight back down. Look
how aggressive it is up. When they're
done with it, if too many buyers come in
at the highs, we will collapse it. So,
you must be paying yourself on the way
up.
Awesome, awesome work, folks. Awesome
work.
Yeah, lots of buyers in this last
candle. Starting to try and uh buy the
highs getting caught here. So, just be
careful. Where did I say that painoint
was? I can't even remember. 29s 529.
That's where the sell is stuck right
now. You got a little shelf being built
out here. 50 to 55. You kind of want to
bid above that. Otherwise,
you might see a little 20 point wash
coming here. You're starting to lose
that little shelf at 50. I'd be very
careful here.
Here's 50. Can they reclaim 50? They
can. They can reclaim 50. Strong buyers
today on the tape. Strong buyers on the
tape. All right. ES into its 20day. So,
it's completed its mean reversion. Same
for the SPY. Just think about that. U
just be cautious about that. Where's the
cues? They've also got above the 20-day.
All right, so mean reversion complete
and those lower Ballinger bands will
start to catch up the next few days on
the daily. 80 is your only next target.
I'd be looking at 80s is your next
target.
We go to the uh
hourly. You'll see what I was looking
at. All right. So once we squeezed
through this, we held dips over previous
day value. We we squeeze through current
weak value. We're coming up to this
level up here. This is where all right
is supply. We do not expect price to get
above that. All right. And if we get
back under here, this would be the look
above and fail. So just be cautious. You
should have trimmed a lot of your money
if not all of it at this point.
Lots of sellers keep piling in here at
40s, 37s, 40s, and 30s and they are not
winning. They are not winning. The tape
is still aggressive. This is all Nvidia.
Look at look as soon as Nvidia got
through that squeeze level. Remember the
white line was at 78. We had earlier
7830. Soon as we got this, this is it.
This is the market squeezing out because
we're taking out big pivots in uh names
probably with massive expireies today.
You would imagine
massive expireies today for OPEX.
I'd love you guys to get 80s here. It
would be fantastic.
You're almost there. You're almost
there. Might as well go and do it. You
are almost there.
10 points is all you need. A little
squeeze up. They are offering above now
at 90. Is there anyone above that? Yes,
there's a big level. 600, you got 200
lot. But yeah, 80s is the level if you
can get up into it. And again, I'd say
you don't want price below 42 to 30 is
where the sellers got caught. All right,
if price comes below that, I would be uh
taking your position off. You can always
get back in. Remember folks, we can
always get back in.
This can potentially be RBS. All right,
it's an old pivot, so I will convert
that. Although, I don't really think it
would hold up that well if we came
flying down into it, but we will see.
Yeah, quite right, Adam. All right, back
down to the where these sellers came
flying in. We just talked about these
sellers. This is where they keep trying
to sell aggressively down here. They
haven't been getting their way. They're
not getting their way again. All right,
again, they're not getting their way. So
that 42 38 and well 2930 that's where
they keep trying and they are not
getting their way which means currently
there is someone just absorbing
but if he pulls be careful because we're
very thin on that expansion up right
look at this shelf be careful if we
leave this shelf there is not much here
we can come straight down into this
right the only hope balls have got is to
do a little trap and go but if they lose
this shelf there's no structure we will
wash aggressively This is why I'm saying
you must take profits as we move in.
Only helps hope bulls have got is to do
a little uh trap play under here looking
for the breakout shorts to come in and
then just use their pain to go upside.
Uh same it's the same stuff I gave you
this morning, right? ES just tagged into
its 20day. The only thing left upside
would be sort of 885
to 88 890 88 8.90 890 885 to 890 would
be the only upside you've got left on ES
right building out this shelf
view do this as gray right that's your
volume being built out careful when you
leave
Let's see. I really hope you guys get
the uh 580s. That' be really nice for
especially those that took the dip into
here. We talked about this RBS zone.
Almost 200 points. I mean, you you
should have lot most in anyway, but uh
really really good.
It's nice when a plan comes together.
They I didn't really expect them to do
it out the gate, but they got aggressive
quickly uh today out the gate.
Opening range now set as well. So, you
are dangling at that orb. Just be aware
of that. So, if you lose this, we go
back inside the opening range. Same kind
of level. So, your opening range high
right now is basically 50 for those of
you playing the orb.
Got the squeeze locked in 4K. Thank you,
Alex. You are welcome.
But flows and toning. Love to log in and
have you your soothing commentary as the
market does its thing. Thank you for
this. Good day. Thank you. Uh Billy,
thank you for that.
10 minutes to high impact news. What do
you think?
Well, the consumer sentiment, I mean,
I don't know if we get much of a move on
that. Home existing home sales should
should be a poor print. Home sales have
been in a decline in the last 3 months
and home sale value. But yes, we do have
10 minutes. I I I I'm not going to give
a prediction on on news. I think today
is more about the gamma levels. Do I
trail my stops? It depends on what uh
account I'm trading and whether it's a
trading draw down or end of day draw
down. I will always trail my stops once
I hit 1 R 2 R3R etc. Um, and I'll always
take profit
depression index.
I mean, you seen I don't know if you're
reading the news, but like even Ford
came out this week saying they're going
to have to change their agenda like
dropping all their EVs or at least a lot
of them. The F-150E or whatever they
were calling it, it's getting binned.
Lots of people wasting billions of
dollars
investing in these EVs that they're not
going to follow through with. Home sale
prices have been in steep decline,
especially in uh places like uh Texas
and uh California, Los Angeles, Austin
getting hit very hard at the moment. Um
we've had more and more people unable to
make mortgage payments, more and more
people unable to make car repayments,
more rep repossessions taking place. Um,
so but you know CPI looked great
yesterday, but if you looked under the
hood, like I always talk about how much
information was included in CPI, about
20% of what normally would be included
because they've got no data apparently
from the government shutdown. How do I
read that? I read that as smoke and
mirrors. Absolute [\h__\h] They don't
want a disaster coming into Christmas.
They don't want a disastrous, you know,
six months of prints into the midterms.
That's how I read that. Honestly, I
think they're cooking books. they
wouldn't be the first lot to do it.
They've been doing it for as long as I
can remember. Okay, coming in testing
the edge of this volume shelf. You can
see we've got tight here. Um I almost
don't don't really trust this here. I'm
going to be honest because of where it
is. It is an RBS zone, but if we leave
this, I would not be surprised for us to
revisit that. Uh the track would be
something like this. They've got
unfinished business. I would not be
buying anymore up here, right? Do not
be. You should have be holding your
positions, not buying more. Here goes
ES. ES is trying to break out to the
upside here. It's having an attempt. New
high day on ES. Can it hold a bid above
though? Can it hold a bid above?
Market's just cooled off here.
Completely cooled off. Where's the VIX?
Under previous day low into the 1515s.
Yes, pulling back inside its range.
Do I got a video on how to trade
orderflow? Uh, I have a course on it.
Just went live.
flowzonerader.com. Use code launch. It
would get you the course for uh $299.
But if you want to just learn volume
profile, there's a free free uh like
master class on my YouTube you can do.
Okay, you're starting to get a bit
sticky here in this area. If they make a
decision soon and leave this area, I
would be, you know, watching into 65 and
definitely down into 50s. You're
starting to see a rejection here to
leave the area. The only thing is this
RBS zone, but it's higher time frame and
it might very well not hold because we
have no volume transacted there on the
day. You can see how thin it is.
How much of a [\h__\h] show over in Europe?
What's the I don't know what your
question is there. Honest question. Is
it much of a [\h__\h] show in Europe? I
mean, I'm sure it is. I don't live in
Europe. I live in Los Angeles, but
Europe's a big place to say something
like that.
You're talking about numerous countries.
I'll tell you about the UK. It's a [\h__\h]
show. But I don't want to talk for
Italy, France, Germany, everywhere else.
Like Europe's a very big place.
But the UK, yeah, not not not so good.
Government, not so good.
How much percentage of TP do you guys
normally lock in? We will do it based on
structure. We You can see how I play.
I'm not saying like
anything else other than pivot points.
Look at that little trap. It's a good
trap there. If they don't reject here,
we're going to go higher because shorts
just came flying in there again. If they
don't reject here right now, they are
going to get caught underneath his break
because the only thing I said the only
hope bulls have got is for a little
trap. They are looking possible here,
especially if they break 55s.
That's their level that they need to
base back above. They're trying.
They are trying.
Have they got any juice here? They have.
They've got to send it now. There we go.
You've got to send it now. You got to
get back above 70s now. You've just held
55s.
They've got to soak 55s now. No good.
There's a little imbalance here at 47s.
Where's that volume? Yeah, 47s is BPO
currently.
Bulls have a chance here. I'm telling
you, after doing this, trapping bears,
bulls have a chance. But they just came
flying in here. They need to hold this
for that rotation.
I'm interested. I am interested after
seeing those bears get trapped, but it's
the worst trade location of the day.
Do I really want to risk anything?
SPY can't get above its 20-day here. So,
we're stuck at mean here in the markets,
right? So, those of you who don't look
at dailies, I would advise you look at
the 20-day on a daily with daily
Ballinger bands. That will give you your
expansion levels and your mean reversion
levels. We are holding this profile. We
need to get above 55. If if bulls get us
above 55s here aggressively, not just
like tapping in leave 55, they have got
a shot at going 480 48580s
and 600s. They are trying over and over
again. Here passive seller at 65 and 70.
Once they start leaving 55s
aggressively, they're going to squeeze,
but they have to leave. And at the
moment that reseller stepped in and now
he's trying to step down to 60.
They can't do it. They can't do it.
They're trying. They've tried once,
twice. Yeah, twice so far.
Back down to Vo we come. And if we lose
gray box under side, still think this is
possible down here. So we can mark this
out down here.
These are your levels between traps
underneath. Top side is to here if they
can hold battle in this gray box. This
is not where you want to enter. You
don't want to be getting involved in
inside a shelf. You want us to leave a
shelf. They're going to have one more
attempt. So they I would say this is
third and final attempt for them.
They've got to go and they got to go
now.
ES is doing it. ES is showing strength
here. ES's new highive day into 880s.
Q's relative weakness. Can't get through
these refresh sellers into 65 and 70s.
It's a good drive from ES. Really nice.
Yeah, news 10:00. Quite right. News in
what? 30 seconds, 20 seconds.
You will get those prints.
You might see a few levels get washed
either side. It would not surprise me.
You can see on the hourly, if you go
back to the hourly where we've got this
red line into these sort of 80s 86s,
there's the wash. So, they've just taken
one side out straight into that red
block. All right, 80s 86s. Do we see
continuation now? Are we going to go
through this to 600 now? So, you should
have hit your TP here. Just hold on.
Hold on to your runners. All right, hold
on to your runners. 600 above is where
they're trying to fill. There's a wall
there. ES has just hit your TP as well.
What did we say? 85, 86, 88. You want to
be locking some into that. Really nice
once we left. Shame they have to do it
on the news, but if you held through
that, congratulations. This is your TP.
Only thing left is up here. If you're
going to come and tag value, you're at
700s, but you know, you should be pretty
much done with it. Pretty much done with
it.
Really like really nice. It's a shame.
It's a shame they have to do it for news
for you guys, but if any of you held
through that, that is well over 200
point trade with me live on stream. All
you had to do was take that red dip in.
Um, I did talk about it when we were up
here. If they held this, it would be a
re red dip to go. They did trap sellers
down there. We can go over it. I called
it live. I missed my entry down there,
so I had to join later. But there's
sellers down there.
All right. in this red dip in this is
what you're always looking for an RBS
zone where aggressive sellers come in,
right? These are market sellers and
you're seeing absorption and old buyers
hold price up and aggressive sellers try
again again and then we go straight
upside and since then they've been
caught and you can see they've tried the
whole time up here
and their pain point if you right in the
middle of this right all these sellers
think about all these guys trying to get
the roll over and they come aggressively
on this snap they're looking for that
volume to be exchanged lower that was
the uh bear trap we talked about and now
they are absolutely,
pardon my French, [\h__\h] They are
[\h__\h]
They are saying mad
zutal. I am in so much pain, right? But
you just you just hit you hit 600. So
should should be enjoying it.
Nice guys. Really nice. Look at all
these people on stream. 655 of you.
Thank you for joining folks. Smash that
like and subscribe button. We will be
doing some giveaways. We've tapped our
supply block. All right, this was our
expectation for probably the top play
today. Um, if they want to be really,
really, really aggressive,
you could look for 650s, which would be
I'll show you why, but I doubt I would
doubt it. But you just never know. All
right, if you wanted to be really
aggressive
up here. All right, this pivot. All
right. So, what have we seen here? Big
strong downtrend, right? Liquidity
build, liquidity build, pull, push back
up. Yesterday said we talked about the
build of an inside day and then at some
point we will make a decision which way
we are leaving that. All right, if you
going back and watch yesterday's video,
this is what we talked about. Well,
we're quite obviously using yesterday's
inside day for expansion. We're using
these stops here for expansion, but we
understand this is fresh supply. We're
not going to get long in fresh supply.
The only way we could now get long up
here would need to be higher. It sounds
weird. We would need to be above
previous week value and a hold of 700.
Otherwise, I'm not interested in longs
anywhere near up here.
Any of you joined me yesterday should
have been sort of prepared about this.
What's the indicator on the side of the
candle?
Uh, I assume you're talking about this.
This is a footprint chart, right? This
is order flow. This is footprint
showing you what's going on inside of
the candle. So, you're seeing some
sellers step back in. You've got this
volume shelf here. If you leave, all
right, if sellers take control of this
now, this here will happen because
you're very thin. Buyers potentially got
the move they wanted. So, the sell can
happen. It can still happen if they come
under, reject, and start washing back
down to here. That can still happen. But
the overall trend is up. Buyers will
want to defend this. All right, if they
fail to defend this, remember they've
hit a big target. Buyers will want to
defend this. If they fail to defend it,
this to the next volume level is
possible. All right, this can be a trap
level. So, I' pay attention to it. But
if you are desperate, desperate,
desperate for the short, you need to be
looking for that and nothing before it.
Uh I will stream um Monday, Tuesday next
week. After that it will be on pause. Um
I will try and do like the odd session
in between. I I'll let you guys know.
I'll have to have a look at the
schedule. I might go away for a bit. So
footprint you mean footstep footprint
versus map. Uh it each their own. I use
both. you could whatever whatever you
find easier to read I would say is the
best thing. The good thing about um
bookmap is you see the orders above and
below price. You won't see that on
footprint.
Okay. So back into this gray shelf.
Really nice. So I can't remember who
asked me about those targets from ES but
you hit them as well. You hit them as
well. The only thing that you've left is
that 8075. But the block like we talked
about was 85 to 88.
What do I think of the dome? I use the
DOM. You can see it top right of the
screen. It's vital for for reading
price.
This gray gray box top right of or right
above me here. Here. I think that's it.
That's the dom.
Are the Trading View orderflow tools
worthy? Yeah, they're good. They're
actually really good. I'm really
impressed with them. Really impressed
with them.
So, gray box, this volume shelf, buyers
are trying to defend this. You don't
want to be short early. All right, you
will need to leave this shelf, come
under, reject this shelf, leave buyers
stuck to trade downside. Otherwise, you
cannot be thinking about downside move.
Look at the top right of your screen.
Lower time frame conditions, higher time
frame conditions, currently bullish.
Flow zones are supporting price. All
right, we have had a really nice upside
move here this morning. I was actually
long out the gate, which is very rare
for me, but I saw the buyer stepping in.
Sold some here. Missed this reload. Had
to join a bit later and then missed a
ton of this unfortunately. But there we
go. Still locking in some nice profits.
If we leave this then uh I think we
might might come down to there. I'd be
watching the midpoint 500 in VWAP and
I'd be watching this down here.
If you're wondering what that blue box
is, it is a pivot
get it accurate from Thursday. All
right, it's Thursday's this one here.
Oh, no it's not. It is from That is a
complete lie. It would be a pivot from
Wednesday the 17th of December
like so. I wouldn't pay too much
attention to it, but I've got it marked
out because it is high time frame.
Maybe just pull this down a bit.
Something like that.
Okay, starting to test the underside of
this gray box. You need to leave this
gray box, back test it to stay heavy.
But sellers keep coming in down here. I
will tell you now, from 46 to 37, they
keep trying to get an aggressive move
away from here and they're not finding
it. Which is why I would not take a
breakout short personally.
I would need it to retest it. They're
trying. They're getting very aggressive
here. You need to see this stay heavy on
a retest. If they reclaim it, there's no
short to be had. If they go straight
back inside there, you just can't short
it. It just means they're going to get
trapped all over again.
So, back in to test it. And it looks
like they're going to find a bid is
point control. If they trade through
this, it goes straight back upside. So
no rejection like we talked about. It's
still just trading in and around here.
What platform of this trading view
surely doesn't have heat map?
This above me bookm
still there. Why has it gone missing?
It's still here.
Shouldn't be a problem with that.
Spider's still just stuck around these
20 days.
There's a lot of questions here, guys. I
would advise just go through my stuff on
YouTube, right? My Trading View setup is
really simple. It's my Flowzone Pro and
V1. That's it. And some volume.
You can get Flowzone Pro on my website.
Um, you will need to do the course
really to truly understand it how it
works. You get a version of it for free
with the course.
Yeah. Most most questions you have are
probably uh there are probably videos
for free on my YouTube all about it.
Yeah, no worries.
No, no, no. You don't need to say sorry,
guys. No reason to say sorry. All
questions
valid. But most most if you're going to
ask out like my setup or how I trade or
what I do, anything like that,
everything will either be on my website
or or on my YouTube channel.
Yeah, not not sure what happened there.
Sorry, mate. Um, but yeah, I will never
delete indicators. So, if they ever get
pulled, it'll be trading view, but I pay
for the pro, so that they can't really
do that. Okay, in this shelf again,
we're just battling here. They're
waiting to build volume. This is a like
a lower time frame example of what we
did yesterday. Once we leave volume, we
can be aggressive with it one way or
another.
Was
680 a put wall on spy? It definitely It
definitely was a call wall on the way on
the uh
definitely was a put wall on the way
down and it feels like it might be a
call wall now because we keep banging
into it and rejecting.
We'll see. Big buyer just came on a tape
here. 200 lot at 550 trying to support a
bid. Let's see if he's real. Why would
you bid the Vo like that? He's legit.
He's legit.
Weird.
He's refreshed as well. Weird, man.
Weird. Why would you bid like that up
there? Very odd. Look at that exchange
there. If anyone's watching, huge
exchange there now, right? So they sold
through him 236 lot. Why was he bidding
such big size at 550s?
What a weird place to do that.
Am I calling the shelf point of control
the highest volume of the day? Well,
well, it is. It's both those things.
It's a shelf. The gray box is the shelf.
uh point of control is the red line.
We're starting to leave this shelf, but
this is where sellers keep coming in and
keep getting stuck. Right. Every time
we've come down here, there's been a
passive buyer.
Is he? Where's that 550 lot?
546.
So 546 to 550. Sellers need to defend
that because they've just come flying in
there to fill that weird buyer.
And you've got offside delta there. So
well on on side at the moment. So five,
what did I just say? 546 to 550s.
They're trying to sell through now
because they've had to just take out
that buyer. So the question is, do we
leave this shelf now? Do we come VW up?
Do we leave V up and go 460s? Or do they
come straight back inside that shelf?
Starting to see more aggression here
from sellers. But someone is still
passively bidding this down here. If he
moves, it snaps. But he's not moving.
What did I say? 46. I keep forgetting
what what I'm saying this morning. 46.75
and 51. 5051. That those are the levels.
Brain's not fully in gear yet. Clearly.
So, this is the tap back in. Sellers
need to sell this or a move lower.
Otherwise, we go reclaim and we go
higher.
It doesn't. So the shelves don't need to
be the highest range of volume. They are
literally shelves. This one happens to
be the highest volume node. They are
high volume nodes, but they don't need
to be the highest, right? This one
happens to be the highest. That's your
point of control. But shelves are just
things like this where you have a clear
edge like here. If this was a bit more
built out, it would be really good. like
clear edges and in here no volume.
Right? So in no volume they can act as
support areas where we trap like we did
here. But if they can't trap then
there's no structure here to support
then you imagine we slice down to the
next level. This is why sellers if they
defend this and they get a break they're
going to look for higher time frame RBS
and then this. If they can't and they go
back inside then they're going to keep
getting trapped underneath the shelf.
Thank you sweetheart.
sellers a week. Yeah. I mean, they keep
trying. They're trying and trying and
trying and trying and trying and trying.
Can see them on the delta. They need a
break. They need it to break lower now.
They they are trying to reject this gray
box, but they need to break lower and
they are struggling to break lower right
now. But if they break lower, it could
get a little bit violent.
They're just trying in this candle again
without getting any leeway.
So, I'd say it's basically all sellside
from 50 under. So, if it's all heavy
delta from 50 under and we're not going
anywhere, what does that tell you?
Right? If it's all sellside delta from
50 and under and we're not breaking
away, means there's someone absorbing
the tape here. So, sellers will need
this breakdown.
They've come flying in here. So, they're
trying now. Here we go. There's their
breakdown. All right. So, let's see if
they can maintain it. Right. Can they
get into this blue box and gray box or
are they going to get just instantly
absorbed? This is what happened earlier.
So from 50, let's mark it out and I'm
going to show you from here is all
aggressive selling and no real buying.
Well, there is buying but it's passive.
Right? You see
this
this this
what did I say from 50? This this this
is all people market ordering sells.
Have we moved lower? No, not yet. Right.
So there is a passive buyer absorbing
here looking for a rotation higher right
now. That's the battle. Passive buying,
aggressive selling
back into gray box. So sellers will have
another chance to defend this level. And
point of control now is 55. And it's
starting to be reclaimed here.
If the market would clear the imbalance,
would it drop to point of control 2530?
You mean the old point of control? Um,
no.
The point of control right now is at the
highs. This is your PC.
So
the rotations right now
could be this and I'd expect them to try
and hold a bid there and then rotate in
this zone to fill this in. If they lost
this back down to value if they reprint
over this then they're going to look for
600 and probably weeklies up into
sevens. Right? Those are the rotations.
Here is is where they're building
liquidity. I don't trade in here. Okay?
As a rule. If you hear me say I don't
like trading rotations, right? that this
is a micro rotation in here. This is a
buildout of volume. What I like to trade
is if we leave, test, stay heavy. If we
leave, test, stay positive. I don't care
which way. This is the probably the
harder trade today only because we think
about what we've done. We've already
done this. All right. So, yes,
momentum's up, but what are we buying
now? If this is value, right, we're
we're buying okay, fair value on the day
is currently high, but we're buying
premium within current day and we're
buying premium above previous week um or
current week, I should say. So, we don't
want to buy this high really, but it
might not give us a choice. All right.
Now, sellers keep rejecting up here over
and over again. So, buyers got caught on
that last wick push in sellers still
have not taken control. What's the ES
doing? Still in no man's land, hanging
around its 20 days. Okay, so if you look
at the spy, it is literally just stuck
at its 20-day. Why is that important?
Well, when we look at the dailies, this
is just how I trade and many of you
would never have traded this way
probably.
This is your mean on the daily. There's
your top bowl. There's your lower bowl.
This is your max move, max move. The
other thing we have to respect here is
what we talked about higher time frame.
Where are we into 20-day, 50-day, edge
of shelf? All right, edge of shelf. So,
it's going to struggle to move much
above this. It's very unlikely that
we're going to get into this next block
here. So, they're going to keep trying
to sell this. And this is why we have to
think about where are we positioned? Do
we really want to be buying up here? Not
really. So, if you are going to buy up
here, what are you going to need to see?
You're going to need to see trap
sellers, a reclaim of a shelf, more
trapped sellers, and you're going to
have to play momentum long. This would
be a smaller size position because
you've lost the location, but you have
the momentum. sellers now starting to
come in. Let me get back in and focus in
on this otherwise I'm going to miss any
potential setups now while I'm teaching.
So you can see this is a little shelf
here that de developed. If they start
snapping this BW is available. Yes,
still at its 20-day still at its 20day.
Still sellers selling these lows here.
Where did that big lock come in? I keep
I can't think. My brain is not working
today. Where's this big lock? 55s. Okay.
55. 47s and 55s. God. Come on, brain.
Wake up. Maybe I just need to get this
coffee in me first.
Wakey wakey.
Yeah. Uh, a little bit. I mean, there's
a bit both sides right now. It's just a
battle. It is just a battle. If you look
at bookmap, you can see it like both
sides just keep getting pinned. They're
trying to be aggressive on the sale
again. ES coming back down to 20day
again.
30 is the level right now. They've sold
that numerous times without success of
getting through under that. It gets
thin. Gets much thinner under 30.
And they stack 20 underneath and tens
and and the 500. So the buyers are like,
"We're going to have everything you
want. You you sell it if you want. We're
going to keep gobbling up." That's what
they're saying at the moment.
700 of you in here. What is going on?
It's amazing. If you're new here, smash
that like and subscribe button. And here
Monday to Friday, 9:15 Eastern time, we
do pre-market show and then try trade
all the way into lunch.
We will do some giveaways today. If
you're new as well, worth checking out
the community page on YouTube. I am
giving away a free funded next account.
Um, by next Tuesday, we will announce
the winner. I don't I don't pick the
winner. Funded next pick the winner.
Completely free to enter.
All right, they're trying again at these
30s. They're being aggressive at 30s
again. They're still being absorbed down
here.
Surprised they haven't flushed 20s to be
honest. Looking at this at the moment,
that big guy just sat there looking to
get flushed into by the looks of it, if
you ask me.
30s is the level. 30s, 30s, 30s. They're
trying. They're trying. They're looking
for that flush. Here comes the break.
There's the 20s. Okay, now can they go
05s?
Here we go. Okay, thank goodness they're
actually starting to play ball properly.
All right, so probably into 05s and 500s
into this RBS level and and VWAP. And if
you lose VWAP, we're going to come all
the way down. This is a higher time
frame RBS level which dates back to
Wednesday the 17th of December. So they
are bidding off it. Interesting. Wasn't
sure if they'd bid off that if I'm
honest because we're very thin. So
sellers have a chance here to react
here. The rotation here is clear. Right?
They must sell up here, close under
here, get down into here. Buyers will
want to absorb this, use this, use all
these sellers pain, and get back above.
That's the rotation. We are in a
rotational market. All right. I know
we've broken out of that December
17th pivot. But we are that's this right
here that they need to hold.
And if we don't hold it, it will be a
look above and fail. And if we do look
above and fail, we think about how
vertical we've been. If we leave buyers
trapped up here and we don't hold the
pivot, all right, then we can use all
this volume to rotate aggressively. So,
it is definitely a bit of a battle day
today over time frames.
And it's OPEX just to make it extra fun.
Okay, so sellers took control 330 uh
330s, 530s,
that's where they really took control.
So 5 I'd say the levels right now 530s,
538, 547. That's where the sellers took
control. They will need to defend those
levels. If they don't defend those
levels, they will start to be squeezed
out. They will start to be squeezed out
if they can't defend those levels. ES
currently holding above PDH. SPY looking
like just stuck between the 20-day and
VWAP right now. VIX is trying to catch a
bit of a bid.
You can see 500 being bid down here. Do
they wash into him? Do they wash into
him?
I would be very careful about bidding
this down here if I was you. Only
because we lack volume.
If we'd built out structure here this
morning, if we'd done something like
this, I think it would be a really good
bid back up, but I think it's a little
risky.
This is uh the New York view up. All
right. So, 24-hour VWOP's down here. New
York VWOUP is here. New York VW, you can
just do an anchored VWOP. Anchor it to
your 930 open. Right. I'm interested in
cash players. You go and watch my videos
on cash gaps or anything like that.
Always interested in cash players.
505 500 on the book. Both of those on
the book. ES relative strength holding
up above PDH right now.
If they lose this, you will go uh all
the way down into this gray box. Right.
If they don't defend this, remember,
we're very thin. You will come all the
way back down into here. So, buyers,
this is sort of last chance for them.
Uh, if they want to go back for the
highs, if they lose this, you're going
to come all the way down into the box.
So, if any of you took the short for
these rejections, right, that's your
cover one, and this is your cover two
down into here. Anything beyond that is
a bonus. Uh, I wouldn't be looking for
much beyond that, if I'm honest. And
then we can build out a rotation here
for a bit. If they do, if they do lose
this, they might want to build it out
before we make a decision on what next.
Like I said, very thin here.
99's here.
Here
we go. Starting to let it go. So, you
might come all the way down here, folks.
So, those of you in shorts, I don't know
if you're in this BEu, I feel like this
is the type of trade you like now. Le
the leaving of shelves, but this would
be your next cover point. So, be out 50
plus% and see if you can get a drive
into anywhere from 60 to 55. Beyond that
is fantastic and an absolute godsend.
Shorts from 538 trim sum. Very nice.
Yeah. So once we left really good,
right? So we talked about it for ages,
didn't we? Leaving this, trim some into
here, hold some into here, and I'd hold
like 10% beyond that. So I'd be like 50%
out here, maybe another 30 to 40% out
here, and then 10% just in case they get
really nasty because if we lose this, it
is technically I just want to make sure
I'm in the right levels. This can be a
look above and fail. The next level will
be 400. So this is the big one. If you
lose this, we go back into range. But
here you can see, so we're repricing now
like we talked about into the next
shelf, right? So I'd be covering some
into here.
Really good.
Really, really, really good. So you can
see thin up, thin down. This is why we
come and repric. Um, so if you're going
to hold runners, what what you really
want is to get under this blue box. If
you get under that blue box, this whole
thing
will be a fail breakout. Right? If you
get under this blue box,
this whole thing will be a fail
breakout. If we hold this blue box, it's
just a breakout retest. Okay.
Going to get rid of this because like I
said, I'd made it darker because wasn't
convinced it would hold and it hasn't.
Okay. Into gray box. This is your cover
point for some of the shorts. You want
to be covering some of your short
position here, please.
Hopefully, it makes sense.
Yeah, I'll be covering some of my short
now. Definitely in in and around this
area and then hold holding if you've got
enough size, you can hold runners. I'd
definitely be covering some of my short
here because we know this is the edge of
value down here into 50s, right? So,
it's highly likely that you see some bid
come back in here. Now, if we lose edge
of value, like I talked about, we got
24-hour VW up, previous day high,
GlobeEx, all down here. If we lose that,
it's a whole different ball game. But,
you know, this is thin. We just came
into like wick to wick. If you look
here, wick to wick. Maybe this gray box
should have been here. Wick to wick and
we're founding a bid. All right. So,
hopefully this is making sense to you
why I'm like, you need to be 80% out
into this gray box,
right? We are day traders. We're not
swing traders. I mean I am a swing
trader but on this stream we are day
trading which means you have to respect
level to level and guess what if we
reclaim this what happens giant squeeze
right so shorts need to defend this we
reclaim this giant squeeze is on
this make sense for you all hopefully
this makes sense for everyone right we
left shelf we repriced we went to edge
we found a bid right and we might well
rotate between this like I must have
said that about one minute ago we can
easily do this for a little now until
they make a decision. If they get very
squeezy, they're going to do this.
I will remind you, some of you might be
new. We are in OPEX, right? Daily,
weekly, monthly, yearly expirations
today. Only happens four times a year
with the contract rollover as well,
right? Used to be quad witching. We call
it trip witching now. But these are days
where we get big drastic moves very
quickly.
If you stick with me long enough here,
because lots of you will be new, you
will just start to see these setups
because they come at day after day after
day after day after day. You will see
them. So, they're trying to protect.
They just built out a little node here
and they reacted
just above it.
So shorts are trying to take control of
this market at the moment. They want to
complete the rotation down into 450 at
the moment. That's what they want to do.
Whether they can do it or not is a whole
different thing, but they would like to
complete the rotation down. ES is
finding absorption uh into its VWAP.
cannot get a close under VWAP right now
on the ES. So you're seeing absorption
over there.
Um what was that node there? 14s. So
buyers got stuck on that last wick above
12s.
Can the sellers get a new lower low and
see some follow through to uh current
value area low or do they get caught
down here is the question.
They're trying.
Might need a little reprice first to see
if they come back in at 500.
And if they don't then we're going to go
up.
There you go. Up back up towards 500.
And they will need to sell this now
otherwise they will get caught.
Yes. Absorbing VW up
back to its 20-day.
We get back above this. The next
rotation's going to take place. This is
a little bit messy here.
Just let it poke through a bit more than
they probably should have there.
Yes, very very strong. Back into its
range already. So, gaining strength
there.
You can see this edge above sort of
around here. 30s like we talked about
before. I can move this down a little
bit. Something like this. It's a little
bit messy, I'll be honest. Shorts will
need to defend that. We're going to get
rid of this now. Shorts need to defend
this area. These are the rotations.
Bulls want to defend this. Shorts want
to defend this. These are the rotational
areas.
Bull's trying to be very aggressive here
right now. Uh into this shelf. Let's see
if there's a passive seller. This is
where they started selling before. 30s
up to 50s is where sellers took control.
So that's where they need to maintain
control. If they want the rotation back
down, if they don't maintain control,
they're going to get squeezed out.
Do I mentor one-on-one? I don't. I
honestly I don't have the time. Um, but
we do do group sessions. Disc I don't
have thousands of people in Discord,
right? It's a small Discord. We do do
group sessions. I'm trying to do them
more regularly where I give everyone in
the group, you know, opportunity to
reach out and um ask questions so I can
help them. And that's completely free.
Right. This is a onetime fee to do the
course and Discord and the group
sessions come with it. So, like I said,
I'm not not here to uh take thousands
and thousands of dollars off you. I do
want you guys to learn, but I I
genuinely don't have the time to do
one-on- ones.
I wish I did. Maybe one day I will.
Right now, I still have to trade my own
book. Right. So, you're starting to see
them try and drive back up through 30s.
Can they get to 50s is what they're
looking for. Do sellers reject this? If
they don't reject it, we are into
squeeze potential. So, you can see them
reselling here. 40s, 45s, 50s. Bids are
at 30s and 20s right now. It is a little
bit messy. Like I said, uh balls doing a
pretty good job here. Bears probably
should have defended a bit earlier. It's
fairly typical on NQ.
What's the onetime fee? 649. It's on the
website. 6 For649 you get a 20our
course. You get a version of the
Flowzone Pros, you get and you get
Discord.
But like I said, you might be new today.
Make sure you like how I teach. Don't
just go and spend that money if you uh
don't like how I trade or teach. Right?
Go through all my free videos first on
YouTube. Make sure make sure you make
sure I'm the right person for you.
Sorry, I'm just trying to watch this
book here while I talk. So, if I'm not
looking at camera, that's why I'm just
watching this seller at 640 because he
keeps reloading and juggling.
They're trying their best to defend this
gray box.
They're doing a good job so far. They
should have come in earlier, I think,
but uh we will see. This is the area
where they attacked it last time. There
you go. They're attacking it again now.
There you go. Thinking, are they going
to join in here? Here we go.
So, a bit of a two-leg into shelf. Bulls
now will want to defend 14. So, we're
going to get a tightening of range here.
Bulls will want to defend sort of 14s.
Back to 40. This guy reloading at 40.
Does he move out the way? And do we
squeeze through now?
If we repric this, I'm telling you, the
shorts are going to get caught. All
right. If we repric this, the shorts are
going to get caught because they've had
numerous attempts and they didn't
complete rotation and we're back inside
gray box. So, I'm watching this now to
see if we hold for longs. Shorts are
trying to come in here and they're
getting squeezed. We're going point of
control now. 55s. Buyers getting trapped
right at the high of that candle.
Watching for acceptance over 55s now.
No acceptance over volume point uh VPO
on the day. So, this is biggest
contested area of the day. We've had
market shorts and market buyers come
there at the same time. So, big big
battle. I'm going to wait to see if we
get over 55s and hold a bid because I
don't want to get caught in this gray
box. I'm going to wait to see if we get
over 55s and hold a bid to join long.
Otherwise, I'm not going to join. I know
I said earlier it's probably the worst
location of the day, but you just feel
like they got a few caught there.
What we looking on cumulative delta? How
we looking?
See this
strong buying coming in very aggressive.
Okay, so this passive selling here
waiting to see if we get above Vpo. Can
we get above the VPO? This red line
which is above There you go. finally
adjusted. 50 52 55s. We need to base
above that.
We need to base above that. No, not long
yet. No, no, no, no, no, no. Who? Who's
just asked that? No, no, no. I'm waiting
to see if we get above this gray box,
right? I don't want to trade into it.
All right, we didn't get down here for
that rotation. So, I'm waiting to see if
we do one of these.
So, remember the red line on your screen
is point of control on the day. It's the
most it's fair value on the day, right?
It's most contested area. I'd much
rather actually be long down here, but
we didn't. What I would have liked to
have seen if I'm honest is this, right?
That would have given me a cheap long to
drive back up. I'm not seeing that
unfortunately. And I'm not going to get
long into the shelf. I'd need to get
above the shelf. Remember, same way we
talked about leaving the shelf. This
trade here downside, we left the shelf,
rejected it, got below, came into that
level. We would need to get above the
shelf, come back to it, offer the buy
up, right? I'm not going to trade into
the level. I don't want to trade in
here. I want to trade an edge of it cuz
people that trade in here will get stuck
because look, look at all the volume
we've created. Think about all the
buyers and sellers. This is the price
that they agree on. That's why we're
trading here so much. We need one side
to be stuck. We have buyers stuck here,
so we sold down. If we have sellers
stuck here, we will buy up. We will use
their pain. I'm not going to I'm not
going to become the liquidity. I'm going
to use the liquidity. So I am either
going to think about buying here or
buying here and I will think about
fading once I see enough buy side stuck.
Uh this is based on reclaiming of flow
zones but I mean when we go sideways
like this you ignore I would ignore a
lot of it down here is like a better buy
right once we go big expansion that
should trend up right. So once we go
tight like this, you got uh flow zone
momentum cloud, New York VWAP and uh
deep pullback all very tight. I would
tend to ignore that a bit more and wait
for these to you be used to develop
trends,
bro. How can we get the order flow order
free platform like footprint? Thanks. Um
there's a video on my YouTube. If you
trade with prop firms, it's free on
trader of eight and ninja trader.
I put the video live maybe two two three
weeks ago. Just go and watch it. It
shows you you will need to turn it on on
trade of eight, right? You need to
basically just click a button to say you
accept and then you will have free
orderflow tools. So VWAP, uh, footprint
DOM, I think Lucid you can pay a bit
extra for a DOM or something. I I pay
with CME anyway.
Do I trust the buy and sell indicator? I
do. I do, but I like them more when
we're um in a trend. Like, so when we're
leaving a range, I like them more. But
but yeah, I mean, you can use them in
range for scalping, but I really like
them. Like when we're a breakout long or
a breakout short, they're so good. When
we go into trend days, they're so so
good. Okay, so battling over this area.
Here you can see the battle in this
area.
It's free on Top Shet. I I don't think
it is. I don't think you get any order
flow on Top [\h__\h] You might you might
get some volume, but you you won't get
uh footprint or anything like that.
Yeah, this is Yeah, it's custom
maintenance. Um Flowzone Pro, you get
version. I need to do a doc so you all
know you can buy it on my website but
you get a version for free a version of
it for free if you do the course and I
teach you how to use it in the course.
Hey Alex, are you trading Profit Trader
Pro? I am. Have you been forced to
switch to Pro Plus? I have not. Is there
a fixed lifetime payout cap? There is
not um normally it's around uh if you
link them together normally it's around
10 I think it's 10,000 one trade 10,000
in 10,000 each account one trade I don't
think they'll move you before that
because they haven't moved me um
yeah there's uh but the I mean there's
no problem of being moved live there
because it works exactly the same way as
as the pro account right
keep the same money trade the same way
daily payouts And there's no cap. Zero
cap, which is awesome.
Still trying to find this bid on the
edge of this range. We're still going to
wait here. It looks pretty good bullish,
but it's a bit early. It's a bit too
high risk, but definitely you see this
seller on bookmap. He just got
absolutely fooked trying to sell into
20s.
So, they're still trying to absorb 25s.
It's that same level. I'm still going to
wait. It's too risky here. But buyers
are passively stepping in here trying to
soak
soak up everything. They're trying to
soak the bid. VIX is making a new low of
day here. Interestingly, we've got
slight divergence. ES has not made a new
high day. SPY is just stuck at that
20day right now.
You're interested in the course. What do
you need to do to start? Head over to
the website flowzonetrader.com.
That's all you got to do. Sign up.
Alex, a good prop firm to move. I want
to leave Topstep. Um, I'd probably move
to Lucid, honestly. Uh, if you trade
with Topstep and you want the same kind
of rules and the and way better service,
I'd say Lucid. Uh, code FCT over there
will get you, if you're new, it might
even get you 40% off. Otherwise, it
would get you 35% off right now, I can
tell you. Um, what is it? They emailed
me yesterday.
So, if you buy five flex accounts or pro
accounts,
um you get 50% off your first two
purchases, 40% off the others, and a
free reset. So, they're probably coming
in at about 60 bucks right now for an
account. That is a onetime fee, by the
way. No activation fee, no monthly
rolling fee, onetime fee, right? Payouts
every 5 days. No consistency rule on the
uh uh SIM funded accounts. They're
really really flipping good.
I'd say like my my top three right now,
Apex because you can still have 20
accounts and if you're patient, they
will get you get the biggest payouts.
TPT for daily payouts and then Lucid.
Those are my top three. And then after
that, Funded Next and Tradeify. Everyone
else leave alone. Unfortunately, right
now I haven't talked about it live. I
have emailed them because I want
clarity. I don't want to absolutely [\h__\h]
on them on stream. Um, I do have
accounts with them, but
funding ticks have not done themselves
any favors in the last week. Let's just
say that. Let's just say that. But we're
still rejecting this range. So, shorts
are still
trying to hold versus this. They want a
breakdown. They want to get into this.
That's where the sellers are trying to
get into. This is the rotation. We
talked about it, right? This is the
rotation that they might build. So, I'm
not going to buy this unless we come
down here and I see sellers stuck or we
come up here and hold this and I see
sellers stuck. I'm not going to buy in
between that range.
You see flow zone starting to flatten
out now. Everything's starting to
flatten out which means the setup right
now
is worse and worse and worse is best way
of putting it.
Yeah. FCT FCT is the code for all the
prop firms other than uh take profit.
You can use code flowzone, but FCT will
get you 40% off if you buy f if you're
new, right? If you're new,
it will get you if you buy five
accounts. Oh, no, not even if you're
new. Just for anyone. I didn't know
that. My bad. So, if you buy five
accounts, which are flex or pro, I would
say go with the flex right now. You will
get 50% off your first two purchases and
then 40% off the rest of them for a 25
and 50k account. and you get a free
reset
super cheap onetime fee. No monthly
rolling, no activation, no [\h__\h] like
that. So if you trade with Topep,
that's probably where you want to go.
It's it's the closest thing to those
rules, I would say.
I don't trade my funded futures. I have
I have no uh nothing good or nothing bad
to say. Lots of my students love them. I
I've never traded with them, so I can't
comment. I can only comment on who I've
traded with.
ES coming back down towards its VW. SPY
doing the same. There's still relative
strength over there. One thing I would
say, this is getting very ugly. All
right, this is now the level. All right,
here's your pin high.
There's your pin low. This is the
rotation. This is a failure to make a
new high. If we fail to make a new low,
we will just keep doing this. If we make
a new low, this is where they're going
to want to come.
But it's starting to look a little bit
ugly out here. It is just a lower time
frame players battling right now with
the higher time frame players. I'm just
going to wait for it to make a decision.
I don't mind bidding or bidding. And I
also don't mind selling if we start
cracking and going back into old uh old
value. That's also okay.
You can see that point of control was
protected by the sellers very very well
there.
Your short 539, same entry as before. I
don't know if you were the same guy as
before. 539. It's again it's good short.
Like it's a good short, but I would be
covering something to this, right? It's
a good short. I'd be covering something
to this because this is where shorts
last got stuck, right? This is where we
think about this. Look where the shorts
last got stuck. It came flying in
here, here, here, and here. And they
just tried again there. All right. So,
I'd be covering some into here just in
case. And if you get a new low, then you
look good. But I would always be
protective of where they're stuck before
because you might find them being like,
"Oh, get me out break even." So, even if
you're only covering 10% or something, I
would pay myself on this into this
pivot. And then, if you get down into
here, great. Remember this gray box is
where you want to be covering and then
this blue box. And then if we get back
down into previous day value, well,
good for you if if you get that move, I
would say that will make you a very
happy person on a Friday.
So ES into view up, spy up. All right.
Like I said, I would be covering a
little piece into here. you you look
good for a move down, but I would always
respect what has happened when I look
left. But if you get a snap here, the
gray box is the target and then the blue
box. All right, so if you get a snap
here, cover and cover
this. There's your value on the day. All
right, so this is discount on the
current day. So I'd be covering and if
you get lucky, you get this.
All right, I'm just going to use the
bathroom. I'll be right back, folks.
All
right, folks.
Oh, you're almost there for your TP. So,
remember this is a current week current
week value area high.
So, if they're looking for expansion,
they will want to defend this sort of
blue line and gray box. All right, so
just be aware of that. You had a big
buyer just step in and he stepped in
again. So he's trying to move up here.
What is he doing?
He could have been covering to be
honest.
Could have been covering.
What's your long target? What do you
mean?
We're not in long yet. So
we can discuss targets as and when it
starts shaping up uh not before because
it's going to be based on structure and
volume and what's available. So we just
wait. Thanks Alex for your knowledge.
Green week for me. See you next week.
Awesome. Awesome work Mar.
Yeah. repricing that whole uh candle
from 9:45 this morning.
So, they're still holding this rotation.
You can see like this great box and the
current week uh value area high, right?
They're just soaking and straight back
to VWAP. This is like I don't like
trading these. This is We talked about
this, didn't we? We talked about this
probably needing to be built out because
this is so thin, right? This is the
battle, right? So, shorts are defending
this, bulls are defending this. This is
your whips saw. Uh let me just check
where are we at on the options. So
probably I would say probably cool wall
that's holding up spiders and the
opening of the day was probably a bit of
a put ball down at 675. So that's the
rotation over there.
They want to complete this rotation.
We will see.
Can I please measure the bullish move?
You mean from the start of the day? I
You mean the opening range like this
9:30 low?
Yeah, you're in the 50.
So, gray box is in the 60s. little node
here that you'd be losing value at that
point. You'd be trading back inside
current week. I will remind you,
you must be looking higher time frame.
Current week's value,
previous day value,
day before that's value. We've moved
value up. We've moved value up. We're
trying to protect this. The question,
it's a question right now. Are buyers
willing to defend this or is this going
to be a look above and fail back down to
this block? And is that going to hold or
is that going to be look above and fail
into old value?
But if we don't hold above this level
right here,
then we're going to go back into the
current developing profile and we could
think about 330s then potentially
potentially. It's a bit early to say,
but potentially
right now they're doing a good job of
trying to absorb this level. This is
kind of what we did yesterday. What was
the level we bought bid off yesterday?
I'm trying to remember what we kept
buying. All right, there. Same thing.
One, two, three, four attempts they had
of breaking down underneath uh the 95s.
I think it was 220s was the level for
the rip. And uh same kind of thing.
So lower time frame sellers I would say
are in control. Lower time frame higher
time frame bulls have got a chance.
They've got a chance.
You haven't seen anyone chart the way I
do. I'm blowing your mind and you like
it. It's probably uh not because I'm
particularly good. It's probably more
that most people on YouTube are
particularly [\h__\h] Um to be quite honest
with you. Uh I am nothing special. These
are techniques uh that have been around
forever and ever and ever and ever and
ever. It's uh you know, I've done my
10,000 hours plus. It's more that a lot
of uh
people on
Discords and YouTubetubes are probably
teaching
absolute nonsense or not teaching at all
or not teaching at all.
How do you move account group from Apex?
I don't know what you mean. What's an
account group? Do you mean how do you
delete an account? uh you will need to
go into your history of uh payments or
active subscriptions and press cancel a
subscription there if that's what you
mean. Otherwise, I don't know what you
mean. Do I have a contact at TPT by any
chance? Having a payout issue customer
service is atrocious. Yeah, they are a
little bit slow. I don't have a contact.
I have I can give you an email that I
use which they always get back to me up
on.
Give me a second, mate. I'll find it.
Uh it's just Nick. Nick at uh Nick is
support at take profit trade air. Sure
it is. But that was raised from a ticket
and then I had a discussion with them.
Normally I raise a ticket and it takes
can take them up to 24 hours to get
back. Um Chris if are you this isn't
loaded and and and by anyway are you a
student? If you're a student talk to me
in Discord and I can raise an issue with
them because we have a have deals with
them. If not I can't do a lot other than
tell you who to email. Normally they
will get back to you. It can just take a
day.
So, a little low volume node here.
We're starting to build out. This is uh
bears are doing a pretty good job here
at the moment.
But the question is,
can they force this breakdown into here
or here? And if if there's a an
inability to hold under, we will come
back up.
I'm just waiting right now because I
didn't slap it bearish up here and here.
So, I'm waiting.
I'm trying to be flexible today. We we
talked about it right at the beginning
of the day. I talked about it in D
discord. We're going to need to be
flexible today. And you want to be very
careful the closer and closer and closer
you get to expiry today.
Two weeks. No way. I I had like two
replies yesterday. I I would re I would
re raise a ticket.
I had two replies yesterday because I
didn't have a credit put in my account
and I had to question something else as
well.
No, that's not a thing. Rob Drag, take
that information out of your head. They
they dump NQ on a Friday is not a thing.
If you go and look statistically, that
stat will not exist.
You will find just as many many days as
they pump NQ on a Friday.
FCT Teresa blow zone trader FZT.
It's above if you look above right now
on the screen or at the bottom of the
screen. Code FCT.
No worries, Chris.
Um,
what's your higher time frame, Nihow?
Is it an hour or is it a day or is it a
week or is it a 15 for me? They have the
chance of flipping
but they need to confirm with this
pullback. We are in the pullback after
the breakout. Right?
If we think about this, just think about
like some trend like this. Let me draw.
Okay, we've built liquidity.
We've broken out. Are we going to hold a
pullback? If we hold the pullback and
bid, then yes, this can still be a look
above and fail. All right, remember like
trends get confirmed when we hold
pullbacks. All right, in here we were in
liquidity build. In here, we've built
it. Now, we've used it. Can we hold it?
If we can't hold it and we come back
down into here, this is nothing more
than a big old bull trap.
While I'm trying not to be too biased
today, I'm trying to be like, let it
develop. Do I want to play expansion
ranges beyond what's normal on an OPEX
day when we've had a killer week?
previous week value area low for me is
way higher up here at 714 right now.
They're still bidding off here, but
again we're developing a little little
shelf here at 88. So I'd say if they can
bid and hold above 88, they got to then
get through VWAP. ES is still holding
its VW up and maybe they come and test
up here. This is what I don't like is
this developing this way. So it's not as
sharp now. We've like extended that a
little bit more that slope there
unfortunately. And then we've got a
little bit here and then a little bit
here, a little bit here. It's a teeny
bit messy
at the moment. I'd say sellers are in
control.
Sellers are in control. Here they come.
Let's see what they're going to do here.
Are they going to be aggressive and get
us down into this block? And then what
are we going to do? Are bulls actually
going to step up in this grail blue box
today? Or is this a look above and a
fail?
Yeah, give me a second, Ericin, because
I just want to like focus on this now
just in case we get a lot of trap
participants, in case there's a
mean reversion back into range setting
up here as we come into this gray box.
Just what let me uh just watch this for
a second. So, we've had a [\h__\h] ton of
sellers just come flying in here under
previous week close. So, 70 to 60 was
all aggressive selling. So, just trying
to see here if they get follow through
or if a bid comes back in again. We
haven't come back down into this blue
box yet.
Still getting absorbed here. There's
definitely a passive bid here starting
to to soak, but we're at value area low
on the day. If they start expanding
through here, this is going to be like
potential mean reversion trades. This
why I just want to wait for a second
before I answer you.
Rebidding at 65.
So I'd say 70 is is the line here.
Sellers need it back below 70 right now.
Balls keep coming in here. I'm just
waiting to see if they get hit down one
more time and then see if this guy on
tape wants to actually absorb. He keeps
moving away from 65. So, might be a bit
of a spoofer down there.
This level here. Sellers tried it again
there and failed into 75.
Definitely seeing some absorption here
on the tape. I want to see one more
little flush down. Doesn't need to make
a new low. I just want to see a little
pull down just to know that there's a
buyer willing to absorb.
Starting to see it. We need a pull. I
need a pull down to see this buy. I
don't want to [\h__\h] get caught here.
Otherwise, I'm going to have to play
over it. You mother clucks.
Very close to getting involved there.
Maybe some of you took that value low
reclaim. It was nice. Okay, here we go.
Pull back in and show me.
Pull back in and show me, please.
Come on. I've been so patient. If you
just go without me, I'm going to be
somewhat miffed.
That line in the sand 70s
20 points higher now. Come on,
you buggers. You caught those shorts and
you went, you didn't give me a chance. I
should have just slapped the market.
[\h__\h] happen sometimes. That's twice
today. Twice today I've seen them
trapped and not be able to get filled.
Oh, so annoying.
All right, so what did I see? Same thing
as always. All right, into the gray box
where I was thinking about bidding and
these guys got caught, right? They got
caught and then we just went and I was
just looking for one little tap back in
somewhere down here to leave these guys
trapped that I could long out of. And
and unfortunately we're just going
straight squeeze out of it cuz these
guys are all caught at the moment
cuz I wanted that for the first move
back into VWOP. So
we'll see. We'll see.
No, you did. You didn't distract me. You
didn't. I I was I was zoomed in and
ready for it. I just there was no real
entry. I maybe could have marketed on
the reclaimer 75. It wasn't new,
honestly. It's just I didn't see I saw
what I wanted to see with the trap
players, but I couldn't um didn't see
exactly the entry I want. Maybe they
come back down and hold this m like
maybe maybe it's very risky now though.
You [\h__\h] Oh, thank you. You little
[\h__\h]
Little [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] waited like an hour for that.
Oh, the fun of the fun of trading. Eh,
you draw it out, you wait for it, you
see them trapped, and then gone.
Oh, that's funny.
All right, maybe if they get through V
up, they probably come and visit up here
into 26es. So, if you are long, uh,
we've got a ton of imbalances to start
taking out. So my next target here would
be sort of tens and twelves and then
through that 20s. These are just
imbalances and then 24s. Um the big
selling started at 24. Uh there's a
there's a cluster like 24 to 30 and then
38 and 46 is where they were earlier. So
I'd be taking profit into these like
drives higher. Right? We're in a
rotational market.
Surprise surprise. We're in a rotational
market. These are the edges like we've
talked about. We are likely to do this.
So, I waited for an edge, right? Because
if we're in a rotation, I've got to
trade an edge back upside. You don't
want to join the mid part of this range.
It's way too risky now. All right? You
you when we're trading rotation, it goes
against trend, right? Trend, you like
this and this and this and this and you
can join later. When you're trading
rotation, you need to trade someone's
pain. Profit profit and then if you get
acceptance, fantastic. But
a called it absolutely perfect, but
couldn't get it. I'm sorry, guys.
I'm sorry.
Oh god.
just shows uh like
markets are funny things, right? I
didn't want to limit order in here,
right? Cuz I don't know if they're going
to flush it, but I saw them get trapped
and the moment I saw them get trapped,
look at these candles. Boom, boom, boom,
boom, boom. We never gave me just this.
It's all I wanted. All I wanted was a
tiny little pull back in to see these
guys get stuck and start to cover. But
we just rushed. And this is your TP. All
right. So now I'd be out a good chunk.
All right. Most of my profit would now
be out of this cuz we can rotate back
down again. This is a straight squeeze
up. We can rotate back down again. If
you find acceptance above, then well,
congratulations because you are going to
get the best trade of the day. If you
get that, if you find acceptance now, if
you bought this down here on the reclaim
and you find acceptance over this, you
are going to get a monster trade. I
promise you. But you should be paying
yourself.
How did I know they were trapped? Uh
because they they sold the low of day
into the pivot. Remember like this is
we're in a rotation, right? If we're in
a rotation
and we're moving value up, right?
Remember previous days values here,
right? So we're moving value higher. So
that means shorts in here are stuck and
the day before value is like down here
somewhere. So shorts here are stuck.
Shorts here are stuck. So where do I
want to pay buy? I want to buy at a
level where I think is cheap on the day
and where they might be forced to cover
and I want to buy where people who don't
understand rotations are being too
aggressive. So
this right is discount on the day.
That's our discount. So, I want to buy
in here. This is an area where I'm
interested to buy. Now, my signal to buy
that again because we're in a rotation.
I don't I ignore flow zones basically in
a rotation. So, in this in this wick
here, I want to see trap sellers
on this breakdown
under here.
We get trap sellers. And I actually see
it way better on Here,
let me show you. All right, all of this
was sell side, right? All of this move
under value. Look at all this delta.
It's all sell delta. And here, big big
level. And here at 80s, so you would
have heard me say 82s, 82s, right? So,
all I wanted was a little pull back in.
I can't draw on here annoyingly. This is
why I don't use Ninja Trader to teach.
But all I wanted was a move up, a
pullback, leave these guys trapped, and
then I can trade the squeeze. That's all
I wanted. You could argue I should have
marketed in, but uh it's a harder, you
know, I don't know what fill I'm going
to get. If it skips and I get an awful
fill, I'm going to be fuming.
Exactly, Scott.
Exactly that. Scott
Raph got 40 points. 480 to 520s. 480s.
Really nice. You got that? 480s to 520s.
Yeah, it's really good. And like just
hopefully, you know, you'll run users
go. You never know. But we're going to
protect this shelf, right? But if you
get going, you might be laughing. You
might have the trade of the day here,
guys. You might have the trade of the
day here. They're getting really
aggressive on the buys here. They are
trying to reclaim. So, they're piling
in, looking to get back above this gray
box now. And if we get back above that,
I will consider buying if we get back
above pull back and hold it. Knowing my
luck, we get back above and we squeeze
100 points.
Point control is red line.
So this is where all the sellers were.
All the sellers came in earlier today
from 25 to 47. we get back above that u
and definitely if we get back above 57
it is go time right for the market but
as long as you've paid yourself some
you're okay
I'm not actually using volutric bars.
I'm using a third party indicator. But
you can use volumetric bars. Yes. Same
thing.
Okay. Sellside imbalance here at 47s.
They need to get above that.
They need to get above 47s and they need
to get above 53s. And if they get above
value at 65, it is absolute [\h__\h] go
time for this market.
Here we go. You guys are
God damn it. How can I give you guys a
banger like this and not be in it? Okay,
give me something to get get involved
in.
I would not be short here. There's
nothing in here to stay short. You've
got you've got a level, but you've
traded into this is the third time
you're probably going to see a bit of a
squeeze. I would not be shorting against
this strong momentum. We're in a
rotation. Yeah, location is okay for the
short, but look at the momentum. Strong
upside then very might well squeeze
everyone out. ES is looking for IB high.
We're going to look for the same here.
Top side of this gray box. And we're
probably going to squeeze it all out.
Here we go, folks.
Value area high on the day 66.
Initial balance right up at those highs
at 600. So that would be your target if
we get through value area high. So we
get through 66. I'd be taking some
profit in and around here. And then
you're looking for a higher day. And if
you get very very very lucky, you will
get 700 today. Very lucky. But we are
you're not going to uh assume that. So
I'd be out a big chunk of my profit
here. Probably 60 70% if you took this
reaction here. 60 70% 10% here and then
hold 10 just in case you get up there.
Right.
I'd be out most of my money in this gray
box.
If you see a rejection, the problem with
the short now is how we've built, right?
Because we've built these nodes here.
All right. So, maybe you see something
like this, but your cover points are
going to be here and here, and we don't
know if bids come flying in. Remember,
it's OPEX. I I'm less inclined
now because we haven't come up here yet.
This the momentum is so so strong. Like,
maybe they offer this
I don't like it. Like honestly,
you can get caught here very easily
short side, but it's up to you, man. I
don't want to tell you what to do. I
personally would ignore I want to play
edgeto edge. Yeah, you're seeing a bit
of a reaction here. Sure.
You You could argue you're looking for
the same thing as earlier, but I think
Bulls have taken control of this at the
moment if I'm honest.
There is definitely a battle zone up
here. There's no doubt about it. like
you're absolutely adamant. You need to
see a reaction here and you need to be
covering into this and this. But I think
bulls are looking to complete that at
the moment. It feels like yesterday
though. If we look at uh price
yesterday, it took a few goes. Was it
yesterday or the day before? Yesterday.
Is this yesterday?
Right. The whips saw, right? The W
W W W W W W W W W W W W W W W W W W W W
W trap late buyers dunk it retest back
to the same level react back down to the
same level react midpoint. We're sort of
in this stage here, right?
Maybe you get that move. It's just feels
feels a little bit iffy. That's all I'm
saying, man. I I don't want to put you
off if if you like trading I hate
trading rotations, right? You should
know that if you're joining me here. I
absolutely hate it. Especially as the
rotations start to get tighter because
at least this morning. All right, we had
expansion from here to this red box
which has been here before this morning.
Then we had move from here to here. Then
it's got tighter and tighter and
tighter. Right? So the range was here.
Then it became this. Then it became this
again. Now it might become this. Right?
We are getting tighter and tighter and
tighter. There's less points to aim for
is I guess a better way of me saying it.
But do not let me put you if your trade
is if you are a range trader, if you
like trading the exits of these shells
and you don't mind scalping 5, 10, 15,
20 points, do not let me put you off,
right? You must trade your setup. You
must trade your setup.
Move this down. This box is slightly
now. That's what I mean. They're
developing this over and over.
How long we got left there? 45 minutes.
Do some nice giveaways today.
All right. Q's holding their 20 days.
Spies back over their 20 days absorbing
on VWAP. ES over 20 days. Absorb VWAP.
absorb PDH
still got a target above there on ES to
aim for it can still go for those 6888.
Um
surely gamma level must be 680 on uh
spy. So I'd say if we get over 680 I'm
assuming I don't know but I'm assuming
we move into positive gamma. 615 I'm
sure I wrote this on the cues. Let me
check. Uh, I'm sure 615 was back into
positive gamma on the cues. D. Why can't
I remember that? Come on, Alex.
I'm sure it's 600 to 615s.
600 to 615 call. So, if we're above 615s
on
Q's, which we are, technically we're in
positive gamma, which means a squeeze.
There is squeeze potential. There is
squeeze potential above 615. We're
trying currently trading 616. So, and
that last pivot that held on that
pullback was 615. So, we have squeeze
potential today on the queue. So, I will
just say that
what's the indicator point control on
Ninja Trader? Um,
it's a third party. Let me see what it's
called. It's not just point control.
It's called city footprint. It's paid
indicator
back in this rotation. The the gray box,
the box of death where I do not want to
participate.
Right? So if you can see how I trade, I
don't like uh participating in volume in
the shelf. I want to participate at the
edge.
Cyd I think it's called city.
The website would be sorry I'll get up.
You give me a second.
TP.
Let me just post it. going be easier.
That's the website there.
Above 6825 on S&P there's a positive
drift. Mm to buy ES passively as the day
goes on. Yeah, similar to Q's basically
Q's above 615 positive drift. Same
thing.
Market's gone asleep in this gray box.
Jeff Patson says, "Got to run here.
Beautiful week, Alex. Thanks for your
work you put into your channel." You're
welcome, Jeff. Thanks for joining.
Appreciate all you new followers. This
is amazing. 770 of you on stream.
Fantastic. Just waiting for us to leave
this gray box at the moment. If you're
like, "Why isn't he in a trade? Why
isn't he doing anything?" Well, I missed
my entry at the lows. I'm going to be
honest with you. I missed the entry at
the low. So, I have to wait now. Have to
wait to see if we find acceptance above
this gray box. If we leave the gray box
to the downside, I'm not convinced I'm
going to touch it now given that we uh
have put in couple of lows down here.
And every time we've come down here,
right, we've seen some big passive
buying and this is the 615 level on QQQ.
Why can't I draw that? QQQ. So, I know
we're in positive gamma above that right
now. I think the market is trying to
drift higher.
location was great down here. Um, this
morning I bought bought it out the gate.
I just saw too many uh bears ruining
themselves and I bought straight into
this move here and I sold a bit too
early. I had a reload and probably sold
a bit too early and then uh just had to
wait or this pullback and I missed it.
Missed it. Called it. Missed it.
Happens. It happens. I'm not going to
get every trade, folks. But this is why
those who are like, I want a signal when
you buy and sell. The problem is I gave
you the signal here when I'm talking
about it. I I told you I'm going to
drift into here. I'm going to look for
trapped sellers. And I told you they're
trapped. They're trapped. I'm going to
wait for a pullback. But you guys might
not need to wait for a pullback. And if
you didn't, well, you've got a move I
didn't get. So, this is why it's
important to understand what's happening
in the chart. I'm not going to get
everything. Sometimes I'm going to get
it wrong.
Sometimes I'm not going to take take
trades that you guys might take might
like to trade. So sellers keep coming in
here getting caught.
Who's this guy coming in at 35? These
idiots. 35 32. They keep getting caught
here. Sellers keep getting caught here.
That is what I am seeing at the moment.
Just passed a 50k flex account with
Lucid. Congratulations my friend. I
passed two of them yesterday as well.
First time using them this week. Awesome
work.
Why can't I get long right now? Why
would I? Let's frame this another way.
Why would I want to get long right now?
Where's my edge in getting wrong long
right now?
I don't want to buy fair value on the
day and fair value is near premium. I
want to buy discount or I want to keep
at least see lots of people stuck and us
potentially get ready to move value up.
Oh no. There we go.
I don't want to buy here. In fact, I
don't want to buy or sell in here at
all. Right. What's happened if you've
bought and sold in here?
No edge for me. That's where the edge
isn't. When we leave it. When we leave
it. When we leave it. When we leave it.
Probably get edge.
Ray Ray, I've been trading since 1994.
You are very impressive. Keep preaching
patience
or you have no shot. Missing trades is
okay. Exactly, man.
Exactly. I learned the hard way a long
time ago. Chasing trades will get you
wrecked. Trading in bad locations.
Key to trading for me is trading in good
locations and beyond that it's time.
That's why I actually think swing
trading is way way easier. If you size
down swing trading, if you're trading a
good location, chances are you are
buying yourself enough time to get a
good move as long as your stop is
correct. Hardest thing in day trading is
waiting for that location and then you
don't have much time to attack it. Like
we just saw, didn't get the exact entry
I want. Went without me. Missed the
prime location. Don't chase. Let it go.
My French felt felt fluid. It's not that
good. Really really isn't very good.
Thanks, Ray Ray.
All right, sellers are trying to get
this breakdown away from this range, but
every time we're coming into these 30s
and 20s, they are getting themselves
caught.
Delta is still positive.
We make a higher high. What's this
pivot here?
That's not good.
We're making a higher high. Uh,
Delta's more positive here than it was
here. So, there's definitely passive
selling here. Just a battle. We got to
wait. We got to wait for some form of
expansion.
Feels like it wants to go, but what it
feels like what it does. Yeah, exactly.
Trades by SD. Uh, I agree. Just range
rotation, right? We've moved value up,
but it but we're just getting stuck at
at edges of levels. Uh look at spy spy
680. It's got to has got to be a put
there. Once we get through that, maybe
we get going.
Is Trump talking Raph?
I've given up listening to him recently.
Honestly,
totally given up.
Just over 30 minutes left, folks. We
will do some giveaways.
Passive selling is limit order selling,
right? Limit order sending. Someone just
selling, refreshing their limits, right?
Just refreshing limits, not hitting the
market, not slapping the bid, just
refreshing the limits, just placing
offers out there on the ask over and
over and over again.
Are they still activating funded
accounts same day at Lucid? Yes. Yeah.
Market looks like it wants to break up
here. He's trying. ES is trying. They
got to get through these 680s on SPY.
They're They're trying to get through
the 680s on SPY. We're still in the gray
box, but they are definitely attempting
to do it.
Keep banging on 680. 6. It's not once
got a 5m minutee close over 680 today.
Every time we've got 680, we must be
finding a put wall here.
Must be finding a football here. Two
more minutes left in this 5minute
candle.
Look how tight we're getting. Like so
inside this gray box, we've got like a
this developing here now as well. You
can see that. Make a bit darker maybe.
Right.
getting really tight.
Really tight. This is why someone said,
"Why not long now?" Just because this is
what's happening.
I want to trade the momentum. I I don't
want to become the liquidity.
Do I trade ENQ for volatility? I think
ES is a little better index to trade.
It's each to their own. Yeah, like the
volatility is good. Um, I've traded it
quite a while now, so I understand its
personality, how it operates, how it
likes to go through stop runs, how
sometimes it's a dirty bugger and leaves
it. Um, it's each to their own. I used
to trade ES, but I've got used to NQ
now. And I only like trading one really.
Keeps me like knowing what the levels
are the next day. You know, the same
reason I left small caps and large caps.
I swing I will swing those now. But um I
don't want to have 10 different levels
in my head. It's nice knowing like I
know 615 600 level on QQQ. I I know 500
was a level on NQ. 600 now the level
today. I know above that is 700. I know
they're easy levels at the moment, but
that's just what they are based on the
tape. It's not that they're whole
numbers. That's actually what they are.
correlation between ES and NQ. Do I ever
consider one can already be outside the
zone to buy like now ES and ENQ? Not
yet. Yeah, I mean I I'm watching them
for correlation. Look, we're starting to
break 680 here on spiders now. Um but
it's also understanding why the
correlation is or isn't there. Like if
we have relative strength in one, it's
understanding why. Like if ES is
stronger than ENQ, it's because
healthcare or finances are running that
day or tech is relatively weak that day
etc etc. Here you go. So here's the
break and look at look at spy above the
680. That's the key right into value
area high on the day here into the edge
of this gray box. Can we find acceptance
over this? They are offering higher now
into 75s. Right. So they're trying to
use it as a magnet to draw up
I'll call you later. All right, darling.
So, ES taking out high of day. Uh,
almost completing that move into the
8875s we talked about this morning.
Not quite taking out previous day high,
previous week high. Zoom this out. Not
quite taking out previous day high
on uh spiders. That is
they have a chance to squeeze here. If
they can hold the bid. They can hold the
bid. They have the chance to squeeze
here. Big if. But that's what they are
trying to do. Force a bid up.
Still not left this volume here. But
they are trying. They are desperately
trying.
Yes, took high day, traded back inside
its range. Can it find a bid here again?
Can Spy re rebid 680 or is that a failed
look above?
Back down to the 680s. It's going to
come trading 68025s now. Does it find a
bid in front of 680 or positive?
gamma or not. Is it a look above and a
fail? We are about to find out.
Cannot get above this gray box. Once we
get above this gray box, you probably
get a swipe higher. There will be a lot
of stops up here at this point.
So, seller's trying to walk down now. He
moved from 65 to 60 to 55. Someone's
desperate to get filled here at 55 60
lot.
He's getting impatient.
There's no real bid till 35 right now.
He's getting very impatient. He's moved
to 50 now. He's trying to walk down now.
He's getting very upset. He's not
getting filled.
51 is the level. That's where shorts
came flying in there. there. So if they
print back above 51, they can reprint
higher here. It's getting very tight
though. So reprint 55s will be the next
reprint. If they There you go. 351s. Can
we go 55s? This where they're re
attacking this sell side.
And if we can get through this, there is
a potential squeeze because they've just
sold very hard into this now. So 60s, we
get through 60s, we go 70s. If we get
through that, we go 600s probably. Yes.
Trying to go again. So they held the
680.
So they've got a chance here to squeeze
out
560. They keep refreshing
the lack of buying momentum up here into
it.
There's a refresh seller here at 60s.
Keeps trying to come in and then walk
down.
Still nothing for me yet. Not outside
this big gray box yet.
Rebidding 50s.
That seller at 60s moved to 57. We're
very tight seven point range here.
Something's going to give. They can't
stay here forever. They've got too tight
here. They're juggling the tape.
Something nasty will happen soon. They
can't stay like this forever. Someone's
going to get swiped out or washed out.
One side of it. There's too much volume
coming in at this level.
Look at this battle.
A little buy side imbalance.
Sellers need it under 30s. Honestly,
they need to exit 30s. These sellers.
I'm going to get some water. Oh, this
does this. Be right back.
Wow. Still not moved.
Jeez.
Can't believe that's still not moved.
It's like a double little node here.
It's gross. Gross. Gross. Gross. Gross.
Gross. There's too many sellers here
though under 51s. So they sold 51s, 47s,
38s, and 29s. And if we start breaking
above value high, they're all going to
force be forced to cover in my opinion.
So here's the attempt at 60s. Once they
break that, they should swipe 70s and
go. There you go. So now the question
is, can they hold a bid? Right? Because
that's the stop run. Can they hold a
bid? Right.
So, here's 60s.
Are they going to go 70s? Can they hold
a bid now?
Because sellers can use aggressive
buyers to passively just smack back
down. So, want to see if they hold a bid
or not.
At the moment, you had stops getting
popped there. Not actually that many,
but there were stops being popped.
back down into range. Aggressive seller
coming in here at 55s again. It's just
still
not not enough. Not attractive enough
for me to do anything.
You seeing both sides.
Someone's going to get hurt soon. Like
they could just drop this back down to
30 really quickly. And if they snap
that, they get a big wash. Or if they
keep absorbing this little pocket in
front of 30 and 40 and get a breakout,
they can go the other way. Um it is like
a I don't know what like we're at the
edge of value on the day, but uh
all all I would say is in this pocket
here
is all sellers
and if they stay stuck, this is
possible. Now, if they take control,
that collapse can happen again for sure
because this is the edge of value. This
is the edge of the shelf. You can see
why I don't trade in these gray boxes.
Someone asked me earlier, why why no
long? Well, I just don't want to trade
in this. You'd have to sit in this for
so long.
Yeah, totally divergence. Yeah, ES took
made a new high day, but it actually
missed its key level.
It missed its key level as did spy.
Missed its key level.
Yes. Ray, Ray, that's a really good way
of putting it. Tug of war. Definitely.
Definitely. So, if you think about point
of control,
right? Point of control. This is the
price at which buyers
and sellers agree on because it's where
most volume has been traded and you need
both sides to trade volume, right? So,
that's where they agree is fair value.
And if we look at price around that,
right,
sellers keep trying to sell under here,
buyers keep trying to buy above here,
and we keep getting stuck. And that's so
that's a really good way of putting it.
It's a tug of war. What we're doing
right now is we have acceptance in this
range. This is fair value. All right? If
buyers deem this is too cheap, we will
leave this range. If sellers deem this
is too expensive and buyers get
exhausted, we will leave this range. If
they just keep agreeing on price, we
will just keep doing this over and over,
right?
Joe bouncing around the level we were at
at 10 a.m. but lower volume bearish tilt
for me. It being Friday heading into
quad witching. Yeah, I mean totally is
quad witching. Um
I wouldn't be too bearish on it.
I honestly I wouldn't. The only thing
that you've got going for you right is
that this has been an edge and that you
probably have some buyers trapped up
here. But if you think about this, that
is not bearish. This is a potential
squeeze up right into this. And if we
like we talked about, where was
yesterday's value? Where's today's
value? Where's the days before's value?
Where's the current week's value? Where
are we above it? So, we're auctioning
higher. I wouldn't be bearish on this.
There you go. Starting to break now.
Finally, they're trying to do it.
Try and try and create um
neutrality in your head where you can.
So they can they find acceptance above
where we go blue to gray, right? And we
get a new value area high. Can we let
out those buyers from earlier? How many
buyers were caught there earlier? Let's
have a little look
where we have. So we have a sellside
imbalance here to 67s.
We have another one up here
into 80s and most of the buying volume
look was right at that high. Some idiot
right at that high. All right. So, we'd
be watching
these guys here, these guys here. So,
I'd be taking some profit into this
70s. If we get 80s, great. And then
higher day. And then above that, we
might have some room. But you just want
to lock in into that push, which you
might have already done while I'm
talking about it.
Yes, we just just just did just came
right into it.
What's my streaming schedule for the
holidays? Let me have a look. I haven't
really thought about it, but let let me
have a look now.
We can make some agreement together as a
team of what works for everyone. Um,
how can I make this? No, I want the
other way. So, I'm assuming we're
opening 22nd, 23rd. I will take 24, 25,
26th off for sure.
So I will probably trade Monday, Tuesday
next week
and maybe Monday, Tuesday the following
week and maybe the Friday, but probably
not. So let's do 20. Let's guarantee
22nd, 23rd, 29th, 30th, back to usual on
the 5th, I think, unless I go away on
vacation.
Only thing that would worry me here is
if bulls don't get the break. We've
built a [\h__\h] ton of liquidity in here
now. If bulls don't get this, that can
happen real quick.
We're coming in for lunch. Honestly, you
got 15 minutes left. Like,
here comes the bears. The Bulls are not
getting that breakout. I would just I
would personally
you guys do what you want. Personally, I
would leave this box alone until you
exit this box one way or another. Leave
the box alone until you exit it one way
or another.
Bears are doing their best here to step
in aggressively.
Heading out. Great week. Love you, Alex.
Appreciate your ongoing contribution. No
worries, mate. Take care. Take care. All
right. Starting to exit now. Starting to
see some bearish exits. They're going to
come sweep these guys out. Just going to
have a look at liquidity on the foot.
Where are they stacking in? There's not
that much actually. Doesn't look very
good.
I'm still neutral bias right now.
I live in Los Angeles. Yeah, I'm in LA.
Right, let's do a giveaway.
Bears have got a shot here.
I'm not going to play it. Bears have got
a shot here though. The S is breaking
down. Bears have got a shot here. They
might get this wash now. They're coming
for it.
What I'd say is they entered again at th
30 to 50 is where they've just come
flying in. They must keep price below
those levels. You have a little shelf
here. 35 to 40. That's basically where
they must reject. If they fail to reject
that again, then you are not going to
see any further rotation. If you're
going to see further rotation, you can
attack potentially for VWOP and
underneath VWAP, the gray box below. If
they reclaim the stuff above, I'd say
you're in big trouble.
Like again, I'm not going to touch this.
I'm neutral bias. I don't really want to
do anything else. We've had a couple all
right trades. I missed missed the big
one. I would have liked.
Let's have a look at quick read on the
mag. Tesla 1.35% down. Nvidia 3.34% up.
It's trying to get back inside that 180
level we talked about. Uh Microsoft 4%
up. Meta 0.38% up. Google 0.89% up.
Amazon 0.71% up. Apple 0.41%
down. Bids are trying to come in here.
So, they're going to try and reclaim.
This is the area for bears. They got to
defend this now. Otherwise, they're
going to well, they're going to ruin
their uh Fridays probably.
Now is their opportunity. And that 680
on SPY. You want to see SPY reject 680?
So, do bears force a lower high and
start aggressively washing here? This is
the question. This is their opportunity
to do it. It's right here, right now.
You need to see a aggressive wash here
and a breakdown through the 520s, 515s,
510s, 500s. Otherwise, they are going to
get caught because they've just sold
here at 30s. Again, remember 30s to 46s
is where they've been attacking this all
day. They will need to see a breakdown
here.
They need to exit this gray box. So, if
you're short, you're looking for this to
wash down. There you go.
There you go. Right. So, you'd be
looking for VW up here or at least this
wick here ideally and then VWAP and then
all the way back down.
The tape shifted pretty quick there.
Look at that tape shift. Okay. Let's
see.
VWAP coming up. So, I'd cover some here
and see if you get a wash down to gray
box, but you should be out a good chunk
of it here, folks. All right, if you
did, take that.
If you get a continuation, you want to
get back down
here,
right? This would be like yesterday.
They're going to do this garbage. This
would be like yesterday.
And if they reclaim that, your shorts
are off the table. Okay, so shorts are
in control. What did I say? 30 to 46.
Something like that. There you go.
Shorts are in control from here. If you
let go of this, you're going to get
this. You must respect some of this
volume. Cover some to there. And then
here and here. If you get very, very
lucky. That shifted so quick. Then
once they uh let go of that gray box.
Look at this shift here.
So quick and now this and now this is
possible.
Midday price action. I just think I just
think it's cuz it's it's OPEX. We're
just pinning. Like I think the big thing
for me is this.
All right. We know 680 is their level.
And we got a new high and then a
rotation and then they can absorb here
again. Right? We're just pinning until
we see like the bigger level snap. 75
would be the next one right the way down
here. Right where we bid off the start
of the day. So we bid off put wall sorry
bid off cool wall into sorry bid off put
wall into cool wall pulling back. That's
that's all it is. It's quad witching.
Right. It's not a day to be like, I'm
going to risk all my accounts and go
crazy.
Swing traded this week. Uh
yeah,
the best entry for me if you were
bullish was here. This move here was
highly probable back upside.
And the best bearish move would have
been this from Monday,
right? Because we left old value
and that was you could have taken puts
down. Um what was our level? It was the
old contract was 930. So I'm trying to
remember what that new contract level
was. I think it was this 25,000 was 930
on the old contract. That was the exit.
So, you could have got you could have
got basically 700 point uh short this
week or you could have taken calls from
here. Um
and I probably would have exited some on
that first push up because you don't
know if it's going to fail. So, in all
fairness, 400 point upside, 700 point
downside, both available this week if
you understood the rotations.
All right, let's uh get out of it. What
What have I just done? No.
No, Ninja Trader. No, no, no, no, no.
Please don't [\h__\h] up now. There we go.
Yes. Smash that like button. 800 of you
watching. Let's get it up to 400 likes,
please. And then we'll do a giveaway.
You guys get me 400 likes, I will give
you Apex accounts. There we go. Fair
deal. Maybe even 500. You're capable of
it. You're more than capable of it.
Don't type it too early, folks. All
right? Because I haven't done it yet.
I've got to set it live, otherwise you
guys don't get entered. So, I want you
guys to have a chance of winning. So,
don't don't type it yet.
Don't type it yet. Just smash that like
button for me.
It's true, Robert. I mean, I don't
disagree with you. You 800 of you
watching. We should have 800 likes. I
don't disagree with you. It doesn't cost
you anything to hit that like button.
So, you can see the reaction. So, they
bid back in. I'm just going to show you
this why I saying this is where the
shorts got trapped. This is what
remember earlier we were talking about
the range was bigger here and then it
gets smaller and smaller and now it
might just be here to here right because
this is where shorts got caught and this
is where buyers are now caught and this
is now the rotation. So it's going to
get smaller and smaller as the day goes
on unless we get a breakout either side.
Breakout would be here or here right
Swizzy. soon as we do this uh giveaway,
we will go through levels and I'll give
you what I'd be looking at for the rest
of the day, which wouldn't be a lot if
I'm honest. I'd be very very careful on
uh trading in the afternoon session on
OPEX, but I will give you everything.
All right, let's set this up.
Hang on, hang on, hang on, hang on, hang
on,
hang on, guys. I've not set it up. Hang
on.
Guys, if if you keep doing it, I have to
wait for you guys to stop. Otherwise,
everyone who's done it already won't be
entered,
and I want you guys to be entered.
All right, to make sure you all enter,
we're going to do course first because
we do the FCT one afterward because I
don't want you guys not to enter. All
right. So, we're doing the free uh
introduction to trading course. So, just
type course once. We'll give that away
first and then we'll give Apex account
afterwards. So, just type course once
I give you guys a minute to do that. So,
all the way back to the gray box
already. You can see the rotation.
My least favorite market. Some of your
favorite markets. And look at our
reaction at the gray box. Right. So,
it's going to continue to go each side
until they get what they want.
That's 30 more seconds.
You only need to type it once, guys.
Just type it once.
A still that's awesome, man. First time
watching. Made 330 on a 10K funded clear
analysis. You're welcome, man.
You're absolutely welcome. All right,
I'm going to pull the winner.
Don't worry, E-Rock. If they've done
multiple entries, Nightbot instantly
deletes them. So if anyone has typed it
more than once, instantly gets deleted.
I don't even need to do it. That's why I
was saying just take your time. Take
your time. Which view indicator are you
using that shows regular sessions? I
keep my trading view on extended hours.
So uh it is actually customuilt by one
of my students, but all you need to do
is use an anchored view up to the 9:30.
That's all you have to do. All right,
the winner is there you go, Joe Bag.
He's been a regular the last at least
this week. I've seen that name a lot of
times.
Are you here, Joe?
Joe bag 009.
Waiting to hear you here, Joe. Are you
here, Joe?
I'll give you 30 more seconds.
You need to let me know you're here.
Otherwise, we're going to roll it.
Joe Bag 9. There you are.
Congratulations, mate. Congratulations.
Okay, you need to send me an email
info@flowzonerader.com.
I'm going to make a note of you now and
I'll sort you out with a free
introduction to trading course.
So, Joe bag
All right. So, you're the winner, Joe.
All you got to do is send me that email
and I will sort you out with a free
introduction to trading course.
Okay.
free Apex account. You know what to do.
Type code FCT. That is always the best
price on pretty much all the prop firms.
Use code FCT. It will get you the best
price.
Currently 80% off with that code on Apex
and $25 reset. So just type it once.
Again, you only need to type it once. If
you type it more than once, Nightbot
will pull you out. So just type it once.
We'll pull a winner.
I love some of the names I see in here.
So like so good. Heath Edger so Good.
Yeah, no free funding tick account. I've
stopped working with them
until I get a decent reply from them.
Okay, let's pull this winner. Three,
two, one.
Omalabi one,
are you here? Omalabi won.
Yeah, Omalabi won. Congratulations. Free
Apex account on its way to you, Omalabi.
Um, same thing if you just shoot me an
email
at flowzone trader
info@flowzontrader.com.
Send me a screenshot of you logged in to
your YouTube just so I know it's you,
okay? I want want to see you logged into
your YouTube and I will sort you out
with a free account.
All right, so let's set you guys up for
success this afternoon.
What would I be looking for? All right,
you can see your range here. All right,
you can see there's your value area.
There's the high. This is a Pshape,
right? With Pshape, this is a strong
move. All right, because we've left
previous days value and we've left
current week's value and we are
aggressively moving higher right now. In
fact, has current week's value moved up?
Yes. All right. So, current week's value
area high is now this blue line in line
this here in line with this. This is
your bid support. All right. You want to
stay thinking about a rotation between
here and here. All right. If you're a
rotational player, these are your
rotations
all the time. We're inside that. This
will get tighter as we develop more
volume. Like you're seeing here,
right? This is where shorts are stuck.
This is where buyers are stuck. They can
rotate this. If they find acceptance
above, they can go for this move. If
they find acceptance below, you're
watching gray box and blue box for
downside pressure. Um, I doubt we come
into yesterday's value, honestly.
I would say this is a bullish rotational
day right now. Right, we are in a
rotation but we are bullish in a Pshape
above current week in current value
above old value. Right? So my edge
technically is bullish but for sure
they're struggling to get much more of a
breakout to the upside. But that's what
I'd say. I wouldn't be bullish on the
breakouts. I'd be more bullish on dips
when available when it's clear and when
you see short stuck. All right? just
like we had here. I know I missed that
one. We called it, but that was the one
that frustrated me today. I waited all
this time for that move. Um, so that's
what I'll be looking at. Those
interested, if you're new here, go
through my YouTube. All right, there is
so much free education on my YouTube.
There's a ton of shelves on and free
courses on my YouTube on how to trade.
Right, bring this over. If you're new
here, if you're like, I like how this
guy's trades, but I don't understand
what I'm looking at on the screens.
Head over to YouTube. There's a ton
here. All right, all of this uh here,
trading strategy, and education. All
right, there's a ton of videos in here.
Go through all of that. If you like
volume and market profile, watch all
these ones for free first. All right, if
you like that and you want to learn
more,
there's some courses over here. So, this
is a 20hour course. This is what comes
with the flow zones and with the
discord. And if you want to do the
volume order flow course that just
launched, okay, you can use code launch
in capitals, it will get you this right
now and show you
launch
in capitals. It will get you $100 off
right now. That ends in January, right?
Boom. $299. Right? So now's the time to
do it if you're interested in learning
that stuff. There is no pressure to do
it. Like I said, go through everything
first on YouTube. Do not be spending
money if you don't like how I teach. Um,
that's about it. I have a new video
launching this weekend on my five prop
firms I would recommend for 2026.
And I'll also explain why and which one
might be best for you in those prop
firms.
Um, everyone else have a great Friday. I
will pop in in Discord later, but I
think we've absolutely murdered this
week together. We've had a big green
week. It's been really, really fun. And
um be safe. I want to leave you with
this. It's OPEX. It's rollover. It's end
of year. There is $7 trillion exposed in
this market into close today. I'm not
joking. 7 trillion options expiring into
close today. Please don't get caught the
wrong side of it. Right? If you've made
money this morning, be happy with it. If
you're going to sit here and trade this
like into the close, know that it's
likely to get wonky. It's likely to do
some weird aggressive moves because they
need to reposition on every single
contract, including the futures
contracts. So, don't get caught. All
right? It's just one day in one trade.
We come back next week or we come back
next year when the real volume will
return. would be in the new contract
with good volume, with good levels, and
we can forget about all the
repositioning, rebalancing. All right,
so nice and chill. Uh, just read the
last few things that you guys are saying
here.
Is it worth getting the course if I'm
only with Topstep? Yeah, it doesn't
matter who you're trading with. Like, it
doesn't matter even if you're trading
your own account, swing account. No
discord with the volume course. No,
guys, a lot of people have been asking
about that. I've thought about it, but I
just don't think it's fair because you
will need the basics or the the
fundamental knowledge of how the market
moves and why and how I draw out the
levels. And I want everyone in Discord
to be trading the same way. I'll talk to
the guys in Discord, but I I don't I
don't think that is right. I think it
will cause some issues. Sorry. Sorry.
For now, for now, I'm going to say that
it's not about money. It's just about
creating the right ethos in Discord. Um,
Discord is free if you do the 20our
course, right? If you do the long
course.
Um,
yeah, Discord lifetime access if you've
done the 20our course. The beginner to
advanced course. Exactly. Yeah, I'll be
on next week. So, Monday, Tuesday next
week, Monday, Tuesday the week after,
and then back to normal the week after
that. Is Top Set the best? No, Top Set's
the worst. I wouldn't touch it ever
personally. Uh, they don't treat people
well, and their system is poor.
How would you use indicators on top
step? You well, you'd have to use emas
and volume profile and vap.
Yes, you buy uh yeah, Eddie, if you buy
both courses, if you just go on the
website, buy one uh go to buy one
course, it will give you a discount on
the second course. It will come up and
flash. You just buy it together, it give
you a discount.
Um,
sorry to read the last few things here.
Thanks a heap, Alex. I paid Discord and
listen to you instead of this is the
best channel. Awesome, man. Thanks for
joining. Really appreciate it.
Appreciate everyone new here.
Do my indicators work on trade of eight?
Um, they haven't been built for trade of
eight, but you could add them to trade
of eight.
Oh, right. Sorry. Sorry, Cesar.
Hey, Alex. I invited a couple people
today and while I can trade, I can't
teach someone to save my life as a mean
reversing trader. They said it was the
most educational thing they've ever seen
online. Oh, thank you, Dr. Wall Street.
That's very, very kind of you. Thank you
for inviting people in. Thanks for the
kind words. You're welcome, Christie.
I'll speak to you uh if not in Discord
on Monday.
I like that, Johnny. That's a good one.
Top set gives you lots of vacation time
since their system seems to be down
these two times a week. A stressful
vacation, I would say.
All right, everyone. Um, big love.
Thanks for joining. Really appreciate
all the uh new followers. Oh, one thing
I should say, maybe I didn't say it. Uh,
if you go on the community page on my
YouTube, I did a little post, right?
It's for a free funded next account. All
I want you to do is write underneath
what you're going to do to improve your
trading in 2026. I'm going to send all
those entries to funded next and they're
going to pick at least one person for a
free account. All right? And we will I
will send that to them by Tuesday and
hopefully they'll reply straight away.
All right? Big love everyone. Thank you
for joining. Trade safe. Use hard stops.
Don't be doing anything stupid into the
close. Peace and love.