Morning team.
Morning. Morning. Morning team.
Hope you're all doing good. I hope
you're all doing good.
Okay, I'm going to start today really,
really simple. I've had a really tough
24 hours, especially the last 12. I'm
going to ask for patience and kindness
from you guys in stream today. Please
keep the chat positive. I don't have the
patience for it today. All right? I'm
really struggling. So, please let's show
up in our best possible self here today.
And I will do my best to be here for at
least the next 60 minutes. And if I have
it in me to be longer than that, I will
do it. But I just ask you to guys to
sharpen the best way. All right, here we
go folks. Let's have a look at what
we've got. Weekly model for those who
have done the course. All right, we have
the high of week, the low of weak, the
inside bar building the liquidity, the
failed breakdown to the 5-day, and we
are traveling up towards the 20-day.
This will be your mean reversion from
outside the Ballinger band, inside the
Ballinger band to the 5day to the 20-day
to this shelf here. All right, same
shelf we talked about early week. Same
shelf in the newsletter. We can look
left and look at the yearly kind of
spikes. And we have some nodes up here
into 600 and into towards 700. Both of
those are big big gamma exposure levels
today which I will go through. All
right. Big gam gamma exposure levels
both intraday. 600 intraday and 700 for
the week.
Okay. So I am still considering whether
they do it today or later in the week. A
big old bull trap in here which is then
sold into. All right. But how we act in
here is what is going to determine that
we've already just swept the high of
yesterday by a tick or two. I don't
think it's enough excess. And we will go
through that now
in the hourlys. All right. This is what
we were looking for yesterday. We talked
about the controlled selling. The
controlled selling yesterday. Controlled
selling push. Controlled selling. And
they caught them on NFP into this old
pivot in just in front of this node
here. All right. They didn't quite get
there. This node here we were looking
for to buy the 100s. We talked about
this wash if it hasn't cleared all out
to the 100s holding and then probably a
rip to clear out these stops here if not
these stops here. Right. So, we've done
the first level. We're looking at this
above 500. There is a very good chance
that they will set a bull trap. Now, you
can see I've put this on today. It's the
first time I've done it, but I'm going
to pay attention to it. It lines up
pretty well. So if we look at that 600,
look at the edge of the previous week up
here from the week starting the 26th of
Jan, right? It's back to the old value
area low if we get there. So a squeeze
can happen if we base and hold here. All
right, so where we are now, if we build
liquidity here, they can look for this
squeeze to take out 515s up to 600.
That's your intraday gex level through
that 700. My feeling is that in here,
probably in front of 800 because we
haven't got really a level to get up
there that if they protect this, it is
likely to be a big bull trap. I would
like to see a squeeze out into here. I
don't know if I'll play the long. I
might well wait for the short and see if
they trap bulls anywhere above 500 into
six, maybe into seven, but right ideally
into six. If they track bulls buying
high for a complete collapse back down
to repric this NFP candle, I will be
watching 360s. I'll be watching previous
day value area high and I'll be watching
the previous day point of control down
here. All right, this is what I would
like to see. I don't know if we get it
today. They might save that or tomorrow.
I don't know. But I would like to see
bullsh and a collapse back down inside.
And if they stay heavy for the rest of
the week, then I'm going to be watching
this naked point of control down here.
All right, that is definitely doable.
That would be a fantastic trap if they
do it. If they don't do that, if they
decide, hey, do you know what? We've
sold tech enough. We're going to go full
bullish, then they'll base here and look
for this. And we'd have to wait for them
to rehold a similar level and go again
and stair step very much like this,
right? We'd be looking for the same
thing again. All right, so I will
consider that. It's not my preference,
but I will consider it. My preference is
to look for the fade on a big bull trap.
Lower time frame. Um, you can see we
have just taken out the previous day
high and previous week B area high. This
is the same level as yesterday. That
gray box where we trapped those balls
yesterday. We just cleared them out and
we're trading back inside right now. So,
we're going to watch I'd say
if they're going to dip and rip this
morning, we can watch this level into
here to see if they hold that to do
that. And then you're looking for five
and sixes. Remember five and sixes. If
they completely collapse it and 300s and
we see how they act at 300s, I will buy
the 300s. If we don't clear out and we
just drop down and we trap bears down
here, I'm happy to buy the 300s for this
rotation back to fours. Um, but we will
see. We will just have to see how we go.
I'm not convinced that that's what
they're going to do, but let's just go
step by step. Yes, we're going to go
through everything now.
Okay, same push on ES. Hasn't quite
cleared out previous day high. Very,
very close. Same kind of thing. Okay,
you'll see this controlled selling.
Controlled selling. There's your trap.
There's the dip and the rip. All right,
you will see this time and time again
when we don't run any stops. It is being
manufactured in controlled selling, run
the stops, run down. Controlled selling,
run the stops, right? when they don't
get run out that is very controlled.
It's uh done very purposefully let's
just call it that way. So ES same kind
of idea and then you're looking for
726es if it goes going I assume is that
alltime high or is that a high close
just have a little look on this not an
alltime high.
Okay.
So everything above this right now above
7,000 keeps getting sold. uh edge of
here 716. So be watching 716 and then
yeah 728s and then 743s
spiders.
Same story as your NFP.
All right, closed the gap taken out the
highs. You can see this level up here
that I've been watching. That is your
high. That is your pivot high on the
spiders that they're trying to pin
through. pull that down. It's a little
bit out.
Here we go. There's your pin high, your
alltime high. That's what they're trying
to get through right now. So 97.84
or somewhere around that. All right.
They're trying to come and clear out
this liquidity. Same kind of story as
the 7,000s. Everything above there keeps
failing. It's getting dangerous though,
I will tell you. They've had a lot of
attempts I would say above here. They
need to hold above here to do that move.
And I'll be looking be very careful
about a clear out once they do it. But
we'll see. again broader market rotation
into broader market uh QQQ you'll see
the relative weakness versus spy on the
daily right way off way off these levels
up here that we're watching and we have
build this gap technically so really
we're watching to see if we find
acceptance through the 16s right now
yeah we have to see if we can find
acceptance through 16s and 17s for that
gap and base over it same kind of story
as we've just gone through on ENQ,
right? I'm thinking about the trap play.
That's what I'm really thinking about
today. I want to see maybe I get it
wrong and I don't get a play for the
day. That's also okay. Okay, Dixie
starting to find a bid. You can see
there you go off Dixie
bid, but already fading back inside.
Uh so did gold sell? Gold did sell and
then rebid off close. Okay, VIX still
trading downside off that. Okay, so big
buy side pressure coming in. Zoom VIX
out. Undercutting this here. I'll be
watching this block into here.
I'll pivot here now. I'll be watching
Vicks into there to see if it finds a
bid into there or not. So, if we do the
trap, right, if we do the trap and VIX
fades down into this and finds a bid,
that's going to help my thesis. So, if
I'm looking for the trap long on uh trap
to reshort ENQ, if we come into this and
find a bid on VIX and start doing this
and that times out with the ENQ in the
market, fantastic.
All right, Apple.
How's it called? A bid. Still in a range
here. Three days range. All right.
Inside it weekly range. Nothing to do
with that thing right now. Dead.
Amazon starting to try and find a bid.
All right. Uh same kind of story. Big
wash. Probably retraced 50% of that
wash. All right. If you did that, that's
50% basing out in a box. Nothing to
really do with it. All right. Nothing to
really do with it. Goo.
No undercut there. Wash held these lows.
Hasn't come down into it. Bit of a
basketball here and it's not breaking
lower. So maybe Goo can look for relief
up here sooner rather than later. But
again, not something I'd want to trade.
Nothing there. Looking great. Uh Meta is
a bit more interesting. That's perked up
a little bit. So you can see the failure
to break down and make a new low.
There's the rip up. Okay. And coming
back into these boxes here where they're
rebidding at. So, this thing wants to
try and get going. So, we look good. I'm
still long meta. I want to see a rebre
out of 83s and see if we can get back up
here. It would be great to get all the
way back up there.
Uh D
Microsoft.
That looks that looks good. That's a
better look. All right. Better look.
Failure to break out of the lows. Come
down. Retested. caught a bid, break out,
retest, caught a bid, come back down to
the same level. This is the pin, right?
They got to hold sort of tens. They hold
tens, they've got a shot. Microsoft
looking a bit better there. Uh let's
have a look at Nvidia. That thing much
better now than last week. All right, so
we can talk again about the same thing
even on the higher time frame.
Controlled selling down pivot fails to
make a new low. There's your long
trigger. Look at the EMA supporting it.
And we're upside now into like sort of
an inverse head and shoulder kind of
thing. And this thing can really hurt
some people soon. There will be stops
here. We can set price alerts up there
right now. Is that the high
of this? It is. Okay. So, we'll be
watching for breaks and fail breaks
above
9450s.
Stick that in there so I know it's
there.
Which will mark out well with the cues
if they do the fail break. If they're
just going to break out upside, I'll
have to find a way of joining. We'll
see. Tesla, same kind of stories.
Nvidia. All right. Same kind of story.
You can see this coming right back to
the upside. You'd be watching Tesla for
a break and hold over 30 and then you'd
be looking to take partial out into 40,
44, and then 50 if it can get going.
might be due a little bit of a washdown.
You know, it wouldn't be surprised if
they want to do one of these before they
get going. Wouldn't be surprised at all.
Equally weighted.
Wakey wakey. There we go. That's your
mag for the day. So, gapping up. Equally
weighted. Is in a gap up. So, we do have
strength so far. Uh Hood got sold off in
earnings like we talked about. It's why
we took some profits up here. I will be
looking to see if they hold this dip
though. All right. They did have a miss,
but actually the amount of cash on hand
is pretty good. We just see if they want
to rebid this up over the next few days.
If this is a giant trap, but we will
see. We've paid oursel either way. Uh
Netflix as well. Big push yesterday
coming back into range. Needs to hold
this then I feel positive about it. And
that's the story of the tape guys.
That's what we're looking at. So main
thing I'll be looking at today ideally
is a big old bull trap like I've talked
about would be my preference.
If not, if they're going to dip before
taking out all the highs, I will
consider joining long. It is not ideal.
It is not ideal. Oracle. Yeah, Oracle
still looks good. I'm still long.
Oracle.
Yeah, Spy and ES both taking out those
highs. ES now trading 707s.
707s, I should say. Um,
yeah, Oracle looks good. Nice push up.
Just needs to hold. We want it to base
out at sort of 60. Just needs to base
out at 60. We don't want it to give back
that big squeeze move all the way back
to 50.
Uh, where's my QQQ?
Sorry, guys. Just get my charts ready.
All right, let's see how we go then,
folks. Good luck, everyone. Um, I will
be patiently waiting. So ideally, we
come and clear out some of these levels
and I get a short up here somewhere.
Otherwise, if they don't take it and
they just drop down, I'll think about a
rebid down here into 300s, maybe here,
but I don't really like that bid there.
I would rather ignore previous day value
high today. But we will see.
We are trading right at the high of uh
the current week.
All right, here we go, folks. Let's get
some volume on it nice and early before
Alex forgets. Mentally fatigued right
now.
All right, previous day value area high
coming up here. There's the wash through
it. And we next be watching 63s if
they're going to come all the way down
to previous day point control. Why is
that not matching up
360?
That's way off, isn't it? Wow.
Measure this out real quick.
We can do big discrepancy again.
Well, maybe it's Ninja Trader off.
Right, there's the dip and rip. So,
let's see if they can clear out some of
these highs
into this gray box. Remember, there are
stops at that gray box, the top side of
that gray box. The first lot stop lot of
stops are into sort of 90 91 and the
next lot at the top of the gray box.
That's what I'd like to see cleared out.
I'd love it if they clear all this out
even if they want to shove all the way
to 600. Previous week open as well by
the way is 530s
530s.
All of the mag green
spy shoving up here as well. Not too far
away from that 98 kind of level we were
looking at
and watching the 20-day 50-day on QQQ as
well. 20-day currently at 1840 50-day uh
1930 1940.
All right. Come on market. So, we're not
too far from the 20-day on ENQ as well.
Somewhere around 550, 560. Let me just
check that on that shell. 550 20-day.
Okay. Sellers keep getting caught at
these lows. So, so far into 35 was very
early and it's very jumpy and it's NFB.
Back to these 30s where these sellers
keep getting caught.
Yet again, they got caught there.
They're looking for a resqueeze here.
I'm not long in any of this. I'm just
telling you what I'm seeing on the tape.
I'm not longing any of this. But you can
see right here, these sellers down here,
I'm at 40 and under, especially down 34
so far. Cannot get a follow through
downside. All right, so they keep piling
in there. They're not getting their way.
They're getting tested again now. Same
level. Do they get follow through here
is the question.
Maybe the first time they see follow
through today. to that New York open
and previous day value area high which
is also different on here to Ninja
Trader. It's not very useful. I got 410
on Ninja Trader as value high right into
here. So they dip that again. Have to
watch these 30s and 40s now. Right.
That's where the sellers came in. If we
reclaim 30s and 40s, this thing should
technically squeeze.
We will we will wait. I'm not buying up
here. There's just no way. I'd much
rather they come and clear out this
level and offer me to short.
What's the gray zone? 480 to 515. Uh it
is there's a node and a pivot. If you go
back to the 4th of Feb,
4th of Feb in here, if you go on an
hourly chart, look at the 4th of Feb,
you'll see it.
Okay, these sellers starting to win now.
So maybe previous day point control is
going to get tagged here if they get
follow through. That is going to be
really shite if they're just going to
clear out this high and leave all of
these. It's very dangerous to play
much rather they go higher first. It's
going to make the short much much better
if they can go higher first, but we need
to be aware of it.
11th
one when they talking 10. Okay.
Watching this down here. If they rebid
it into 300s,
man, if they just do that tiny clear
out, that is so lame.
Watching this level down here into 300s.
So, into current week, this red level is
current week
point of control. The developing weak
point of control is what they're bidding
on at the moment down here at sort of
70s and 60s. If we lose that, it's
possible we go all the way down to 300.
This short would be paying now. That's
just didn't go high enough for me to
want it. Do not like that we didn't
clear out that gray box above. Naughty,
naughty, naughty, naughty.
So, previous day value area low
possible. This is current uh weak point
of control. It's possible that they wash
down into here. But there is lots of
opportunity down here right now
to wash down here and then see if they
rebid it or not. This wasn't my
preferred play. I would have preferred
the short, but I will watch this into
here.
Sellers starting to be aggressive at 70s
and not getting their way.
Very aggressive at 70s again, not
getting their way.
Yeah, they're starting to get caught
here at 70s. You might see this try and
push up. Here we go. Watching the 40s
the 400, sorry. That's where point of
control on the day is. There's the
squeeze. I'm long now through this.
Okay, let's see if we can get to VPO.
Taking a piece out here.
Want to see this basin hold over 400 or
I'll cut cut on the rest. So, just a
squeeze trigger over 70 and through the
400 to the 420 test. All right, just to
test this, right? Sellers, like I kept
saying, kept getting stuck at 70s,
right? So, there was a squeeze back up.
They've resold point of control. They're
trying to get down to here now. So, I
took the long just a snap long. I know
it was really quick, guys. I can't help
it. It's what happens when you read the
tape. Some of you would be upset, but I
can only play how the tape moves when
I'm looking for stuff like that. It's
not like a pre-plan. is literally
reading the tape
back into these 60s. They're trying to
find acceptance lower now. So, sellers
win here, we can wash down towards these
300 levels.
Just a quick scalp long there for like
40 points is all I got there, folks.
Just trading one account at a time here.
So, same level 70s here where they keep
piling in.
We can see they're piling in again. Look
at this. They've just piled in again at
60s. All these sellers are going to get
caught. This is where we just pushed up
to 400 and then 420. So, we are whippy
here. Sellers are currently caught at 70
and under. Definitely at 60 and under.
There is a buyer caught at 400 and they
resold it at 410 and 420. So, like we
are just ranging in quite a violent
amount of range here while they start to
get themselves stuck. It's okay to just
let this do what it wants, folks. The
better level if we're going to bid,
right? If they're going to trap shorts
to go long, the better bid will be down
here somewhere. All right, point of
control gets put previous day value low.
That would be a better bid. The better
short in my mind
will be over here, right? Will be in
here somewhere. is the better short in
my mind.
That's what I was waiting for and hoping
for this morning.
Okay, let's see. Let's see see if they
can get down into these 300s.
Give you a readout on the mag. Haven't
done that yet. Tesla 1.88% up. Nvidia 1
and a half% up. Microsoft 0.76% down.
Meta third of up. Google 0.06% up. Uh
Amazon quarter% down and Apple 0.62% up.
See, see, can we get down into here?
It's too late for me to short now. Maybe
I could have taken that, but I'm just
going to wait to see if we can get into
here and how we operate when we get down
there.
They're
looking for that breakdown. There is
liquidity lower into 25s and then 300.
So shorts sellers are trying to sell
this down to get that move. Got 24hour
VWAP there. We can time it with ES as
well into Globe X and VWOP which is
around 86
and SPY into 95 as well.
So, we'll see. Do they come into those
levels and find a bid?
What's the New York View indicator? Uh,
it's made by someone in my Discord. I
don't think it's for free. It's uh it's
a gift by the legends in Discord. It's
one of the good things about being in
the Discord. You get lots of free
indicators that everyone works on. Okay,
they're trying to get this squeeze back
up to point of control, which is 70s
right now. Here's the tap through 70s.
I'm not going to retake this. I've
already had one attempt of this. If they
lift this, then you're looking at 400s
again. I still want to wait now to see
if we can come down to 300s.
Trying to be patient.
But if we look at the hourly, right,
remember this is what I call God chart.
We go back to the hourly. You can see
the developing profile. We're coming
right into the middle of this current
week's D-shaped developing profile.
right into fair value for the week. If
they lose this, all right, then maybe
there is a bid off here from three from
300 back to 350. And if they squeeze
back to fours, maybe they just bid off
here in into uh
in this uh point of control level 350s.
We'll see.
Much rather they come down into this
right now. Much much rather they come
down lower.
Am I long? No, nothing. I'm nothing
right now. I'm waiting to see if we come
to three. What I'm waiting for to make
this clear, I need need to make this
clear. When we come into this zone here,
I'm waiting to see if sellers get
trapped. All right. If sellers get
trapped, I will consider a long back up.
If they don't get trapped, they might
well want to go to gap fill for 220. So,
I'm not just going to bid on this. I
need to see someone stuck. Currently,
they are bidding off the developing weak
point of control. They keep bidding off
it.
O. So, we're going to go and test those
trap players at 400 again.
Kind of ugly there on the book up at
400. We've got a delta both sides. We've
got 127 lot trapped at 400 as a seller.
Just tap back into him again.
Messy, messy, messy.
When you look at ENQ on Trading View,
your price numbers don't match. So, you
probably got delayed data then because
these are the correct numbers,
right? They're testing these 400s again.
Man, if that's the dip and they don't
come down here, it's going to be very
hard to trade. It means we haven't run
the top side and we haven't come down to
the bottom side where we need to go. I
really need this to come lower. Okay,
they're selling 400. So, that seller up
there still present.
still present in the 400s.
Keep talking about this guy right here.
All right, he's still present. He's
still absorbing the tape right now.
They are going to want to want they are
going to want sort of 300s. And if they
snap that, it's rule out the twos.
Wanted to be short today above all this.
The weekly model is starting to play
out. It's one thing, but we are still
just inside the previous days range.
and come back for those fours again.
ES can't get through its new view yet
either. So, just rotating here a little
bit. Building out this big node down
here. It's a big node down here. You can
see a spike here. This is where the sort
of control is right now. It's where they
keep reselling into this this node here.
This spike. I'm going to remove this
gray box because we've been here a lot.
And I'm going to remove this red box
because we'd also been here a lot. And
I'm going to remove this node from
yesterday as well. Clean this chart up a
little bit.
surprised. I'm somewhat surprised that
this is their morning play. They are
holding their hourly pivot. They are
holding this hourly pivot here right
now.
right here.
They are trying to absorb high on here
to complete this move at the moment. I
am somewhat surprised they haven't come
deeper before looking at it.
All right, back to these fours again.
Shall we look belong? I mean, it's up to
you. I just you got to understand zoom
out where you're looking for long. Like
I if I'm going to get long, I want it
down here. I really don't really want to
get long here unless we push and base
and hold. I'd much rather look at longs
down here if they trap.
It's just how they're moving it today.
They're not coming into key levels.
I'd rather be patient and trade in an
area I don't want to trade in. Here
comes the squeeze back towards that New
York open.
Yes, still not through New York VW. This
squeeze can be sold into. Honestly,
it's very iffy here, folks, because we
haven't reached. You have to understand
what I'm saying. We haven't reached this
and we haven't reached this. All right?
So, your positioning right now is in the
middle of this. These are the edges I
want to play here and above to sell here
and below to buy. Only if they trap,
right? Only if they trap. I don't want
to enter here. My location is so poor. I
really don't want to enter there.
We need another 40 plus points to get a
long entry.
I wouldn't trust trading because you
think news is negative, right? Most
stuff is priced in before it happens.
All right. Yes. Back to New York open.
We are back to previous weak value area
high here.
This node balls will need to hold this
node now. If they don't, we're going to
trade down to the 90s. And if they lose
90s, we're going to trade all the way
back down again. Here we go. It's just
washy, guys. This is why I'm trying not
to enter in here. It's far too dangerous
in my mind. Far far far too dangerous.
Here comes the wash back down.
I still think this is the target. But
here's point control for the day now.
This is fair value. This is aggressive
here, folks. Here you go. They want
those 300s. What I'm saying? They've got
to come to 300s first. This is
aggressive. All the way back down. Do
they pop and sell this then? So 400 is
going to be key. If they lose 400s, you
might look for a follow through
downside. Now, if they lose 400s, if
they can't reclaim 400s, they might try
and resell it all the way back down. If
they reclaim 400s, then they're going to
go and fill these imbalances up to 26s.
It's washy, guys. I cannot say enough.
It's very washy.
Not getting through the fours.
They keep protecting the fours here.
There is a chance for this move here
that I just talked about. They are
selling fours. There is a chance
to come down here right now if they sell
paws.
Back to fours. They go.
Watch these fours. They're imbalances
above fours all the way up to 26. But if
they keep selling falls, there's they
are going to look for that breakdown.
Fair like I'm not going to enter a trade
here. This is a no trade zone. But I
would say I would be watching this,
right? Because we have this guy that
keeps selling up here into fours. All
right. And an imbalance here.
Here's the push to four. So what they do
now is absolutely key.
If they reclaim it, then there's a
squeeze up to 25s.
Trader bait down again. Are you joking?
Oh man, you put me off trading. Really?
Is that Is that actually true?
I will not enter if that's actually
true. Not on an NFP day.
Okay. Rejecting 410s. Previous day value
high. They don't bid fours. They're
going to look for the wash here. If they
can't hold the fours,
it is messy, messy, messy. ES cannot get
through that New York open.
Okay, trade of eight down. Guys, be very
care. I wouldn't advise trading if if
trade of eight is down. Do not do not do
not trade. Do not trade if trade of
eight's down. You are asking for it.
I didn't know that cuz I haven't entered
since that first trade. But uh yeah,
just be careful.
Yeah, some of you saying it's bad, some
of you saying it's fine. They're
probably not a global outage yet.
Order delayed on execution. A lot of you
saying
CVD looks weird. Um, it's kind of
matching up on the 5m minute with what
we've had so far. All right, they're
going to try and lift for 25s now. They
don't know what to do here. This is the
problem. Everyone who's smart wants to
trade in extreme and now they're just
building out liquidity. I think we need
to come down here.
Sellers trying to pile through here.
Might get follow through here folks
watching this.
So they keep testing that previous day
point of control for me. I have this on
Ninja Trader. I have a previous day
point of control is 62s. I don't know if
anyone else has the same. I'm going to
double check that now. Yeah, it's right.
You might see follow here through here,
folks. I think they're going to go for
those 300s. They've trapped enough times
up there now. So 70s is where the
sellers keep getting stuck. So they need
to follow through under 70s.
Rotation. Rotation rotation here is
stuck between New York view up and
24-hour view up. So back to PC which is
88s here and 92s and if they fail that
they will look for follow through
P. Do they fail this? They're going to
squeeze right the way back upside.
Great. 400s again. Can you please make
your mind up and get out of here for us?
Big seller coming in here
trying to force lower. If he doesn't do
it, he's going to get caught. He's
coming high.
So, we haven't completed a rotation
either side today. That's the problem.
We haven't hit gray box or gray box. We
are in no man's land right now.
What are you not doing? Honestly,
just go to 300 or or rip it. Do
something.
Literally no man's land.
Okay, back to the 70s where the sellers
keep getting stuck.
Are you going to sell through now or you
going to rip it back up again? Oh,
you're going to pop it back up again.
Right into the edge of this node. We're
just trapped between 92s and 63s right
now. We can't find acceptance outside of
any of it. ES is stuck between 24-hour
VWOP and New York VWOP.
We are just not moving anywhere.
How about that? after an NFP rip, we
just do nothing.
I think we want to go 300s, but uh we
got to get under these sort of 70s
aggressively
in 60s.
Tra more shorts there again. Someone's
absorbing here under 60s. They need to
snap hard and then they'll get a run to
25s. There they go. They need to snap
here hard and you'll get a run to 25s
and maybe you'll get those 300s.
There you go. There's 50s again.
Someone's still stepping in the tape
there trying to absorb.
There's literally nothing you can do
with this.
Protecting edge of value.
The problem is this location right here.
Like I keep talking about
this location. There's your weekly
profile. We are just trapped in here.
All right. They've either got to get
above here and try and complete this or
below here and try and complete this. We
just don't want to trade in here. This
is the wash zone from the last few
sessions.
It is the wash zone from the last few
sessions. I'll move that up here,
haven't I? There we go. That's better.
Chop city. Yeah, absolutely. Absolutely.
It's amazing the amount of volume that
he can build out.
Okay, look at ES as well doing the same
dance. So, we can see New York VW
24-hour VW up. ES the same stuck between
these two and it's stuck in this. I
think they want to come down into this
honestly, but they keep saving it here.
You cannot deny that. If too many people
get stuck one side, it will be so nasty
to move back the other way.
There's no edge here right now.
So here they go. Trying to lift back up
to fours.
So 350 to fours is your range right now.
50 points range.
There's nothing outside of that yet.
Time for coffee. I am actually thinking
about that already.
Why did I place the gray box in the
300s? Because there is a node down
there. There is volume down there that I
am watching
on the developing week. There is a node
down into that. I'm actually playing the
underside of that node. It actually
starts at 22s, right? It starts at 322s.
There is a node that starts on the
developing week profile. How many
attempts are these guys going to have to
break lower? Honestly,
70s again.
Come on. Just go and do it for God's
sake. There they go. Jesus Christ.
Go and get to 20s and 30s and then 300s.
Come on.
[\h__\h] are you lot playing at? It's so
pathetic.
There they go.
Okay. Inter 50s. Can they find
acceptance outside of this node now and
come down into here? I'm wait I'm trying
to wait for price to get down into here.
It's arguable that you might want to
take a short here. I'm not looking for
it. I want to see how we react down
here. I'm trying to wait for price to
get here or here. That's where my edge
is as a trader. All right. It's to trade
at the key levels, not in between them.
I think we're going to get to here.
Okay, VW up there. Nice. Come on. Come
lower. Please come lower. Please come
lower.
Please come lower. Let's be up. They
keep protecting V up here.
There they come. Okay, great. Finally.
All right, let's see what we do down
here into this level. Do they bid or do
they just let go of the whole thing? Do
they bid this or do they let go of the
whole thing? Currently bidding off that
level, aren't they? Look at this rip
back up. So far, so watching this now
very, very carefully. We knew it was a
key level. We're watching now to see if
we trap bears down here, which we have
so far in this count's very quick. We
have trapped at tens. So if they defend
10, we have bears trapped down there.
But we want to see a bit of structure
develop.
Want to see a bit of structure develop.
Waiting to see if they trap these bears
at 10 or not. Do we put in a higher low
here so I can uh get involved with some
decent risk? More bears come in here at
30. I want to see it flush to tens and
get absorbed. If we break down under
that, then obviously there's no play.
They're protecting 10 so far. Still
watching these tens. Can we come and
revisit them? And can I see a buyer
stepping on the bid here? They are
bidding below it though, which is a bit
iffy. And there's a selling out 35s. I'm
interested, but I don't like what I see
yet.
So, this is the 10's revisit. You can
see 310's being revisited because that's
where the sellers got stuck.
They need to buy this now and rip it
higher. If they don't do that, we will
break lower and we will keep washing.
Breaking lower. Okay. So, no bull no
bullish play here yet for me. Let this
break lower.
It's possible they do gap fill here if
they really let go.
300s.
Am I really just going to get that one
play for the day?
Big Bull stepping in down here. That's
not a good sign. This will break lower.
Big Bull just stepped in at 300. Huge
lot. He's going to get caught. You
idiot. You idiot.
H
so hard to position that short. I know.
I I agree with you. I wanted to position
for that short up here. All right. All I
wanted was any move up here to then fade
for this move. That was my plan today. I
know sometimes market doesn't give you
what you want. We know this is a
potential level they can hold. If they
fail this level, previous day value low,
previous day close, previous day low,
all all on check. But this is a big
level even for the options market,
right? It's a big big level. We haven't
retested up here yet. So they might lift
and retest 50s and we can see if they
stay heavy. So if they lift Oh, don't do
that. If we lift and test 50s and stay
heavy, there will be a reshort
opportunity into here and then maybe
down if they get follow through. If they
lift and reclaim, we go back and chop
here before they make decision of what
next.
That buyer is currently comfortable at
300. I'm somewhat surprised. We might
lift here to 50s.
I don't know if I want to do that.
I don't think I want to bid that.
I don't like this guy here, guys. This
guy here with big size at 300. He's
currently comfortable though. We've got
guy trapped at 317. I don't like these
guys piling in long at the lows. That's
not what I want to see. Not aggressive
buyers at the lows. It's the opposite of
what I would want to see.
We're at a level of interest. It's just
I'm not seeing what I like yet. Seeing
the opposite of what I would like.
We might still break lower here. Revisit
up here would be really good. A revisit
of this shelf here would be good for us
to make a decision
up here.
Any revisit here and see how we act
would be good to potentially sell. They
are bidding off this now. So that level
is holding up well. So we have to see do
we resell up into here either 50s or
64s. Do they resell it or are they just
going to bid all the way back up to the
high of day now? So here we go. Is the
drive in 250s?
Is that it?
And reselling it.
Buyer got a little bit caught there at
37. I'm short on this for a small piece.
Didn't get to where I wanted. Let's see.
Watching 25s here if there's a seller
stepping back in or not. Want to see us
flush under 20s because that's where the
buyers came. Here we come. Got to get
back on the 20s. Here we go. Here we go.
Peeling some off here. You can hear me
on my hot keys as we come into 20s. They
can hold this here and re-rip. Don't
want them to rerip. Want to let go of
20s and revisit 300. And then I want to
use that buyer down there as pain to go
lower. Get under that 300.
Get under that 300 now.
Thank you very [\h__\h] much. That'll do.
Here we go, baby. Runners on deck. And
let's see how low can we go. Right now,
we're flipping this. So, failed to
reclaim. Like I said, there were buyers
piling in down here. It's why I didn't
want to bid it. I didn't like seeing the
buyers be aggressive here. We came back
up. We sold this. I sold this. Covered
some 20. Covered some 300. And now
holding to see how low can we go. So,
value area low from yesterday coming up.
Then we're looking for gap fills. Here
we [\h__\h] go, baby.
Don't tell me. I don't tell you what I'm
looking at. I don't want to hear it
today.
Okay, here we go, baby. If we get lucky,
we get down here. You must pay yourself
a bit into valued area low from
yesterday. If we get acceptance
undervalued area low than from
yesterday, it means all the buyers will
become trapped and we can come down into
some of these levels. But uh we are
paying ourselves no matter what. I do
not want to see reclaims of 300 here. I
will cut on a reclaim of 300. So we're
tapping 300. It's where a buyer is
currently caught. Right? We do not want
him to be let out. If he gets let out,
we will push to to 20 probably very very
quickly. So we do not want 300 to be
reclaimed.
So far so good.
They've been in at 40s now, which is
good. They're adding liquidity lower
than us at 40s. Come on, come down. Come
down. Come down. Come down. Come down.
Come down. Wash them. Wash them. We need
to snap this here in the 80s where we
keep building up a little node here in
80s. We want to wash this and come back
down here.
No. 300 reclaim. stops at 300 and I'm
going to put it at 303.
Oh, I'm out. What can you do if you do
me to the tick again?
Get the [\h__\h] out of here. You do me to
the tick. No.
Oh my god.
Oh, I could have risked sevens. I guess
I could have risked sevens.
Oh, you prickies. You [\h__\h] prickies.
Oh my god. I'm sorry. I'm so sorry. I'm
so sorry,
[\h__\h]
I was trying to risk the imbalance.
Oh my god. Yeah, it's going to go good.
Good. You guys should hold. Don't Don't
do what I just did. [\h__\h] me. You guys
look good. So, high time frame algo
here. Uh, this is developing profile.
This is discount on the week. All right.
So on the current week that's
developing. This this area here is
discount. Everything under that deep
discount. This is your gap fill. This is
previous days low. So these are like
sort of runner scenarios here.
I want this back above 303s just so I
don't feel so [\h__\h]
Oh my god. They are watching the stream
guys. They are watching the stream.
I was trapped at where are you saying at
34? No, 30 300 is currently the level
and then above that I would say 16 and
20. Uh 34. No, not really. Nothing up
there. 300 and then 317 and 319 or 320
is what I'd be watching. Like this guy
here is the big guy that's stuck.
Remember when down here I said they're
piling in. And I piled in. Look who got
long up the up there. Some idiot that we
shorted into once we started leaving
30s. There's the short back down. We
pushed through this by a couple of ticks
and take Alex out. And there's a chance
to expand lower now. Really good.
Looks really good.
Oh well, I would have way preferred the
higher day short. But you know what we
did well there, folks? We ignored the
chop. All right, so thesis didn't come
in. We wanted the short today above
here. All right, and we considered a
long here if we didn't get that short,
but we did not set up the long here.
What we set up is liquidity being built
here. Everyone who bought this today
looking for that move got trapped. We
broke down. We don't let them out. Then
we play trend for continuation. All
right. So,
it requires patience, guys. Like it's
all this all the market requires is
patience and understanding. Let it do
this [\h__\h] Let it leave the area and
then let it fail to reclaim for a
continuation.
Go short now. No, I wouldn't be going
short now. The short was here, wasn't
it? We I drew it out for you. Lit. Quite
literally drew it out for you.
That's it. Momentum, patience, momentum,
and location. TP for shorts. Well,
you're you definitely in and around
here. So, previous day value area low is
one. I would say current week low 50s is
one. I would say 218s for previous day
close is one. I'd say previous day low
at 200s is one. um underneath that
150 for that overnight swing point. You
know what? We get pretty thin as we
start getting under these 250s, guys.
I'll be honest with you,
underneath these 250s for this current
week, we actually get pretty thin. Look
at this Pshape.
This is the current developing week
since Sunday open. If we get under this,
we're pretty thin. I would be watching
this move here to 100 110s. I think this
is possible here guys. I think that's
possible right now. If you get under
250s you might get a runner to 110s
which means what? You would have got a
huge winner up
watching 250s.
So, what's that? That's 80 points. And
if you lose this, I'd watch 110s.
Honestly, I think you can get down into
somewhere down here.
[\h__\h] hell, mate.
I have to be really calm because like I
said at the beginning of stream,
I uh am struggling a little bit today,
folks. Um, so I have to be very very
careful about taking something else.
rule above 80% played out beautifully
today. Price opens above previous value
air high drops through and holds 80%
chance we get value air low. Yep,
exactly quite right.
Shorts from 50 uh 353 runners left. Nice
work. Trading with you after learning
your course becoming fun and profitable.
Thank you very much. Awesome, Sam.
Thanks again, Alex, for teaching us how
to be patient and waiting for the market
to react. You're welcome, Doc.
Thanks, guys. You didn't get back in. I
didn't get back in, Raph. I didn't. I
didn't. Like I said, I'm I have to be
very careful with my emotions today. I'm
uh
uh I don't want to like cause drama on
chat. I'm I'm not having the best mental
health since January. So, I have to be
careful. This this is uh I don't want to
do something stupid, right? When I
position well, if I know I'm not really
sharp right now, I can't be doing
something stupid like entering late,
which there's more of a chance I do if I
don't feel like really on the money.
Nice info risk.
No, it's all good, guys. I'm not going
to end the stream now. I'll stay with
you for a bit. All right, gap now
filled. Same on ES. That yellow line is
your cash gap. Same on ES. ES coming to
cash gap. So this is a big TP. Same on
SPY. Same on QQQ. So you're coming into
cash gap. The yellow line on your chart
is cash gap. If we get under there,
that's under the previous day close. So
cash gap now filled. You're now looking
at previous day low. And I would hold
runners for 110. I would take a big
chunk out here for the cash gap fill.
And I'd be looking for 110 now.
get my everyday bro do dose. Yeah,
that's what I'm about to go and do. Look
at the VIX, guys. Do does anyone
remember what we said? If the VIX holds
a bid there, where we think we might get
short? Remember at the start of the
stream? Let's see if you guys remember
right above the blue level. And we said
if it comes into here and holds and
rips, that will give good confluence for
the short. Well, there's the hold. It
didn't even get there. They were so
aggressive, which it would have been
better if if we'd got to here, right?
Then the VIX would have got to the blue
box and we could have got short really
really high on the day. It's just is
what it is. It's not wasn't A+, but it's
good. All right, you look good. Here's
previous day low and you're now holding
for 110s.
Oh my god. Oh my god. What a what a
trade. Just a casual 200 pointer for you
guys on stream again. All
right. So, they're bidding 170 and 155s.
You get under the 155s, you should get
110. They're getting aggressive here.
Move your stop down with this because
they're getting very, very aggressive.
You do not want like that fast snapback
and to lose 50 60 points on a fast one,
right? I think you should get 110s
towards 110. So, here you go, folks.
[\h__\h] me.
What's at the 110s? uh the previous
week. If you go to the previous week um
volume profile, you will see a shelf
develop into that area. All right. If we
look at previous week, remember I just
said if we lose current week, remember
this is current week. We're very thin
under here. We can repric to here,
right? So we have overnight low there as
well. So 140 to 110's big level. But
this level here is what I'm looking at
whether they find a bid on this shelf
from the previous week. So if we think
about this pivot d pivot hold d we're
coming back for this level here right
we're coming back to back test it they
lose it look we do have a naked point of
control down here this is what I was
looking for this week uh anyone who's
joined me this week will well know I
have talked numerous numerous times
about I think we will set a bull trap
between here and here and I will look to
trade that down to the old naked point
of control. That is what I really wanted
to do Wednesday, Thursday, Friday. We
talked about it yesterday. We've talked
about it in Discord extensively. Um,
this is not uh
yeah, this isn't like a a a what would
you call it like after the fact moment.
This is what I have been looking for.
You even Foster Scott said yes. They
setting up the weekly model. Well,
there's anyone who's done the course
will know the weekly model. what I'm
looking for backside of the week.
Try and find it for you when I put it in
Discord.
Here we go.
Even in Discord, I stuck it in here. So,
on the 9th, what was that a couple days
ago? What I'm looking for up to anywhere
above 500 towards 700 for a retest back
down lower to that old naked point
control. It's the same move, guys. Same
move. Right, you're almost there. Look
at that. Into the 140s. You are almost
there.
All right. So, be very very careful.
Like I said, you don't want this to rip
your face all the way back up. Now, you
do not want this to rip your face all
the way back up. Now, they're going to
try and sell 190s at the moment. There's
a seller up there. 300 lot. He might
spoof and lift. So, you got very close
to this gray box. I was looking for
this. Well, this gray box is the bid,
right? The 140 to the 110s. They came
what a tick tick or two shy of it. There
or thereabouts. You're there or
thereabouts.
You're becoming my new favorite morning
guy to watch. Your analysis has been
great. Thanks, Josh. Let's read all
this. You're brilliant. Thank you, guys.
Thanks for the positive talk. Out for
the day. You're the best live trader
ever. Nice. Hopefully, you got some good
wins, Alex. Some of my indicators need
to be updated. Do they really? Let me
know which ones, Max. That's news to me.
Nice trader. I was looking for someone
to validate my short and I found you.
That makes me laugh.
I think it's a short. Let me hop on
YouTube and see if anyone else does.
What happens if it was a long and you
thought it was a short and you went on I
don't know
you went on top [\h__\h] and they told you
full full port longs here.
Can I please explain the cash gap? Uh
yeah, it's the close of 4:00. So it's
not the close that you would have in the
futures market at 5:00. It's the close
of 4:00. Why 4:00? 4:00 is when cash
finishes trading. All right. So we think
about 9:30 to 4:00. That is your New
York hours. So I care about those New
York hours because that is when cash
trades. Same reason why I do my profile
based on 9:30 to 4:00. For me,
everything is based on cash where volume
is.
Just bought back my positive day from a
down day. Nice.
My initial plan was to buy 300 before I
joined the live. Thanks, man. You saved
my ass. No worries. Yeah, I mean I was I
was considering it, but like I said, the
tape was really bad here. This is what
this is an important lesson for you guys
is I was considering the buy here. I
said I'll be interested in a buy here if
I see what I like in here. I didn't see
what I liked. I saw the opposite of what
I like. I saw big buyers trying to buy
it. You might think, well, why isn't
that what you like? What I want to see
is big sellers being absorbed by big
buyers. I want big aggressive sellers,
big passive buyers to try and do this
move. I do not want big market buyers
there. That is not a good sign. That is
a sign that we might well do this. All
right, 110s are on deck here, folks.
140 to 110s. So, I would pay yourself
here. You're developing a bit of a range
here now.
You're so goated. Keep streaming. You're
paying my bills. That's nice. Good to
know. How would I classify the setup
based on what riskreward or what do you
mean with VP? How would you classify a
setup based on I'm not sure what you're
asking there. Um maybe just maybe I'm
just not understanding. I'm sorry. Feel
feel free to rewrite it for me.
I can't say how much I've learned from
you. My mental health is [\h__\h] to you
help me control. That's great, Joey. Oh,
thank you. Who just give that? Taylor,
enjoy the coffee. We appreciate that's
so kind, Taylor. Thank you very much for
that super chat.
Yeah, don't revenge trade. One of you
just said you revenge traded. Don't be
revenge trading, guys. No, no, no. None
of that. None of that. None of that. Do
I live stream every day? Yes, I do.
Monday to Friday, 9:15. It's really
important you guys join me at 9:15.
Here's the tens. We're going to get
these tens hopefully. Do not want a fail
breakdown here. There's a big seller
stepping in these lows. Uh they are
bidding at 25. We have an old node at
20. We should get tens. But just like
the gray box is a big cover point for
me. So I'd be paying yourself a lot into
here. If you get lucky, you could look
for this. But I would really I'm not
convinced we go too much lower than
this. If we do go a lot lower than this,
then it's possible if they want to do a
big shakeout, we're going to go to
24,800.
I would rather they save that for
tomorrow for me when I hopefully feel a
little bit better.
Plus 4K. I could hug you, Alex. Nice,
Ian. Nice work.
Yeah, tricky start of market today.
Yeah, it was. It was very tricky. Thank
you for your daily analysis, Alex. Can
we catch another move on the way?
Can we catch another move? Uh may look
maybe there's a bid back up but we have
to be aware we are now leaving volume.
All right this is the kind of play that
we talk about when we leave volume it
can get aggressive. We're going to be
stuck between two areas. So current
week's volume right we're leaving
current week's volume. All right if
we're leaving this we can get
aggressive. We have to respect this guy
and this guy here. So our cover points
are this guy and this guy here. Maybe we
get follow through. We're going to have
to wait and see if that we're going to
do this move now. or if they're going to
save it for later in the week. But I
would say your edge has gone now unless
we start rejecting all this. If we start
rejecting these nodes, we can look for a
new trade down. I wouldn't be looking
for a new trade down unless we like take
out liquidity, develop liquidity, and
sell. What do I mean by that? Take out
liquidity, create liquidity, resell for
the next level of liquidity or push back
up, reject key level, resell back down.
Um longs today are going to be very
tricky. You're you're going to be
counter trend to when we are leaving big
volume. It's very very risky to do it.
It might we are due a pop. Right.
There's your tens. We just hit the tens.
There you go. So that is your TP. Just a
casual 210 pointer for you guys on on on
stream. If you want to hold to see if we
get down towards uh 24800, by all means
do it. I wouldn't blame you.
You know, if you were if you were short
from here and you if you've had micros
or or your big size minis and you just
have one left, sure, why not see what it
can [\h__\h] do, right? You never know.
We might really go for that naked point
of control. It would be hilarious if
Alex got stopped stopped out to the tick
and it does the full move in one day.
That would be just my luck.
Would you try and follow trend? Yeah,
it's best to follow trend definitely.
It's a much easier trade. Much easier
trades to follow trend.
What upgrade do you I use on bookmap? Uh
you need you're going to need the uh
global or global plus. I have global
plus but you might be fine with global
and you need data.
Is join Discord free or do you need to
take a your course? Yeah, the only
course that we get you Discord is
beginner to advance. Uh, it's like I've
talked about, you might be new on
stream. It's just so that everyone in
that discord, okay, is trading the same
way. It's for everyone's protection.
Free Discords or monthly paying Discords
when you're not trading the same way. I,
for me, I think are problematic. It's
how you get arguments in chat. You put
people off trading. What we have is 200
plus traders trading the same style
looking for the same things which means
they can support each other and varied
levels of traders which means when I'm
not there they can still support each
other I'd still be watching these nodes
now you technically you've hit TPS but
technically you can stay short if this
stays rejecting you do not want it to
develop here all right because you don't
want to really be given back 100 points
do you right so technically if you
reject 50ish
right Technically, you can continue, but
I would be very careful about this
snapback. We're very thin in here.
Um, call that whole move, Alex. You're
the best. You're welcome. Am I looking
for a long? No, not anymore.
Do I live stream every day? Yes. Cut
some short with smart moves. Got to stay
disciplined. Still made 300. Nice work.
I'm also out for the day. I'm up 2K,
down 2K, back up 1K. Hey, that's yeah,
that is a walk away moment, right? If
you up 2K, gave it back and went down 2K
and you're now positive, just walk away.
5 minute orb doesn't lie until it does.
Yeah, same with every trade. It doesn't
lie until it does. And uh people lie.
Out of the day, super green, Alex, thank
you. You're welcome. Do you have all
these indicators in your course? Yeah, a
free version of this comes with the
course. Free version of this. Um but you
can upgrade if you want it. And you can
upgrade if you want it for ninja as
well.
You're welcome. All the breakdowns start
with TJR and he taught me a lot. But the
way you break down is incredible. TJ, I
taught you a lot. That is the first time
I've heard someone say that. But
love from India. Yeah. Love back to you,
man.
Re-entering at 290s.
Is it dangerous? I might have missed
this. This might be old. Way away from
290s now. Sorry, I might be way down on
chat.
You've loved trading since you found me.
Nice.
Can I explain the trade? You missed it
yet? I'll get I'll reexlain it very very
shortly.
Can you still trade futures at 4 p.m.?
Yeah, you can trade 4 to 5:00 p.m., but
then we have a break five to 6 and then
they reopen 6.
Um,
here we go, folks. Oh, this runner is
going to pay. Oh my gosh.
Oh my gosh.
All right, gray box is a next level that
I had marked. I'm going to check what
that was from now.
What are you from?
I think we're sliced through that.
Honestly, there is a bit of a node
there. Oh man,
I am not ruling out a move to 24,800
today.
Uh I'm not ruling out this. That will be
a 528 point short by the end of the day
if it pays. If it plays, most of you
should have made all your money anyway.
I'm not ruling that out.
Thanks, guys. All the new guys
subscribing.
Crumb crumpled fedora
adding the pain onto me.
Oh, that's funny.
That's funny.
Cory Miller, I recommend Alex uh YouTube
on volume placement and use. The best
I've seen so far. Nice. I like the fact
you don't scam anyone. I've been
watching your stream for a couple days.
Thank you a lot. Beginning with order
flow using Sierra Charts. Awesome. Nice,
man. I don't mess with TJR. No. Like you
trade CFDs. That's just says everything
you need to know in my book. But
if you think he made all that money from
trading, you are bonkers, mate.
Alex, genuine question. Is order flow
and footprint equally effective for
London session also. Yeah, it's the same
thing for all the sessions. Obviously,
you have less volume, but you'd be
looking at the same kind of things,
right? So, be looking at if I was
trading London, I would have be looking
at the previous day and the current day.
So the current day if I was trading
London is I'll be looking at Asia. Where
are those traders trapped in Asia? Where
are the high volume nodes in Asia? Where
are the low volume nodes? Where do I
think we can trade to and trade to
search for liquidity? Where are we going
to build all the same stuff, right? You
just have to be aware that you're
trading trading lower volume. All right.
For me, that doesn't mean you use more
size. It means you use less. You might
make less money, but it can skip. If you
get a newsp or a big player on the book
in Asia and London, it will run you. You
have a 520 point stop, you're going to
get lifted 30 40 points.
Love your British accent. Where are you
from? Well, originally from from Sussex,
but I lived in London until uh from 18
to 30. How old am I now? So, 34 and then
now I live in Los Angeles.
1,600 viewers. Are we really? That's
incredible. Smash that like button for
me, folks. This stream is growing and
growing and growing and growing. Yeah,
you guys have already locked well over
200 points in in here. All right. And
we're This is the ultimate target. I
don't know if we do this today. This was
my target this week. All right. This was
This is what I wanted this week. All
right. This week, I was waiting and
waiting and waiting for this move here
to do this move. I was looking for this
to happen on this day. On this exact
day, I was looking for this to happen.
Those who have done the course will know
why. And then I'm looking for this move
down to here because this is a naked
previous week point of control. That
would be my ultimate target. Uh I don't
know if we get it today, folks. It might
be that we save this and we build some
range out here for the rest of the day.
We might come and revisit. I don't know.
But this is my ultimate target this week
if we can do it.
Do not let this run back. This is very
very steep since the last swing point
since we got in. This is very, very
steep. You have a bump here. All right.
Do not let this look. We're already
reclaiming 96s. You want to be careful
here, folks. So, you might want to full
TP. Unless you're willing to sit in this
all day. You might want to full TP out
now.
Can I look at gold? I'll look at gold
shortly. Best feeling about trading
after a week? immediately jump on the
wrong side of the market. Oh, Peter,
sorry to hear that.
Why don't I like CFDs? Uh because the
guys that you're following uh can
manipulate what they're saying they've
ordered and and bought and haven't and
it's not a centralized exchange. It's uh
yeah, not good, man. Lucid trading
website down. I don't know. I haven't
checked. Not sure. I know it was down
yesterday.
Who's this guy spamming? Show us your
profits. Do you want to get blocked?
Who is this guy? Right, you're getting
blocked, mate. That's like a million
messages.
What is wrong with people?
No, I put him on timeout. Don't worry,
guys. What do I think about ICT if I
pass test? What do you mean if you pass
test?
Look, I will say this and I say it
clearly. Some of ICT's teachings are
very good. They are not all his own.
They are regurgitated of others
teachings. But I do think he has made
models, let's say, which people can
understand and digest. Do I think
everything he says is truthful? No,
absolutely not. Does he make the
algorithm? No. Is there one centralized
algorithm? No. Other than liquidity
provider, there isn't. Does he lie about
a lot of things? Yes. Is he a compulsive
liar? Yes. Did he speak to God? I doubt
it. Did he get kidnapped in a white van?
I doubt it. But can it help you be a
better trader? Yeah, probably.
You claim you're a trader yet you can't
make a single profitable trade for me.
I'm down 1,700.
What are you talking about?
Sorry. If you've lost money, that is on
you. I have not called one trade which
hasn't worked on stream today.
That is on you, mate. That is literally
on you. you and you will never be
successful until you change that
attitude because you will look for
excuses of why everyone else is making
you lose money instead of realizing that
it's you who can't trade. That's a fact.
So the best thing about trading is it
will show you the worst parts of
yourself as an individual. It will show
you your greed, your fear, your ego and
you my friend have all three of those by
writing something like that. And that is
a fact. And until you can look at
yourself in the mirror and journal and
get rid of those things, you will never
ever have success trading. If you're
going to blame everyone else, it won't
happen. And that's not me being harsh.
I've been you, mate. I've been in rooms
saying to people, you [\h__\h] told me to
do this and you did this and you did
this and you did this and all it comes
down to, I didn't manage my risk. Fact.
And today I gave you a 200 point winner.
I didn't get the 200 point winner. I got
stopped out unfortunately, but I gave
you a 200point winner. It's up to you to
manage. So, seriously, have a hard look
at yourself.
My goodness. My goodness.
Ah, it's wild, man. I ask for some peace
in chat today after what I'm going
through and this is what I get.
Time to leave the trade. Yeah, I would
say so. Unless you're short from down
here and you're going to look for the
whole swing. If you're if if you're
short from up here and you're looking
for the whole swing, but like we have
now developed we are developing here,
right? So they will build liquidity out
here. I don't think they're done with
it, but they will build out here. It
really depends how much you're willing
to give back. Are you willing to sit in
100 points giving back? All right. And
then look for the bigger swipe down into
here. It's that's the question. That is
up to you to manage.
Yeah, I know. Someone emailed me that
yesterday. I might go members only. I do
subs only. I might have to start doing
members only in chat because it is
getting ridiculous.
VIX catching a
VIX is trading between two blocks. So
VIX just failed that 19 test. All right.
And it's going to come back and test
towards 1836s. Uh and it will need to
catch a bid between 1836s and 1813. If
it does that, we have a huge inverse
head and shoulders developing on VIX
with a fail break lower. a very very
good bear trap on Vicks and if they
catch this bid they can run it higher on
Vicks.
Welcome to the team Frosty.
Where can they get volume node
indicator? This is okay. I'll do it the
one time today. It's the only time I'm
saying it today guys. It is in Nightbot
has told you constantly. You come down
to here, right? Me forecasting and
measuring tools. You go to anchored
volume profile. All right. You anchor it
to the 930 open. If you're going to do
what I'm doing, you don't have to do
that, but that's what I do. 930 open.
These are how you have it. Width 20,
placement, right? Inputs. Tick per row.
I have it set to two. If you want to use
numbers of rows, you can have it set to
a th00and. That is all you change,
right? That is all you change.
Yeah, I know, James. That's why I
haven't done it yet. But it's um it is
uh it is tough. Anton, bro, you're the
best. I went over my 53,000, my apex
with your help today. Thank you, bro.
Yes. Okay. Go. You asked for gold and
silver. All right. Let's have a look at
gold and silver for you guys.
All right. Nice bid on gold off this key
level. I would be very careful. Failed
follow through still. Let me just clean
this up so I can see the high.
But it is a hedge to dollar.
I wouldn't be trading silver the same
way as gold. If one's got a chance of
going, it's going to be gold. All right.
So we're failing 61 fib. All right. So
your pullback was very clearly into this
key level. If we think about very very
basic principles, right? We're breaking
out, pull back, build liquidity, build
liquidity, break out, retest,
and go. Massive wash into what? This
area here where we broke out from. All
right. So we expect a first bounce from
there. Where have we come up to? 61. All
right. If we fail 61 fib or anywhere
around here and I will put some volume
on shortly, we will start doing moves
like this for a bit while it builds
liquidity. If we fail this shelf, then
that's when you'll get extension down.
Until that point, we don't need to be
uber bearish because it might be that it
wants to reclaim and hold. Let's just
have a quick look.
Okay, so you can see even here, look at
the node that held. That's why I had the
gray box there. So, we dipped in front
of that node. We've reclaimed we're
very, very thin here above 27s, aren't
we? All right. So, bears will want to
protect this because that means bulls
are all caught up here. All right. So,
it's a 61 and it's volume. All right.
So, I would be sure I would be
positioning short against that. All
right. I'd be looking for a short
against that for a rotation, taking
profits on the way down and waiting to
see is this failed follow-through. All
right, but I would be paying myself
here. What I would not be doing is
positioning myself long into it. If
you're going to get long now and you
haven't got a pullback, you are going to
need to wait for it to base and hold
above this shelf to offer that back up.
All right, hopefully that helps. And I
will look at silver as well. Silver will
not be as good, I'm telling you, because
it is not a hedge. It's way
overextended.
There you go. So, silver, same kind of
story.
Failing to reclaim shelf. All right, if
we just put shelf on,
first bounce was sold into, which is
your typical failed followrough. So high
to low. We came into shelf. They sold
the shelf. Same thing as I just talked
about on gold. What they might do in
gold. They've resold this shelf. We've
broken down for a new low here. All
right. And we found a bid right into
here, this node here. If they fail again
up here, then there might be follow
through and a collapse down into the
next nodes. All right. If they reclaim
this shelf, then there's a chance of a
squeeze.
Same story. It's exactly the same setup,
but silver is not a good hedge in the
market to dollar. And this move is
[\h__\h] stupid. All right, this move is
not the same. This is ridiculous.
310% ripper
since March. No, mate. Unsustainable.
Parabolic. It's like a small cap.
Parabolic.
The moment you saw your grand and your
granddad trying to buy it and adverts
coming on TV and radio, you knew it was
game over.
All right. So, right into the edge of
this. If they start reclaiming this,
then they're going to start squeezing
and they're going to go and back test
previous day low, previous day close.
So, longs now are starting to try and
bid this up. It is a question of if and
where shorts come in. Like I said, you
should be done with it. Unless you're
trying to hold for the whole swing,
which I said I'd be looking for this by
Friday. I'm not necessarily looking for
it today.
Which chart do I look at for gold and
silver? Uh the futures market or
whatever is on Comx.
You're in spy calls off where like their
90s then I'm guessing on spy.
You're back to previous day low here on
spy. This is a big big big level on spy.
I will tell you there is a buyer still
stuck at 190. All right, so we now have
we're trading back into these levels,
right? We've had some big buyers step
in. There is still a buy stuck at 190s.
We have some imbalances to fill if they
want to go rippy rippy. So 190 big level
here while they make a decision now.
tapped into him. No acceptance above him
yet.
There is an imbalance here. They're
going to get tight here. They have to
make a decision. If they sell him, we
will wash back down. If they get above
him, there is a squeeze out.
Still can't get through this buyer. He's
a big boy.
200 that he got caught. Here you go. So
they're selling against him right now.
And we're going to come back down to VPO
probably into 50. So 90 to 50 a possible
rotation here. So 90 to 50
possible rotation. If they rebid 50,
they will try and take out that 90.
There are loads of imbalances higher
here.
No, I'm not going over the setting and
volume profile one more time. I'm sorry.
I do it every day here 10 times. It is
in the Nightbot. Just scroll up.
Nightbot literally above where you've
written, like four lines above you,
Danny. It literally tells you. I trade
using anchor volume profile. I set it to
two ticks. It's anchored at 9:30 New
York open. Blue and red boxes on my
chart are high time frame SNR levels.
Gray boxes on my chart are key levels of
volume. It's all there. It's right there
above you.
It's not about you. It's just I honestly
I have to do it on stream every single
day. It's too much. There's free videos
on my YouTube on it.
still tapping into this guy at 190.
You're stuck through that. They can try
and squeeze. So, you got previous day
low and previous day close above.
All right, I'm going to get myself that
coffee. I think I need it for myself.
Um, what I will do is we will do a
giveaway before I go.
Let's set you guys up. There you go. 190
still rejecting. So 90s to 50 is still
the level. Just gave it to you. But you
know, I don't know what I'm talking
about. Apparently everyone chat wants to
[\h__\h] call me out today.
It's literally just done it in one
candle. Um,
hold your head, mate.
All right, we'll give away an Apex
account here.
Uh, currently 80% on sale. Use code FCT
for Apex. All right, if you type it in
chat once, please don't spam. Please,
I'm begging you. Please don't spam. You
won't win if you spam. All right, just
type it once in chat. I'm going to go
and brew myself a coffee. When I get
back, I'm going to pick a winner. Stay
here, chat.
Okay,
sorry guys.
All right, let's pick this winner.
Chili Lifestyle X90E. Chili Lifestyle
X90E. Are you there? through lifestyle.
Chile lifestyle, are you there?
Delete this. Maybe
give you a couple more seconds to say
you're here. If you've switched streams,
we will be giving the Apex account to
someone else.
All right, so little poke through 190
failed into previous day low and GlobeEx
lost the 190s and 150s and now I have to
see if they put in a higher low.
Um, we can have a look on orderflow to
see who's trapped down here. Like we
said, buyer caught here there. Another
huge buyer came in. You can see these
buyers keep getting caught. They are
piling in here. 290, 163, 235. You see
the delta, they are too aggressive here.
If they do not break out, they will
cause a new low. All right? Or at least
a retest towards these guys. 100 and and
then 90s really. So, they need to get
above their average price here.
Otherwise, they're going to be in big
big trouble. Big big trouble because
they keep piling in here with some
serious size. Okay, we haven't had him
turn up, so we're going to reroll. I'm
picking a winner now. FC Mike 1969, you
are a regular. I know you are regular.
So hopefully you are here, my friend,
for an Apex account.
FC Mike, are you here? FC mic
PC lifted now to shifted to here. This
is a big level now for the nice work,
dude. This is our level for the day. All
right. Under here, they're looking for a
rotation. You need to be very careful.
If you are going to take this short, you
must be covering some down here because
you're shorting very very very very low,
which is not what I would be doing. Uh
if they reclaim this, we will get a
resqueeze up into this. All right. So,
they're trying to reclaim. They're going
to look for the reclaim and squeeze. So,
look for a second leg up and then maybe
they refade that down into this thin
vault. Right, these are your overunders,
these levels for the day. Uh, dude, can
you just email me
info@flowzonerader.com?
Just send me the screenshot and I'll get
you set up. Thank you, my friend.
All
right, we do one more giveaway.
Hey, Alex, should I mark out the
previous week volume profile on an
hourly or a minute chart on Trading
View? Uh, I actually do it on an hourly.
Um, but it's far more accurate if you do
it on a minute chart. The what you find
with Trading View is the lower uh time
that you do it on, the more accurate it
will be. It's whether you've got the
patience to do it.
whether you got the patience.
All right,
see if Alex can uh lock back in here and
look for another trade.
See how far we lift here. Uh watch this
initial balance to view up looks
probable here, doesn't it? Midpoint
looks very, very probable here.
VIX into this key level now. needs to
find a bid here in the 18s on the VIX.
If and when the VIX finds a bid here, I
think we will have a shot at a reshort
down. Uh last time sellers came in was
at 39 and 50. All right, so we're going
to watch those levels. We have an
imbalance at uh 56 up to 64 and
obviously previous day value area low up
at 300 again, which was the big level
that we traded away from. So we're
lifting up into these levels right now.
It's a little bit squeezy. How high can
they go for this lift? They are bidding
or offering sorry at 260 right now.
We've just left a huge imbalance in that
last candle. If they trap enough buyers
up here, there will be a decent wash
back down on a second leg. But let's see
see what we do. We know Dex level today
was at 300 and we lost that. So that's a
big level to watch.
Here we go into the VWOX like we talked
about. So a big imbalance here into
where these sellers are. Big DEX level
above into 300. How do we operate here?
Do they resqueeze higher and higher and
higher or we game over here? How much
how much further can they squeeze this?
Basically, can they get back to threes
or not?
A huge imbalance on the way up there.
Big old squeeze after leaving this
volume.
See how high we can go and if they offer
a short once they trap enough.
So at 350 same or 250 sorry 350 250 same
level as before. Wonder if they can lift
higher here
this into 80s 80s.
It's starting to get a little bit stuck
here.
Not a lot of buyers trapped in that.
Just some selling into 60. Not a huge
amount of buyers trapped in that. I
think this is done. Yeah.
Yes. Probably wants to be up as well,
I'd imagine.
Here's the imbalances
in towards the VWAP. Remember 300's the
massive level.
Big old squeeze. Once they're done with
the squeeze, they probably let it go
back down the other way. Probably just
trap enough buys in at the highs and
then they'd be done. It's just do they
do it here or do they do it up into 300.
If they came three reclaim 300, it's a
huge recovery.
But I'm interested in how we operate
around here now. Do we offer a sell back
down from here? Do they trap enough
buyers? Here's the start. Still
absorbing. So sellers got stuck at 50s
before. So, we're watching those 50s for
acceptance underneath for a drastic snap
right the way back down after a squeeze
out. We haven't tapped VWAP yet on the
indexes. Worth noting.
Watching this very very very carefully
here. Still bidding in front of the 50s
right now. They're looking to trade
higher still. Once we lose 50, there
might be a play.
W this bit up pretty aggressively.
Here's the 50 tap again. Still absorbing
it.
Still looking for higher. They're still
trying to squeeze us.
Here it goes. B. So 80s and then 300s.
The big level. Remember the GEX level.
Still watching these 50s for a trigger
entry. If I'm going to see continuation
short under 60s. Watching this under 50.
Sorry. Watching this here.
Still absorbing that there.
Very interested in their short when
they're done with it.
And they want to lift up here is the
question.
Do they want to get all the way out to
65s? That would be huge move if they
were able to do that. Waiting for
backside.
Sip of coffee while we wait.
No audio is not way low. I'm just
talking low. I'm running out of energy.
Okay. Do they go 300s then? By the looks
of it, they want to retap these 300s.
I think we will get stuck somewhere
around here. Unless they lift through
this node here and get all the way up
into the 65. I think we will probably
see it get stuck and a rotation back to
80 is probably coming soon. It is
probably coming soon. Maybe on the new
hour after the new hour.
Watching these 40s and 50s. That's where
the sellers keep getting stuck. Once we
get under that, we might see
continuation lower.
Here we go. 40s. Do they fill these
imbalances now? Still bidding 40s.
They're going to flush this through the
40s and fill this little imbalance to
35s or not. reselling here at 50s. All
right, we might see a wash here if this
seller steps in.
Here's the imbalance.
Filled the imbalance. Does this seller
hold 50s now? He's there at 50s. We want
to see if he's actually going to hold it
or not. If he holds it, I'll consider a
join. I'm not convinced we're done yet,
but if he holds it, I'll consider a
join.
He's filled. I think they might squeeze
a little bit higher here. Trying to time
this if I'm going to get involved.
We have buyers caught above 63s
and we have sellers caught at 40s right
now. And that's the that's the 20
points. That's all they've got right
now.
VIX is not finding a bid where it needed
to find a bid. So sliding back down,
finding a bid down PDC, trading up to
PDH on VIX.
I'm interested in this short. Just
waiting to see if we let go of 40s or
not. Keep they keep rebidding 40s. If we
keep sell trapping sellers here, there's
nothing I can do, right? They keep
rebidding versus this guy here. These
are all the imbalances we can fill if
this guy takes over and we can maybe
trade down to 190 at least. So, that's
what I'm looking to trade if possible.
Here we go. Back to 40s again. Watching
this again. If this guy just leaves the
tape and lets it go, I will join short.
We already did the giveaway. You're
asking how to do the giveaway. We
already did the giveaway. No, I'm not in
yet. I'm watching the 40s. I'm not in
yet. We are still absorbing 40s.
I will need to either see a break under
40s that gets sold into aggressively to
join or I'm going to need to see a push
up towards 300s which is sold into which
where they trap buyers. I do not want to
just enter here and wait. I want to see
a reaction. I do not want to enter early
and just wait. That would be a front
side short. I don't want a front side
short. I want a backside short. Right?
So, I need them to leave and do this or
I need them to push and do something
like this and trap buyers up here. I do
not want want to just enter there. There
is no trade here to just enter there.
This should be here.
40s again. Right. Still perking my
interest at 40s.
Do they snap this? Now they're coming
in. They're still trying to bid 30s.
Here's the first imbalance filled now.
Do we get a reaction at 40?
Want to see a seller step in back in at
40. Not seeing it yet. They're trying.
They're still bidding 30. They're still
stepping up. I think we're going to wash
a little bit deeper, but not enough.
Come on.
What are you going to do? You're going
to do one more shove up, you dirty dog.
They keep stacking 30s and 20s. There's
still a bid on the tape here.
It just trapped a few more people here
again sell side. There's no follow
through sell side yet. Watching 40s
again on this next tap in to see what
happens.
straight through it. No trade.
I think they're not done with it. I
think they need to do like one more
squeeze out or something at the moment.
It feels close.
Where are we on that hourly?
Just like can they lift to 312? It's
very possible looking at developing
week. It's very very very possible. I'm
looking at this.
Very possible that they want to come
further up into this node here. Very
possible. Big wash. Save. Now we found
bids. We will see.
So I can see the better.
We'll see.
Okay, stuck a gray box again.
Still interested. I just wonder if they
need to lift. We're still interested
here. It's looking very messy on the
charts here. Buy just got caught at 45
in the last 5m minutee candle, but we're
not accelerating away from him back down
to the 190s, which is what I'm looking
for. Starting. They're trying to try and
sell now. They're trying to now sell
these lows. Here we go. Here we go.
Here we go. Come on then. Let's get to
200s and 190s.
Do not want any reclaim of 40s here,
folks. All right. No reclaim of 40s. We
are into imbalances. You can take
partials on the way. Do not be like
overstaying your welcome if they start
on a reclaim. All right? Because this
dip can hold. I would love it to get
down into 180s and below. It's what I'd
really like.
They're trying to bid 20s here. Look at
this aggressive bit of 20s. He should
sell through this 20 if he gets stuck to
200.
Come on. Come down to 200 for me. He's
still bidding 20s. Keeps refreshing.
Come on. Get under him. Come on. Get
down to 200 and then let's go. Let's go.
Let's go. Patience, guys. Patience.
Patience. Right. Let's see how low we
can go. Can Let's see if we can get the
190s. Is the twos? Is the bid at twos?
If we lose this, we should go 190.
There's a bigger bid at 160. Here we go,
folks. Here we [\h__\h] go. Hey, didn't
tell me what to do. Shut the [\h__\h] up.
Not in the mood for it today.
How many times I tell you I will get in
if we leave 140s. If we leave 140s
aggressively. I don't know what else to
say.
So, bidding 200s. If we lose 200s, I'm
going to cover some 190s and then 160s.
All right, so they're bidding this shelf
here. We want to cover some into this
shelf here. All right, they're trying to
hold this here. All right, so we're
going to cover some here and then 60s.
All right, so we're going to be most out
into here because we will then expect a
bounce and if they sell that bounce, we
will look for a new low.
We're early here because they can still
do this, but we are positioned well
versus this volume. All right. And we're
covering some and some more here. And if
they lift and they resell it, we can
look for lower.
I'm watching this guy at 200. Don't want
to reclaim a 30s.
We have an imbalance right at 30s. And
that big shelf was at uh 3975. So, don't
want to reclaim a 30s. Here we go. Come
on. Follow through. Follow through.
Follow through. Follow through. Follow
through. Come on. It threw this guy at
200.
Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come
on. Come on. Come on. Come on.
Let's go. It's only a 56 lot here. I
just want to see us trade through him
and snap.
Then big buyer is at 190. That's where I
really want to cover. I really want to
cover more at 190.
He's added more size here. He's
determined to hold up 200 right now.
Want to be careful with ES at previous
day low here. Want it to snap previous
day low. Don't want it to reclaim it.
Here we go. Get through this [\h__\h]
guy. Come on. Come on, sellers. Here we
go. Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Here we go. Here we go. Here we go. We
go. All right. Here we go, folks.
Covering a little piece into here if I
can get there. Do not want to see them
wash and reclaim. Oh, you dirty [\h__\h]
All you had to do is drop down a tiny
bit more to hit my TP. What did you hit
there? 92s. You missed me by two points.
That might be it. That might be all we
get. It might be all we get. Be very,
very careful now. Come on. Come on.
You guys saying uptrend baby. We are not
uptrend baby. We are not uptrend baby.
We are down trend baby. This is pullback
baby. We are leaving volume, baby. We
are downtrend. We are too leg. We are
pull back. We might well continue down
here. Do not think that this is going to
do all the way back up there. All right.
Do do not think we are in uptrend. It's
not necessarily the case right now. We
are starting to leave volume trapped at
310s and above. Right? We are starting
to leave volume trapped at 310 and above
this week. We are starting to reject
that after a failed breakout. We are
starting to reject that. We are digging
down into previous week levels right
now. We have a naked point of control
which it wants to revisit. This is not a
big protrend update. All right. Do not
think that.
Is Lucid better than TPT? They're just
different. It's not that they're better.
They're just different. Right.
Different.
Can I call you baby again? Yeah.
Here we go. Come on. Come on. I need a
break down here. All right. Trimming
some there. And if we get under this
guy,
this guy. If we get under this guy,
we're going to look to trade into 50s
and 60s. Right. If we can get under this
big blue line, we're going to look to
trade down here because that will mean
these big buyers will start being stuck.
And this is what we're talking about. If
they keep chasing and we can keep coming
under their price, if we can get under
150 today, there is a good chance that
we'll auction down to the lows again.
All right, but this level here is
massive. This is not a madeup level.
This is quite genuinely where they've
been trading in and around.
Here we go. Come on. Let's see if
there's acceleration under 90s. I'm out
a decent size here. Let's just see if we
can get acceleration down. Gray box P.
I'd really love it if we let go of this.
If we let go of 50s and 60s, right? We
know that they might well want to bid
here. They will want to protect here.
But I tell you what, if we do this, we
are coming back for this.
Don't know how it stayed on stream so
long.
We're going to get it. Come on. Come on.
Stop saving it. This guy on the tape is
relentless down here. This is maybe the
same guy as the other day. Is it the
same level that we're bidding? Oh, it
is. It's the same level where we had
that relentless bidding on Monday.
Interesting.
Interesting. It's probably the same guy
gobbling up down here.
Still think there's a wash potentially.
Is that the Tyson setup? It was a bit
dirty because we didn't we we set the
low. We didn't retest the IB. But yes,
technically we came in, we set the IB,
we traded back to VWAP. We're trying to
trade from VW up back to IB now if
possible. But we will respect this. But
if we get under that, we're looking for
this, aren't we? So this is the Tyson
trade both ways really. All right. IB to
VW up, V up to IB.
Exactly that. You should be covering a
decent chunk here if you haven't
already. All right. So we traded from
30s and 40s down to here. All right. If
they cannot sell through this, they
might well come and revisit this node
again, which will not be fun.
That bar is really trying to get
aggressive down here. Look at him on
bookmap. Just nonstop. Bid bid bid bid
bid. Look. Same guy. It's got to be the
same guy. I'm out of this, guys. I'm out
of this. Same guy. If I show you
bookmap. Look at this guy. He is [\h__\h]
relentless down here. Like just gobbling
everything possible. Okay, we're going
to come and revisit that same level, the
30s and 40s. Sellers need to reject this
level. If they do not reject this level,
we have a second leg up.
A third leg up. Sorry. So, revisiting
30s and 40s. There you go. There's the
revisit of 30s and 40s, right? Why
there? Because this is where we just
broke down from. All right. Understand
that this is where
we just broke down from. Right? This was
the level where I kept saying they're
trying to absorb it. Once he gets out of
the way, he will stop out. This is him
stopping out. There's the wash. We come
down into the same level. We bid off.
This is why we talk about level to
level, right? We come down to this
level. Oh, I don't want that.
this level that we just broke out from.
All right, bid back down. Retest stuck
between these two. Protrend is what?
It's lower technically. Protrend is
lower right now.
What's my setup or what do I need to buy
and subscribe to have the same data as
you? D
for which? Sorry, mate. I'm I'm on
different screens here. Do you mean on
trading view? On trading view, I use my
flow zone pro
right here
which uh you can buy on my website or
you get a version of the course and just
anchored volume profile and I'm running
bookmap and on ninja trader I use uh
twin peaks for uh
uh footprint.
No guys, your uptrend is relief right
now. Zoom out.
Zoom out. Remind me how the market
works. Does the market just go like
this? No.
Create volume. Leave volume.
That What's this? If we've just left
this, we've failed to break out here and
we've just left this. This is a pullback
and that should be sold into. If they
reclaim up here, okay, fair enough.
Uptrend. We reclaim. But until that
point, unless you were fishing down
here, all right, the fact that we've
been in a sell and your VWOPS are here
and if we go from the high to the low of
the day
coming into the 50%, maybe they get to
the 61, which was the 300 level, but
sellers should be selling in here. All
right, they should be selling in here
looking for this. All right, or at least
looking for this, which we just got the
retest of this, right? If buyers reclaim
this, then we can argue we're going to
use that liquidity. But right now, I see
this as nothing more than a pullback. I
know the range is big. I know that this
has moved from 25,000. Well, it's like
what 200 point pullback, but that's
because we've done a five or 600 point
sell. All right, so we've done a big
sell pull back. I would expect this to
get sold into somewhere around here. We
got that first cell down to the node. If
they reclaim this level, then we can
think about that. Sure, I'm not going to
argue with that. But right now,
don't get too bullish biased here. Do
not get too bullish biased here.
Yeah, but the DJ is what 30 stocks which
are heavily manipulated. Um, and DJ has
not got, if we have a look at the
breadth right now,
Vix is going lower. You are right. Vix
is going lower.
If we look at the breadth right now,
this is probably going to like pause as
soon as I bring it over. It always does.
All right. That's the breadth
all in ES. All right. All in ES. What's
big in NQ? This one. This one. This one.
This one. This one. This one. So, all
the big boys other than Aqua Nvidia
major cell. All right.
What's big in YM? Hello.
All right. So, why you think it's
pushing? All right. So, it's breath.
It's breath rotation right now, which
has been the story since October last
year.
I mean, you say semis are pumping hard,
but you're acting like they're taking
out the highs when they're saying that.
They're rotating off the lows like ENQ
is. Can they reclaim is is the thing.
But
I would say look if if we start breaking
out on Nvidia above that high that
morning high which was also Monday's
high, right, which we failed in twice.
But if you look at Nvidia, it's pro
probably just doing a 61% retracement.
Yeah, it's a golden zone retracement
until it proves otherwise. Same thing on
this. I don't know what to say, guys.
I'm trying to help the best I can, but
I'm not going to fight with you guys. If
you guys just want to long this because
you think the market's pumping and it
has to go higher, like I said, it's your
book. You do what you want. But all I
know is we've left volume, we've left
weekly volume, we've broken down, we're
pumping back up to retest that. We are
likely to try and trade lower. We need
to get under this. But the higher
probability right now is here to here.
And if we lose this here to here, the
lower probability right now is to bid
here expecting this. That is not a high
probability move. Sometimes it happens.
I will not deny it. Sometimes it
happens. Zero TTE goes absolutely
bonkers and we go [\h__\h] mad. But that
is less probable.
Ralph Finnvvis Finnvvis.com
finnvvis.com.
Exactly, Joe. Exactly. Exactly, Joe.
I haven't. It depends how you're going
to turn up and show up today, mate,
because I haven't got the patience for
it. So, if you want to show up and be
cool, that's fine. If you've just shown
up now and you're going to question
everything when we've nailed over 200
points today, it's up to you, mate. It's
up to you how you want to show up on
stream.
It's totally up to you.
S&P back to green. Not saying we're
pumping. I mean,
okay.
Where's it back to, though? Look, I'll
try and help you guys here.
Zoom out. Okay. It's gone. It's gone
green.
It's a nice recovery.
How good is it really?
How good is it really? All right. How
good is it really?
Big sell.
Okay. Failed to break lower here. Can't
deny it. Failed to break lower. That's
the start of the relief. Where is it
likely to sell? Between here and here,
right? They are likely to sell it
somewhere in there, right? And they're
likely to look to return probably to 90
to retest that. I'm not saying it has to
break down, but just cuz it's doing this
when you're like big pump, it it's moved
50% off a 100% move. It's it's retraced
50% which is likely somewhere around
that to be sold into. Likely somewhere
around that to be sold into, right?
Which is what you're seeing. So to call
this a big pump for me, it's not a big
pump. A big pump would be like this.
Okay, that's a big [\h__\h] pump. Sure.
Right. And we see that sometimes. we see
that. I don't think this is that. I
think this is like failure to break
lower, failure to break lower. No wants
to short the lows. They're waiting for a
retracement into a level which they can
sell into. That would be my view on this
on this market right now. But it's just
my view. What do I know? Let's see how
it plays out. Alex might be wrong and
I'm happy to be wrong, but like I said,
I think somewhere between here and here
will be an area that they will want to
sell right down to here. And under here,
they will look to try and get down into
these
How did I get those candles with Ninja
with the Delta? Uh, it's from a place
called Twin Peaks. Um, and it's called
uh
have to look it up. I remember what the
indicator is called, but it's Twin
Peaks.
Uh, I can post it in chat. Hang on.
There you go. You get like a 5% discount
with that link as well.
It could try and hold and grind to
that's it for big moves. Yeah, it could
like it can come up to here. Like we
said, it can come up to here. A back
test of here is very very possible. It
can come up to here.
But like I'm not going to buy this here.
I'd much rather wait for buyers to get
short, wait for buyers to get trapped
and look for the short back down like we
just did here. We just had this move
here, right?
So the plays today were
the leave of here. Was it 40s? I'm
trying to remember. It was up here,
wasn't it? So
this
some of you got all the way down into
10. Tens was the cover point. All right.
So some of you got this,
right? And then we just had
this,
right? And now we're waiting. If they
lift it, like I said, if if they want to
go turbo today,
fine. Go [\h__\h] turbo with it all you
want, guys. Uh I will not be playing
long from here when I I quite literally
know that we've just left volume. All
I'm looking at is the Audi. I don't give
a care about anything else. All I'm
looking at is who's trapped this week.
They are trapped here. And until we
reclaim that, they are in trouble. Until
we reclaim this node here from Sunday,
they are in trouble. All right. So, I
would expect them to try and sell this
for a move back down. And if we break
down there, my expectation is we will
revisit this at some point this week. If
we reclaim this range,
then I will shut my mouth and we will go
in range rotation and I will not touch
it. And if we get above here, then Alex
will tell you we're going to pump up
here and then we're going to set a trap.
And that might be later in the week, but
I don't think we will do that now. They
should have done that today if they were
going to do it. But hey, look, these are
just my ideas and my thesis. What do I
know? Not a lot.
I always talk about I'm just a
40-year-old man who's pissed off most of
the time. Grumpy old man.
Yeah. 50 to 61 retracement. Yeah,
exactly. So, you could line it up with
the IB
here to here. All right. We're right at
the 50 right now. The 61 would be into
the 300. It's a GEX level as well, which
we should have held earlier and chose
not to hold and sold through. So, we
know there'll probably be sellers
hanging out there again, right? So, and
we have this node developing here now.
So, if they lift through this node, they
will try and lift to 300. If they get
through 300, arguably the squeeze is on
to 364, right? We're very, very thin. If
they get over 300 and they don't sell
it, arguably the squeeze is on.
I look 30.
I'll take that.
Where did I learn orderflow from? Just
selftaught really. I've used bookmap
forever. I used to use bookmap in uh in
uh small caps. Bookmap is so useful in
small caps because you can see the uh
the manipulation really well. Reading a
tape in small caps is [\h__\h]
impossible.
Well, at least I found it impossible.
Thanks, Carol.
Will you be happy if Arsenal wins
something? Yeah. Well, obviously that
would delight me. It's been a long wait.
I missed the move earlier cuz I had to
take my kids to school, but I still got
600 times three. Nice. Nice, mate. 1,800
quid.
Alex, you mentioned getting in on the
breakdown to of 240. Do you wait for
candle closure? No, I'm not waiting for
closure. I'm watching bookmap when I'm
doing that. So, if we're leaving a shelf
like here,
all right, when we know that this is a
shelf here, I'm waiting to see the
buyers get caught on bookmap and
aggressive sellers start to go from
passive sellers to aggression and then
I'm joining for that move.
All right. Maybe you're going to get
300s. I will have egg on my face. If we
get above 300s and base and go rip to
the highs, I'm going to look like Well,
just [\h__\h] what are you going to do,
mate? Market will do what it wants. I'm
not fighting against it, that's for
sure.
I am 40.
85. 85, baby.
I'm new here. Is this guy good? No, he's
terrible.
Do I recommend leaving limit orders in
key areas? Uh, no, not really. I think
it's really dangerous to do that unless
you're playing a pullback.
Unless you're playing a pullback
protrend, I think it's dangerous to do
that. I think it's better to look for
what happens in that area.
Oracle's under 160. Oh, it's only 1.66%
down. Have a look.
I'm still comfortably up. I'll check it.
Oh, mate. That's fine. What are you
talking about? We're long from down
here, right? We're long from down here.
If you if you're with me in Discord, I
don't know. We're long from down here.
There's no problem with this whatsoever.
We might even gap fill and still bid,
right? So, if this is the first push,
right, we might even come down here and
then rebid back up.
Uh, I've got no qumss with holding this
right now. I'm long from down here. I'm
just until it fails and breaks down. I'm
not worried at all. Not at all. This is
just a pullback and I want to see if we
absorb the difference with this pullback
compared to like why are you longing
this and and not in NQ. Um because this
right here's the big difference.
This is ridiculous.
They are panic selling it.
They're panic selling software.
We are deep in discount into a block
here. It is worth bidding on that block.
And I will see if we can get a
retracement. If we can get a retracement
off this
if this market goes bullish in general,
right, we will get up here at the
minimum. We will get up into 3840s. that
will be a $100 winner per tra per uh
share.
So, I'm not concerned right now. Not in
the slightest. It's not my favorite
stock. I'll be honest. Uh it does have
some potential debt issues, but I do
think they've oversold it. I do prefer
the uh ETF.
Okay. Okay. They're starting to sell up
there. What do you know?
What do you know? What do youing know?
What do you know?
Where can I get the course? Pinned to
the top of chat, mate. It's pinned on
the top of chat. Just hit that link tree
or go to flowzonetrader.com.
I'm really enjoying best loser wins
after you recommend it. Any
recommendations for next read? Uh, yeah,
for sure. Uh, to get my Audible up
because I always forget what they're all
called. Well, we all know my favorite
one, right? Golf is not a game of
perfect. That is I think that's the best
book for traders. I know laugh, but I'm
serious. It is the best book for
traders.
All right, let's have a look at my
library in there. All right, the world
is for sale, I think, is a great book.
It's not really a trading book. Well, it
is, but it's just a great read. Um,
where is my library?
Fooled by Randomness.
Great book.
Uh,
what else do I think is good in here?
Obviously
all the unknown market wizards obviously
they all very very good uh mental game
of trading Jared Tendler very good
obviously trading in his own Mark
Douglas
um outliers I actually quite like Mark
and glad Malcolm Gladwell because it's
important to remind yourself there's
always the possibility
um
atomic habits James Clear be right up
there. I think those are those are
pretty much it. Those are the good ones.
Oh my god. What is happening, folks? Oh
my god.
Oh my god.
[\h__\h] hell. What is happening?
In Market Wizards, they barely mention
order flow. Well, probably because well,
it depends which ones you've read. The
original market wizards, you got to
remember we're talking about the 80s and
stuff. They would have been pit traders,
you know, so when they were buying the
guys buying soy and and corn and stuff,
they wouldn't have had order flow. They
would have been having to judge based on
macro environment. And I don't mean a
macro like 10 minutes before a candle
and 10 minutes after. I mean the global
macro, economic and political
environment is what they would have been
trading off.
Oh my god, what the [\h__\h] does Alex know?
Oh my god. Oh my [\h__\h] god. What are
you lot going to do who talked a load of
[\h__\h] What are you going to do?
opinion of Patrick Wland. I like Patty.
I like he's Marmite. I I actually really
respect Pat genuinely. He's been at it a
long time.
He's a big personality.
He's great at like um
being that big personality, right? And
um I can't comment on his trading
because I don't really watch him trade.
I remember him trading small caps back
in the day. I've seen a little bit from
him. I know he likes the old flag. Uh I
don't think he uses higher time frame
too much. Um but I like Pat. I got no
issue with Pat whatsoever. I think he's
done a lot for the industry. I think
people talk a lot of [\h__\h] Pat has gone
through a lot. If you follow through
followed Patty for a long time, you will
know he has not had the easiest life.
So, anyone who makes a success of
themselves, I will give absolute [\h__\h]
kudos to because he's a self-made man
and that I respect no matter what. No
matter what.
Made a joke and night yelled at you. You
probably did it in capital or something.
Don't worry, it's it's not a big deal.
Can we visit today's lows? Uh, let me
have a look. You've got to get under
this first, right? So, the first trade
we talked about trapping buyers up here
and trading back down to here. You need
to get under this and then maybe we can
have a look. I'll have a look on this
one for you so you guys can all see it
rather than my ninja one. Let's have a
look at what we did. Did we trap buyers
at the highs?
Strong selling up there. I'm going to
compare this to ninja in a second just
out of interest. All right. into some of
these imbalances which were starting to
fill. Let's have a look at the low of
day. What was the auction like at low of
day? They good excess. Not great. All
right. So, we can probably
What would I be looking at? 100s for
sure. And
yeah, 70s we can maybe do it. Let me
just check ninja now because sometimes
it's a bit more accurate.
Is definitely more accurate. Okay. This
is what I'm seeing on NT. Right. So on
that last shove, what happened here?
Hello. Who's at the high day? Oh, longs
are caught. What do we like? Longs that
are caught. What else do we have at all
these high candles? All of these guys.
All of these guys.
All of these guys. Guess who got caught?
All of those guys. Oh yeah, they got
[\h__\h] caught. What happened when we
dropped under 40 where the selling
started? Oh yeah, we [\h__\h] knifed.
Why? because it's the same [\h__\h] shelf
where they're trapped above. Sorry, I'm
getting annoyed now. But there we go.
I'm wound up today. All right, we've
come back down to where where the big
buyer was. 190. What did we say the
rotation is? 50s 50s or 40s to 90s.
That's the rotation. We can price back
up here. They can still try and resell
this. All right, we have some imbalances
down here. They need to get to go lower.
The big gray box is what it is. All
these massive buyers. All right, look at
these massive buyers. We need to get
under them to get low of day. Until that
point, we cannot guarantee low of day,
but we can talk about going from here to
here. If we get under them, all right,
we can talk about using their pain to go
from here maybe to here 89. We have to
see if they actually want to auction
lower. All right, so we have to see
about this. We don't know. This is why
we position ourselves short
for their pain. here. All right. Once we
leave, we cover some into the level
where we know they might hold and we
hold in case we find acceptance lower.
All right. It's the same thing all the
all the time. Location, momentum,
location, momentum. Where is the best
location to get short? Up in here when
we leave buyers trapped. Where are we
going to cover some? Into the next
location where buyers keep absorbing.
Where is the ultimate target when these
buyers get stuck? Down into low of day
and possibly the naked point of control.
All right. So,
I don't know what else to say, folks.
This has been on here the whole time.
What we've been looking for
sucking Premier out of options before
nose driver. He might well be right.
Rooks are similar to to me. I don't know
if he is. I know he trades momentum. Uh
I I Could not comment. Could not
comment.
Alex, what's the statistics you were
talking about with the 80% chance taking
out value area low? Uh, it also depends
on the day, but yeah, if we're if we
trade above value area high, previous
day value area high and lose that,
there's like an 80% chance that we will
revisit the value area low the next day,
the same day. Sorry.
Yes, I have tried to put my system into
an algae. It's like it's impossible.
I've tried honestly. I've tried so hard.
If anyone wants to have a go at it, by
all means have a go at it. It's really
hard.
Um,
they could see all the flow in the pit.
Who was trapped the other? Yeah, they
could, but they would have to see it and
listen to it. probably they probably
they have talked about that at market
wizards but not in the same way. Okay,
so there's your bare flag. Can they
break down under here? So if you were
short, you're covering some into here
and you're hoping you find acceptance
lower.
Nice, Tyson. Great work, mate. Nice.
Lots of you getting that. Alex Berlin,
another 800
clear ball. Alex, Crystal B, you mean?
Yeah. Yeah. Hopefully Raph.
Oh, yeah. V viral viral contents telling
me I run my mouth a lot. Well, it's
because people in chat are just
ridiculous.
Thanks, Kyle. Appreciate it, man.
Some of you saying long now. Not for me.
Not for me.
Do I think NT is better for footprint?
Uh, yeah. I do. I do. I think it's a
little bit more accurate than Trading
View, but Trading View is not bad.
I've watched you for three days, and the
amount you've gone over in those three
days burned my brain.
Do I think your strategies align with
Cammy Capital in regards to volume
profile? I've been watching your channel
and his channel. Uh what does he trade?
I thought he traded ICD.
Does he not? Does he trade volume?
Oh yeah, he moved to volume a while ago.
What am I talking about? I don't know
how he trades volume, but if he's
trading volume profile, then he probably
has a good understanding of where he
wants to enter and exit.
Could we re revisit the high today? I
very much doubt it. You would have to
reclaim all current days volume, all
current week's volume, and break out
with everyone trapped above you. That's
why I keep saying we have volume trapped
above us right now. I think it's very
unlikely we revisit today's high.
Best book for traders. What I think what
I think I mean you can read lots of
them. I think golf is not a game of
perfect personally.
Uh yeah what uh you have to trade 8
days. Uh you don't not just wait trade
the eight days. Tyson
is this resistance turn support or I
mean yes technically it is. I mean, it's
just volume, right? So, we know they bid
off this. We covered, remember, we took
this trade, we covered into this, right?
If you're position short again for the
same thing, you should be covering into
this. But you now have these buyers
trapped here, and we also have everyone
trapped up here, right? Which is why
we're trying to trade lower all the
time. You're protecting this, right?
Here's the pullback. This is the
protrend. All right? This protrend will
really start developing once you get
under here. They might chop between this
for a while. They can absolutely chop
between that for a while. If they keep
trapping here and one side gets more
stuck than the other. Can they get up
here? It's possible. But the protrend is
down right now.
But we are going into look look at how
we're developing these nodes now. So we
got here, here, and here. All right. And
then we have one up here. All right. So
we at the moment we're going from this
node to this node. from this node, maybe
back up. Maybe they resell this. If they
get under this, we'll probably go from
here to here for a minute and then see
if they flush it or reclaim and go over.
If we get over here, then we're going to
try and revisit this node. And we might
do this for a bit. If we get over here,
we're going to go from this to this,
this to this, this to this. All right.
So, these make it clear, especially as
you get through the day, you find clear
levels.
You're running out of time, though.
You're getting into lunch. Oh my days.
What is that? There's a big cover.
Is there news here? Yeah, we've got
talkers.
Netanyahu signed on as a member of the
board of peace. Are you [\h__\h] kidding
me? In what world are we living in where
he should be anywhere near anything
peaceful? Are you kidding me? Wow.
Wow.
All right.
It's Trump's board, right? That is me.
In my mind, that's mental.
It's mental.
Yeah, exactly. That's how I feel.
Wild. All right. Well, if they claim
reclaim here, then they can try and get
back up to 300. You're just back to this
gray box. So, you can see how many times
we done this rotation. This is the third
rotation now, right?
One, two, well, I guess fourth, three,
four.
This is your rotation zone right now.
Does a 25k funding make sense to get
first payout? Yeah, definitely.
H1 just turned green. Let me have a
look. Clean these up.
Uh yeah. Well, it's it's just on its
it's on its open price. It's not it's
not through it.
rotation again. More rotation. So buyers
really need to bid here at 13s if they
have an ambition of moving higher into
lunch.
They would need to bid 13s.
All right, I think I'm going to get out
of here, folks. Have we done all the
giveaways today? I think we have,
haven't we? Trying to remember. Brain is
fried.
Check the swings quickly.
Yeah, we still look good.
Where's Netflix trading at? Still not
the 70s. Want to add in those 70s if we
can get there.
Oh, that doesn't look so good. Where are
we trading that there?
Oh, I don't like that. I might cut USA
rare earth here.
I might have to cut this. Let me have a
look.
Where's it gone
on my watch list? Is it over here?
Looks all right.
1936.
We're We're okay. We're still above 20s.
That's all right. That's all right. I
got worried there, thinking I'd way
further down.
Okay, great to grace still rotation
still.
You're on stuck shorts from 180. Am I in
trouble?
Uh yeah, at a moment you are in trouble.
Definitely.
Remember the the short was up here
covering into here. The ad would have
been here. We don't add in front of
volume. You are definitely in trouble
right now.
Doesn't mean it doesn't let you out. But
if they want to come up to here,
they can.
Like I said, I think the short will
happen in here. All right, we've already
done it once. We keep failing up here.
If they want to swipe, trap lots of
bulls in and short there, they will. You
should not be holding through that pain.
If you're a short 180, you've already
been run out like what? Eight
70 points. What are you doing holding
that?
Uh we do do some stuff on the DOM. Yeah,
in the course in the volume profile and
orderflow course. Yeah, I show you how I
use it. I mainly use it for delta. Um,
but yes, if you're using What do you use
for it? You use Bookmap? Yeah, then
definitely. It's in there. I'll show you
what I use. What platform do I use for
swings? Uh, mainly 212 because I use my
uh tax efficient account in the UK and I
also have one with uh Trade Station. I
actually have a few. I have some other
ones as well, but there's nothing really
in them. Don't use them actively.
Do I see sell 25 265 265
up here? Yeah, this is the kind of area.
Look, they've just held that dip. What
did I just say? If bulls want to step
in, they have to hold this now. Think
about this, right? They have to now hold
this and complete this. This is the area
I think we will peter out in. It might
be that we've already peted out. It
might be that they would want to do one
more pump and then do it. But definitely
this is the area I think the market will
struggly struggle to get above. I really
think it will struggle to get above that
today. And I think the main move is back
down to here. And once you find
acceptance under here, it's to search
back into these lows. This is for me.
This is a pullback. We're now starting
to go sideways. We are building out
liquidity here. If they do a failed
breakout of this, that will be really
nice for you in the afternoon. I will
not be trading the afternoon. But think
about this. All right. If we do a failed
breakout of this, trap buyers, sell back
in, reject, that is an easy sell, isn't
it? Because then we will use all the
liquidity to move lower. What would that
remind you of? Let's look at the high of
day. What we did
failed breakout reject
breakdown reject sell same thing build
liquidity build liquidity trend.
All right, we are now building liquidity
out for them to be able to use later at
the moment.
made 1,149 today. That's what happens
when you experience with shitty penny
stocks for you. That That's it, mate.
I'm with you, buddy. I'm with you.
Do I only trade mornings? Yeah, pretty
much. I mean, if there's setups in the
afternoons, I go there. Deep charts is
good for volume profile and footprints.
It is. is I don't use it, but it is.
I've heard a lot of people really enjoy
it. I have a 212 Iser in the UK. Can you
keep buying and selling shares in an
ISE? Yes, you can. If you you move So,
if you've got a 212 Iser, open up a 212
share Iser. All right. Stocks and shares
Iser. If you leave your cash in there
and do not trade, they will still give
you like 3 or 4%, right? For the for the
positions you don't have on, you'll
still earn 3 or 4%.
But, you know, the S&P and the QQQ and
stuff like that should give you at least
10% a year. So, you can position
yourself into some good stocks and ETFs.
Look, I'm not a financial adviser. Take
what I [\h__\h] say as a pinch of salt.
This is what I do. I position myself
into ETFs, all right, on discount and
hold it forever in my Iser. I use some
of my ISA to position myelves into
stocks and some of it into speculation
stocks where like for example we hit
last year uh where was it? What did we
hit the big winner on? I'm looking for
it. I'm still holding a share. Let me
open up open. We hit open for a 500%
winner.
All right. That small position alone
made me 5% on my whole account. Right.
Which is more than you're going to get
from a bank.
But you got to know what you're doing.
And I'm not I'm not a financial adviser.
So speak to a financial adviser.
Could the course be okay for me if I use
a test? Yeah, for sure. It's it's
principles. Do I do options? No.
Sometimes leaps, but nothing else.
What type of account? Oh, it's for it's
for British citizens called an an ISA
stocks and stock stocks and shares ISA.
Discord paid. It's not like paid, but
you have to do the course. Look at all
these sellers stacking up here, folks.
Into lunch. Look at 6275 87 all stacking
up. Uh it's 100 lot, 100 lot, 100 lot,
100 lot. We've got 400 lots stacked
between 62 and 87. They're stacking up
at the point of control right now or
above it. 62 to 87. Yeah, right in here.
So, there is 400 lots passive just sat
here hoping that they get filled to do
that at the moment.
During pre-market, I trade small caps.
You mentioned how bookmap is
specifically useful for small caps.
Could I explain why? Yeah, totally.
because in small caps are heavily
manipulated. So unless you're really
really really really really good at
using the level two and tape. All right.
If you are trading something, say you
are trading something, I'm assuming
you're a short seller if you're trading
small caps. Am I making that assumption
right? Let's say you're trading
something gapping up
one under 200 300% whatever. All right,
gapping up and you're looking back
historically. Where are the bag holders
stuck? Right? So you're marking out that
level where the bag holders are stuck.
Uh you will see them on bookmap. They
will have their limits there. Thousands
and thousands of shares be sat there and
you'll see where the walls are and
you'll see where the buyers get trapped
above it. And then you can use their
pain to go the other side. And uh you
can always watch Ross Cameron and make
sure he trades into those guys and trade
the other side of him, which is exactly
what I used to do.
Yeah, it's like a IRA. That's it, Hal.
That's exactly what it is.
Uh, Delta's just sideways right now.
Delta's matching this pretty well. Just
sideways,
not making highs.
In fact, we've got passive, to be
honest, we've got passive selling
showing up on the Delta. We've got
passive selling showing up on the CBD.
like
because we're we're not we're not
actually breaking out anywhere up here
on CBD. So, we're we definitely have
passive selling which is what we expect
in this in this area.
Oh, you pay small caps long.
You're the other you're the other side
of me, mate. So, what are you So, what
are your what are your rules, Enzo? So,
if you're trading small caps long, what
are you looking for? Are you looking for
stuff with no dilution
on a gap up with a decent press release
that you're you you just think you can
get a squeeze on?
And what are you looking easy to borrow
so they get more shorts trapped? If I
was looking for a small cap long, I'd
want it easy to borrow. I'd want a
really low float.
I'd want not too much dilution,
like no uh no warrants, no offerings at
the market waiting to be used.
Uh yeah, Alison, yeah, definitely for
for the flow zones. Yeah, it's in the
course. You probably just got to work
your way through the course. I build you
up until we get to it, but it's there.
Small caps are sketchy. They are. I
mean, I talked about yesterday. I've
taken some fat bad losses in the small
cap world.
Just trapped there on me going sideways.
Doing nada. Doing nada.
What were my trades today? They're the
two on stream.
Uh I got stopped out of this one, but
this is what we're looking for. 110s.
And ultimately the target's down here if
we can get there uh this week. Uh I
can't remember where I got stopped out.
Was it here?
I had it stop at 33s or something. Or
was it 13s? I can't remember, folks.
Might have been this [\h__\h] Was it this
[\h__\h] I might have got stopped out
here on the runner. Oh my god. So, I
only locked in 50 points and I got
stopped out there on the runner. And the
best cover. I think most guys got 110s
110s, which was the area. 110s to 140 to
110s, which was originally the area. So
most people got 200 plus points. Alex
didn't. That was the trade. That was the
main trade today.
Let's trade here. I think I took a
squeeze earlier as well. I think I took
a long
here. There was a long somewhere here
earlier today which was very very quick
and very early on. So I was saying to
the guys, don't don't follow me because
of that. I think it was just this for a
retest because I saw the shorts get
stuck. Didn't make much money out of
this. was 34 point. Yeah, that would
have been that one there.
Those were the trades. Short squeeze
long sale after leaving volume. Uh first
attempt at this and now we're just
ranging.
Yeah, I agree. Hope I agree.
If it doesn't close above 300, where can
you expect price to go? I'm still in
sales from 219.
Um,
give me a second.
All right. This is what I'd be watching.
I'm going to tell you the same levels
that you're watching.
Volume point control is key because
we've had big big participants here. If
you lose that, we're trading to 173. If
you lose that, we're trading to 150. If
you trade under 150, all right, it is
very possible that this cluster of
buyers here who are not a small size,
right, these are big big players, you
lose 150, there is a very good chance
you trade back down to 290. If you lose
290, we are looking at these blocks down
here. Okay,
I would love to see this get to 24,800.
I'd love it not to do today because I
don't really want to trade anymore
today, but it is possible. But I would
be covering into some of these
imbalances. Look, we're going to visit
visit it very very soon now. All right.
So, Alex is going to be proved right.
So, you have to wait and see. Now, 70s,
50s, can we get value low acceptance
under that? We can then think about an
expansion model. It's not ideal, but
let's have a think about where we get on
an expansion model today if they go for
an afternoon sell.
Oh, look where the 1618 is.
I wonder if they've done that on
purpose.
right at the naked previous week point
of control. All right. So if if we do an
expansion model under here, you are
looking for this guy here, whether it's
today or tomorrow,
right? What a surprise that they've
calculated it absolutely perfectly to
get into that if they do an expansion.
What made me go short? Where? Uh,
Maro, I don't know which one you're
talking about.
Buyers are getting absorbed. Yeah,
probably. I mean, they they want to
force this down. They would need to get
a break underneath 50s and then really
it can start flying.
What was the screen with those buyers?
Uh, Ninja Trader, uh, I use a a third
party software called Twin Peaks. Alex,
do I think the order flow course is good
after the advanced course? Yes,
definitely. Definitely. It will improve
your entries in my opinion, but uh, ask
the guys in chat, ask guys in Discord,
but a lot of them are finding a lot of,
uh, a lot of edge now from it.
From who did I learn to trade? I've been
in too many rooms, to be honest. I
learned how to not trade from most
courses I did.
I've already gone over gold, dude. I've
already gone over gold. Um, yeah, I've
gone over it. I've We're going to It
looks to me like we're going to do a
failure to follow through on GC.
Right. So, we went over this earlier,
but I'll show you again. This is the
edge of volume. You can see I've still
got it drawn out. If price cannot find
acceptance over here, if we keep
rejecting here, I would imagine you're
going to see an attempt to roll over
lower. All right? So, I would be more
comfortable positioning short here,
looking for this move. All right? And
I'll be covering some as we move down
and then holding runners in case we
trade lower. If you find acceptance over
this shelf, all right, if you're looking
for a new money long, you must find
acceptance here. It must basically do
like a one of these and find acceptance
here and then you can look for that
breakout. Uh the easier short is
definitely on silver. All right. Gold is
a much better hedge to what's going on.
But I would not be long up here right
now. This is you are asking for it if
you get long up there. Honestly,
180 trap shorts could pay out soon. 180.
Um, I don't think so, mate. Let me have
a look.
No, I don't think so.
I don't think so. It's just a big level
all over. I don't think there are many
shorts trapped here right now. You're
trading at previous week close here.
Like I said, 150 is the level. You're
starting to already lose 170. So, you've
already lost 189, you're losing 170. 150
is the next level. And if you lose that,
then all of those buyers are going to be
way out position. All the big buyers we
talked about that were coming in here in
clusters. All right? If you trade under
this, they are all going to be out of
position. They will all be hurt. Right?
Then you're going to have all this
volume here and here trapped because
like I talked about, here's your main
trend. Here's the pullback. Here's the
liquidity build. Here's the edge of it.
If you leave this, you will try and
revisit the lows.
Why I said I would not be long up here.
Like, I just don't think that is a play.
But you guys manage your own book. Don't
be like the guy earlier
saying it's my fault he's lost.
Can we set them for a re-entry in the G
in the gray box for a re-entry short?
Yes, you can. Yes, you can. If they fade
away from this and they reject it,
right? If they fade away from this and
they reject it, you need to see buyers
come and get trapped here and then you
can resell it down to here. It's not the
best. It's great momentum. It's not the
best location on the day, is it? The
best location on the day was here or
here like we talked about. But if they
do that, it is a valid trade. But they
must stay heavy versus this.
Yeah. Yeah, I mean I the reason I get
upset, guys, is I feel like I give a
huge amount of education and energy here
each day and I have people question it
when I'm I couldn't be more clear about
this stuff. Like I really try and help
you guys and when I have it shoved in my
face, I find it offensive. That's what's
that's why I get stressed because it's
like I'm teaching telling you what is
going to happen before it happens. I'm
giving you like really as clear
explanation as possible. You've already
hit TP1. We are now failing 150. All
right, we're now failing that big
participant. If he becomes overweight
and out of out of pocket, all right,
this guy here, right, we have huge
orders. Look at these guys here. If they
become out of position, we will fade
back down, guys. All right, we will be
looking for the 90s and then low of day
and and a crack. All right, why? Because
it's a pullback. It's just a pullback.
This is a pullback until it proves
otherwise.
always remember please like even when
I'm not here failed breakout
creates liquidity
leaves volume
retest volume leaves it aggressively
dumps
pull back what's the main move who's
trapped buyers trapped high of day we
are looking to sell we are leaving
volume here are your short opportunities
here are your cover opportunities now
you can hold runners because you have a
good position
And if you didn't get that or you want
to add, you can look for an ad here if
it trades under and rejects and you can
look for that ad lower or the ad to
trade lower, right? But you can cover
some here now and you can hold some for
lower day and expansion. And like I
said, we did the fib. It's very possible
we come into previous week's point
control. I really hope it doesn't do
that so I can get this trade tomorrow,
right? Because I'm not feeling up to
trading much more today.
Oh, but the thing is, Zach, those people
are here every day. They are here every
day.
They are here. Yeah. You need to trade
away and reject this box. Correct. You
You don't want to just enter. you need
to trade away from it and reject this
box because if they reclaim all right if
they do this you do not want to be short
right because we can dance back in here
but if we reject this now you're looking
for a trade back down and you can look
at these nodes here and here and here
but remember you're now into lunch the
volume's going to be very low now
you think it's the language they can't
comprehend what I'm talking about what
too many big words I try and really like
You might be right in. I try and really
simplify it though. I really really try
and simplify it.
It's fine, Mike. No, like you don't have
to say sorry. It's all good. You're here
to learn, right? You're here to learn.
And I will get [\h__\h] wrong, guys. I'm I'm
a human being. I will get get stuff
wrong.
Why one minute over five minute? Uh I
use both dude. I use both. So on my
screen I have a one, a five, an hourly
and a daily. And over here I have a five
five55. But over here I'm looking at ES
Spy, uh QQQ and VIX. So I'm I'm looking
at all sorts all the time. It's just
when I'm looking at where we're for
execution, I want to be on the lowest
chart possible, right? Because I want to
have accurate execution. All right? If
I'm going to risk versus this and put my
stop here, I want to have accurate
execution. I want to see who's trapped,
where they're trapped, to trade lower.
All right? So, the lower the time frame,
the more accurate I can be with my
execution. My bias does not come from a
one minute chart.
I don't trade off tick charts. I've
tried them, but I just it's fine. But
it's each to their own.
What tool can you use to find trap
buyers and sellers? Uh you will need
footprint or or like a level two. You
don't have to use footprint, right? You
can use like can quite literally use
this, right?
Use the depth of market. We can see
there's a buyer stuck here at 120 lot at
67. Sellers are in control at 170.
There's a buyer stuck at 173. We can
keep going up like you're going to see
what I'm talking about. There's another
buyer stuck at 188. There's another
buyer stuck at 190.
There's seller in control from 200. See
what I mean? So, we're talking about 100
lots which are way, way, way out the
money. There's another buyer stuck at
220. Another 100 lot. Right? So, you
don't have to use footprint. It's horses
for courses. But if you not trying to
sell, I'm really not trying to sell. Go
and do everything on YouTube first for
free on my YouTube. But if you are
interested, I teach you all the ways of
finding it in the volume and order flow
course on my website.
Nice gak.
Are they still stacked up at 260? Yeah,
they are. They are they they're just sat
there waiting to get filled. Uh here you
go. See all these guys? 100 lot. 100
lot. 100 lot. 100 lot. Right. They are
stacked here hoping to get filled. And
you got a buyer down here at the 110s.
Right. And let's have a look. Let's just
have a look before I leave if there's
any big boys down at like the point old
point of control. So 25,000. We have 140
lot. Oh, look at this. The old point of
control. We've got 130 lot down there.
So he knows as well we do have a player
up down there. Let's have a look upside.
Do we have anything above these guys?
No, we have a clear book. We have a
clear book. 26,000. Don't think we're
going there today. I don't think we're
going there today.
All right, I'm going to get out of here.
Uh, I'm done for the day, folks. I will
try and be in Discord later. Um, gray
zones, they're just they're just areas I
mark out based on volume. All right,
thanks for joining, guys. Thank you for
being patient. Thank you for everyone
who bought the positivity today. I
needed it. I promise you, I really
needed it today. Uh we go again
tomorrow, right? We go again tomorrow.
Just keep locking in those base hits.
When we get the 100, 200 pointers, it's
great. Until then, you just keep locking
in. And uh let's see what we get set up
for tomorrow. Hopefully, we get some
continuation trades, which would be
really nice. Peace and love. Use hard
stops, be kind to each other, all that
good stuff. And uh yeah, take care.