All
right, morning team. Welcome back into
Thursday. Nice cool CPI print this
morning. Oh, let's close that.
>> There we go. Is that better? There we
go. Brilliant doubler. Okay, cool print
this morning giving this market a much
needed rally back inside. So, as always,
we're going to start on the daily. All
right, starting on the daily. You can
see very clear inside bar yesterday. Big
sell. Uh in the afternoon, we had some
continuation. Almost made that uh 800
level. We did get outside this little
shelf here into 37.
Um and we've tried to dip outside that
this morning and not. So market finding
a reaction in here. If we think about
the bib of the swing points right now,
right, we found a bid off the 61. We did
talk about that yesterday. Probable if
we weren't going to find a bid here, the
next levels were here and here. So we've
started to find that bid off that 61
fib. Uh now we can think about where
this leg could possibly retrace to. All
right. If we're going to create a new
bare flag and liquidity, probably into
350s. if we're going to go for the 50%
probably into 500s. Both of those are
major major confluence areas. All right,
major confluence areas. So, let's go in
and have a look at that.
If we look now into the hourly charts,
make sure you can see enough of this.
All right. If we look in the hourlys,
you can see this is the developing
profile from the week. All right, this
is current week. It's still developing.
What we have is some big liquidity
created down here yesterday. We've left
good excess at that low, right? So, low
volume node left underneath previous day
point control into previous day value
area low. We are starting to bid back up
off this. We are into or we have gone
back above that low volume node right
here. Bulls have a chance here. I'm not
talking about I want to be clear. I'm
not talking about a protrend move, but
bulls have a chance to do a bigger
pullback leg. All right? Because your
swing point, right, is from here to
here. If we think about this swing
point, we are from the 500s down into
these sort of 880s or wherever it is. We
are already coming into 61 fib. So, our
ideal location to long is not here, is
it? We don't want to long here. This is
into a 61 fib. And we have point of
control. We have this thick contested
level from the week. All right. Maybe
this acts as resistance. Maybe we just
do this in here. We have to see because
every time we've come into there, we've
chopped. If I wanted to be bullish
today, where would I want to be bullish?
Well, I'd want to leave every bear in
the previous day's range, which is down
here, trapped, right? So, if I'm going
to be a bull today, even for the
retracement leg, I will want a pullback
to hold previous day area high. Maybe we
don't get the pullback. I don't know.
But this is my thesis today. What I'd be
looking for previous day value area
high. I'm going to get rid of this white
line. We don't need that anymore. All
right. Previous day value area high
which lines up with this low volume node
at very worst 25100 25,090. All right.
So pull back somewhere into 25,150
25,100ish.
You need this to hold. If you're looking
for the move back upside, you need this
level to hold. So if this level holds
right and we get back inside previous
days range, it means we're holding the
current weekly uh value and maybe
there's a return back in towards 350.
This will be a TP point. All right. So I
would be taking a good chunk of my
profit off if it gives me something like
this. Good chunk of my profit is coming
up into that because I expect it to get
stuck. It might very well slam it back
down from there. If I get lucky and we
find acceptance above, then we can think
about that trade all the way up to uh
25,500.
And maybe this becomes an ad. If there's
a break, break retest and hold, that
becomes an ad. If this morning we do a
straight drive up, all right, if we do a
straight drive up into this, you want to
be very careful about thinking about
longs. Right? If we come up into this,
even if we peek over and you start to
see a rejection back under that node, do
not be surprised to see them slam this
back down. This might look like nothing.
That's 250 points. You do not want to be
the wrong side of some of these moves,
okay? They can happen very, very quick.
Why am I saying that? We're thin in
here. We're thin in here. We're thin in
here. That can re repric very quick if
it wants. So, just trying to make you
aware of that.
It might be that we don't do a look
above and fail. It might be that we just
bang into it and instantly get rejected.
Um, I don't really want to take that
short. I'm actually more interested in
waiting to see how we react down here.
It buys me a bit of time to get a feel
for the market this morning. Letting it
build out some volume. All right,
letting it build out some volume.
If we get back over PC, all right, and
we start to hold there, you need to be
careful because this is fair value for
the last well since Sunday open. But if
they start to hold this and bid, can't
rule out that move here. All right, this
move here to use this liquidity. Cannot
rule that out. Remember the pro trend
right now is down. If we zoom out,
the protrend is down. You have I mean
what I would call about as clear a
channel as you can get. Have we got a
channel on here? Pretty sure we've got
one somewhere. There it is. All right.
About clear as channel as you can get.
Right. That's your channel. We're coming
up to the top side. All right. So, we
want to see if this holds, finds
respect. If you do this move, maybe you
get that move outside of it. If we just
bang into that and they reject the
channel, then I'm looking to see if we
hold a bid there. If we come all right,
this is very much like yesterday. If we
just drift down here without tapping
into that and we come into yesterday's
range, I don't really want to trade in
this, right? are really uninterested in
trading that. If we reject that, come
in, reject that, then maybe I'm
interested in playing that rotation. But
if we don't do anything, if this is just
like a mediocre 61 and we come into here
and we start doing this, well, no thank
you. I don't really fancy do I don't
think we're going to do that, but I
don't really fancy doing that. Okay,
let's have a look at what we did in the
GlobeEx session then.
And you can see right here. Oh, don't
move that. I'm going to need it.
We went sideways
after protecting the previous day value
area. So we tried to break down numerous
times yesterday. Uh we did trade that
upside uh in Discord together. We were
waiting for that retest up here. It
never came to sell back down. So we
traded this upside Globeex. We held this
level here. All right. This level here
held. This is your key level. This is
where they've rotated from basically 100
p.m. yesterday all the way into 2:00
a.m. So, they spent about 12 hours, 13
hours in here before finally breaking
out. They held the retest in London. We
go sideways for a bit into this key
level, which is previous day. Uh, no,
current week value area low, sorry. CPI
comes, call print, upside we go. All
right, so it's looking to retest this
area right now. Look how big this move
is. We don't really want to try and long
up here. We're running out of room. We
really want this to come back down and
offer offer us a re long up. That' be
the nicest way to get long in this.
Okay, moving into lower time frames.
We're going to go through ES, the ETS,
gold, BIX, all the good stuff.
Okay, I'm going to take this off because
I can visually see whereabouts that is
without it.
All right. Yes, same kind of story.
You can see it's doing exactly the same
thing. So inverted sort of head and
shoulders, left shoulder, head, right
shoulder, repric into range. There's
your old range. It's trying to find
acceptance. We might rotate if we get in
here, right? Don't be surprised if we
rotate. If they find a reaction here
this morning and sell this back down and
you're looking to see if it holds the
800s, if it holds 800s, you're looking
at dips. Um there is a massive gamma
level. We're going to go over it on the
spiders,
right? 670 is huge. In fact, so big.
Let's just make sure we draw that on.
Right. Huge [snorts]
put wall.
Huge, huge, huge, huge, huge put wall.
They do not want price under this right
now.
I'm going to set a price alert as we get
close to it as well. If we lose that,
it's game over for the market. All
right. It's that big.
Sorry, just mark this up so I know. Put
all. All right, so 670 massive level.
Uh, guess what the level is on Q's? You
can probably have a pretty good guess.
It is 600.
All right, cool. Wool. Put wall here as
well.
Sorry about just setting these alerts
before I forget.
Okay, so let's go back to spiders so you
can have a look at the ETFs. Right, we
found a bid of that put wall. We're
coming we're already coming back into
this old range. So again, very, very
similar to everything else, right?
You've got a channel. It's a very, very
clear channel down, right? You've got a
channel. Every time we're coming up one,
two, three, four times, we're fading it.
We're finding dips on the bottom to
trade back inside. I would be interested
in this mean today. All right, you might
be like, well, it's midpoint in the
range. It is, but it's more that we've
left sellers stuck underneath it. If
they hold that, I expect them to try and
do something like this today, and that
will be the target. This is big supply.
We don't want to be long up here. We
want to be long from the mean if we're
going to play it up into that.
Same story on the Q's. All right, it's
going to look very, very similar, right?
Interested if we can hold the mean of
this channel. if we can get up into this
so I can sell some into it and hold
runners in case we go willing like I
talked I'm willing to play this back
downside if we have a failed breakout
covering some into the mean but I do not
want to get short into yesterday's value
near the lows where those shorts are
currently stuck VIX let's just zoom out
of this a minute because these have all
moved around
right you can see we're Still in a range
in the VIX really. We are trying to
build.
This is kind of dangerous, right? This
is the area I said every time we come
down into here, we tend to do these like
pretty drastic moves out. That looks
like a bit of a swipe. Now we're stuck
in between sort of let's just call it
18s and 16s. Really no acceptance below
16s and we're sort of coming into the
mid part of that. So it's a bit messy to
be honest on the VIX which is expected
into roll over and opex. Do not forget
we're in a roll over and OPEX week. All
right. Options are going to become more
and more key as we get through this
week. Let's change these levels. Um, we
can set a price alert on VIX up at 18.
And if it starts breaking that
VIX upside breakout, then we need to be
aware about market starting to roll over
if we're going to do that.
Uh, let's have a quick look at gold.
It's still looks like it's in that
range. uh for that person that's trading
it and asked me last week or earlier
this week. All right, you're still
developing liquidity in here. All the
time you're holding this, you're
bullish. The target will be alltime
highs, right? All the time it's doing
this, it's trying to build it to get to
alltime highs. So, you're holding dips
versus 300 looking for expansion. So,
it's like TP1, TP2. If you lose 300, uh
it's a problem because it's an inability
to break out and then this liquidity can
be moved used to move down. I'm going to
have one really quick look. We need to
be aware of this carry trade which is
coming in in the next 24 48 hours
move starting to do drifting down. Let
me just check and then we're going to do
the mag. I'm running out of time here.
Okay, that's pulling back inside. Let's
have a quick look at the mag.
Held the lows on Apple gapping up but uh
inside previous days range. Amazon
relative strength. That's a good drive
away. That will give the market some
juice. So if Amazon breaks 27s, that's
pretty good. Google, same thing. Gapping
up, leaving the bottom side of the
range, leaving those shorts who are late
trapped. Same thing on Meta, leaving
late shorts trapped. Same thing on
Microsoft, although it's a little bit
more messy, but it's got a liquidity run
to do here into 480. So be watching
that. But again, gapping up, leaving
shorts trapped from earlier in the week.
[sighs]
And
Nvidia, same thing. Shorts trapped down
here, back into its range. It needs to
reclaim 75. So, we can set price alert
here for Nvidia. Uh
uh
bullish
reclaim Nvidia. And then Tesla
needs to do the same thing. Needs to get
back above 81s. All right, we just
missed 500. What you don't want to see
is see this this and then that lose.
What you need to see is this hold and a
reclaim for it to go again. So overall
MAG looks pretty good, but it's uh it's
all gapping up. So the easiest thing
will be if they pull back this morning,
that'll be the kindest thing for us. If
we see a nice early morning pullback, we
can hope for it. Like whether we get it
or not is another thing. If we bang
straight into this, then um we have to
see if we're going to do a look above
and fail or what kind of thing we're
going to do.
Does the mag move after hours? Yes, it
does. After hours and pre-market.
All right. Morning everyone. Morning.
Morning. Morning. Market about to open
here. Right. You've got 30 seconds left
for the market open here.
What do you mean? How does the mag move
in after hours from people trading it? I
don't I don't understand that question.
Be very careful. Right, we've developed
one of these here this morning. It would
not surprise me for a little push fail
and a fade back inside. So, I definitely
don't want to be long where we are now.
It's a even if it starts shoving up, it
is not a good location to be long out
of. So, ideally, they come back down and
offer us a dip down into here, but we
will see here this morning. We will see.
Good luck, everybody.
If they're just going to go on a violent
rip, it's going to be a little bit hard
to get involved if they just want to go
and test that supply with lost location
to be bullish up here. The RR is not
good. Doesn't mean it doesn't go up
there. It's just in terms of riskreward,
it's poor.
It is poor.
Here's the shove. So, trying to get up
to previous day open right now and the
current point of control like we talked
about and how we act here is going to be
key. Are they going to get above and
base above or are bears going to come
back in and say no no no no. Down you
go. It's a big big supply area.
Uh yeah, I know uh CC I use it on a 30
minute chart actually the periodic
but I don't use it on uh
on the weeklys and monthlies. Maybe I
should, maybe that would be a good idea.
All right. So, into and around
this point of control. 340s is the
level. 330s, 340s.
And you're seeing some rejection up
here.
And an alert on video. So, Nvidia
already having that uh that big cross
already moving back into its old range
right now intowards the 75s and got
rejected from there.
So, it tried to move back into its
bullish range. It found a bit of a
rejection. If it gets back inside that,
it could be strong. But so far, no. All
of the MAG looking good other than
Apple. So, I'll give you a readout.
Tesla 3% up or just under. Nvidia 1.82%
up. Microsoft 0.75% up. Meta 1.92% up.
Google 1.79% up. Amazon 2.11% up. Apple
0.08%
up. Trying to go red to green. Uh we
want to be bullish today, but we've lost
the location. The location got eaten up
in that CPI. So for me, I just have to
wait now. I do not want to get long into
this uh weekly point of control where we
have found a lot of resistance and it's
very very messy. If we get through it
and hold that's a whole different story.
But ideally they reject this offering me
a really nice juicy dip this morning to
play into.
SPY coming up to its five day by the way
and uh or sorry ES to its 5day. SPY
coming up to its 5day and its 20-day.
Where's the 20-day on ES a little bit
higher for that mean reversion. VIX
getting uh absolutely dunked on here
this morning dropping under 1650. Let's
see if it gets down into those sort of
1580s and 16s. Come on market come back
in for me. Be really kind. So all the
way back down here would be really nice.
You can watch this New York open if
you're a very aggressive bull. We could
watch that New York open. I'd be very
careful about buying up here. Apple
starting to sell now. I really want this
market to come back in for me. I'm not
looking to short. All right. But it's
possible there is a short. Maybe you see
something like this offering this. But
I'm going to focus on trying to be long
down here if it offers it.
If it offers it. So far still holding
that New York open.
Nice patient. Morning
sloth. All right, here's your New York
open. So, they're dipping back into that
opening print.
Nvidia not able to get back through 75.
So, big rejection there. Apple now half
a percent down. There's your New York
opening print. And if we start losing
this and start putting in a lower high,
there's a possible rotation down to
here. It's why I didn't want to buy up
in this red box. Couldn't have made that
clear enough to you. Way way way too uh
dangerous. I would like to be a bull
today though. Ideally, I'd like to be
bullish today.
Big reaction on uh ES into that five
day, right? Just got smacked at 850.
It's already 10 points down off that.
So, you need to see if and when bulls
are willing to come in. We're very very
frothy up into these levels.
Do we repric all of CPI? M into here
would be nice. It would be really nice.
It might not do it. So, Be careful
watching this New York open.
Hello, darling.
Thank you.
All right, building out a bit of a shelf
here. I'll get some volume on this in a
minute. Just let this build out for a
minute. Building out a little bit of a
shelf here in in and around this New
York open.
Yes, losing its New York VW up.
Come on, come down, market. be really
kind to me. Come all the way down.
Down you come.
Right. So, for those of you who are
looking for a short, you would want to
see a lower high and a wash. Now,
you rejected uh point of control. What
did we say? 330s in Discord. I've missed
it by two ticks. Okay. So, we're
starting to see what we talked about in
Discord.
And if this comes down, I will dip to be
involved in Washington internal low.
just that New York opening low. I'd like
it to wash a bit more than that,
but maybe not. Here's the return back to
uh New York open here. Got a little bit
of a feeler on just in case. I'd much
rather buy much much lower. Oh, copy is
not working. Let's get that on.
There we go. Still have it. So, that's a
bit useful. Okay. Out of this because
the copy is not working. Let's see if we
can get down into here now.
So, I'm watching these sort of two. Oh,
it's different on here. What is this
saying?
Have I done that wrong? [sighs] I've got
yesterday's value area high on Ninja
Trader at 208. Don't feel like that's
correct. What's this low? 88.
Well, that's correct.
Okay. Look at the difference there.
So, I'm going to watch 200s, 160s, and
100s to see if they hold. And I'm going
to watch to see if they reclaim that New
York open. We have a very clear shelf
there. I'll put some volume on.
All right. You can see, like I said,
very clear shelf here.
Shorts will want, bears will want to
force a lower high in here and cause
that. If they reclaim this though, they
will get caught. I'm going to wait for
somewhere down here.
Apple in a big sell. Rest of the market
looks okay.
I just need to see if they can find a
bid on the rest of the market right now.
Back into this shelf again.
Keeps banging into this shelf. Question
is, can it get back above 280s? Here we
go. So, rejection of current value area
low.
Oh, thank you.
still into this little shelf.
Good morning, SFC. Morning, everyone.
Smash that like button nice and early,
folks.
See if they wash this down
to previous day value area high. Um,
does anyone have val Where have you guys
got value area high? I've got it at like
208 on Ninja Trader and 160 on here.
It's quite I don't mind 10 20 points
difference, but 40 plus points is a lot.
40 plus points is far too much. All
right, they're going to try and get back
onto this shelf. There's a big shelf at
280. It's where bears are in control
from at the moment.
You have it 210. Yeah, it's okay. So,
this one might be wrong. So, I have
Ninja Trader at 210 as well. So, I'm
going to double this up. All right. Just
so that we're aware. It might be that
they protect 210. We don't know, but
it's worth being aware of. It's worth
being aware of.
And that is the level. It's a bit like
yesterday. Bulls will need to hold
previous days value. All right. So,
we're starting to see some bears get
aggressive here. And they're not getting
the move down the snap that they want.
We have some bids on the tape all the
way down to 200. Here we go. Right. So,
maybe let's see now if these bulls want
to defend previous day's value. This is
where they need to come in. If they're
going to defend it, folks must come in
around here if they're going to defend
previous day's value.
So, we'll be looking for bears to get
trapped down here and to see a reaction
from someone absorbing the tape. If we
don't see that, then there is simply no
play at this level and we have to wait
for a move all the way down into 100.
And if you've been bearish off that
rejection from the highs, you're looking
pretty good right now. Really good.
So, 95 is losing. We might come all the
way down to 100s, but if we reclaim 210s
or around there, be interesting. Bears
flying in here. Apple's the one in the
big sale right now causing major major
problems.
Waiting to see if there's a reaction. No
reaction yet. Just strong selling.
We had rejection from that red box back
down to previous day's value area high.
Waiting to see if bears get trapped down
here. here. Not seeing enough traps yet.
Starting to see a bit of absorption
here. We haven't taken out that 75
player yet, though. Here's previous day
value area high. Do they go for a
reclaim and a scream? Maybe. Watching
this carefully now. We know this is the
area. If we were bullish, this is the
area that they would want to see them
defend. We don't see them defend this.
There's not a lot we can do with it.
Still no defending of it. So, that 175
player rebidding down there is trying to
drag the market down. And they're adding
lower. This is dangerous because they're
adding lower. They want to drag this
market down.
Now they're adding at 150 and 137 and
125. They want this market lower right
now. Just be careful here, folks. Until
we see a strong bid and a strong
reaction, I'd be very careful about
looking for any move back upside.
Yes, doing much better.
Nice reaction off VWAP. Okay, here we
go. Let's watch this now into 210s. Do
we have excess down there at 85s? A
little bit. a little bit. We have a low
volume node at 25 right now. And if we
start really reclaiming 240, it's off to
the races. So, let's see. Do bulls have
a go here. We're starting to have a go
here. All right. Here's the low volume
node into 25. Can we re bid over this?
No, is the answer. So, still holding
that low volume node at 25. They need to
rebid over that. The bulls to have a
really good go. They got that door shut
in their face at that low volume node.
This little node right here. [snorts]
So that's definitely the overunder right
now. And uh 200 is big sellside delta.
All the time they're under all the time
we're under 200. Bears are in control.
They want to fill this guy at 75. He
keeps rebidding down there at 75 trying
to drag the market down. And now he's
bidding at 62 and 50. So little
concerning that we're going to go all
the way down to be up here, I would say,
because they're trying to use big size
as a magnet. He is starting to lose a
bid. Apple's still in a cell and Nvidia
got absolutely hammered from that top
range. So, nothing here, just a backside
move. If you took the short here or here
for the lower high like we talked about,
congratulations. I am waiting for this
long to come in and it might be that it
doesn't come. It's it's possible.
It's possible, but this is the area
around here if it's going to come, but I
need to see some strength.
Still haven't filled this player at 75
who's playing games. He is playing games
down there.
I'm on the H contract. You will be able
to tell by the price on the side.
Everyone who asks that, right, just look
at the price. They're very different
prices.
We rolled over on Tuesday. As soon as
the volume rolled over, we rolled over.
They're still trying to bid at 75 and
50. Little concerned about a flush
coming to fill these guys.
I'm not sure we're ready. I don't think
we finished this auction lower yet.
Yes, it's weak as well. Very, very weak.
There's the spy
76es. We know 75 is a big level.
Still waiting here. I'd love to get
long. Just waiting to see something to
give me some interest.
Maybe a reclaim of value. What I don't
like is these bids below us. I do not
like how they played. We definitely have
some shorts trapped for the first time
today. 85 though.
Remember, we've got to watch this low
volume though. That will act as
resistance all the time. They're
rejecting that. They can still shove
this down. I don't like this bids
underneath. If we can get over 200, we
have delta offside. And if we can get
over 25, there's a potential squeeze.
Watching this carefully if these guys
actually want to play ball.
I can't get up to that low volume even
even up there right now. VIX has done a
spike back up to 17. So be careful.
Come on, market. I'd love to be bullish
today. Either swipe lower or get going.
Don't just sit here. Nothing I can do
here right now.
I hate that they're adding liquidity
lower. It does not make me think this
auction's finished. Point of control
right now for this session is 88 now.
And everyone is bearish underneath, but
they keep adding liquidity lower again.
They [\h__\h] doubled up that size
underneath.
Messy start to the day based on what
they're doing with the volume.
This is where bears got stuck where we
are now. 85 and under. And I'm not
convinced right now that we're not going
lower. If Mr. 75, Mr. 150 pissed off,
I'd maybe think that we were done, but I
don't think we are.
Trigger for me would be
10 125 basing above that probably. We
did just leave those bears trapped again
into point control. So 85 is stuck. Here
come the bulls and slammed in their face
again. So this 10 and 20s, I'm watching
this now to see if we're going to break.
Have they actually got any strength
here?
Can't get over this little low volume
node. Can we get over this low volume
node and start attacking upside
175 still on the book down there? He's
still not left. I don't like that he's
not walking up.
Tricky, tricky.
Watching these 25s. That's the low
volume. Rejected it again.
Rejected 25s again.
And that's 7 Mr. 175 still there. Big
rejection of 25s again. Don't like that.
Mr. Mr. 175 hasn't walked up. So, we got
to get over that low volume node and we
need Mr. 175 to stop being a bit of a
prick hanging out down there because
he's trying to attract the market down
to him and he might well get it. Bears
are stuck underneath 85. But if we've
just rejected low volume node, if this
is a lower high, oh, don't do that. This
is a lower high, we might very well come
and sweep. Oh, you're going to not let
me teach now today either. E, we might
very well come and do one of these,
which we're starting to see happen.
There you go. [\h__\h] hell, mate. This
is all because this player at 75. Oh,
and now he's left. What a [\h__\h] What an
absolute [\h__\h] I knew he was going to be
a dick today. You could see it.
[laughter]
Oh, what a bell end. He wants price much
lower then, does he?
Let this [\h__\h] mess around. Right, he's
gone to 160 now. Let's see if he gets
himself caught. Still not in. I'm
watching to see if we expand through low
volume node. Then our join. Here's low
volume node. I've got to see us close up
above this now. Starting to join in
here. Starting to join in here. We need
to hold price though. We got to get
through this and accelerate. All
starting to get trapped through at 36.
Want to see acceleration moving stop
into the money.
What a knob that guy at 175 was. There's
always some [\h__\h] on the tape early
in the morning.
Okay, so long from here. uh watching
VWAP. I've already taken a big chunk of
my uh position off. Really, we want to
hold over this. Otherwise, I'm out.
Okay. Out here already. And if we rebid
this at 210, I'll be interested in
taking it again on a reload. If we lose
210, I'm not really interested. I know
there's a guy playing games on the tape
today. So, I want to be careful until
he's done playing his games. I want to
be careful. Here's the red dip into 110.
Now, do they hold this? If they don't
hold this, be very, very careful. It's a
good dip. Good hold so far. There is a
bid there at 14s. I know. And he's come
back on at 75.
It's iffy, man. It's iffy in here. I'm
going to tell you. I'm going to be very
honest with you. We should be bidding
back off it, but they couldn't get
through this low volume node. So, bears
are in control. We're underneath VWAP.
This here is holding us down. I'm flat
right now. I wanted to see if we held
tens. We didn't. It's possible they come
back down into this and this. Look at
them adding at 75 and 60s now. This
guy's trying to attract the market down.
I need at this point I actually want the
market to flush everyone out. I think
they've built a lot of people in here.
It would it would actually be beneficial
if we flush everyone out. Bare flag.
Yeah, absolutely. That's is what it's
currently looking like, right? Because
they had the opportunity here.
Where's to dip and hold this and do it.
They couldn't do it. So, they should
come and run these out. But bears are
stuck here, right here into current low
90 to low. Well,
94s into the lows. We have excess. But
this guy keeps adding lower. So, he
wants the market lower.
So, I can show you. I'm pretty much
flat. All right. Just a couple trading
at the moment together in a little
bundle.
It might be we come all the way down,
which is fine. If you're short, you've
looked very good that failure. This was
the short really. And uh there's value.
So, let's see.
Let's see.
Shorts coming flying in. Not getting
much of acceptance lower here. We're
pretty close to VWAP. Same on the ES. Uh
shorts did just come flying in. If we
get back above 91, they're all going to
be trapped.
Is he adding lower again?
62s. He's at right now. 6250s.
75 GX magnet. Yeah, def definitely. I've
got the whole thing marked out.
Let's battle down here. The bulls are
trying to bid off this area. They're
trying to hold previous day's value.
So this was the interesting. This was
the level I had on Trading View and this
is off Ninja Trade and Trading View
level just held. Weird
weird weird weird weird that there's
such a big um discrepancy between the
two. [snorts]
All right, watching again. Same looking
at the same thing just to see if bears
get trapped down here. Not going to be
aggressive. Just waiting to see if they
do. If they do, we can play upside
because it means we're not having
acceptance into previous days uh value.
That's all I'm looking for. I'm looking
to lean on previous days value to see if
bulls want to hold it and control it. If
they're not willing to hold it and
control it, then there's no play here.
And uh the next level will be down here.
All right. So, if bulls want to sort of
do something like this, there's a play
back upside. If they fail this, this is
the next side to check. If we're going
to fail that, I don't want to play. This
is my no play zone down here today.
Don't want to play in yesterday's
levels.
They're still in control. 62 is still
the level right now. No rebidding 62s.
We're pretty [clears throat] close to
VWAP on ES. We're under VWOP on spiders.
So, you got divergence there.
No, don't change that. Thank you. All
right. Bear's getting stuck down there.
Still not repric over this uh 210s.
It's still bidding at 62s. Still can't
get over 210. So that's your rotation
right now. 62 to 210s. If you get over
210, your rotation is to 240s.
Guys, you keep like
which contract? NQ. Please guys, please
use your eyes. Look at the side. Look at
the price. Look at the contracts. Big
difference in price. You can see it
really easy. Everyone's rolled over now.
If you're trading the old contract,
you're way behind on volume. Here's the
reclaim. Looking to see if we can
squeeze. Watching to see if we can close
back above 210s and 220s. If we can't do
that, there's no play. But if we can
close back above, I am interested in it.
Watching very carefully with this
divergence between ES Spy and V1.
Spy through it. He has not had it yet.
Don't like how we built this out, but
hey. Coming into VWAP here.
Yep. Okay, let's go then, baby. Let's
go. If we're going to go through it, we
got to go up into it. Yep. Yep. Yep.
Lock some in. Let's see if we can get
it. Are you going to offer any more
into this low volume node again? They've
got to hold this node and accelerate.
Otherwise, there's no play here. Come on
then. If you're going to go, you've got
to go. Stop [\h__\h] around this morning,
please. Market.
Beautiful. Go, go, go, go, go, go, go,
go, go, go, go, go, go. There's value
high on the session. Let's go
accelerate. Accelerate. Accelerate.
Taking some off here cuz we're
stuttering into the 50s. I want to see
acceleration now up to 7980.
That's my next TP. And if we get through
that, we get going. Really nice. ES has
already done that move. So ES is already
into its New York open. That's why I'm
locking in some profit. If we get back
over New York open, New York session
goes red to green. So far, they're
defending it. So locked in most in this
drive.
I keep moving that accidentally.
Really nice. They're still holding. Just
don't let this come back below 37. Now
we've built a little shelf there at 37.
Low volume node. Still down at 25. So we
need to hold above this node for bulls.
Do not definitely don't want 220. 220
where I came back in. Don't want to lose
220.
Looks good. They're going to try and
accelerate here.
little shelf up here. They're trying to
accelerate. This is the ES New York
Open. They want to accelerate back
through it. So, what they're attempting
to do at the moment is to accelerate
through this New York Open. They keep
getting stuck here on the ES. It's a big
overunder.
Here they go. Last attempt. If they
can't get through, I'm going to cut the
rest. They've got to go and they got to
go now.
You got to go and you got to go now.
Come on, baby. I've only got a little
bit left. You got any juice? Yeah, let's
go.
Let's go.
All right, bit more off there. Big
reaction. I'm going to wait now for a
reload if we're going to come back down
and fill.
Only a runner left now.
It's getting frothy up here. Big big
battle here.
We should go 80s if they're going to do
the same move, but ES is uh going under
over under over. It's getting rejected
now. out. So let's see if they rehold
this dip now. So this needs to be held
as a dip for buyers
if we're going to go back upside. All
right, that's your sentiment is this low
volume node. Buyers must hold this dip
for rotation. We went into value area
high on the current session. All right,
so no look below. No acceptance under
here. This was previous day value. I'm
going to remove this because this must
be wrong. So trading view was right
today. The 160s. So we came W shape into
previous day's value high. If we hold
this, we should accelerate. This is your
TP
and then up here. It's why I wanted to
be bullish today on pullbacks.
They are desperately trying to
accelerate, but they're they keep
getting stuck up here. Once this uh lets
go, there's probably a swipe um upside
into 80s, but it's a big if button.
Maybe right now.
I hate that this buyer is still down at
175 and not jogging price up. Don't like
that. What is he doing?
Sellers coming flying in here. So, back
down to this low volume node and VWAP.
Buyers must hold that low volume node
and VWAP otherwise they will get caught.
here.
[snorts]
Delta doing delta still up.
Have one more go here. They're holding.
You wonder if they need to do a little
reflush and then bid it back up at the
moment. [snorts]
Getting
stuck here at value area high on the
day. It might be a rotation here.
Yeah, balls need to defend this.
Nothing's changed. [snorts]
Lots of bears coming in here and we're
not moving lower. So, someone is
absorbing this tape up here. But if he
gets out the way, there's a flush. I
want this to still accelerate, but just
let's see. Can they get up to 80s?
They're going to have one more go.
Tapping, tapping, tapping, tapping on
the 65s. They can't get through value on
the day right now. That shelf up here
holding. Once we get through that,
there's probably acceleration. Here we
come. Here we come, folks. There's the
acceleration. Here we come. Can we get
80s and then a price above 80s?
Come on. Give me my [\h__\h] TP. Go. Stop
[\h__\h] around. Sorry, my French.
Very close to this blue line. That's my
TP. And then I'm runners for up here.
Come on. You How much you missing me by?
You bastard.
Sellers have lifted. We should go. They
just lifted. They're readding here.
Sellers keep adding and then lifting.
Come on. Don't make me take more off
here. I've got nothing left. Come on.
Yes.
Let's go.
Planned out beforehand.
Even in Discord, right, folks in
Discord, let's think about what we've
just done. Right. What did we talk about
this morning? Where was the dip to? What
was the pathing? All right. All drawn
out. We're looking good. Here was the
pathing into previous day area high. All
right. And looking for that move back
into 300s. We're close to it now. So,
locking most in. Really nice way
on a Thursday. Nice. Nice play, guys.
Nice play. Lock most in. You're holding
runners now to see if you get
acceleration. The one thing I'd be
watching in like some of these mag are
not able to reclaim some of these supply
levels. So, you want to be careful. Like
for example, 175 on Nvidia tapped in in
the morning drive slap back down. We're
still green, but we might need to build
out some more.
We might need to build some more.
So W's in chat if you got that with me.
If you're new, guys, if you're new here,
sorry that like there's probably a lot
to absorb. All I'd say is stick with me
for a few sessions. Watch all my free
videos. It will start to make sense what
I'm looking for. You tr truly you need
to be here at 9:15 Eastern time in the
morning. All right, from 9:15 to 9:30, I
talk about the trades I'm looking at. I
talked about today. I'm not going to
take it, but I would like to see price
reject here. Maybe set a lower high.
There's your trend line and a reaction
down to previous day value area high.
I'm going to look, I've very clearly
said to grab longs either from this area
or from this area under here. I had a no
trade zone, but I was looking for a
bullish move back into here. I did tell
you guys if you want to play the short,
it's probably going to be from there.
I'm not going to take it. It's really
important if you if you get here
pre-market. I literally draw it all out
for you.
So, let's see. You got it. Lots of you
getting. Look at this acceleration.
Really nice. All right. So, you're
looking you want to be taking some off
if you've got any left into this level
of 320. Right. If we get acceptance over
this, I'm going to show you higher time
frame while
why this is an important level. Right.
If we get an acceptance over value not
just from today or point control sorry
not from just from today but from the
week. All right we need to drive an
acceptance over it then we can think
about this repric up here into 500 but
there is just as much chance they do a
peak above and they get slapped down
which is why you must pay yourself. This
is a huge volume area from the current
week. All right so you must pay yourself
as we come into 300. You basically you
did just get it. All right you just got
it. So I would be out 80% of your like
play now. I'd be out maybe even more
than
uh let's see who got it with me. Took it
took some time to let you know that
buyer was playing games this morning. He
was playing games.
Project X gone down again. I mean
we talked about it yesterday, last week,
a month ago. put a short out on it.
So, who got it? Who got it? Who got it?
Keeping safe got it. Jonah got it. Scott
got it. The truth not hate got it. Dave
Davis got it. One21, Steven W, John
Dennis, Nick, Aiz, Ty, Luca,
uh,
Mochamad, not sure how to say your name.
Sorry. Jeff, wish it would show your
proper names. 72 Off Sweet, NEC, Haley,
Ghost Hunter, Dave Davis, Ronald Rosco,
Sarah, Keeping Safe, Shiz
Fresh Videos, W. I needed that after the
last few days. Good, good to hear it, my
guy.
Tyson got it. Eddie got it. Luca got it.
Jeff got it. Lowhanging fruit. I love
the name. I love the name. Sigma. Bulls
make money. Bears make money. Pigs well
they get slaughtered. Yeah. Never a true
saying. Chris Thorne got it.
Uh Jolo, I can go over that in a minute.
Boat got it. Sailor got it. That's
funny. Boat and sailor, two different
names. Reby got it. [laughter]
Tells for joining my friend. Julian
Otus. DJ Noah,
it's not a tick chart. It's a one minute
chart, buddy. Gray Kitty got it. Lou
Riley got it. Mono Peacing got it. Aiden
got it. Really nice work. All right, so
we hit we hit the level we were looking
for. So this sort of New York open, we
can still it's possible they still be
bullish, but we can develop a range here
now because we know from the current
weekly all right, from the current
current weekly profile, this is our
point of control. This red box I
expected on the first test to get
rejected. All right, maybe they reject
it again. Maybe we base over and hold
and then there's a re long. All right,
but bulls the reason one of you asked
why was I long bias? Why was I long
biased? If we zoom out, everything
starts from the higher time frame. This
is why you need to get here in the
mornings. All right, we have already hit
a 61 fib to the downside. All right, so
we are in deep discount. All right, deep
discount. We're on discount based on
profile. We're a discount based on fibs,
right? And we
are not getting acceptance under this
shelf. All right. If bears wanted to do
this, they would need to smash us back
down. We're not seeing that. We've
reclaimed it. We're an inside bar. I
expect liquidity to be built out today.
And I expect dips to be holding into
these key levels. So daily for me was
bullish rotation. All right, bullish
rotation. Not bullish, bullish rotation.
If we then go to the hourly chart. All
right, we talked about what price did
yesterday.
We have these big nodes. All right, we
have a at the low failing to auction
lower. All right, we left some nice
excess. We repriced. We drove away from
think about this. Think about if you
were short in here. All right, if you
are swing short in here, who's stuck in
this market? Swing shorts from down
here. All right, bulls up here are stuck
or bulls in here are stuck, right? And
swing shorts down here. So we expect
price to probably move between these
levels and these levels. These are the
current rotations, right? And if we find
acceptance above, we're going to go
between these levels. If we find
acceptance below, we're going to go
between these levels. But what I know is
the person in pain right now is the
person who got short thinking the world
is going to end. All right? That person
is the person in pain. So that is the
person I want to abuse this morning. I
say that in a light manner, right? In a
light manner. That's who I'm going to
abuse. Once we reclaim previous day
value area high, remember this is
previous day's value.
This is current week's value.
If we are going to hold these levels
here, I'm going to expect a rotation
either in here or in here if we find
acceptance. All right. So that means
everyone from here is trapped. So I want
to be bullish all the time they're
trapped. That's not to say you can't
sell this like I talked about in the
morning drive back down to these levels,
but for me it's more likely that we're
going to see something like this. Maybe
after the two-leg they resell it. Very
possible. But it's more likely that
we're going to abuse these people at
least to start. So that was why I was
going to say I said I was going to leave
the short and focus on the long after
the short. Plus, if you rewind it said I
say and it's going to buy me some time
to see what happens. So the bullish move
I said I'm not going to take the drive
opening drive into here because the RR
is too bad. There's your trend line.
There's the liquidity built. This is the
level that we were interested in. We can
delete that cuz that is incorrect. So
trading view coming up clutch this time.
This is the level that we were
interested in and this level. So we were
interested in 160
and 25K if we had to but I really didn't
want it to get down there. So 160 and
opening drive, right? They all come
flying in. They get stuck at current
weak point controlling supply. We get
boom, boom, boom. All right. Everyone
who bought late out the money. Perfect.
I'm watching in here and here to see if
bears get stuck. We move to this. Zoom
in. Show you what I'm watching. This
candle right here, we create excess.
All right. So this is the first time
like okay well bears are starting to get
stuck and then they try again here.
That's the transition. So I was watching
200 220 220 was the key trigger for me
was around here. All right. And once we
started to see this I'm long for the
acceleration
and then out. All right. So it's the
same level.
You pair that with the volume profile.
Right. The same level with the volume
profile. 220s. Where was the shelf? Get
rid of all this. Sorry folks. Where was
the shelf? Right here is build out of
liquidity.
Do this as just gray.
Did we have acceptance below this? No,
we couldn't close this. This is where
those shorts came flying in and got
trapped. The moment we start to break
this level, especially through here,
because they reject it once, now we've
got more shorts piling in again. Once
we're going to get through that, we're
going to see acceleration. So, go back
and rewind it. I know once we get
through that it's probably going to be a
breakaway to the upside. ES was leading
the charge which which helped us as
well. Right. So that's why we were
looking for that. Hopefully that makes
sense.
Hopefully that makes sense.
Um
do you have your bookmap settings
anywhere? They're just standard, mate.
They're not they're not even uh
different settings. Uh there's no like
special settings for them. Um, the only
thing I change is the the DOM. Uh, I I
want to see the delta and price before I
see anything else. So, I know like 250
right now is a control zone for bears.
Um,
how do you see previous day value? You
draw it out. Yeah. So, your 930 levels.
We're getting back into current price in
a moment, right? [snorts] So, you would
go from
into 4:00 and you would just draw that
out and then mark it. I don't know why
it shifted but uh there we go there or
thereabouts. 178 one it was 160 earlier.
I've probably drawn it off by a little
bit probably what happened. Yeah, you
just draw it out and then you mark it
with your horizontal lines. Um go
go on my YouTube there is a free video I
think it's called like volume profile
mastery or something like that. Go and
watch that. All right. So now we're
going to get that build out of liquidity
like we talked about. All right. So from
current we point control to here. This
is why I was long from here and they can
hold this and look for an acceleration.
They can also lose this because now we
can build out a huge liquidity day. So I
would say that probably the easy money
is gone. If they're going to hold this,
bulls are going to need to come in here.
Think about the W acceleration low
volume node. Bulls must hold this. And
really you want to see them get back
above that. The problem now is how we're
building thick levels everywhere. It's
going to get harder and harder as we get
through this day.
Uh stacked yet, I h I have them, but I
have them showing on Ninja Trader. Yeah,
I do. I do. I do. I do.
Sure. I can see all of this properly.
>> [snorts]
[snorts]
>> Um,
is the live recorded? Well, uh, go it go
it sits on YouTube forever. So, yeah,
you can come back and watch this
anytime. Okay, back down to value area
low on the day. So, back into this big
node. So, bulls have not defended that
low volume node. That's not a good sign.
It's a very bad sign. They had the
opportunity to v to defend it. They
haven't. You're going to see rotation
and this looks a little bit weaker now.
So, back into value area low on the day.
This is the last chance saloon I'd say
for bulls to start absorbing price down
here and try and make a higher low down
here. But the way we are acting today
just looks like a rotation. I would not
be surprised to see this just develop in
a big old fat D-shaped profile for a
while until it makes some decisions. So
maybe like a look below and fail and
maybe a look above and fail, which we've
done twice. It really would not surprise
me uh because the move off CPI has been
so big. The move down yesterday was
massive. We repriced it on CPI. We're
probably going to go sideways for a bit,
especially with OPEX. It wouldn't
surprise me.
Uh yes, Indie absolutely could be a
rotational day. Yeah, absolutely. And
like the easiest way to see that, the
easiest way I would say the the first
clue, where's my OBS gone? The first
clue, right, when you're thinking what
kind of day are we in? What where are we
in versus yesterday, right? That's your
first clue. Yeah. So, we're an inside
bar. There's clue number one. Probably
going to need to develop chop. Clue
number two is normally after big moves,
we need to develop liquidity. Yeah.
because we can't just keep doing this
and this. The only time you have that is
if there's like a big news event, COVID,
for example, um you know, if they
announce here, oh, we're in global
recession. AI's [\h__\h] the world. Yeah,
sure. We're going to go panic mode. But
if when it's normal normal price action,
you will see like maybe big days
followed by inside days, big days
followed by inside days. It's how we
build liquidity. Big days followed by
inside days. Yeah, big days, two in a
row here, followed by an inside bar.
It's how we build liquidity. So, that's
your first clue. Your second clue
is the rotation.
Your second clue is this, right? We're
in
current week profile.
We're creating a Dshape here. I know
it's the wrong way around, but we're
creating a D-shape here, and we are
above yesterday's profile. So it's very
possible we move we can move value up
right it's if value was here yesterday
it's possible we move it up we might
move value here but what did we do last
time we were here stuck stuck stuck
right so we know in here is likely to be
messy if we come beneath here we might
come and visit these lows but I don't
really want to trade that down there
ideally we talked about earlier I don't
really
for for bulls they need to defend these
100s I'm not really interested in
trading.
Not really interested in trading in
here, right? And technically
I'd need to see bulls do that. If we
don't do that, um, it's very possible we
go from here to PC. I don't want to
trade it because of how we've built
this. This is a [sighs]
trying to think how I can frame this.
This is a possible move. This is a
possible move.
This is a possible move. I don't want to
trade this one.
That's the one I don't want to trade
today. I'd rather miss that trade. Stick
to my rules. Yeah. Doesn't mean it's not
valid for you guys. If you like trading
from one side to the other, it might be
really nice move for you, right? Don't
let h I'm here to teach you, but I also
have to trade how I know I make money. I
make money sticking to my rules. I hate
playing back inside ranges unless we've
had a huge failed breakout, which could
argue we've done, but hopefully that
helps.
Uh Eddie, yeah, I I only really are
interested in it from the New York
session because it's where most the
volume was done. It's where most the
volume was done.
Okay, so back into this little ledge,
this gray box.
We might build rotation in this gray box
again for a little minute.
Right, we might build in here. Right,
there's your value on the day. There's
previous day value very low. Can they
find acceptance and go back in? And this
is will this act as resistance for
bears? All right. Or the bulls just
reclaim it and we go right back upside
in a rotation. So, it's going to get
messier and messier until they start
making some big decisions.
But value for the day just held for me
on Ninja Trader. Value was down here at
180. So, that's your current value area
low on the day. So, at the moment, they
are unable to get back beneath that.
Bears remain trapped under 82s right
now. All right, that's where the bears
have been trapped. So, they need to let
them out if they're going to look for
expansion lower because we've been down
there 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 times
since the open and we're not seeing
expansion. If they can see expansion,
all those bears will be comfortable.
Right now, they are trapped underneath
82.
Oh, what did I say? I probably said it
wrong then, Scott. Yeah, whatever I
said. If
Excuse me, it's 7:15 in the morning. If
I got my tongue tied and I said value
area low and meant value high, then
switch switch them around. [laughter]
Yeah. I mean higher time frame we are
still technically in a cell right like
on the hourlys and stuff if you think
your pivot to pivot on the higher time
frame is you pivot high is 500 your
pivot low is 880 the question is in here
in those levels we are likely to build
out liquidity right that's that's the
day I'm anticipating if we think about
the main trend right there was your
previous pivot previous pivot built out
liquidity pivot pivot. What are we
probably going to do? Build out some
liquidity. And then they got to decide,
do they want to drag it down or are they
going to come and test this high? Right?
So, this is my anticipation today is a
buildout of liquidity. Hopefully, that
makes sense. A bit like this, right? How
we did this here. Very possible we do
this here because we can't just go down
down down like we talked about. This is
your pullback leg. We're we're coming
into key level 61. So, this is 61% of a
a weekly or a monthly pullback low. This
is a 61 retracement into here. So, we're
probably going to pull back off that and
then we're going to build out. I know
that looks messy, but
hopefully what you guys will understand.
If you're new to trading, you might it
might just sound like [\h__\h]
gobbleygook or something. I don't know
what you want to call it, but just stick
just stick with it. It will start to
make sense, right? They're trying to let
these bears out and come for this value
uh previous day value area high.
Is that what it is? It is. Yeah. Okay.
[snorts]
So, this one is incorrect. I thought I'd
delete that already. Maybe I didn't.
[sighs]
7:15 a.m. I'm in Los Angeles. Yeah, I'm
in LA. So, got that nice British accent,
but I live in LA, so it's uh very early,
right? So, you can see still protecting
value low. Still protecting previous day
value area high,
current day value area low. Bears keep
trying to get under 82s. Keep telling
you bears need to get under 82s. They
are stuck from here under 82s. If we let
them out, may maybe they get that little
wash, but that's where they're stuck.
VWOP's starting to sort of catch up. So,
you can see in here they keep this one.
There we go. They keep attacking these
levels, right? These bears keep
attacking
in
in here, right? They keep trying and
trying and trying and trying. That means
there is someone passively absorbing it.
Doesn't mean it can't come and fill
this. can, but currently there's
definitely a limit buyer or a market
maker just sitting here absorbing it
all. He might let it through and then
rebid it. We don't know, but there's
definitely someone passively absorbing
the tape every time we're coming down
into that right now.
I'd go beyond saying it's passive
because Delta is still going upside. So,
it's probably beyond passive. It's also
aggressive players trying to hammer in
here by the looks of it.
It's starting to sound like a SoCal
accent. Get out of it, JD. No chance.
Grumpy man this morning anyway from
watching the cricket.
FML.
If I've got any barmy army here, you
know what I'm on about. Geez. I mean, I
could moan about Snicko, but I want to
moan more about how bad we have played.
It is embarrassing.
Okay, looks like they're going to try
and let them out here. They're trying to
get a new low of day. There's still
someone bidding down at 150. That same
player 175, the same guy from this
morning. 175 162 150 is where he keeps
rebidding.
keeps rebidding.
[snorts]
Bears keep coming flying in down here.
They are not getting their way yet. They
are not getting their way yet.
Keep reloading. Putting more size on the
take down at 150 right now.
Yeah, London. East London.
Are they going to snap this? And are
they going to hold ES? Coming right into
its view up. Spies lost it already.
Still not at that uh 675 gamma
or spiders. They're still absorbing it
down here, folks. They are non-stop
absorbing it down here. Can't stay here
forever. Someone's going to get hurt at
some point.
Those bears just got stuck. [laughter]
They just got stuck. That guy absorbing
the tape was like, "No [\h__\h] way."
Back into low volume node. This is where
it's going to get a little bit messy.
So do they resell low volume node and do
bulls now try and defend 202s
is the question
the question
so low volume node here this is this is
the problem now for bears uh the bulls
is this low volume node they're going to
have to get through it
and so far they're getting rejected in
this sort of node so this We can just
delete this and VWAP. So that's the also
a key level. Yes, also into VWAP. So
we're going to see more build out of
liquidity here. But bears definitely got
stuck. Like I said, under 82s, they kept
getting themselves caught for whatever
reason. There is someone absorbing down
there.
Here goes low volume node
and we might accelerate if we repric
this. So the next level for rotation be
66es. So balls have a chance here uh to
do this dance or just go straight up on
a squeeze because they're all stuck. So
we did identify correctly these bears
being stuck and they have got themselves
in pain. So just like here, their pain
point here was up. Their pain point this
time was here and was actually around
95.
All right. So they got really stuck down
here and now they're getting squeezed
out and that's why you're getting a big
acceleration. We're going to come and
check 66s and then 78s and then back to
the upside again. So, you can see the
game of trap players. All right, so you
can see why I wanted to be bullish today
and these bears. Who was it in chat
yesterday? Um, someone asking me about
dips. Sorry, I forget who it was in
Discord yesterday saying they were
struggling with pullbacks and I said,
"Use your same analysis, but look for
the pullback level and trap players."
Well, this was the pullback level and
these were the trap players. I can't
remember who said it in Discord, but
hopefully that makes sense. But we are
in a rotation. All right, so you would
be TP here, here, here, and then
runners.
Mo, there was you. There you go.
Hopefully that makes today's a good
example, right? Today's actually a
really good example. Hopefully that
helps.
Do I ex do I look at daily high and
lows? Yep. Absolutely.
Absolutely.
Okay. Here's your New York open. So, if
you are long, if you got long in that,
here's your New York open. Now, dips.
You really want them to hold. You don't
really want them to let go of 66s. Now
we're going to start to see
acceleration. Like all those bears at
low of day are absolutely caught. So you
want to see acceleration now. So you
want all dips to hold. You do not really
want to let go of like 65 66es. Now if
you're bullish, if they hold that, it is
going to be a short covering uh
expedition and you're going to see a
squeeze out here to get long. So
continuation highs and if you get
through 300 there's probably a 300 break
and we can look for this move what's
high of day up into like this kind of
region. So you want this level here
really to hold to do that otherwise
we're going to be in a range rotation.
You do not want to lose this. If you
lose this you're going right back down
into this because we printed straight
up. If they lose this they will print
straight down. So they must hold this
for continuation. Now,
if you're long, you just want this to
hold in front of 66s. Here we go. So,
let's see if we can get acceleration.
Big delta coming in here at 88. If we
pop through him, he will be forced to
cover. Here we go. And we should get up
to 300 here. And are they offering above
300? Hopefully, they are. Seller just
left the tape at 350. So, maybe we can
keep moving up. Nice, nice, nice.
in that 300 that whole number big level.
We're still absorbing here, folks. It
still looks good for upside. Here we go.
Here we go.
Here we go. Let's go. Let's go.
Yeah. Beauty. All right. So, covering
some here or selling some here. And
let's see if you can get a continuation
now outside of this level here. And your
next spot is 330. And then we can start
really digging in. You never know, you
might get 500, but I would be taking 60
70% of your profit off here if you took
that last little dip in here to hold
that we talked about and just waiting to
see if you can accelerate through 30s.
And if you do, there is a chance. There
is a chance to come up to 500. There is
a chance. But we are back into that sort
of 61 fib. So you want to be locking
some in. This is the thick contested
area.
Thank you very much.
[groaning]
Make sure you're locking in here.
So, I'd say next level that they want to
hold is 80s. If they if they dip, they
don't want to lose 80s now, right? If
they dip at the moment, they've got no
reason to dip. If they dip, they don't
want to lose this. Right? So
again if you go and rewind underneath 82
I think it was I kept saying bears are
getting trapped there is someone
absorbing the tape the delta was
actually positive so interestingly and
then once these bears got caught well
they started to cover we went straight
up the only option to join was to on a
hold of this all right so your only
option to join if you didn't take this
break was really here and now we're
starting to pop this last level here and
then we might see acceleration so
through here we might see acceleration
but you want to selling again. This is
your current weak uh point of control
and you can see why I wanted to play
dips today. Hopefully that makes sense
why I was more bullish on this market
today. Buyers got trapped over 330
there. So I'd be selling some into this.
You can reverse off this now. Now we've
popped those stops.
Yeah, I just I just sold into this move,
mate. So, I can show you my last.
Haven't traded all of them today cuz I'm
waiting on some payouts to come through
and some approvals and some [\h__\h]
with funding ticks. Absolute [\h__\h]
Yeah. So, if you don't know folks, I
haven't publicly said it yet. I'm
waiting for them to reply, but uh
Funding Ticks doing some
retrospective raw changes and all sorts
of nonsense. So, I wouldn't advise
trading with them right now. Here
we go. Here we go. Here we go. Here we
go. Looking good.
So, the top side of this ledge on your
current week is 344s. All right. We've
got a low volume node over that. And
then we maybe trade 377. So, your next
target would be Oh, it lines up pretty
well with that, doesn't it? Would be
377s,
which is previous week low. So, if you
get lucky, you get a runner up into
that. Beyond that, we're looking at
500s. It's that simple. I wouldn't bank
on it because I'm expecting a rotational
day, but you never you never you never
know.
Uh what contract size would I recommend
for a 50k account? And two to three
micros is all you need to start. Two to
three micros, especially in this market.
You know, even
if you guys took the break out of the
trap, you're up 127 points. If you took
this little pullback here, you're still
up 60 points. All right, you like you
don't need size.
Oh, mate. CC, it's a joke, isn't it?
It's a joke.
Honestly, I want to be careful what I
said say right now. I'm going to I'm
going to give them a chance to reply to
me and reply to some other people that
are putting pressure on them. Um, if
they don't, then I will talk very
publicly about them. But all I would say
right now folks is unfortunately I would
not advise trading with funded ticks. I
have got a video probably going live
tomorrow or over the weekend on five
prop firms I would advise trading with
next week.
How much is my stop loss? All my stop
loss is dependent on structure. Is
always dependent on structure. So it's
not like a fixed stop loss. I don't
really like risking more than 30 plus
points, but sometimes like yesterday,
there are a couple times where I was
able to risk only five or six points,
which meant I was able to size up. So, I
forget where it was. Was it here? One of
these trades yesterday, I was able to to
risk like very very small amount and I
was able to get like three or four minis
on for this acceleration. And then where
did we trade into end of debt? Oh, it
wasn't here. Sorry. Maybe it was here or
here. I can't remember. I have to get it
up on Discord in a minute. But it your
stop loss should be based on structure,
not based on points because the market
doesn't care about how many points. It
cares about the structure of the trade.
This is looking good now. So we built
out a new micro node here. So I'd say
now you want this to hold. All right.
You're coming to the top side of this
red box. So you want to be locking in a
good portion of profit here. You want
this to hold and this gray box to hold.
You want to be locking in a good chunk
here into 50. Above that, you're looking
at sort the 70s.
We have got guys offering up into just
in front of 400, which is really good.
So, you might just get a big
acceleration here. If you get some
acceleration here, you want to be
selling into it. If it's like a squeeze,
you know, if there's big volume and you
see stops getting popped and we
accelerate, you want to be selling some
into it because we're coming up to that
top side of that weekly rotation.
Yeah, I've taken multiple payouts with
them. Uh 72, but um I don't know if you
saw, but basically they changed all
accounts yesterday where now you have to
trade for over one minute. You now need
over $200
for winning days. Um they changed loads
of stuff. Um and not just for new
accounts, for all accounts. And so
people that have gone for payouts are
saying, "Well, you only have five trades
of over $150. We just trade the change
the rule to $200." like, "Yeah, you
changed it today. You didn't change it
last week when I had those trades." So,
when I say selling some Yes. Yes. Sorry.
Sorry. Maybe that's not clear. I would
say if if I'm going to say about a
reversal, I'll make that really clear
and be like, "Look, we're looking to
short." If I'm saying selling some, it's
because we're long bias and we're
selling into the push. Yeah. We're not
get we're not trying to get short.
Yeah. So the difference is yeah funded
next. So lots of us reply to funded
next. So I have them on text being like
look this isn't okay. You need to change
this. You need to change this. And
they're actually pretty good. They'll be
like oh we didn't think about that. And
they normally like act accordingly. Um
Khaled from funding tick. I'll give him
a chance but currently he's gone
missing. Let's just say that. So it
doesn't look good at the moment.
Doesn't look good at the moment but yeah
let's not talk about props too much. I
want I want to make sure you guys are
making money.
And ES looking really good. So SPY over
its 5day 20-day. The next level for SPY
to trade into is that gamma level of
680. All right. So we're very very
close. Don't expect it to get over that
680 682s maybe. But you know, we want to
be paying ourselves on an inside day,
don't we? This is a big squeeze up. Do
not be chasing long up here. You see how
we didn't really build structure? It's
cuz they piled in short down here. So I
said like they if they get rushed to
cover, well the first one covers, the
second one covers, the third one covers,
and then you get all these guys down
here complete panic and that's why we
get a squeeze and it's going to continue
because they're not going to let them
out. But what will happen is if too many
buyers, right, buyers buy high, they
will get caught and then the dip will
happen and then they'll wash and then we
see if it rebids. But just be careful.
Do not be buying right at the high of
day right now around this point of
control. What we can look for is if we
see an acceleration here and then we
come back and hold this because this is
our weekly level then we can look for
that rotation to 500. It's possible we
can look for that today.
The truth not hate speech 7 the flow
that the analysis was impeccable by the
way. Hey awesome thanks man.
IB set. Yeah. Yeah IB right here. Yeah,
that purple line
[sighs] and we're starting to accelerate
here. I'd say into 400 looks looking
more and more good. So higher time frame
over point of control over this ledge
into this area.
So 98400
through there if you get lucky straight
upside. So you can see the why I wanted
dips today versus this to come up and to
repric this. I I expect the rotation to
happen between here today, right? This
will probably be the rotation. If they
want to go full bull, uh then they're
going to take out 500, but I'm not
thinking about that right now.
Structurally, we are still in a
downtrend, right? Like we talked about,
we're in a massive downtrend. There's
the build out down buildout and maybe we
lose this. Maybe we peak above and come
back down. Maybe it's the end and we're
coming back way way higher. But we can
deal with that tomorrow, next week.
Right now, we're just focused on each
level. So, here is the 70s and through
here is 400s.
So, it got stuck right there. Previous
week low, that little level on your
chart. We just had a reaction there.
Still think it's got a chance to move
higher, but you don't want to be buying
high. You want to be managing your
position.
Yeah, exactly. Coupe. Nice call. Yeah,
that green level previous week low.
Big big level. ES coming right up into
its 20-day as well. So, mean reversion
about to be completed on the ES.
Where is,
give me a second. Where's our 20-day on
the Q's?
So, 520 is our 20-day and 560 is our
50-day on the Q. So, I'm watching that
as well. So, this level here is a
massive level. It's absolutely huge on
every time frame.
Look at this big seller just stepped on
the tape here at 87. and he's trying to
unload 687 lots up here.
So, he's at 38750. He's trying to unload
687 lots. Let's see if we push into him.
Let's see if he actually fills or if he
lifts [snorts]
very close to that 20-day and previous
week low on ES as well. About to tap it.
So, you should have locked most your
profits in. Here we go. We're going to
drive to 87. Let's see if he's legit.
He's still there. He's still there. He's
still there. It's big size. He's still
there. Let's see if he holds. He's still
there. All right. He's a legit seller by
the looks of it. Oh, we're going to fill
him. You need to be taking profits into
this move here. All right.
Especially if we squeeze through him. We
will stop run and we will pop through if
he's legit, which he looks like he is.
He's putting a wall up. If we pop
through this, it might accelerate and
you got to be locking in. I'd be down to
to runners at the moment. He lifted.
He's moved out the way. He's not legit.
He just I was going to say something
rude. He capped his pants and left. So
here's the squeeze through it. So 400's
coming up. That seller was not legit. So
400's coming up. Here we go into fours.
All right. You should be out majority of
your position now. And if you get lucky,
you get fives. Now the only thing we can
now look at is a pull back into this
previous week or current week point of
control for acceleration up here. Again
guys in Discord, this was part of the
pathing. All right. Think about this.
Think about this. So we can look at it
right here. All right, we're into this
move here, acceleration. So the double
bottom acceleration into this and then
the last move is to hold this and get to
500. So we can think about that hold of
300 to 500. Now, right, if they do pull
back and they want to hold this and
build out liquidity here, we can think
about something on a lower time frame,
which might look like this. That's
possible today.
Really nice.
[snorts]
Alex, why were you interested in longs
for today? Is it because we opened above
yesterday's lows? Uh, it's because we
trapped shorts at uh at that lows
yesterday. It's because we trapped
shorts and then we opened above them.
So, [clears throat]
you've got to think not everyone in the
market is a day trader. Lots of people
are swinging traders. Lots of people
like to play the levels at the close.
So, if we build liquidity at the lows
and we open up above it, I want to use
them. I'm going to assume they're
offside. So, 400's here acting as some
resistance. You should be down to like
10% or something right now.
Yeah, top of the channel. Quite right.
We're going to see if this comes back
and it holds the sort of 300. The red
this red box basically needs to turn
into blue. All right. Something like
that. And really, I'd be looking, we can
sort of trim this down a bit. I'd
actually be looking at sort of 320
something around here. So, if they're
going to hold it, remember this is a
straight squeeze up, folks. If they want
to collapse this, they can. But what we
would like to see is a move into here.
And in here, you want to see sellers get
stuck and then acceleration to 500. If
they collapse this and they lose it,
then guess what? This will be a look
above and fail and we're going to come
back in this rotation. And I don't want
to play in here for the rest of the day.
So, either bulls hold this today or I'm
not interested. Um, we've made our money
anyway, right? We've got an hour and 20
left together. We will do a giveaway as
always. We can do some teachings if the
market goes to sleep. It's fine.
I'm green and just about tapping my
hands together to avoid buying. So,
green. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Don't Don't let
your mind trick you and be like, "Oh,
it's going up. I'm going to buy." Do not
do that. All right. Do not do that.
Chisna says, "I'm going to head out.
I'll probably be a regular. I'm enjoying
the commentary. Thank you for a good
day. Thank you for joining. Bringing
positive attitude." Thank you very much.
Yeah, exactly. Yeah, Coupe and Adam
seeing it. Yeah, you see the spoofing.
He was probably the same guy at the lows
today. Probably exactly the same guy.
Jonathan Alvarez. Alex, you're helping
500 plus people here. Thanks. You're
welcome, man. Thanks for joining.
Romo says, "I'm short." ENQ 25,333s.
25,000
333s. Um,
as in if we get back under that or are
you already short? I would say you're
the wrong side of this trade at the
moment, my friend, because we are now
looks like potentially can find
acceptance over that weekly PC. You
you've you've frontloaded that. you're
offside if you're already in. I don't
know if you're saying you're short when
you get up up back under it, but
currently it's not a good play.
What volume profile do you use? Uh this
is an this is anchored. This is an
anchored volume profile to the 930.
We're starting to bid over previous week
uh low here. 500s can still be the
target. I would like to see this pull
back to 300 to interest me at all.
Indie P is so much better than swing
trading on the NASDAQ. Swings can be
good, but you just got to place yourself
well. Passed another 50K account.
Thanks, Alex. You're welcome, Jonathan.
Seriously, great work today. You're
welcome, Greg. What was the hit rate of
my system? I have about a 68%
uh 68 to 74% on average.
Got about $300 on my tape Apex E evals.
Thank you. Nice, Dean.
Made 2K on minis. Thank you. Appreciate
the guidance. So much technical
information to learn. Massive thanks.
You're welcome, Sean. Thank you.
I have a look around the other streams,
but always end up here. Your commentary
is next level. Thanks, the dude.
Hello, USA New York here. Thanks. Happy
to have found your channel. I have a lot
to learn. [laughter] Welcome. Just just
stick around, man. Just stick around. It
will all start to make sense. What do I
think of the 25,400 level? I mean, I
wouldn't be playing upside from here,
right? I wouldn't be playing upside from
here. Think, think about where we are in
the swing leg. Always go back to the
higher time frame. Always, always,
always, always. For me, I always talk
about it. The hourly chart is my god
chart, as I call it. Whatever the hourly
does is what I want to do because
intraday trading, it's important. Higher
time frame, do we want to be long up
here? Think about this here. We've got
this little pivot. We know this can act
as supply. Not it will, but it can act
as supply. I don't want to be long. The
the best long, I'll be honest, was down
here. All right. And then the best long
was here. I wasn't up for CPI. So, we
had to play dips in. We don't want to be
a new money long up here. You want to be
selling into this push. You don't want
to be short because you're not seeing
something like this to short right now.
So, you're either in a trade and
managing the position or your cash,
right?
This is something I think newer traders
get confused with. You don't need to be
in a trade all the time. All right? You
need to wait for the trade to come to
you. You've got that spoofer back on the
tape here at 410. The only trade I would
consider now is a lower time frame pull
back into here, which I see absorb. And
I want to see shorts come flying in
here. And I want to see a passive buyer
absorbing the tape, soaking against
these levels for a rotation to 500. If I
don't see that, if we just come flying
in here and there's no absorption, then
I'm going to assume we're going to go
back into this range, right? And I'm
going to leave this alone. This would be
a look above and fail. And I'm going to
leave that alone. All right. Not that's
it. You would have heard, if you go back
to the beginning of the tape this
morning, you would have heard me say,
I'm going to focus on the longs. Oh,
I've just put you on the wrong chart,
haven't I? Here we go. Right. I'm going
to wait for this. And in here, I better
see sellers trapped. Otherwise, I'm not
playing it. Because if we just go
straight the way back down and reject
this, we're going to go back into range
rotation. And I'm not going to play in
here. Like I said this morning, my trade
I'm looking for is longs. Longs. All
right. I'm focused on that trade. I'm
not focused on shorts up here. I wasn't
focused on the short here, even though I
said it would probably play out. I home
in on where my edge is. My edge now is
being flat. That's my edge because if
I'm in a trade now, if I'm short now,
I'm short without structure. If I'm long
now, I'm chasing. So my edge now flat.
Wait, wait. Let it come in. Let it prove
to me, okay, it's ready. If it doesn't
get to my level, I haven't really missed
anything. Right? If this, let's say, or
you could say, you could argue, hey, you
should have added more size. All right,
partial partial partial out. If it
doesn't come into my level and this
keeps squeezing, I don't feel like I've
missed anything. My trade's happened.
All right, this trade's happened. I
don't feel like I'm missing this because
if I take a long here and that works,
that's chasing. I'm not missing it. I'm
not missing anything.
Yeah. So, let the trade come in.
Adam, do I think we've flipped to a long
bias? Uh, no.
No, not not yet.
Potentially, you know, the the the lows
yesterday and what we've reclaimed
today, right? Potenti potentially we've
come into that higher time frame level
that we talked about in the newsletter
that we said bulls will probably want to
defend. But if you look at the daily
chart and you look at the hourly chart,
they are not yet both bullish. Now if we
start
getting above 500, closing above 500,
holding bullish sentiment above 500, we
can we can talk about that maybe.
Can I chart BTC?
Yep.
Uh on on what kind of time frame you
looking at it?
[sighs]
Right, you're in a cell. It's as simple
as that. I've set like you're in a cell.
All right, that's your level.
You're building out liquidity right now.
You've got a look above and fail up
here.
You've got volume trapped from here.
Even if we want to do profile of let's
just say from this top side, right?
They're all stuck from here. And if we
do even a bigger profile,
let's do from the whole year.
Where's January?
We can do from this pivot.
All right, you're at the low end of this
profile. All right, this is your yearly
profile. If you cannot find acceptance
back inside of 96,
if you keep rejecting this area,
all right, it means everyone from this
year is offside and you are going to
search for lower prices until you find a
balance. It might be that you find a
balance in here, but right now bears are
in absolute control. If you see
acceptance back in here and it builds,
yeah, maybe you come back into one uh
110,000. But until you find that
acceptance, I'd be very concerned about
trying to find a bid in this market
because if they've deemed these prices
are too expensive, the only thing left
to do is to look for balance. And it
looks like the last balance range was in
here, right? Like really simple, right?
So if we can't find acceptance on BTC
back inside of here, we are going to
search back down into this range. All
right? because this is the last area
that we found balance in. Okay? So, if
we can't find acceptance back inside of
here, we will search down into there. I
don't care what the news says, what the
whales say, what anything. This is what
we're going to do. We're either going to
find acceptance and do this, or we're
going to not find acceptance and do
this. What we're not going to do is [\h__\h]
around in here. So, don't be the uh I'm
not suggesting you are, but don't be the
retail guy getting stuck because you
read some news article. I I don't know.
You know what I'm saying? Just just
trade the chart in front of you. Like I
always say, you got to trade what's in
front of you, not what you hope, you
think. You got to trade what's actually
happening in front of you.
When can you confirm buyers and sellers
are trapped? Do you wait until the
pullback
pull back above below where the trap
play? Yeah. So, what I do is I I'm
look for a level like this is holding
pretty well, this little low volume
node, but it's still too high for me,
right? So, I'll look for a level like
this is the weekly PC, right? So, I want
to find see if we can find acceptance
like anywhere here or even down here.
And then when I'm looking at this, what
I'm looking for is like what we saw here
to happen here. So, I'm looking for
strong selling to come in and be
absorbed. So, let's say we come all the
way down into 300, right? Which we can
see we've got an old imbalance down
here, right? Right now, under 300, we've
got these sellers stuck.
It's going to not let me draw. We've got
sellers stuck down here. If we see like
a strong red candle, right, and I see
buyers absorbing and this is all
sellside delta, and we start to trap
them under here, then we can use their
pain. It's all about using their pain.
That's all the market is ever about is
about using someone's pain. If I don't
see that, then I won't trade it.
[snorts]
Which prop firm do I think is worth
joining these days? I've got a video
about to launch on this probably
tonight, tomorrow. I'd say my top five
prop firms in no specific order. Um,
Lucid, Flex account, Lucid, uh,
Tradeify, that new account where you can
choose daily payouts
or payouts every 5 days,
funded next, Apex, TPT, in no specific
order. Those are your top five. That's
who I would be trading with next year.
Those are where you are going to get
regular payouts without too many rules.
I'm in two micros still from last night
at 25,000. Should I ride this whole day
out? I would have a stop point in mind,
my friend. So, you know, that's an
amazing trade. I would say you don't
want I would not want this to come back
below 260 and that means you're going to
give back another 100 points, right? So,
I would I would sell one micro now if
you haven't sold one. I would be taking
one off now. I would be looking for a
break of 500 to take the next one off.
Um, and I would not want this to see
come back under here. All right. So, if
you're basically swing long, you don't
want it back under here. You ideally you
want it to hold this, but I would have
already sold one into this move and
maybe you get this if you get lucky.
I think funded next if you're a beginner
is the best. I think Funded Next and
Lucid
both both the same and the new trader
fight they're all the same. They're
basically offering the same service.
Funded next uh Funded Next is really
good if you're beginner because it's a
onetime fee. Can take as long as you
want to pass. Lucid as well. Flex
accounts. Lucid. What is the indicator
on the individual candles? Yes, it's
footprint. It is footprint.
Hi, Alex. Other than you, what would you
recommend material books or otherwise?
Uh what are you
um I can recommend a lot of stuff but
what what are you looking to learn? Is
it psychology stuff? Is it technical
analysis stuff? You tell me what you
want to learn and I'll tell you who who
I think is a good trader and mentor for
you. No, I would not recommend top step
ever.
I've never tried my fun futures. I
haven't tried them but uh maybe I will.
I definitely don't look like Andrew
Tate. Do I look bold,
[laughter]
Mac? I'm on funded ticks. Yeah, I'm not
happy with them right now.
How do I see the upside target of 500?
Uh, it's the pivot, right? If you look
at the hourly,
where did we come from? Where did we go?
Where did we come from? Cot Joe, this
right here. Nice pivot. All right. So,
we're just runners up into that. We
might not get there, right? It's why we
were long for this move. We might not
get there, but that's your upside target
because that's the pivot. We get through
that, we If we get through that, only
two things happen. Fail breakout and
back into range or
break and hold and a squeeze. I would
doubt we are going to do the break and
hold and squeeze only because well if we
get there in the next couple hours we
are basically doing a straight slingshot
off the lows and trying to hold that is
very hard. It's more likely that we need
to build this right over the next couple
days but we can deal with that tomorrow
and Monday. We don't need to deal with
that right now.
What footprint do I search for? Um, it's
in your candles.
All right. Up here. See where it says
candles? Is that on your chart? Can you
see that? Just waiting for my stream to
catch up. Yeah, in here down to here.
Footprint. Volume footprint. I'll do a
video on how I set it up. But yeah, it's
you need the pro accounts. We are still
holding this low volume node here. They
are. Let me just zoom in on this because
I've been teaching you. Have we trapped
any shorts down here? We have. We have
trapped under 65 and 71. So all the time
you're holding 71 now, if they bid over
71, they might resqueeze this, but
you've got sellside imbalance that we're
banging into. For me, we haven't dipped
enough. It's very possible that they do
a continuation here. They definitely
trap some at 71 and 65.
So if you are long, you look good. I
would just basically say you don't want
it back under 70. So we're going to test
this guy right now into 71. They want to
hold him. If they don't hold him, then
they're going to test 65.
So this is the level where bulls need to
hold otherwise bears in this last 1 2 3
4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12 12 30 minutes would
be left out or let out sorry. So we just
tapped into Mr. 71. We're building delta
there
71 on the tape. Yeah. So you can see 71
as 10268 63 all around that level. But
we keep filling these cellside
imbalances into 85. So your range right
now is 70 to 85. That's it. I I need
this to come deeper for me to be
interested. I don't want to bid around
here. But if you are still managing your
position, it's okay for now. It's
starting to lose it now. So back into
the 60 now. Maybe the flush back down is
starting to build into this low volume
node that we put in.
We have to see how we act when we get
into there.
still holding that low volume node.
Still acting as support. They're going
to try and sell through it here. Just
watching. There's a bit of a dance on
the tape sign to develop. I'm still
waiting for this to dip down and come
lower. It might be that they don't come
lower and they don't let me join rejoin.
And that's also okay.
Low volume node. Low volume node. low
volume node. They're trying over and
over again. Here they come. So, let's
see. Can we get nice and deep? So, I'd
be watching 50s and I'll be watching 27.
Sellers got stuck there into that low
volume node again. Big reaction
instantly.
SPY, sorry, ES back under its 20-day.
SPY took out previous day high as well.
So, we want to be aware of that.
Lowhanging fruit has been taken on the
spiders as well.
Bro, how we get free order flow
platform? Um, well, you get order flow
on Ninja Trader and Trader if you're
with a um there's a video on my on my
YouTube. Just go on to it. It was only
posted like a couple weeks ago how to
set it up. You get free order flow if
you're trading with um any of the
platforms like Apex, TPT,
uh Lucid, they all have free order flow
with Trader 8 and Ninja Trader now. You
just got to know how to set it up.
How many rows on profile volume? You
either need to do a thousand rows or two
ticks in my mind. Which copier would I
recommend right now? Um probably
affordable indicators is the best copier
out there. It's a onetime fee. No
monthly [\h__\h]
Is level two data significant in your
trading style? Yeah, it should be like
once you learn to read the tape, it's
important. Otherwise,
it's fine when you start to trade like
to learn to see structure in candles.
You're starting to see a little bit of
absorption here into that low volume
node. But really, what really matters
is what's happening inside of those
candles.
They're banging on this node here.
So this is the battle. This is the
rotation. Sellers are trying to sell
against Can you let me draw it today?
Sellers are trying to sell against this.
Buyers want to buy dips underneath this
right now. In fact, this can really
we see can it can come all the way down
if it wants to be nice. Be a better dip.
Never used Lelu. Can't comment. can only
comment on people I've used.
How do you get order flow on Trading
View? Um, you will need to have a pro
account. I think it is
sellers just tried again under 60
getting caught again under 60. Look at
this guy reloading 500 lots at 380s. I
wonder if he moves. Is this the spoofer?
So, we've got 500 lot at 380, 600 lot at
410s right now.
Why do I feel like he's a spoofer?
No. Uh I don't think this is a short
right now [sighs]
for for me. Like even if Okay, maybe it
washes down into here, but look at the
print. Look what we're doing. Like I
think you need to if you're adamant on a
short, you need to see it let go of big
structure. You're not seeing this. For
me, this is just a back test of where
we've broken out from. Um so I'd be like
somewhat concerned trying to take the
shorts have got trapped all day. Like is
the location good? It's not bad. Is the
momentum good? I don't think so. I think
this is more likely to trap shorts to
move higher until we get back inside
current at least current day's value.
We're above initial balance. We're above
previous day high. We're above VWAP.
We're above um point of control on the
current week. For me, it's not a
location you want to be short at. We're
above current point of control on the
current week, the developing profile.
We're watching this 380 guy. I want to
see if he lifts.
Uh I'll give you a link in a minute.
Just let me watch this tape for a
minute, guys. Sorry.
We get back through there. There is a
squeeze. Let's thicken this up. They've
made it like this. I think there's a
squeeze if they get back through. I
really want to buy a dip down into here,
but I don't know
if we're going to be able to do it at
the moment.
Small liquidity feels like it's kind of
gone to sleep a bit here.
Just got the big players and that's kind
of it.
Everyone's left. What's going on?
Where were the last big sellers? 9 29s.
28s.
28 29. [snorts]
See, we keep holding this low volume
node. And what's interesting is this big
seller, these two big sellers are not
actually walking down. If they're
adamant on selling, they should be
walking down and they're not.
Here comes the building works outside.
Sorry about that, folks.
Value area high on the day is all the
way down at 21.
We've got some offside sellers at 310
and 339 and 343.
Still want a bit more of a flush here to
perk my interest to get long into.
Not seeing it yet.
Yeah, everyone just left. It's really
weird. They're starting to come back on
the tape a bit now. Very odd.
Here we go. So, they're going to drive
lower into these levels. Come on then.
Let's come and test it.
And if we don't see absorption and
sellers get stuck, then there's
obviously there's no trade, right? They
don't absorb, there's no trade.
350 check. Where are those sellers? 346
343 340.
Starting to see it.
Does she have a good walk?
Okay, perfect. All right, thank you.
Now,
they just trapped. Here's the 80 test.
Uh, I don't know. I'd like them to come
there. I'm not I'm not convinced they're
going to they're going to go there at
the moment, mate. I would love them to
come down there. I'll be honest with
you, but uh we're holding this little
low volume node. This can be a bit of a
shelf. I'm waiting to see what we do
here. So, like are we going to do this
or are we going to do this and come
right down and give us like a really
good discount to bid back up off? I'm
not convinced here. Um and this seller
just left at 380 now. He just left the
building. So, here we go. Let's see if
we go 390400.
They're juggling around here. See this
seller just playing games.
They're trying to rebid this up now.
We'll see.
I don't see why they're stuttering. He's
He's gone. He's gone. You bull should be
putting your foot down. There we go.
Right. So, next level. Really? They're
looking to sell with size is 410.
Liquidity's just left the building
again. What is going on here?
There's no news due. Zoom this out.
there. H. [snorts] All right. So, 380
big seller left. Uh, but we're seeing a
little bit absorption there. I think
we're going to squeeze now. We should
squeeze now at this point. It's a bit
It's a bit tricky. They've made it
tricky. Here we go. So, 400 410s. I
wouldn't be surprised if 410s lifts as
well. SPY about to break out upside as
well. Watch SPY previous day high. We've
already poked through it. If we start to
bid above, it's going to get squeezy.
Here we go. Right. So, they held this
low volume now. So, now really all bulls
need to do is defend this shelf and we
should go
big if but uh that's that's it. Yeah, I
had a feeling we weren't going to make
it down there. Mo, if you just look on
the tape, like the the selling into this
low volume shelf kept getting absorbed.
Um so that selling at sort of 65 to 55,
you'll see it right right here. They
kept absorbing it. So there was a
passive and these guys were stuck. So
there was a passive buyer stepping in
here and then once 380 left that was it.
There was no one to hold it down. So
here we go. So 410s now
is where the liquidity is. They keep
adding up at 410s. Big level at 410s
and then through that really 430 is on
the tape but really potentially all the
way up to 500. We'll see. They can fail
breakout this. Remember they can fail
break out this.
No worries, Mo.
So, uh, Spy needs to get above previous
day high. It needs to hold a bid above
previous day high. Keep every time it
comes into it, it's being sold. Remember
that 680 big gamma level. Every time
it's coming into it currently, it's
being sold at that level.
So, this can be look above and fail if
they can't get back through it. And on
the spiders I'm talking about, did ES
make a new high? No. Failed to make a
new high so far. So, this dip into this
gray box needs to hold for bulls.
Otherwise, uh, no more upside, I would
say. So, they got to hold this dip into
this gray box for bulls. Otherwise, no
more upside.
And definitely a few buyers got caught
at 92s. They're going to have to
accelerate through that to let them out.
They're looking for 410s. Here they go.
They're trying. They're looking for 400
410s. Spy back over. We're going to go
now. Come on. You got to let these
buyers out. You can't keep [\h__\h]
around. If you're going to go, you got
to put your foot down
messing about these players.
I bet you 410 lifts as well. Bet you he
lifts.
Accelerate. Come on. Where's the
liquidity? Go. Who's here? Hello. They
all gone to sleep. Hello. What are you
doing?
Can you get some size on the book? No
one's come to play all of a sudden. It's
really weird since we've got up here.
Everyone's got scared.
Yeah. Really slow. It's re It's so
weird. It's so weird. Like the book's
just stopped.
Like that player at 400 left and then
No, like no one's come on. I'm like
literally watching the book and it's
still there's a guy flashing at 1875
now. So he's trying to get a pull back
to 1875 and he's moving down. What is
going on here?
That gray box is your overunder. Now for
bulls, as long as you hold above that
gray box, uh potential squeeze for high
day. If you if you lose that gray box, I
would not I would not uh touch it. You'd
be buying very high if you're buying
here. But they did trap the sellers into
the little blue box below which was that
low volume node. That's where the
sellers got caught. Here they come.
They're going to try now. Some big
players coming on.
Might be a bit of absorption here, you
know.
So buyers have tried over 90 one, two,
three, four times with aggression and
not got their move. They need to get
their move and they need to get it soon.
It's not lunchtime. It's got an hour
left to lunchtime, my friend.
We will get a liquidity injection. It's
just a matter of time.
Here we go.
There we go.
Tapping fours.
Buyers come back in at 75 again. So 300
lot trying to support the bid at 75 and
80s. Sellers at 410. That's your
rotation at the moment.
I wouldn't be surprised if you do break
high of day to see 410 pool. Maybe they
check the fundamentals.
You never know. I mean, I I my feeling
is we're going to drive higher for them
to resell it JD. Uh not necessarily now,
but just in general
carry trade. What's day 18? Tonight,
right, between tonight and tomorrow.
I think I I wonder if that all got
priced in though. Everyone's so
concerned about it, including myself.
But we'll see. What's going to be
interesting is
do they start selling uh US assets and
does that cause a liquidity problem
where we get a cascade or have we
started pricing that in already.
It's trying. It's desperately trying it.
It's desperately trying it. I think
you're going to get it. I think you're
going to get it.
Here you go. Here you go. They're coming
now. They're coming now. Let's see if
this guy at 410's real. I'm going to bet
he's not.
I'm going to bet he pulls.
could be wrong, but I don't think he's
real. Every time we've seen that size
today, he's left. So, few people front
running him because they're worried
because it's massive size.
And look at the bid at 375. He just
left. Oh, he's real. Oh, he's real. Oh,
he's real. We're filling him.
Okay, big seller. He's legit. Let's see.
Oh, he's real. That's a wall up there.
you get through him, you've got a little
bit of a blue sky scenario. But that is
a legit seller up there trying to unload
and he's adding to it. Here we go.
Retesting him. Filling a little bit of
him. Filling some more of him. He keeps
reloading. Oh, he's gone. Did they fill
it all there? Yes, they did. They filled
him. Okay, so be careful here. You need
to get back above 410 because you have
565 lot buy side on the market filled
there. Okay. So, if you don't hold a bid
above that now, that will be a pain
point for those buyers. But you look
good for that rise up into 430. All the
time they can hold above at the moment.
That dance. He was legit.
Thanks. Done for the day. Another WC
tomorrow. Nice work, Gray Kitty. Great
name. Great name. All right, that 410
seller coming in. So buyers are
currently stuck up there at 410. All
right, that was a 560
odd lot. We can have a look at it on the
book. I can zoom you in so you can see
what I'm looking at. You better have
taken profits into that. Okay, this
participant right here, 652 lot. All
right, we sold into him. He's he's the
pain point right now. So bulls, the big
bull I would say is stuck here. All
right, and definitely stuck top side of
that. And if we move to the delta, you
can see it here like a sore thumb. 410
564 lot buy side. All right, huge. Look
at the volume. Look at the spike. All
right, until you get above that,
everyone who got bullish up there, as in
all 564 of them and the 161 lot below
are all stuck. All right, they are stuck
now. So, it might be that that is the
end of the auction. We will see. But I
would be probably done with this at this
point.
No, not sell like well take your profits
now but not short sell now. Not short
sell now.
I wouldn't be short selling against at
like into this yet. I would for me we
would need to leave leave this and you
still have this here, right? So maybe if
you're looking for a return back into
just here or you're looking if we leave
that and a return into here. But uh
technically we're not going to go on a
short rotation until we get under all of
this. So this is just a pullback
intraday, right?
Intraday. But yes, if I was long from
this dip, I would be selling into that
move. Hopefully that makes sense.
Like it's hard for me when you say sell
now. Let me know what you mean. Do you
mean are you short selling now? And I
also like I need to understand what type
of trade you're looking for. If you're
looking for a scalp back into support,
sure. If you're looking for an actual
breakdown of structure, no.
Really?
[\h__\h] hell.
Uh that is the hedge against tonight.
This Let me check the daily as well. Did
we break out of that level? Yeah, we're
breaking out that level. All right, so
it's going for the all-time highs.
Remember, we've been talking about this
on GC holds above here. We're building
that liquidity to go for highs. Uh this
move here is the JP hedge, right? This
is them coming out of US stocks and
going going back into GC again. Now,
it's all about tonight and tomorrow.
Absolutely. What a flipping move. You're
right, though. That's why it went quiet.
Everyone, everyone was like, "Okay, long
GC. Long GC."
[clears throat]
Wow. Good eyes there, uh, Peter. Thank
you, mate. I wouldn't I wouldn't have
seen that. Good eyes.
Got you, Joe. Okay, cool. Good. Good to
know. Good to know.
So, this gray box is where the volume
was created. Uh, all I'd say is look,
all the time we're holding this, bulls
still have a chance, but like like we've
talked about. Late bulls are currently
stuck up here. All right, late bulls
with big size are stuck up here. This is
the rotation where we built and broke
out from. If you lose this, this is
what's going to be really hard. Now, if
you're looking for short, if you lose
this, you have IB high value area high,
current weak profile, point of control.
So, it's very likely that they find a
bid here. We don't go back into
rotational short until you lose that.
Right? That's what's going to be hard
about looking for shorts today, right?
Until you lose this, right? And then
maybe you repric this whole thing, but
[snorts]
I'm on the downside minus 700. Any
recommended scalp trades
for me? The setup is still bullish. Um,
but we know we've got players stuck. See
that gray box held? Again, this is what
I'm saying about the most you're going
to get is a scout down to here until we
let go of it. So,
You know,
you can only play what's in front of
you. That like you've got to ignore what
you're up or you're down. Try and take
that out of your trading equation. All
that actually matters is is the volume,
the price, the setup in front of you.
Nothing else actually matters.
Caught shorts there again.
Right. These guys are offside. Tra it
back into this guy. This guy. This guy.
Caught a bid. That's the gray box. The
big bull guy is stuck up here. If we get
back over him, he's going to be very
comfortable with all that size.
I'm going to use the bathroom here,
folks. I will be right back.
We're still building out here. Still
above the gray box. They still trying to
come and test up that player we had on
the map. All these guys were stuck from
405 to 410.
I don't know if you guys are are
I can't tell because you're text you're
writing it like if you guys are serious
or not. Any any comments on top? I mean
my comments been the same as it has for
a long time. Don't trade with them.
Simple as that.
Yeah. Live every day. Monday to Friday,
9:15 Eastern, we start.
How much I'm up or down dictates my risk
size. How choosy I am. If I'm down,
market size, if I'm up or stay until I
see a Well, that makes sense in
fairness, Joe. That does make sense.
You'll risk that does make sense.
Aggressive when you're trading well and
you've built a buffer. That does make
sense.
Do I use a separate feed for bookmap
that shows level two? Um, well, I use
their data feed. I pay for it.
For the education question, I have a
good base knowledge of tech analysis,
but it seems like I need to learn more
about auction theory.
Horses for courses for me. Yeah. Oh my
god, we're into a problem again, are we?
Mr. Error has come back. When did that
start? It's completely out the blue.
[\h__\h] mate.
What the f?
What the fudge?
I'll do that update after today. I don't
think I'm going to take another trade
now. Anyway,
that's pretty annoying. It's been
running really nice all morning.
What is the rainbow chart on the top
right of the screen?
This is part of the flow zone pro.
All right. So, just a quick reference
tells you sentiment right now. Higher
time frame is trying to move higher.
Lower time frames trying to move higher.
Alignment is for upside moves. So, if
you're trying to play a bearish move,
you're fighting against that until it
flips.
Alex, I'm on ES. I'm looking for the
test of IB. If it holds, then the long
back up for a scalp sounds like a good
plan. Where's your IB?
Yeah, you've got a bit of structure
below. So, your IB is at 55s. So, I'd
say 55s to 48. So, you've got 5day
moving average, initial balance, uh New
York VWAP, and your pivot from your sort
of 10:00 a.m. high and morning drive
high. So, that whole area needs to hold
and be absorbed.
Um the one thing I'd just be aware of is
the spy. All right, we we keep wicking
the previous day high. cannot get above
it and you're into a supply zone on the
spy. So just be aware of that.
Don't all I'm saying don't be expecting
too much more upside today. If we end up
like breaking out and going upside it's
great but don't expect it because our
expectation today remember was a range
rotation. If we get more than that great
expectation was a range rotation.
I'm going to have to [\h__\h] close Ninja
and restart this. This is pretty
upsetting here.
Let's try this again. See if we can get
that five minute chart working.
Was fine all morning. I just looked over
now and it's bathroom break obviously
ruined it. Back to this gray box again.
So if you lose this, you've got those
levels below. For me, there's I lack
edge in this market right now. So it's a
leave alone for me at this moment.
I think it's better for Ninja Trader. I
think Ninja Trader is cleaner for it.
It's [\h__\h]
Absolutely [\h__\h] it. Two days in a row.
I have to build a new chart.
How can I do that?
Sorry folks, I'm just trying to think
out loud how I'm going to do this. Um,
this what I had to do the other night.
Duplicate.
Do I have one here?
Still holding that gray box.
Uh, I can sell like it's an awkward
question. Um, yes, my my course is all
you need for sure, but I'm sure there's
plenty of other people out there who are
also really good. I don't want to um,
you know, oversell.
Yeah, I just launched a new course. It's
on sale right now because it's a launch
price. So, it's uh
299 with code launch. Have to put it in
capitals. 299 with code launch. But it
everything's in there that you need.
But again, no pressure.
No pressure to do it.
Give me a second here, folks. I'm just
trying to figure out if I can get this
uh five minute chart fixed.
still holding that gray box. You can see
we're starting to build thicker and
thicker volume. So, I'd be less and less
interested to see how profiles now moved
up as well. You want to be careful with
this PC now. Everything's moving up. I
don't like this for buyers at the
moment. I think it's getting more and
more dangerous.
Uh Mo,
I I think you're still in chat. What I'm
finding is when I build a new chart, it
gets rid of all those problems. Have you
had something like that happen?
Try I think I've fixed it just by buying
a new chart each time.
Footprint. Okay. Yeah, that fixes it.
Only with other footprint indicators,
but not this one. But I reinstalled NT.
Okay, you can see like keeps offering me
this F5 update. I saw you messaging me
about that this morning. Maybe I was
going to have to get that figured out.
doesn't like something.
Okay. So, coming back into this box,
you're starting, this is why I say I
don't like it. The more you visit it,
you're starting to build out this now.
That's going to become a problem.
And we're into thin levels. So, it's
looking more and more ugly by the
second. I would say this right now.
Wonder if it's a data issue or
something.
Series.
Sorry team. Bear with me. Bear with me.
There we go. I think it's a data series
issue. If there's too much
uh if if I have too much data series,
too much going back, it's a problem.
I think that's what it is.
Good to know. At least I know what fixes
it.
me save this now. Sorry team. All right,
I'm back. Sorry team. I had to focus on
that a minute. Uh D, can you please
explain the table top? Right. I think I
just did. Right.
Lower time frame, higher time frame.
Higher time frame at the moment is
trying to move back up to 500, right?
That's why it's bullish. lower time
frame is in a bare market because we're
starting I mean this will flip backwards
and forwards but we're starting to lose
these levels. All right. And if we start
to lose this there might be a bigger
drive. This will flip back bullish once
it gets back above here. If we go into a
liquidity building stage, it's where the
time frames are not necessarily aligned
and we might move where's my back down
into here. Okay, that will go into a
liquidity building stage where the
market's building volume for the next
leg.
Yeah, I think that's wise, Mo. I think
that's might be why.
Did I close my trade? Yeah, out ages
ago, man. That was for me.
No, not with the new course
unfortunately because the new the the
the
order flow and volume profile course is
very very focused on teaching you volume
and um and uh order flow.
It might be that you've done someone
else's course or you've been around for
a long time and so that you understand
structure and how
you think the market works based on how
that's not to say like I think one way,
you think the other, I'm right, you're
wrong. There's lots of ways of
interpreting it. Um, but it's more like
a supplement for people and I'm adding
to it every day. But the beginner to
advanced course makes in my mind is 20
hours of knowledge to make sure you
understand all my teachings on like what
I'm looking at and why and the order
flow and volume profile just adds to
that. So the discord is with the 20our
course. Um I know that might not be
advantageous for some of you but it just
means that everyone in the discord is
trading the same way. If if I did it for
the order profile or volume profile and
orderflow course, it would mean your
interpretation might still be different
to other people. So that's the only
reason.
That's the only reason. I did think
about doing it with it and I was like it
might cause issues in Discord where
people will be looking the other side of
the trade too much. But
all the courses are on
flowzonerader.com.
Everything's there. You can click the
links above like Nightbots posted it.
Learn that little post on Nightbot learn
to trade 20our course. Discord
indicators 649.
That's onetime fee. 20our course and
Discord for lifetime and private
education we do in there as well. It's
just a onetime fee. Uh the order volume
profile and order flow course is
currently on sale. I've only just
launched it this week. $299
right with code launch in capital.
You get cheaper access, Eddie. You get a
a heavily discounted access.
But again, guys, like before you go and
spend your hard hardearned money, make
sure you like how I trade and teach,
right? like go through my free lessons.
Make sure you like not just how I trade
on here and how I see it. Make sure you
like how I teach because if you're going
to sit there and watch me for 20 hours
or six hours, you you and you've spent
money, you better like how I teach.
Otherwise, it's just pissing money down
the drain. I don't want you guys to be
unhappy. So,
would I need the beginner to get volume
profile trading? No, you can just do you
can do the volume profile and orderflow
course if you just want if you just want
that. You don't need to do the beginner
to advance. I advise people do if you're
look uh trying to think how to explain
this. If you're new to trading,
my advice would be to do my beginner to
advanced course, right? First, so that
you've got a good basis of
understanding. If you're not going to do
mine, that's also fine. Go like, but go
and go and find someone who's going to
teach you properly like how to read
price, how to read volume, how to read
market structure, what you're looking
at, why the market moves. understand why
the market moves, then go and do volume
profile and order flow trading. If you
just do that with no understanding of
the market, it is just going to you're
going to be like, "What? I don't know
what I'm looking at." Right? So, if
you're new, you don't have to do it with
me. Like I said, I've got free stuff on
YouTube. Go and do it with someone else
if there's another mentor or or whatever
you like. Like, no shade, no offense
taken. It's all good. It's really
important you guys spend money
only on good products, only on people
that you like, as in they're teaching
away their pedigogy.
No, Jonathan, I'm sorry. I I only have
so many hours in the day I'm available,
mate. I can't I'm a oneman band here. I
can't make another Discord for the new
course.
um six figure trader consistently and
yeah my results I go into the Discord
all the time.
How do I get order flow and BP with
Discord? Yeah, you would have to do the
unfor unless I change it but I just
think it's not fair on the other people.
It will just cause confusion.
I'm not it look guys this isn't for me
about making money. This is about
being uh respectful and consistent with
the guys who are already students who
are already in the discord. So that at
the moment there's like I don't know 150
plus of them. They all trade the same
way. They are all looking for the same
setups. We have a very small but close
community that look after each other. If
I start doing it where people just do
volume profile and orderflow trading and
are coming in, their understanding is
going to be totally different, it's
going to shake other people out of
trades. And that is always, in my
opinion, when Discords start to go to
[\h__\h] Um, I don't want that. I want
everyone looking after each other,
trying to trade in the same direction
and being supportive. So that that
that's the only reason, guys. It's the
only reason. And I've been part of
plenty of Discords on my way up. I've
been
mentors on Discord where the main guy in
Discord is full of [\h__\h] and it caused
major issues so I left. That's how this
whole thing started. Um,
what level is the big seller at? Uh,
well, the big buyer got trapped up here,
right? This is the level the big buyer
got trapped up. So, it's imp impressive
that they held this dip to be honest. We
I got caught monologuing here and
talking to you, but uh we held IB. We
reclaimed P. We reclaimed this shelf.
They just need to take this out now. I
just be careful. But they're trying to
do this move here. But we have this big
player like we talked about on bookmap.
Um you will see him. I'll pull it up so
you can see him.
All right. This guy is still stuck. This
is the guy who's in pain. in this orange
box that we talked about earlier, this
850 lot who got stuck at 25,49.5
and then under him 129 lot. Uh so
basically 402 to 409, right? Just call
it 400 to 410 is the buyers who are
stuck. If they get let out then look,
they're trying to lift it. You can see
they're trying to lift it and let price
come up right now. So they're trying to
get up to 415, 430, 450. It's where they
want to drive to. These guys have got to
get out the money first. In the money
first, sorry. [snorts]
They're trying though. They're
definitely trying. Last two candles
trapped sellers at 94s. That's for sure.
I've missed the long entry, man. I've
like talking to you guys. I've already
missed it, unfortunately. Uh it was
probably down here. I haven't even
looked, but I'm sure down here some
shorts just got caught. Yeah.
Yeah. That transition there. If we go to
low time frame.
Yeah. That was it. That was it.
Repricing this sellside imbalance. This
purple level here. Big heavy selling
down into it.
Sellers caught at the lows.
Transitioned. Held their pain point.
That was the the entry was there. I got
caught talking to you guys about other
stuff. Unfortunately, this is what
happens unfortunately when I talk about
other stuff and then I lose focus and
now I've missed a trade opportunity. So,
the only other trade opportunity now
would be a breakout and pullback into
this zone. You'd need aggressive
breakout and a pullback to hold the top
of this to get up into there. That is
probably the worst location of the day,
but you are with momentum. But remember,
these guys are all stuck. It needs to be
an aggressive breakout and a pullback
that holds this level. And your location
is terrible, but that's the only thing
left. Otherwise,
Like I said, I don't like shorts. Even
though you're building this because this
is the weekly point of control that's
been developing. This is the level where
they would keep holding. So, we talked
about this numerous times.
This is why I'm not short bias today. Uh
higher time frame. You see this right
here? Here's your profile, right? They
can keep holding this. They might fail
up here, but they can keep absorbing
this. So, I'm
want to be short biased really until we
do that.
>> [snorts]
>> gold new highs. Yeah, it's going to like
I said, like we talked about last few
mornings, that thing will pump once it's
built enough liquidity up.
Why does ES do the same thing as NQ?
Does ES have those big players stuck as
well? Always confuse me. It Why does it
or why doesn't it?
I mean it if we're moving
if we're moving like well weighted right
if we're if today is a day let's get
this up
where mo most of the market's rebounding
which is what we are seeing. All right.
So if we look at the breadth today, all
right, not much red, like a bit of
energy, but if we were going to think
about ES, if we were going to have a big
divergence day, well, you'd expect
finance to be down or healthcare to be
down. We're not. So if we think about
all of this, the top 500, everything's
green. What's really green? Tech. So
Microsoft, Nvidia, Google, Meta, Tesla,
Tesla, Amazon. All right, Mag 7, big big
green. 60% of the NQ heavily weighted,
40% of the ES. So still going to be
positive.
Apple,
you know, green but not great. But the
finances and healthcare where you might
traditionally see some weakness in a
divergence day if ES was weak. Well,
you're not seeing it. So the breadth is
good. Everyone's moving upside today.
No, my education does not come from ICT
concept. Although I don't think all his
concepts are bad, but
they're not accurate.
head and shoulder. I mean, it too early
to say. I can see what you're looking
at, but you know, the drift at the
moment is higher. Just the I've missed
the buying opportunity here.
Unfortunately, got caught monologuing.
So, I've missed my 50 an extra 50 points
here. I'm not going to chase it.
Otus, I went through the course,
switched to micros, watched all the
videos you shared yesterday, and I'm
back to green today. I'm just trying to
be 1% better each day. Thanks, Alex.
Nice work, Otus. Congratulations, mate.
That's all you can do, right? Each day,
even me, it never stops. It's 1%
better each day. Compound, compound,
compound, compound. Just 1% better. That
might be one less trade a day. It might
be, you know, waiting longer than you
normally wait. It might be attacking
that one trade, which is A+ that little
bit more. It might be ignoring subpar
setups. It might be you're the guy that
takes random trades because you get
bored and not doing that anymore. All
you got to do is 1% better each day and
over the course of your career, it will
really start to make a difference.
No, I live in Los Angeles.
Is the trading view order flow indicator
sufficient for volume trading or do we
need bookmap? The trading view one's
fine. I think it's really good. Like I
genuinely think it's very very good.
Yeah, you can see them. They probably
they probably lift, but uh remember we
still got that trap player. Uh if we
come up to 10, look at this. 564 delta.
He's still there at 10. So they need to
get above 10 and sweep all this out,
right? That's what they're trying to do.
They need to get above 10. That player's
still stuck at 10. If they let him out,
we probably do like a little swipe up 15
20 maybe 30 and then probably settles
back down and sees what it wants to do.
But it's too late now. I'm not buying up
here. Like the the bid was down at the
50s. The trap underneath like like the
low volume node bid, the reclaim bid,
right? The bid was here. That little
trap into here. We always talk about
these low volume nodes work as good
traps into that blue
breakout sellers came in here, got
absorbed. There's your micro head and
shoulders and they're trying to do this
pop. This is the final target that they
want. But they're going to run these
stops here if they can. But yeah, good
eyes, Adam. Like you can see them just
refreshing up there. But, you know, if I
had been long off that low, I would have
already sold a chunk of my position
here. And the next swipe that we have
through, if they run the stops, I'd be
selling a chunk more. But I'm not in a
position. I got caught [\h__\h] talking
about Discord. Got in the way of my
trading.
Giveaway time. Is it that time? Yeah. 15
minutes. [laughter]
Is that the only reason you guys are
here? All the free education, all the
call outs we give, but we're just here
for an Apex account.
We don't care. We don't want to learn.
Give us a free account.
[laughter]
Do I have any videos in mind that I
recommend watching? Uh,
yes. Um,
what are the best videos I'd say to
watch? uh watch all my if you go on my
YouTube there'll be like a slate on uh
like learning to trade
and volume profile. I haven't done one
on orderflow yet. I will get to it next
year. Right. So if you go to my YouTube
and bring this in.
All right. I would start I don't know if
you're new or like what level you are
but come down into here
trading strategy and education I would
make your way through these but the the
really good ones to watch are here
volume and market profile right to
understand key levels I'd watch that and
then you know it all depends what level
you're at but this one's very good uh an
the one on anchored VWOP's really good
the one on WOFF if so you can understand
traps. There's tons, man. There's lit
there's so much in here. Um, but yeah,
just
there's tons. Honestly, there's so much
there. I don't know what level you're
at, so I don't know what you need to
need to learn, but I would focus on
understanding key levels. Uh, WOFF, even
the 21 EMA, people like don't understand
how useful just have basic EMA is to
showing you if price has caught up to
good value or if we're way too extended.
You know, if we're way away from EMAs on
any time frame, that should be telling
you if you're if we're long, right?
Let's say
let's say uh like we're up here, price
is up here, and we're way away from
these flow zones, and the flow zones are
still here. You don't want to buy
because we're expecting a pull back into
flow zones, pull back into deep pullback
flow zones, right? When we're
accelerating away, it's normally a
squeeze. You want to wait for the pull
back in for a continuation trade. basics
like that that can even if you're
trading volume profile and order flow,
however you're trading, they can set you
up really well for understanding like
where where is value and what you're
looking at.
Not new, but I'm always happy to watch
and repeat. Thanks. Hey, good for you,
man.
This is my software. Yeah, Emma, this is
the Flow Zone Pro system. So, it's all
on here.
So, you get like a free version of this
uh when you do the beginner to advance
course or you can upgrade to this
version if you want. It's totally up to
you. And I also have it available for
Ninja Trader. But if you're just going
to start and you don't want to spend
money, I would advise put a 21 EMA on
your chart. There's a free video I did
on like the power of the 21 EMA. Watch
that video on how to use a one and a
five minute 21. Watch the video on
Ballinger bands if you don't understand
Ballinger bands on daily profiles. how
how important they are. Watch that video
completely free again. T there's tons
there's tons there, man.
Can you promote my YouTube on your
YouTube channel? Yeah, I I mean I'd be
happy for you to do that. I I don't know
if you're able to do that how it works,
but yeah.
Troy says, "Yeah, the 5 minute 21 and
the 200 video is excellent for newer
traders. Also, volume profile." There
you go. caps in the 21 video, 21 EMA
video is really good. I still use it on
my chart on that one and the VWAP video.
I use 1450 and 200. Yeah, I mean
whatever works for you. I'm very similar
and there's like if you do the like this
is completely free, right? This
indicator here that I made, right? The
trend friend pro,
right? This is based on five minutes.
It's very simple. 2002 21 in between we
don't touch. Once we reclaim 21, you're
a go for upside. All right, that's free.
There's a video on that as well. It's
completely free. You can download it.
Right? So, I'm not asking you to spend
your money doing my course. Like, do the
course if you like how I teach and you
want to further your knowledge. But
there's like I said, make sure you uh f
make sure first you have the capital to
do the course if you're going to do it.
I only getting into debt. I did a post
on that the other day on Instagram. I'm
concerned in America about the amount of
people spending on credit and in debt
right now. It's not good. Right, we're
coming back for these 4410s. There's a
refresh seller. Keep coming in here.
Once he moves out the way, they might
let those bulls out. Uh you got relative
weakness in spy right now. Be very very
careful. Like I said, I would not be a
buyer up here. You are asking for it.
You are buying the worst price of the
day.
What is this indicator? It's the flow
zone pro
or this one or the other one? This is uh
trend friend trend friend pro. This is
flow zone pro.
It's a big area here. This 90 is really
thick. Really, really, really thick
here. You can see the profile building
out here. Really thick.
Yeah, exactly. relative weakness and spy
cannot get through that previous day
high and it's back under the 80. If we
lose 80 like we talked about I can't
remember some one of you was looking for
longs on spy you know you need to watch
uh IB high five day and 20 days both at
uh 67850 which is also your sort of uh
9:30 10 a.m. high. So I'd be watching
for SPY if it wants to trade back into
that range and hold. VWOP starting to
catch up there as well. So I'd imagine
into that kind of range maybe they find
a bid. But you know, I'm going to keep
repeating myself. Remember, today is an
inside day. Our expectation was
rotation, right? The max max I think we
would go to today is 500. But the
expectation is rotation.
Like if we break out of here, let's just
think about how much liquidity we've
built and where we could go. I'm going
to do two types of fibs today. So, let's
look at this. No, let's look at you. If
we break break out of this range, right?
So 200% or the 100% move will almost get
get us there. If we look at the initial
balance today,
right, 2x initial balance will get us
there. And if we look at
a pullback one,
it's looking at that opening range as
well.
opening range is bang on the money as
well for a 100% move of the opening
range. And the last one I just want to
quick look at
is do one of these. Okay, so 618. So
there's good confluence to get up there
if they can catch a bid. It's a big if,
but they are doing their best right now.
But if they keep trying up here and
getting stuck, they're going to get
going to get in trouble. But you can see
point control shifted up here. Now,
we're not finding acceptance over
values, but this is starting to look
like a potential trend day, isn't it?
Look at this.
If we can get over here, this is
possible. It's what they're trying to
do. But that fourth 10 player, he is the
problem right now. The guy who got stuck
in this wick up here is your problem.
I wouldn't be playing breakouts in this
market. Yeah. Because if you're going to
play, if you're playing the it doesn't
mean it doesn't work, but if you look at
the hourly chart, look at where you're
buying.
Look at the current week profile. Look
at the hourly chart. Look at where
you're buying. Uh where are you guys?
Yeah, it means if you're going to buy
410, you're buying the edge of this
shelf, right? And they might just poke
it and slam it in your face because
here's your swing, right? The buys were
here, here, and here.
It doesn't mean it can't do it, but it
you got to ask yourself, is it a good
buy? Are you just hoping price moves
high? Are you like, I really want it to
do that. Is it a good buy? That was a
good buy. That was a good buy. That was
a good breakout buy. That was a good
breakout buy. That is not a good
breakout buy. Even if it does it, from a
technical standpoint, what you are going
to do, let's say you get rewarded on
that trade. You trade 410. Let's say you
get the 90 points to 500. Let's just say
you get it. You're going to do that the
next time and it's going to flush on
you. You be [\h__\h] Because you're
training your brain to do something you
probably shouldn't do
in my mind anyway.
But each their own. You got to trade
your own your own book, your own system.
Back into this guy. So if they get
through this 415 420 is on the book.
They are adding. Look 415 just left. So
[sighs]
410's a problem. Remember, if you were
stuck at 410, if you bought 5 75 lots at
410, uh you're probably going to start
unloading some.
Carla, what I'd look If we got to 500,
what I'd look for is a break above and
and a drop underneath and then using it
as resistance. All right. So, if you
want to play that short up at 500, if we
got there, what I'd be looking for is
something like this where trap buyers
come in and then failing underneath and
then using that for the downside move
back to four. Yeah, that's possible, but
you need them to get trapped above. You
don't want to just if we just do one of
these, you don't want to be slamming in
short here. You've got to let it trap,
come underneath, roll over. Don't be
front side. Do not be front side.
>> [snorts]
>> I know you have said you can see the
order flow in different areas. Which is
the easiest to read for you? Uh
[snorts]
it's a really good question. Um
I think
I think footprint I'm starting to enjoy
more and more. Traditionally, I've only
ever used bookmap, but I am actually
really enjoying footprint. Um, bookmap,
the difference with footprint and
bookmap on the footprint, I can't see
the levels above, right? And I can't see
when people are spoofing and people are
legit selling and any of that. You can't
see it. Whereas on Bookmap, I can see
it. And you could get that data on level
two on the dom. But like I say, the dom,
unless you're watching it with like a
eagle eye, all right, then you're not
going to see when someone's on and pulls
and ons and pulls. Like this guy at 410
has just come on. If he moves down to
405, now he's moved up to 420. I
wouldn't see that on the level two. It's
moving too quick. I can see it really
quickly and easily on bookm
I I would say that's probably true of M
that 410 player they didn't let him
through did they all right so that 410
player he's still stuck up there and
he's probably the guy starting to dump
he's probably like [\h__\h] get me out of
this why did I buy that hive day what an
idiot And I was like, "Okay, I'm going
to I'm going to dump." And what you had
there is more people coming in. If you
look at bookmap, 61 lot, 50 lot, 20 lot,
11 lot, 7 lot. So their pain right now
is 405. So sellers jobs now is to stay
heavy versus 405, 410. That's the
seller's job. Sellers job is to leave
these guys boxed in above this little
node. All right. Sellers will
desperately want to do this, this, and
this. All right. Buyers will desperately
want to do this. That's the battle
coming into lunch. We are going to do a
giveaway at lunch.
Show my setup.
Right. This is a big player.
sellers starting to be aggressive here
versus that player at 40510.
ES coming back down to the level. Can't
remember which one of you is watching
it. ES starting starting to do that
drift back down into initial balance.
Right. So you got IB 5day 20-day VWOP
pivot all between 855 850 on the ES. All
right.
You can see I've just been still like
the only possible buy opportunity I'd
say was this here when I got caught
talking about Discord since then I just
I don't think there's edge right now. I
don't think there's edge in the market
right now.
But SPY's lost that little shelf. But,
uh, if you look underneath,
look at the 9:30, 10:00 a.m. drive, look
at your New York VW, look at the 5day,
look at the 20-day, look at the initial
balance. All right, it can it can absorb
in those level. That's what's going to
be tricky about today is the rotations
can we can drop a little bit, we can
absorb, we can go back and back test. I
don't think you're going to get a big
trend move today, but we've had a decent
move out already, right? Like I mean
just bear in mind the ENQ is up 490
points right now.
No. Would I long on this pullback on GC?
Oh. Uh
have we taken liquidity
rejection?
Uh, no.
All right. So, you've rejected daily
players. You got three uh three wick
highs up here on daily.
You caught a bid over this move. Your
rotation is between here right now. You
built volume here. Bulls are currently
stuck uh at 400 and over. So, you
actually you actually want this to drift
down here and hold uh for a safer buy
before it does anything else. Yes,
you're holding the deep flow zone
pullbacks. But yeah, I would be looking
for this and see if they find a bid here
or get back over this block here into
400 and PC and leave sellers trapped
underneath here and then maybe but
you're going to have to take profit into
this move because it's a strong
rejection up there. But that's what I'd
be watching either here or a reclaim.
[snorts]
All right, into lunch we go, folks.
Let's do a giveaway.
How did I get into trading? Um,
watch the uh you watch the podcast I did
with Austin, but uh
I uh
I almost did this a job in my 20ies. I
went in and interviewed at Deutsche,
Morgan, um everywhere. Got offered a job
and then ended up having a pretty good
career in music. So, didn't do it and
then come back to it.
Um,
yeah, I've guys, it's delayed. I think
it's about six seconds. Unfortunately,
it's the quickest. I've got it set to
the quickest thing possible. If it could
do no delay, I would do no delay. I've
got it set to the quickest thing
possible. It's not for my uh benefit.
It's just it's how YouTube do. If you
watch any streamer, they can't do it
quicker than that. So, I think it's six
seconds. But if they've sped it up, they
sped it back back up. No, I'm not
looking for a long now. We've got three
drives.
Three drives
with the same players trapped and we're
leaving this. I'm not really interested.
I think we've hit target for the day. I
don't think there's much to do. Like, if
they lose this, they're going to trade
back inside. I'm not interested in all
this today. We've made our money, folks.
Like, my job is to take high probability
trades when it's there. I'd rather let
this build out liquidity for the rest of
the day. Now, um, let's do a giveaway.
Let's get that set up.
Yes. Remember, if you spam the giveaway,
Nightbot just pulls you out. So you when
I set it up, you only need to type it
once. All right, I'm going to tell you.
Give me a second. Give me a second. Give
me a second. Give me a second.
I'm going to give away an Apex account.
Okay, just type FCT in chat. It's all
you got to do. And we'll randomly draw
someone.
No worries, Zach. No worries, mate.
We give away an Apex account. So, if you
want to support the channel,
if you use FCT
at Apex or most prop firms, pretty much
every prop firm other than take profit,
you can type flow zone in. But, uh, I do
benefit from you using that code. That
money goes back into equipment industry.
sellers are trying to step on the gas
now. So, ES starting to fail IB. It's
going to come back down by the looks of
it into that 7850 on uh
on SPY, that old pivot, which is VWAP
5day 20-day pivot high from 9:30 10 a.m.
And they will need to find a bid there.
If they find a bid there, if you are
going to bid on that and they find a bid
there, you need to now be aware that
buyers at higher day are trapped. So if
they return back up there, you want to
be selling some, right? You want to be
selling some on that return back in.
Think about who's trapped, where they're
trapped. Right now at high day across
the indexes, we have people trapped. So
if I was going to look at ES for
example,
right? You can see participants are now
trapped up here. So 5day and 20-day and
pivot is here. So buyers will
desperately want to hold this. All
right? And then if they do hold it, you
want to be selling some back into there
because if shorts do pile in and if
these buyers are stuck and they say,
"Fuck this. I want out." You're going to
get a move back down. That's the
rotation.
If you lose this, look out below.
[snorts] Couple more minutes or 30 more
seconds.
What indicator do I have on the chart
with the buy and sell signals? It is the
pro the flow zone pro. It's my
indicator. You can get it on the course.
Get it on my website flowzonerader.com.
So buy right into that zone we just
talked about 67 850 and they're trying
to find a bid there.
They can't find a bid there, it's going
to be in problems. So I give you guys 10
more seconds.
5 4 3 2
one. Let's pull a winner.
My gosh, I struggle to say that. Unauna.
Unauna. Have I done that right?
Hopefully support Arsenal. That's a
great name. If you support Arsenal.
Unauna.
[laughter]
Great name. If you support Arsenal,
are you here? Unauna.
[laughter] It's rigged. I mean, they
might not even be an Arsenal supporter.
Just just good if they are. You're here.
Yeah. Unauna. Okay, cool.
Unauna, shoot me an email. Uh,
info@flowzonerader.com.
Send me send me a screenshot of you
logged into your YouTube
and uh I will sort you out with a free
Apex account.
Spy losing those levels. ES coming into
its 24hour VW up here at 840. If they
don't find a bid here, this market will
go night night. Remember, we were
squeeze up. We've trapped buyers at
those highs now. They will need to find
a bid here or hereabouts. Otherwise, it
will be night nighttime market. All
right, here's BWAP. Um,
any questions team? Any questions team?
So, Unauna just shoot me an email info
at flowzoneontrader.com.
Send me a screenshot of you logged in.
Do I place positions on stream? Uh, no.
I mean, sometimes I'll put I'll pull it
over, but I tell you before it happens
what I'm looking for. Um, I'm very very
clear. here. So, even at the beginning
of the day, I told you I was looking for
the dips in here. I told you that I was
looking when we had shorts trapped, I
was looking for the trade out of here
and then the little hold of that. All
right, I missed this one here,
unfortunately. And the hold of that. So,
I tell you well ahead of time. Well,
well ahead of time.
I know I have no problem buying one, but
damn, I've been here since 15 people
showing up. I know it's mad, man. I
appreciate all you OGs. I really
appreciate you. You've been here for
since September last year. It's crazy
how quickly it's been growing recently.
Very blessed. Very thankful.
Very, very thankful. Um, any questions
here, team? Otherwise, I'm going to get
out of here for the day.
What is this? Is this the New York Open?
We're right back to New York Open here.
this blue line,
right? That's to New York open. So, you
can see this volume got left. Someone
asked me, would I buy here? And I was
like, no. Because you've had three
drives. One, two, three. They're all
stuck up here. These buys, they're now
starting to stop out. Here's value on
the day. We can come right back to this.
Now, if they really want to, they're
going to come right the way back down
because look at this rice. Okay, they
had the ability to hold this. They
didn't. They can keep slamming this back
down. And if we lose this level, oof,
it's pretty ugly. But this is the
rotation
to make it very clear. We expected
rotation today. This is your inside bar.
All right. We are trading inside.
Where is yesterday? From here. All
right. This is yesterday.
We expect liquidity to be built in here.
Just like this. Right. Trade down, build
liquidity. Trade down, build liquidity.
Bulls have a chance. They have a chance
to hold. They might not do it today, but
they have a chance to hold, right? But
we've repriced into that level, 400. We
can't get over 400, so they can't get to
fives. We're going to pull back in.
Maybe they find a bid here into 162. I
don't know. I have no idea at this
point. and they can be very happy with
it because they've hit their target
upside.
Thanks, Aiden. Thanks. What time
tomorrow? 9:15. Same every day, right?
9:15 uh Eastern time. 9:15 Eastern time.
15 minutes of pre-market we do every
time.
How do you join the Discord? It's uh you
have to do the beginner to advanc
course, right? It's it comes
complimentary with that. It's just a
onetime fee. 649. You do the beginner to
advance course, you get uh version of
the flow zones and you get discord for
life. No monthly fee, none of that
stuff. Um best choice funded next
challenge, rapid or legacy. I think the
legacy is best personally, Eddie. I
think legacy is good. I might be missing
it, but I'm not seeing the link to the
new course. Can you post a link? Yeah,
no worries. Um,
there you go. That's the new new course
right there.
Um,
hopefully Wrath, it will come. It will
come. Be nice.
GC is selling too. Yep. Well, probably
failed that move. to got slammed into
that uh supply like we talked about.
Could I look at gold again halfway down
from the open DC?
Yeah. So, that supply held up and you've
just lost the it needed to hold this
pivot and you've lost it, right? So,
Right. So, you can see this supply,
right? You needed to hold that pivot and
it's lost it. It's coming down to where
we last found buyers. Um, but really, if
if if we were going to be strong, even
if we rejected this, you would have
wanted to hold this top side, right?
This starts to look like more like a
failed breakout. So, you want to be
really careful now on GC. If it finds a
bid, if we start if you start rejecting
this area, that can happen, right? This
is the edge of that liquidity you've
been building since I know 11th of
December. Higher lows, higher lows,
higher lows, trap, go slammed back down.
If they reject this, we can rotate all
the way back down. Uh on higher time
frame, so lower time frame, you'd expect
some reaction soon. We've caught bids
there. Did that sweep everyone? It did.
All right. So, you'd want that to hold.
The reaction off the highs is very
strong. Swept that. I would imagine
you'll find a bit of a bid soon. And it
what you really have to ask is do they
sell? Let's pull this out because I
haven't extended this. There we go. If
you fail to reclaim uh 365,
you fail to reclaim this, you're going
to rotate back into this like pivot low,
right? And look out below if you start
losing that previous day low. If you
reclaim this, there's probably a bid
back into like some of this area here.
You can think about like the midpoint of
this range, right? If it claims it,
reclaims it, right? And you'd expect
this to resell. So, if they hold this or
they reclaim this, once you get into
here, you will probably find that bears
will come back in and slam this back
down, right? So, that's a strong sell.
At some point, they will probably bid,
they need to get through this for that,
maybe a two-leg, and then they will sell
it back. All right? Hopefully, that
helps.
Very
heavy
very heavy market in rotation.
Uh
you're in short since 25397. 397.
Awesome. Well, once we lost PC, that's
incredible. It's probably best entry of
the day. I'd say once they couldn't get
back three to 410 and lost PC. Fantastic
entry. Fantastic entry,
Sailor Red, you're a legend past Apex
today. Congratulations. Congratulations,
Jason. If I don't only I joined If only
I had not joined an inferior Discord,
I'd be like Flynn. Wait, where's Flynn?
Did I miss something?
Um,
Alex, I started the new course last
night. The production quality material
is awesome. The OG videos are great, but
this is next level. Yeah, thanks, man. I
was thinking that I might have to go
redo all that old course at some point.
I don't know if I've got 20 hours in my
life to re-record and do it all.
Do I have any videos lessons with supply
and demand levels? Uh, yes.
I think so. Um,
I think so. Let me have a look. Pretty
sure. It's been a while since I've
looked.
Let's have a look. Um,
there's one on how to draw key levels.
So, I'm just trying to read them all to
see where
um [sighs]
session volume profile Oh, that probably
has it in as well.
There's so many videos here.
Breakout trade setups probably has it in
as well.
Reversal trades probably has it in as
well because they they will all trade
off key levels.
You need help with a purchase? Did you
have you emailed me?
Where have you emailed me? What's your
email?
I can't see anything.
Unless you're J Styles.
Check my spam in case it's gone there.
This is truth, no hate. Let me know your
email so I can search for it, mate.
Otherwise, uh I don't know what to do.
Give you a minute to reply here.
Yeah, I can see your one, Unauna. I I
can see your one, but someone's saying
that I need to check my emails because
they've had a problem with a purchase.
There's nothing there.
So, I don't know what to say there.
Okay, into this gray box again. We just
talked about
that big player from uh 5175's down
there again. That same player.
All right, guys. I'm going to go. I'm
not seeing a response in this guy, so it
makes me think maybe it's not right. Um
those in Discord, I'm going to pop in
this afternoon. Let me get a coffee,
walk my dog, all that good stuff. Get
off the screens and uh we will be back
tomorrow. Uh let's close out this week
strong. It's been a really good week um
since we left that shitty balance range
that we were in for two weeks. So, it's
been much much nicer to trade. Surprise,
surprise. Tomorrow though, we're going
to be very careful. Um because tomorrow
we have issues with
carry trade, we have OPEX. Um and I
expect after that lighter volume and
final day of roll. So, we're going to be
careful. All right.
Uh, trade safe, use hard stops, all that
good stuff. You can see the rotation is
taking place, right? Still protecting
previous days value, but shorts now can
potentially have control uh leaving
these buyers stuck. So, we have to see
how you act once you get back into
there. If you get back into there, might
not even get there. And, um, peace and
love everyone. Take care. Look after
yourself. See you tomorrow morning,
9:15. Remember, 9:15. That's when you
want to turn up so you can see what I'm
looking at for the day. Take care.