Morning
everybody.
Good morning everyone. Hope you're doing
well. Hope you had a good afternoon
session yesterday. Really really
much better action really in the
afternoon session. Um which we managed
to catch as chat for the long was really
proud of everyone in Discord catching
over 100 points to the long side. in the
afternoon once it finished failing to
break down. Okay, so what we're going to
do is have a look at the daily chart.
All right, as always, we're starting on
the daily chart. Uh for those of you who
have done the beginner to advanced
course, you should be looking right now
at your typical weekly model. Think
about Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday
relationship. All right, think about
that Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday
relationship.
Especially if you're going to look at
ETFs as a bit of a hint for you. Okay,
so what have we seen? Well, we broke
range last week. Friday went into a
strong sell. Monday continued that sell.
Tuesday gap down into the old point of
control on the old weekly candle like we
predicted
in the weekly newsletter and on Monday's
morning session. Once we got there, it
is likely that buyers will try and
defend that level. All right, this is al
also over 50% of a pullback. All right.
So, it's a level that they are
interested in defending. Now, if we look
at the yearly profile, you can see we've
started developing quite a thick area
here between this red box and blue box,
which surprise surprise is pretty much
the weekly range right now. All right.
So, it's a big big big level that we're
looking at at the moment. So, we need to
be careful of rotations. When we
consider this current high of day we've
put in overnight and we consider this
edge and we consider where we broke from
and we also look at the EMAs. What do we
have? Well, we have every single cluster
there. All right, 5day, 20-day, 50-day
all here. This is a big level. Don't be
surprised if we do a dance like this for
a while. It's going to have to make up
its mind. If we're going to see
rejection here, all right, then today
you could think about a look above and
fell. Remember, there's not much news
coming today. When's all the news
coming? Tomorrow and Friday and the uh
carry trade as well coming Friday and
over the weekend. So, I would be
somewhat aware of this low volume node
here. Any traps that they want to set in
here. Now, if we find acceptance back
into the old weekly range, sure, we can
rotate in here into Christmas. But
right now, we are literally in balance.
There's flat. There's plus two standard
deviation. There's minus2. Here's your
zero line. All right. Just be cautious.
I would say like there's no big big A+
trade. The A+ trade was that down and
was probably that back up and they made
that very choppy. Uh now we just have to
wait and see what we do. Now we can find
a little bit more edge here as we move
into the hourly charts. Right. So, let's
just move into the Actually, before I do
that,
uh make a note of uh these weekly levels
cuz if you're on the new contract, it's
going to show you the weekly levels down
there. They are incorrect. All right,
they're incorrect. So, make a note of
these weekly levels. Your previous week
low, uh value low, 741. That's the main
one that you probably need to be looking
at right now.
All right, into the hourlys. Just focus
on here with me. Let's move this down.
Focus on here. This right here is the
current weekly profile, the developing
weekly profile. You can see for now we
are trying to find a bid outside of it.
So what did we do yesterday? As a
reminder, here's your old naked point of
control. We drifted under it overnight.
We back tested it. We held it in New
York. We went very, very, very, very
choppy, but we held that naked point of
control. This was the buy zone that I
kept talking about earlier in the week
and back end of last week and the
newsletter where we'd probably find a
dip. All right, this was your 930 on the
old contract 930 level.
So since then, we are now building out
one of these, aren't we? Right, there's
a new channel being built out. The
question is, is this a continuation
channel to sell? Because I'd say the
strong high is there, the low is there.
This is your swing point. Right now, we
are trading within this swing point and
we just failed at 70 fib. So I'd be
aware of that. I'd be aware of this
channel, right? We're not technically
backside until we let go of this
channel. It's possible it might want to
come and sweep this high, maybe repric
some of this low volume node. All of
these things are possible. So, we need
to be aware of that. So, what does that
mean? There's two plays really I would
be looking at for today. If you're going
to look for the fail breaker out or the
look above and fail, you really want to
take out this high here, 520s into this
low volume node, and you want to see
sellers come in and absolutely smack
that back down and produce one of these
for a trade back inside this range. All
right, so your short opportunity will be
a rejection up here or an ad here. Um, I
would avoid trading in here like the
plague, folks. All right. I would not be
uh trading anywhere in let's call it
330s to 220s. Try and leave that alone.
You can see what's happened there. All
right, that is your liquidity build
area. For me, the easiest move if you're
going to play short is going to be
trying to sell that back into that
range. If you're looking for longs, it's
pretty simple. Either we hold the
current uh developing weekly profile or
more likely this move back into the
previous day. All right, previous day
value area high to find a bid around
here. There's lots of confluence around
this sort of 350 320 area. All right, so
something like this up that would be
TP1. And if you get lucky, you get a
move like that. All right, that would be
a 200 point banger if you get that
today. Would be fantastic. Those are the
two moves. If we just come back in here
and do this,
right, no trade day for Alex. I'm going
to make that clear now. If we're going
to trade inside yesterday's range, I am
not interested. I'm going to just
measure that out just to make triple
triple sure. But I'm pretty sure that's
accurate what I put out there. Let me
just check just in case.
930.
Yeah, that's good. That's good. All
right. So, those are the two plays. Look
above and fail or dips inside that hold.
Not going to trade yesterday's range,
right? Keep it nice and simple. Keep it
nice and simple because there's no big
news drivers today. All right. So, it's
very very very very very very
possible that today is just like some of
this and maybe a little fail break,
maybe a little fail break. It's very
very possible that we do something like
that today. Don't go giving your gains
back. All right? Don't go giving your
gains back.
And what did we do overnight? We can
have a look at overnight. All right.
Asia found a bid. All right. So that big
drive yesterday uh in Discord we caught
it from down here. We were long in the
afternoon
uh 200 around the 200s. 220 was the trap
level. That's where bears got trapped
and we played long. Very proud of a lot
of them got 100 points. I don't know if
any of them sat in more of it for the
next dip. Um we missed my target. My
target was 450. We missed it by six
points. My final target, but it was
there or thereabouts. And then
overnight, what have we done? Well,
after we came up to that target, there
was a big puke out overnight. We've gone
sideways, but we are holding the top
side of this range and you're seeing
expansion higher coming to back test
this 20-day and 5day. So, new range
maybe to be created here. We will see.
We will see. Nice and slow this morning.
I'm not going to be attacking it uh out
the gate, I don't think. Okay, let's
have a look what else we have going on.
We'll have a quick look at the ES and
the spiders and the Q's and the VIX and
the MAG.
Okay, so zooming out on the ES,
see where it is versus those levels. All
right, coming in for a back test of that
900 level we said was so key. All right,
so yesterday we left value. Remember
we've had value here. We had relative
strength. It finally left it and it's
finding a bid now and it's going to come
and back test that 900. That's your
level. That is your level. We go back
inside 900 then we're probably going to
chop. If they bears react to this then
they're going to look to retest towards
the lows. Right? So that's very very
similar kind of setup right now. Uh if
we look at the spiders you're going to
see the same thing is coming back into
that range. Right? Pre-market 680.
Remember remember the gamma levels that
we had on the way down. I said 75 would
be key yesterday. It's pretty much lower
day. [snorts] 75, 680, 682,
685, 688, 690. Those are the those are
the levels for you guys playing spiders,
but you're looking exactly the same
stuff. Does it reclaim the old level or
are we going to see a sharp rejection of
around here? All right. So, is this a
breakdown and this is a retest to sell
or are they going to reclaim and this is
look below and fail? All to be found out
in the next couple days, I would say.
>> [snorts]
>> Q's exactly the same thing. So, if
you're struggling with the rollover,
just make sure you're looking at the
ETFs.
It will uh do you a massive favor. So,
we can see where we found resistance
yesterday, this edge here. And you could
even argue there's a little shelf up
here right now, which maybe it can hold
if it can get through this and repric
this thin level. So, there's some
repricing to be done in here. Very, very
possible like we talked about. So, dips,
if they hold dips, we're looking for
that. And once we get up there, may very
well be looking for that trade back
downside. So, probably just trade in the
balance. Uh, let's have a look at the
Dixie.
Found a bid. It found a bid. So, well,
it'll be interesting to see how we act
here coming into the JPY carry, but
maybe one of these. Maybe one of these.
Kind of similar. Uh, let's have a look
at gold. I know some of you are trading
gold. Yeah, you're still in that same
range by the looks of it. We talked
about this yesterday. I can't remember
who asked me. Right, these are your
pivot highs. All the stops are up here
right now. Gold's creating a range in
here. All right, if dips hold, they're
trying to get back up up into this for a
breakout. All right, if they fail the
dips, you're going to come back in here.
That is a failure to take out the high
and we build liquidity and that can be a
little bit dangerous.
The VIX. All right, VIX is getting
melted this morning. All right, it's
getting melted back down this morning.
Let's zoom into this.
It's starting to lose some levels.
This is your new rotation right now.
Okay, you can see very very clearly if
we get under here
next pivots's down into here into the
sub 15s which is very bullish for the
market. So just waiting to see how we
act in the VIX. You can see it's going
it's very much like the rest of the
markets right now. We are just in a
rotation at level to level to level to
level to level to level to level to
level to level. We're just checking out.
All right, just think of it like I don't
know a stair. You got resistance above,
support below. You break support, you go
to the next level, you test it as a
resistance. That's all we're doing on
every single market right now. It is a
buildout. All right, MAG is interesting.
Some of these caught a bid. So, let's
have a little look here.
So, slight gap up there on Apple and you
can see really Apple would get going
over 7576.
All right. If it can get back over that,
we can maybe trade into the mid. Yeah,
76 is going to be key through that 77's
retest. All right. So, this is what
Apple's trying to do. It's trying to
create a sort of one two day base here.
If it can break out outside of this,
it's got a squeeze probably up into this
fib up into 77. So, it's got a couple
points in it if big if it can get going.
But, we do have a gap up there. Amazon,
you can see very big gap up there. Uh
this was on AI news. Um
so let's see if it can hold. You know,
AI has not been holding well recently,
but you know, if they hold this dip,
which they're trying to do, then then
maybe they get a bit of relief out of
this. It's what they're attempting to
do. Where are we in relation to
everything else?
Not too bad. Looks a bit backsidey, but
not too bad. Goo,
this one continues to be in this channel
down. Just waiting for this to peter
out. All right, this continues to be in
one of these. Eventually, we will
probably go sideways and catch a little
bit of a relief rally. So, just waiting
to see what happens. I'd say really
there's still nothing to do in Google
from a swing point of view. Meta, uh,
I'm still long in this. Um, up pretty
comfortably in this, but uh,
yes, what we going to do with this with
this thing here? I don't know. I'm long
from down here still from the 82s, I
think it is. Small size. still haven't
added, but let's see if Meta can start
to
box in a little bit
as the chance to come back up. All
right, so big if because this can be
like the market a fail breakout on one
of these for remainder of the year. So
very very similar to what we're looking
at in the cues opening up flat but is
above the base.
That doesn't look too good.
That really does not look too good,
right? One attempt, two attempts, lower
high, lower high, lower high, back into
base. Uh be avoiding anything on
Microsoft right now.
And Nvidia, this is the one that's uh
everyone's got eyes on, but it just
cannot get going. I don't I don't think
it's going to get going until the end of
the year. I can't see uh why it will.
It's had numerous attempts to reclaim.
You can see like the constant shove up
being sold into. So double tops up here,
alltime highs, failures, failures to
reclaim, failures to reclaim. There's
going to be a lot of liquidity built out
into these levels. If we get a snap of
that, it's night night time. But whether
I think next week becomes a bit cleaner
if I'm honest, but we will see. Tesla
looks very strong like we've talked
about for a number of weeks. It looked
good. I kept saying here, it looks good
for the breakout. Even this this hold of
this level looks good for the breakout.
Uh we are at alltime highs. 500's got to
be the target yet, hasn't it? 500's got
to be the target psychologically. We can
think about even the leg of the break.
Let's just zoom out of here and have a
look at some of these.
What's the extension 21s? And then let's
have a look at the handle
and the 2618 is 98. So just call it 500.
All right. Tesla wants 500. Whether it
can get there or not, I wouldn't be
buying now, but uh we've been calling
for this break. Too many people short
side on Tesla like always. Uh let's have
a look at some of the beta names.
Oracle, I'm interested in this once it
gets into and fills the gap. So, still
looks weak there. AMD should have caught
a bit of a bid
flat. It tried. All right. A little bit
no man's landy like we talked about.
Not expecting too much out of this
market today.
It just looks a little bit messy
and a little bit messy for me. Like look
how condensed everything is. So many
horizontal lines. I hate seeing that. I
hate seeing that. But we will see. All
right folks. Um what did you guys think
was going to happen today? Let's end
this poll.
Well, that says everything, doesn't it?
A third of you looking to just learn and
have fun. A third of you looking for
dips versus value area high. And a third
of you looking for a fail breakout. That
is uh Well, that says everything about
this market.
That says everything about this market.
Right. Here's the open, folks.
Let's see what we get.
on so I can see you guys.
Hit that like button nice and early for
me
and we will do some more giveaways
today. Again,
Apex did uh extend their uh cheap
activation fees until the 23rd. So, you
have a bit more time to pass those. And
uh on top of that, they did just launch
at 80% sale as well.
Okay, so most of the MAG other than
Nvidia looking okay. Here's the dip back
into previous day open, previous week
low VWAP. We're watching that sort of uh
previous day value area high level
around here to see do they want to catch
a bid into that level or not is what I
would be interested. Are they willing to
catch a bid into that level or not? Are
they going to close the gap?
That's what I would be thinking.
Just let this settle out and hopefully
we don't have the same problems as
yesterday. So far
the indicators in Ninja being very
smooth which is a good news. It's the
first day this week where I have not
woken up to major tech issues. Long may
that continue.
Yeah. Also $20 reset. Yeah, quite right.
Which is good. Some sellers getting
caught at the lows there being absorbed.
We haven't come into the level of
interest yet though.
Although we did come into that blue box.
I just missed the gap close there by a
little bit into 80s would have been
nice.
Oh, here they go then. Back to the top
side. Bulls piling in here. We didn't
get the level that we wanted to buy at.
Not yet. So, I'm watching it did come
into the blue box. I'm watching this gap
fill here and uh down here to see how we
at. So really, you know, I I would like
to see something like this would be
really nice. That that would be really
nice. We just want to be careful if we
get a backside move. So just let this
settle down.
See if the mag can catch a bid. Here we
come. Coming back into these levels now.
So gap filled potential. Ideally we come
and back test previous day value area
high and they find a bid there. If they
like I said if they don't find a bid
there um I will and I just got an alert
on Nvidia. some videos crossing downside
of a major level. So, you want to be
careful. I'm not willing to trade in
here today. All right. I'm not willing
to trade in this zone down here.
No chance.
No flipping chance.
So, they keep trying to sell 22s down to
400.
There we go. That's better. Wondering
what was going on there. [snorts]
Long for the day. Long for the day if we
can hold dips. Yeah, if we if we're
willing to hold. I mean, I don't really
like what we're doing right now here.
I'd rather see this close the gap first.
We came pretty close on the spiders and
pretty close on the cues. I don't like
it when we leave it open by that tiny
little bit. So, either we gap fill or
come down into previous day high and I'm
long biased if we show that buyers want
to step up and hold it. All right, I
don't want to be too biased because if
we let go of this range, we're going to
go into the death chop. So, we're long
if we can hold that and we're looking
for a breakout and we're going to sell
the breakout because it's very possible
that we're going to do a rebalance. Go
to the beginning of the show. Talked
about all of it.
Very tight range these opening few
minutes, folks. So, buyers get keep
getting caught over 22.
All right. Sellers keep selling that and
sellers keep getting caught into 400. So
you've got like a 20 point tiny little
range here. Just let it breathe. You're
4 minutes into the day. Haven't even set
that opening 5m minute bar yet. Let it
breathe a little bit.
See what we get here. Give a read out on
the mag. Tesla 0.85% up. Nvidia 1.85%
down. Microsoft 0.10% up. Meta 0.10% up.
Google half a percent down. Amazon just
under 1% up. Apple 30% down. So like we
talked about mixed bag. Oracle still
getting smacked. mixed bag in the MAG,
right? Rotate. We've seen rotation out
of tech recently or at least out of the
AI risk names into some of the safer
assets, even into some small caps, which
is why you've seen the RTY have relative
strength the last few weeks. Here we
come. So maybe, sorry, let's move this
up. We're getting this gap fill now. All
right, down into here. Just going to
remove this white line. We know where it
is there or thereabouts. And just try
and clean up this chart again because
everything is so tight.
one. It shouldn't look like this though.
Give me one second
a little bit ugly. Let's just reload
this.
It just does it horizontal without all
the little bumps in it. There we go.
That's better, isn't it?
All right. So, coming near to this gap,
Phil. Near to previous week low, near to
previous day close. Sellers got caught
down there again. We still haven't quite
closed the gap. ES hasn't quite closed
the gap. We're watching to see if they
close the gap and then if they come into
previous day value area high. And this
is the kind of area where I'm interested
in bidding in. If they hold this, I'll
consider it. But I want to see if
they're willing to hold yesterday's
value area high. If they're not willing
to hold it, I will not be bidding on it.
Right? I'm not bidding against it.
[snorts]
Make that clear.
Okay. Gap now filled on the Q's. Not
filled yet on the spiders. Still got a
little bit of downside to come.
There we go. All right. Coming into
these levels. Right. So now I'm
interested to see if we're willing to
hold these levels. We might not be
willing to hold it. So I don't want to
bid against it. I want to see sellers
get trapped. So here is SPY now filling
its gap. And we are into these key
levels, folks. So, are we willing to
hold previous day value area high,
previous day point control around here?
If we're willing to hold and we're going
to trap sellers, I'm willing to buy. If
we're not willing to hold, then I'm not
willing to do a thing. I'm not going to
trade in yesterday's range. Yesterday
told you told [clears throat] you
yesterday showed you in that range how
choppy it was.
So, I'm selling at the lows here.
Starting to start to get caught. Not
seeing enough yet, though. Here we go.
Starting to see a bid. I'm
[sighs]
small size here then. Very small size
and stop already in place. Let's see.
It's got to get back through these 60s.
Here we go. Here we go. Fantastic.
All right. I'm going to sell a little
bit of a pop into this because buyers
just came in there and got hit with a
refresh seller. So, I'm being very, very
cautious as I start the day here. Not
convinced we finish the auction, but
sellers are trapped under 40 right now.
So that's the level it's going to have
to hold. Doesn't hold 40, then I think
we reflush down and we can think about a
reload if and when [snorts] they retrap.
But all the time we're above 40, sellers
are currently stuck on the lower time
frame.
Got to hold 40 here. Got to hold 40
here.
[clears throat] Testing it. Testing it.
Testing it. Do not hold beyond 40. There
you go. Breaking 40. Reclaiming. Okay,
that's good sign. They're trying to sell
through it and not getting their way.
>> [snorts]
>> Do not hold under 40. Okay, do not hold
this under 40. They can snap very, very
hard. This is why I've already locked in
some profit here. [snorts] They're
retesting. You can see how sensitive
this 40 is. It's where the sellers keep
trying to sell and they're not getting
their way.
But you want to be careful because if
the absorber moves out the way, this
will flush hard. All right, I'm now out
of this. So, just a scalp to start the
day. Can always reload. Oh, you mother
[\h__\h] [laughter]
Why couldn't you turn up before I took
my stop? Eh,
you little prick. You little prick.
[laughter]
All right, just
[\h__\h] hell, mate. Give this a second.
H that's a nice hold. Really good hold.
Now, uh buyers do keep getting a little
bit caught here into 60. So, there's
only about 20 point rotation here.
Waiting for this ledge to be built out.
You've got a ledge at 45. I would still
say if they let go 40, this will flush.
Just be careful.
Big sellers coming in here. And if they
get caught at 40, it' be the same thing.
I'll get some volume on here because we
are actually developing a bit of a shelf
early.
Very early.
I'm [snorts] flat on this at the moment,
folks. We had I had a little scalp up
there. Just waiting to see now. All
right. little scalp up waiting to see.
You can see how sensitive this 40 is,
right? Every time we're banging into it,
there is someone trying to absorb it.
But if he runs out of bids, you're going
to see a flush. I'm just warning you
that now.
And the next level down would probably
be into 75 and 60 right around here. So,
they need to hold this really. Sellers
got caught there again into that low of
day. This is a battle here. We are in a
technically in a cell, but I'm just
watching if we're going to go in
rotation, they need to hold this. So,
I'm still flattening this. I had one go
for a small little scalp
and uh sellers are piling in here. Mag
is starting to roll a little bit, so
maybe a deeper dive. This is my nogo
territory. If we're going to fade into
this, I'm not interested in touching it.
Technically, we can rotate down to
there, but I really don't want to trade
yesterday's range. I've made that clear
from pre-market. That is not the trade
I'm looking for today. We're either
going to go expansion and I'll trade
upside or we're going to do a fail
breakout of the high and I'll trade
downside. I'm not going to trade in the
chop zone.
There they go. So, more sellers get
caught at 10.
Technically now red on the day, not me.
The market is technically red on the day
because we're underneath PDC.
And we just see here
trying to reclaim its PDC here. It's
attempting to reclaim. We're attempting
to push. We're attempting to trap. Are
they going to have another go here?
Yes, they are. So, they're reclaiming
40s. This is very, [snorts] very fast
moving at this point on the tape. Just
be careful here.
Tempted to have a bid here, but this is
fast, fast moving on the tape. Someone's
pissed off.
40 remains key. Sellers now got stuck at
20s. They're trying to resell 40s back
down to 20s here. And let's see if these
sellers remain stuck at 20s or not. But
I don't want to bid against this until I
see a strong reclaim. Are we doing for
time? 4 minutes left until they or set.
So here's the retest of these 20s.
Do they leave these sellers stuck or are
they going to reflush? Looks like a
reflush coming into 300s. Here we come.
Strong selling on the tape today. I'm
not going to bid against them. Like I
said, now we're underneath value. This
is a no trade zone. I'll just sit this
out. Let this do whatever it is need it
needs to do. If they really want to sell
this down to value, by all means, they
can go for it. I do not care about that
trade one bit. Not one bit.
London low. London low's uh been and
gone. You you probably mean GlobeEx low
into the sort of 94s or something. The
uh Asia low. London lows been and gone.
London low was around sort of 79.
Okay. Okay, sellers got caught at that
low there for just a nancond. Let's see.
SPY coming into its 20-day. So, SPY
about to complete its mean reversion.
VIX is starting to break out. This is
looking pretty heavy sellside. So,
again, not bidding in this zone. They
will have to prove themselves to me and
want to reclaim levels otherwise, well,
there's not really much I can do with it
basically is what I'm trying to say. I
can't do much with it if it's going to
come into my nogo [clears throat] zone.
car sore throat this morning.
Let's watch. Delta is offside at 22s
sell side. So they're comfortable at the
moment. They will become offside if we
print back above 22s and then there
might be a nano squeeze up to 40s. 40 is
the level I'm interested in trading in
and around. I'm not interested in
anything else right now. There's the tap
of the 22s where that seller was. He
refresh sold it. So he's still in
control right now at 22s. He's reloaded
on the tape here as well, making himself
known. So, we're watching if they're
going to break out. They're going to
have to get back above 20s. Otherwise,
these sellers are well in control right
now. Here's the test of 20. So, they're
coming up into this guy. He's still
reloading on the tape here. He's
reloaded again and again. And now we've
popped him. Do we see relief through 20s
now? It's a failed breakout. He's just
reloaded again at 20s on the back side
of this. Balls need to get back above
20s. Here they go. So, they're going to
try and rotate from 20s to 40s now if
they can, unless this fella comes back
in a little bit higher. Still can't get
through 20s. They're trying. They're
trying. They're trying. They're trying.
They're trying. They're trying. They're
trying really hard here. We've got a
passive seller on the book now because
we've just tried really hard to push
through and not getting acceptance.
Definitely someone reloading 20s over
and over again. Sellside. Here you go.
So, bulls had a really good attempt
there. Can get through. There's a reload
refresh seller there at 20s. This is the
battle now. 300s to 20s. And if they get
through 20s, 40s, if they fail, uh, 300s
and we're going to come straight back
down into 65s.
Still waiting and watching. Still in my
no trade zone right now. We have to get
out of this zone for me to be interested
in doing anything today.
I do not want to trade yesterday's range
because if you just zoom out and look at
yesterday, it's pretty ugly that range,
isn't it? We don't want to trade there.
And we've now lost developing weeks uh
point of control. Developing week point
of control at 340 as well. So that will
be previous day value area high
developing weak point of control 340.
That's your overunder for the day.
That's your sentiment shift for the day
in my mind.
Sellers still in control here. They're
absolutely in control. We haven't even
popped this delta at 320s yet. So
sellers still in control here.
So coming back to test these 20s again.
Is that refresh seller here or is he
gone? Are we going to now start to move?
All right. And I'm getting interested
now. Popping through 20s. Can we reclaim
the 40s?
Remember that is your sentiment shift.
Higher time frame sentiment shift on the
day is 40s. 20 to 40s still remains a
rotation right now. So they're going to
try and refresh sell these 20s after
that fail breakout. 40s. It per my
interest and uh couldn't hold. So still
waiting to see are we going to move out
of this range.
Where do those buyers get a little bit
caught there? 35s.
VIX starting to break 1660s as well. New
lower day coming here. There's value
area low on the session. Sellers got
caught into that value area low. God,
this range is getting very, very tight
as we wash between these two levels.
Very, very tight. This range right now
feels like they're going to go expansion
into uh 72s at the moment, but we'll
see. 70s to 60s. Big seller coming in
there. So, stops all getting run here.
[clears throat] Your opening range now
breaking. Here you go. There's the 70s
that we just talked about finally coming
in.
And I think they sell through this.
Yeah, they've got complete control of
the market now on these sellers.
Big sell all the way down. All right,
they took control losing this shelf. You
can see into thin and we're going to do
full rotation to previous day value area
low. So, we're going to be unfortunately
in the area that I'm not prepared to
trade in. I do not have any ambitions of
trading previous day's value. When we
can look at how we uh reacted in
previous days value yesterday, it was
not very pretty.
It is not very pretty. So, I'm avoiding
all this area unless we reclaim an area.
I cannot see a trade that I really want
to take here today unless we're going to
go reclaim of v areas.
Can't place an order on top. My biggest
advice would be [\h__\h] leave top. What
are you doing trading with a firm which
is notorious for do having these issues?
Why are you still trading there? It's
not your fault. But what I would say in
instead of complaining about it, leave.
Leave that firm.
posted about it a year ago, posted about
it three months ago, posted about it a
month ago, posted about it yesterday on
my Twitter. Leave a firm which is going
to keep failing and taking your money.
You do not want to be trading at firm
like that.
You're going to continue to have top set
X issues. All right, plat project X
issues. No one works with them other
than them now. All right, they don't
even have a developer. He left. He quit.
They wouldn't pay him enough money.
Michael Pek, too greedy. Do not trade
there.
Okay. To uh where's the level now? 300s
is the reclaim. That's your opening
range low value area low on the current
session. 300 is your reclaim up here.
You can see we're just developing
another shelf down here. Sellers are in
control here, folks. Sellers are in
control here. This is not what I'm
looking to trade. This unfortunately
this is not what I'm looking to trade.
So, we'll see. Unless we reclaim, I have
no interest in trading this. We talked
about it premarket. This is not what I
wanted to see today. I do not want us
just to go back in value, especially
after an aggressive sell without really
taking that liquidity at the high. So,
yet again, ENQ leaving that 520 high. I
would have been happy to trade downside
if we'd probably taken that first. But
there we go. And the move really for the
cell was probably 9:00 a.m. this
morning, before 9:00 a.m. even. But
we'll see. Let's see.
Maybe I'll think about taking an eval if
we're going to have a uh poor price
action day in previous days value.
Definitely don't want to trade my PAS
down there.
Yeah, Nvidia cracking those levels
dragging this market. Remember we got
that alert that went off.
Morning, Bella. Morning. Morning.
Okay, it's probably going to come into
value. And then remember this old naked
point control that we bid off yesterday.
I really didn't want to see us back
here. So, if we're going to reclaim, we
got to reclaim these shelves here. These
320s. Oh my god, we're going. [\h__\h]
hell, mate. Did we just hit a gamma
level? Where's Nope.
Okay. Well, I'm watching these same
levels upside. So, we got to get back
above 320s and 340s. Not just push.
We've got to start holding higher lows
above it.
Every push is being sold into this
morning so far. Every push so far is
being sold into. We do have someone
trying to step up on the bid at 75
there. Let's see if he's a Mr. Algo and
he walks away
trying to support a bid here.
320s and 340s remain the level for me
like real real interest.
So, I'm going to see some big flip in
delta here as we trade into point of
control on the session at 10.
What was the sentiment shift? I got
trying to remember. 340 is the big
sentiment shift.
340 is the big big sentiment shift.
Bit of a wiggle there. Bit of a wiggle
here. We're going to do a squeeze.
They're not bidding until we get down to
75.
Someone's got themselves caught down
here. Some sellers have got themselves
caught down here. Back into the opening
range on the day. Are we going to
revisit this 340? So, we've got a shelf
here. Sort of 315s.
Get through that 340s. Get through that
as bigger squeezes on. But until that
point, sellers remain in control because
we're underneath previous days or we're
inside previous day's value. We start
reclaiming though. It' be interesting.
It will be interesting if we start to go
reclaim.
I mean sellers still in control but
there are a ton of sellers on this
break. All right, think about how many
sellers came in here. If we are going to
we can't just poke above them. All
right, we need to do this and this and
then there's a squeeze until that point.
Right, this is where the sellers have
come in with size. If we do this, there
is a squeeze out possible. It's how
they've set it up is horrible. I'm not
tap tapping that and letting go of
previous day value. But
I wouldn't even call it a C setup. Uh
honestly, I would not even call it a C
setup.
[snorts]
Let's see.
I am watch. I'm interested in trading
the squeeze if they want to do it.
Here's value on the day again. Tens. If
we get through this, we're going to go
40s. And that's the big big big big big
level.
Is there anyone selling up at 40s? No,
they're selling 20s still. Okay.
I hate that we left the highs and I hate
that we left value area low. That is
nasty.
Here's Bpock again. If we get through
tens and 20s, the move is to 40s. That's
what I'm really really looking for. I
know I keep saying it out loud. It's
half of it is to tell myself, you know,
more than you guys to try and like tell
myself, don't predict. Just wait for it
to do it because it hasn't reclaimed
anything yet and it hasn't even hit
previous day value area low yet. Does
feel heavy. I agree. Pops is still being
sold. But all I'd say is from 947 to
948, a ton of buyers came in and got
themselves caught on that flush down. So
if we can stay above those uh ton of
sellers sorry in here tons of sellers
came in where's my right you see all
this sellside heavy this breakdown right
and then we shifted delta and they tried
again so if we hold here and do this
they will remain stuck which is what
they're trying to do and sellers are
here this is why I'm watching this 340
that is the move that's possible if
these sellers start to cover so I'm just
watching this on the delta and on
footprint and on foot map to see what
happens. We're right into point of
control on the day, right? Big big
shelf. This is the most traded level so
far today is right here.
[clears throat]
What trading platform? Um well, trade
buy your accounts on trader bait and
then you can choose a platform that
suits you.
I I execute on Ninja Trader, but if
you're web- based, if that's why you use
Project X, just get used to trading on
Trader Vape. So, we're going to come
fill some of this imbalance that we just
talked about. The key now is do these
sellers stay stuck? What I don't like I
talked about, we've left this, right?
So, we left liquidity at the highs by
how much? Not very much. By like a
couple points and we've done it at the
lows so far as well. It is um Yeah, it's
naughty, naughty, naughty, Mr. NQ.
you're uh doing it on purpose, but it is
rollover week, so to be expected. Again,
we're dancing in this range. I do not
want to trade in. Come get out of this
range.
Yes, I know. Well, guys, I'm going to
tell you something. Maybe you're new
here. Stop [\h__\h] trading on Topstep.
There. There. I've said it. Said it
aggressively. Stop wasting your [\h__\h]
money paying Michael Pek
for nothing. He's not going to fix it,
guys. He's so focused on moving to a
brokerage account, he can't even have
you trading on SIM and look after you.
And now he wants to go give me your
money so I can crash a brokerage account
and take all your money. Just stop. Stop
giving them money. [\h__\h] him. [\h__\h] the
guys that trade over there. It's all
[\h__\h] It's a facade. They try and
act like they're better than everyone.
They're not. They're not better than
everyone. They're the opposite. So, stop
giving them your money. Instead of
sitting here telling me it's down again,
it's down again. You've been doing that
all year. This isn't me digging you guys
out, but you need to stop and look at
yourself. If it's down yesterday and it
was down again today and it was down 3
weeks ago and it was down four weeks ago
and it was down two months ago and you
know the web developer left and it's a
web-based pro platform, why are you
trading there? That's what you have to
ask. Why are you trading there? Would
you buy a car which is breaking down
over and over and over and over and over
again? You wouldn't. So, don't waste
your money on someone that wants to
steal money off you.
There you go. It's a little rant, but
it's to protect you guys. I've made my
feelings clear about this, not just on
this stream, for probably over a year
now. All right. They failed to break the
low there. We're still developing this
like sort of shelf in here. Those
sellers definitely got caught in that
imbalance into 70 there.
Watching this to see now if we're going
to pop because sellers definitely got
caught into that imbalance. If we're
going to get through the teens, then we
can trade up to the 40s. And that is the
what I'm really interested in is how we
act once we get up there. I'm really
interested this at the moment because
they're starting to try and aggressively
get this through the 20s. This is the
level. If they get through 20s, we're
going 40s. Bing bing bing bing bing bing
bing bing bing. Can you get us through
this level? Buyers, can you get up to
40s? Don't want to see a fa failed
breakout. I need to see continuation up
to 40s. Otherwise, it's a two-legged
that they're going to come and smack
back down. And we're looking at this
seller who's caught up here. That's
where I want to trade his pain. So, we
had sellers come flying in here, get
themselves caught. Big sellers were
traded in here. All right. This seller
is getting squeezed to here. If we
squeeze this guy out, we're coming
straight back upside. So that's why I'm
watching the 40s.
Here we go. Through the 20s, please. Can
we get through the 20s, please? Get up
to 40s and offer me something really
good for the day.
Here we go. Come on, baby. Get me my
40s. Let's [\h__\h] go.
Let's go, baby. Let's go.
Little bit off. Little bit off. [snorts]
I want to add back on if we get over
40s.
O, you got to get back over 40s. Need
the seller to get caught and him become
my liquidity to sell into.
Let's [\h__\h] go. Get over the 40s.
Buyers keep getting stuck there. Down to
one. [snorts]
Let's see. Let's see. Let's see if I'm
right here. We got to get back over this
level.
Come on. Abuse this [\h__\h] here at 40.
Let's go, [\h__\h] Let's go. Let's
go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's
go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go.
Squeeze. Squeeze. Squeeze. Squeeze.
Squeeze. Don't let him reload this. Do
not let them reload. Previous day value
area high.
Let's go. I need to look below and fail.
We need to go upside. Upside. Upside.
Upside. [\h__\h] go. Let's go, baby.
Let's go, baby. Rip some faces here,
please.
Do not want to fail back inside. Do not
you do not [\h__\h] dare do this. Hey, at
least I paid myself. Still holding one.
Want dips to hold into 20s and tens.
Really, there's some couple imbalances
from that squeeze out. They need to hold
20s and tens. They definitely cannot
become back below tens. Sellers are
currently offside under 298. So that I
mean that's the last I wouldn't be
holding down to there, but
if they reload here in 20s and tens for
a resqueeze up, it would be really good.
But definitely sellers are stuck under
300. So you do not want to see this go
back under the 300s right now. Let's go,
[\h__\h] Let's squeeze this.
Come on, baby. Come on, baby. Come on,
baby. You've got it in you.
Some more sellers here into 30s and 25s.
They're protecting previous day value
very high right now. I need to be very
careful if they keep protecting that
because that is uh saying that we want
to go back into the rotation again from
yesterday. Remember, we didn't hit
previous day value area low. Here's the
move back into 20s.
Some sellers coming in here at the low
of this candle.
They're caught again. Can we see
expansion higher now? Caught them
offside again. Got to get back through
value through 40s and we will squeeze.
They're trying to refresh sell this into
40s. It's getting tight here.
We just need to get through 40s for a
squeeze out now. Come on. We caught some
more there. You've got to get back
through. Let's do this squeeze out. You
don't need to reload one more time.
Squeeze it out now or I'm out. Squeeze
it out now. I'm out. Oh, you
[\h__\h] playing around games.
You idiots. You idiots.
Someone wants to play games between 20
and 40. So, I'm not going to sit through
it. I'll just rewait now for us to get
close back over 40 for a read.
Not done below. Yeah, I mean it's
possible, but uh like I said, sellers
are caught under 300. Until sellers get
back under 300, they're in trouble. They
might well come back under 300. Now,
here's the retest. This is where the
delta got stuck last time, right into
this 300. If they close back under here,
we're going to go lower of day because
we did not get down to here, but made
good money on that last shove up. just
what we needed to get a close over 40.
Well, I didn't read add until we got
over 40s, but now we're waiting. So,
here's the 300 test. This is where all
the sellers got stuck and they still
remaining stuck. They're still covering.
If we flush this, we're going lower day.
This feels like yesterday. Looking over
at spy and VWAP at the moment. They've
got to get back over the VWOP on the
spiders.
Not going to rebid this now. It's had
its one attempt. This could be one two
that is resold down. So, I want to be
careful because they re one two leg.
They can resell it. I was positioned
for Where's my pen? for this move here.
They failed. So, if we get one of these
now, they're going to come right down
into this because they haven't tagged it
yet. And we know this is the old naked
point control. No longer naked. So, it's
just an old weekly PC down here. They're
under 300 now or there or thereabouts.
Just having a look at the mag here. Mix
bag. Equally weighted down one point uh
0 point one point 0.18% on the day.
Equally weighted on the mag.
Here we go. Low day. Probably coming now
into value area low.
Buyers had the chance. Failed. And we're
back into my no trade zone. So, just
wait this out. Now,
this is sloppy uh delivery here at the
moment.
It feels uh watching the tape feels like
two guys are a little bit stuck either
side of each other cuz that battle that
20 to 40 uh that happened, what time was
that rotation?
Where was that horrible
shove and puke? Was it here? Yeah, here
at 10:00 a.m. that new candle that was
uh kind of gross.
Uh both sides, not gross, one side. Like
it felt like they were stuck against
each other.
They're not getting closed below 300
here. These sellers,
it's like micro squeezes. Someone's
positioned offside here. It feels like
the sellers are positioned offside under
300s to me. Now you just held it again.
So they're going to have another go for
this 20 to 40 rotation.
Stuck at 25. You can see the sellers at
at 25. So there's a passive seller here
at 25 30. Well 40 50. If we get through
him, we're flying. So they that 300
seller I talked about is still stuck.
We're holding this shelf. 50 is the
level now. If we get through that,
there's a big old squeeze. I am back in
this now from 310.
Value area high here is key. If we get
through value area high, we are going.
Come on.
This is your second attempt. You can't
fail a second attempt. They're
refreshing up here again. Oh my god,
these games are crazy. [snorts]
There's a buyer moving his price down.
Okay, we got a big spoofer on the tape
now. [\h__\h] hell. He's definitely stuck
if he's spoofing like that. 100%.
Now he's trying to walk back in.
Let's think about this. He's bidding
lower. Pulling it. He's He's the seller.
If he's bidding and pulling, he's the
seller.
So, he's spoofing to move this lower.
I'm out of this. If he's going to spoof
to move it lower, I don't want to play
because it means he's a seller.
So, I'll just wait. I'll wait for a
close back over 40 to buy this. Now,
sorry, I have to talk out loud in my
head sometimes.
talk it out loud in my head.
There you go. So, he's reselling it. So,
he was spoofing the bid so that he could
come in and sell it and then he's
pulling his bid so that we can flush
down lower. That's why I had to say it
out loud. Head's still waking up here
this morning.
Head is still waking up. 300 is still
the level point of control. Uh if they
break down under here, this is actually
a fail to move higher. Now trying to be
uh neutral looking at this. This is a
fail to move high. If they break this,
then this is available. But this is
where the sellers got stuck. This 300
and this is the range. You got 40 points
here.
So you got 300 to 20 rotation, 20 to 40
rotation. Over 20 you need to break 50s
and then the squeeze is on. And they
keep refresh selling into these 30s up
here. You can see it on the T. See this
guy's just walked down again.
Real real messy. Real real messy here.
They going to come fill these guys at
40s and 50s. No. Refresh seller again
here. No one bidding back up now. What
are we doing?
I'm going to go 40s, 50s, and clear now.
Come on then. Go. If you're going to go,
you're fuffing around so much. Come on.
If you're going to go, go
value area high. We got to get through
value area high. Through value area
high, there's a squeeze up to 70s.
Through value area high, there's a
squeeze up to 70s. Remember, this is the
pain point from that big seller this
morning we talked about. I'll go back on
bookmap and show you him in a bit.
Should squeeze through here. Here comes
the 50s. Buyers were offside here before
at 50s. That big seller is at 57.
The old big seller, the old delta is at
57.
We should go and test him. Really
spy and ES now through VWAP looking much
better as an alignment. VIX got crushed
back under previous days low. Alignment
is upside. It's just depends if this
refresh seller is going to keep being a
pain up here. And the answer right now
is yes, he is.
My god, why won't you let it retest?
So, they're leaning on previous day
value high right here. They're leaning
on this level to try and resell. This is
another failed breakout to the high
side. All right. So, this is two
attempts now to break out. One, two.
They cannot get through here. The more
they try, the more buyers keep trying up
here, the more they get stuck. Sellers
are now stuck down here. This is the
rotation. If sellers win, they will get
this. If buyers win, they will get this.
This is your liquidity buildout. It's
tight range liquidity buildout, but
that's what you've got. So, 300 to 40 is
basically your liquidity buildout.
I'm waiting to see if they were abused
some of them, but right now nothing.
Back down to 300. So that refresh seller
coming in again, not even getting
filled.
Back to point control on a day. Huge
liquidity build out here, folks. Sellers
right now are caught offside. There's
big delta at 300 and then more at 90s.
That's where the sellers are caught.
buyers are caught offside at 336, 338,
347, 350, which we haven't tested for a
while. That's that's your rotation,
right? That's where it's testing each
side of until we base above or base
below one of those levels. It is nothing
more than volume being built out.
And SPY rejected VWAP again and VIX
catching a bid off previous day low. Oh
my god, this is messy. Can you please
make your mind up? Well, to be fair,
we did say in here is going to be no
play because of what happened here
yesterday, right? If you look at
yesterday,
it's telling you what it's going to do
in here. So, it's why we need to wait to
get back above value.
Doesn't look very good though, right
now.
Does not look very good right now, I'll
tell you that.
This is like yesterday. SPY can't get
back above its VWAP. All day yesterday,
SPY was holding us down. Every pop into
VWAP got sold until we came into that
last couple hours. Here you go. They're
taking control back to the 300. If they
sell 300 here, I would imagine we're
going to go lower day. If they can close
under 300 otherwise, same rotation 300
to 40 to 340.
Yeah, I agree. He was a seller. Exactly,
Raph. He was spoofing the bid because he
was sellside. Right. So, he was putting
bid support in and he was selling down
into it and then he was pulling the bid
hoping that we just fly through it.
That's why I was saying it out loud in
my head. I'm like, "Okay, if he's a
spoofer bid side, then he wants the
price lower."
Just waiting. Got to wait here. Got to
be patient. We're in my no trade zone.
Alex, you're in your no trade zone. You
said you would trade here. Don't [\h__\h]
trade here. You said you wouldn't trade
here. Don't trade here. Don't push
buttons.
I've had a I've had a couple attempts.
I'm up nicely on the day, but I did tell
myself I would not trade in this level.
So, maybe if I'm going to take
something, I'll take some emails, but
not not some P. Look at this moves
around 300. It's getting tight, folks.
Jesus Christ. This size coming in is
wild in this candle. What are you doing?
Someone's stuck.
Two people are stuck.
mental.
Let them fight it out. Matt, I'm going
to sit here and have a coffee and watch
bookmap.
Look at You can see in the last few
seconds we went 290 320 290 like quick
quick quick
level like a like a I don't know what
you call that. Spring. They're waiting
for one side to get stuck and pop. And
at the moment it's just a battle.
2370. If I got a guy above it, I can
see.
Yeah. I mean, you can see the big bids
are down at 237s.
Is that previous day value or low? It's
above it.
It's there or thereabouts.
This just does not look good. This looks
like yesterday.
This is why I said I wouldn't trade this
level because price yesterday showed you
what it wants to do on this level, which
is be a pain in the butt. The buys
yesterday,
uh, it was 220, right, chat? The guys in
mind our Discord, we were bidding off
naked point of control, break of 220.
There's the squeeze. That's where the
sellers are stuck from yesterday. You've
got short sellers stuck down here. They
will remain stuck down here if we don't
let them out. So we also need to think
about that because that there was big
size stuck down here yesterday
and this is the the key level. So if
these guys remain stuck, we drift
upside. If these guys are let out,
we can't rule out this. We can't um I'm
not thinking about that until we get
undervalue and until we we have to
reject 220 and 200 and then we can think
about that melt to 800s. I didn't think
it would come today. I'm going to be
honest with you. I did not not think
we'd do this move today. I still don't.
But I'm aware of it. Saying it out loud
because I'm going to have to shift tone.
If we start letting those sellers who
were stuck from yesterday out, if we
start going into a major sell, we have
to be aware of that.
Have to be aware of it. Almost 500 of
you watching. Thank you for joining
everyone new here.
Thank you for joining. Smash that like
button. Smash subscribe. I'm here Monday
to Friday.
from just before the New York open 9:15
in the morning New York time. We go
through pre-market analysis. The levels
I'm looking at, the trades I'm looking
at today. Been very clear at the trades
I'm looking at. Actually, none of them
have come in. If I'm honest with you, we
didn't get the look above and fail and
we haven't held value. We've gone right
back into yesterday's range, which was
the one trade I said I did not want to
take. The only other trade I would
consider, if we lose yesterday's value,
like I said, if we start losing
yesterday's value, we have to be very
aware of this weekly level. It's a 50%
pullback on the fib. It's an old naked
point of control. But if we start
rotating under here, there is a sell
previous day low and this is the next
target. That's based on the daily
profiles. All right, if we go back to
the dailies for those of you who might
be joining late, it's important to make
sure you're zooming out, understand
where we are. All right, if we are going
to keep losing this, we it's possible
we're going to test the bottom side of
this shelf again. This is the old PC.
All right, and if we lose that, the next
level was really 800. I would expect
buyers, like I've been saying, I expect
buyers will try their best to defend
this area. This can easily be a
rotation. You can see this part of the
D-shape. This can be a rotation here.
So, we need to be aware of that. Balls
really technically don't take control
till you see that from a technical point
of view, but they will try and defend
this level here.
It's back on. Sorry, folks.
Okay, so they've caught them again
in and around these same levels. We're
getting a huge node now starting to be
built out. It's a 10point node. You can
see this. Do you remember anyone that
was here yesterday? The gray box, which
was the rotational box. Well, it was
probably around here. It's here again.
All right, that is your rotational node.
Until we leave that, until we have a
breakaway from that, you can see this
refresh seller here. 366 lot. is trying
to refresh sell at 320s.
Green on the day. Staying patient now.
Perfect. That's all you got to do. That
that is our job every day. Thinking
about purchasing the program. Does the
indicator draw the volume zones out? No,
we do that like ourselves manually. You
bet. Honestly, you're better off to draw
it manually as well. Getting good
habits. All right. Filling this seller
here at 20s. Are we going to start to
squeeze through 20s? Is it going to get
back to the 40s? Is it going to reclaim
40s and go for a squeeze through to 50
and VWOP at 65? Or are they going to
refresh sell these 20s and look for that
rotation again? We are. See the gray
box? We can do you know what? I'm going
to remove this just to clean it up a
little bit. All right, that's your
rotation. We've got another little node
here. Can they find acceptance above all
of this area or is it just going to be a
pot to sell into again?
So, New York view up here. They're going
to have to clear. There's lots of
problems now. You got previous day point
of control. Uh developing profile point
of control is this thick red line. New
York view up previous day value area
high. Above that there's a squeeze out
until that it looks a little thick to do
anything.
They're based on VP Nick. Yeah, based on
VP. I do look at uh TPO occasionally on
a 30-inut chart, but to be honest, if
I'm looking for like single prints and
stuff, I can see it anyway.
back to the 300 then. So the 320 to 300
rotation continuing
until we get a close outside of one of
these levels. We don't really have an
edge in this market. Sellers trying to
get aggressive here.
This is where they keep selling. The
biggest delta on the day is right now
sellside at 298 and they just caught
them again. Right? 298 is the biggest
sellside delta and then 250 right so
they need to get under 298 to get down
to 250
having another go here es rejecting VWAP
again here but it's holding its 20-day
zoom this
It can't get a close either way here.
This is so ugly at this point.
Back to 300.
Are they really going to sell this? Are
they going to resell this? I should say.
Can they get a close? No, they can't.
Trying again. They're trying again to
sell and and again to sell. They're
trying again to sell. They're struggling
here. There's definitely a little bit of
passive buying. Well, a lot of passive
buying trying to absorb the tape here
cuz they've had numerous attempts to get
under that delta level
and a reclaim again. Wow.
Back to the 20s. Maybe
passive selling here. 10 15 20. We're
just in a very tight range here, folks.
While they make their mind up,
rejecting VWOP again. So spy is stuck
between 20-day and VWOP. It's basically
at its mean reversion. That's what
you've got on the spy. And the ENQ
or the Q's are well, they're below every
key moving average right now. But we're
not getting follow through to the
downside that they keep looking for.
And this is terrible.
This is like yesterday. No follow
through. sellers should take control
here at this point. Like they've had
enough opportunities to take control.
Kind of weird that they're not in many
ways. You know, you've got the
opportunity. Why not grab it with both
hands?
Failing again there at the lows. [\h__\h]
hell, sellers.
Back to 300 again.
Oof. Oof. Oof. Oof. Make your mind ups.
Back to test 300 again. That's where
that delta was offside. volume point of
control on the day now three or six.
We're starting to move away from volume
point of control but we're not seeing uh
follow through down to value area low on
the session now. Can they expand this
under 80? No is the answer so far.
Sellers came in again got absorbed
again. So there's still a passive buyer
here and there's still a passive seller
above. Passive sellers were at uh 340s
then they moved to 320s now they've
moved to 300. They need to stay in
control of 300. If they stay in control
of 300, there is a potential wash. Value
area low soaking again at 280s. Oh my
god, we're into anyone who's been
joining me here for months. We're back
into those 20 point range rotations on
NQ. That's what we're back into. So
really, sellers need to reject this
shelf. All right, they've worked really
hard to get back under this rotation.
Failed look, failed look, failed look.
They've worked hard to get under. They
need to sell this now back down to value
area low. If they fail to do that, they
keep flying in here. they cannot get
this break, we'll probably do this move.
And this is like your avoid at all cost
kind of area. You do not want to trade
this gray box, right? You can see every
time we come in a gray box, it's kind of
gross.
So that seller was 300 like we talked
about and we're coming to test him
again.
And again testing him.
It's all the way down at 240 right now.
I'm somewhat surprised.
Where are we at at spy? 78. There must
be a gamma level at 78.
Under that we go 75s. There must be. Can
anyone tell me is there a gamma level at
78 today on spy?
Bet there is.
I bet there is mate.
Market's gone to sleep.
Come on, market. You should move lower
now. You've had so many opportunities.
These sellers are doing a terrible job
if I'm honest. An absolutely terrible
job. Mag's starting to go green here,
folks.
Mag is starting to go green here.
Here's
the relief. Back to point of control on
the day now. This is so bad.
[laughter]
Back into that grain box. Reject point
of control.
Set still have an opportunity. All I'd
say is I'd watch this rotation on the
mag.
>> [clears throat]
>> back into gray box.
Oh my god. Can we have a trade today?
Can we move away from this one way or
the other? Please, market, please.
Please, please.
Let's
see where this is versus those
being a shell. Yeah, it's the next
level.
Just trying to find a beard back to it.
Still spy on VWAP. Still stuck. Look,
just look at the spy stuck between VWAP,
PDC, and 20 days. Right at your mean
reversion.
We have no edge here at the moment.
Literally no edge on any time frame
right now. back inside yesterday's
value. Probably at the midpoint of
yesterday's value, we've created
a point of control inside the midpoint
of yesterday's value until we see until
we get a break outside of these levels.
Uh you're going to continue to see this
kind of nonsense. Right, back up to
where that buyer last got stuck. 357
lot. We're now above him at 17. We're
going 20s. Like I said, the rotation is
starting to take place on the mag. This
is the one thing you want to be careful
of. Can we get back above 40? So, I'm
interested. I'm definitely interested if
we hold dips into 18 now cuz that's
where buyers came in. If we hold dips
into 18 and then we get back above 40s,
I'm really interested.
And his previous day point of control
and developing profile point of control,
you got to squeeze through 40s now.
You've done so much hard work.
Let's leave this range. Just leave this
[\h__\h] that you've created.
Okay. 40s, 40s, 40s. This is where we
keep trapping bulls. I want to see
continuation now. I do not want to see
sellers come back in and defend all
this. Otherwise, we're going back into
range, which will be like yesterday.
This is what happened yesterday. Every
time we came up, we defended. And I
don't want to trade range. I'm going to
avoid range. So, I want to see a break
away from range today. I tell you what
though, we are holding the opening range
low.
sellers here 45 50 65
are they willing to hold where is that
buyer coming 18s 18s is the level above
18s buyers are going to take control of
this market for me above 18's definitely
above 305
come on spy you're going to get through
your VWAP finally QQQ trying to do the
same
I will consider dips into 318s and I
will consider buys above value area
higher on the day if we can base above
which is 40s and 50s which we're
starting to now do
be careful we are like right into the
edge where buyers keep getting stuck up
here so I'll consider dips if 18s are
willing to hold not if they're not
so we at the moment we're just showing
another rotational day look at the
profile it's very much like yesterday
edge to edge I don't want to fade this
I'm waiting for a break outside of this.
Can you let me draw it? There we go. Or
what did we say? 18s. We're back under
it already. So, no dips and no trade. No
acceptance over. Can't even hold the big
delta that came in.
So, no trade here for me.
Same zone. And I'm not going to trade
this zone. If it's not willing to hold
key levels once it develops it, there is
nothing to do. I will happily trade
downside if we leave the zone as well.
I'm not going to trade in and around
this zone.
Just look left. Look what it did earlier
today. Look what it did here yesterday.
I do not want to trade this zone.
Oracle is getting slammed. I just got
price alert. We're getting close to that
gap now on Oracle. All right, so semis
must be getting [\h__\h] murdered. Nvidia
2% down. Oracle 2.73% down. AMD 1.6 7%
down.
What happens once we close that gap on
Oracle? That's a question. 178 was the
gap fill on Oracle, right? I think that
was a gap fill. Back down to value area
low on the day. Still haven't hit
previous day value area low. We are in a
tiny range rotation. Most of the range
is taking place here, folks. Uh 40.
Remember, we never got a close above 40.
40 to 280. So, you know, 60 points. You
got a measly 60 points. I'm not a range
rotation trader. I try and avoid these
like the plague. So, we have to wait. We
have to wait.
Do they complete the rotation all the
way back down to previous day value area
low? It's questionable. It's possible.
We can't rule anything out. Anything is
possible. But the moment, I'd say no one
is in control. Bears probably have the
edge, but no one is in control of this
market right now. Bears have the edge.
They should complete rotation. They've
had enough attempts to complete
rotation. They should really come down
to previous day value area low. But why
are they not aggressively leaving?
There is must be a passive buyer on this
tape on dips and there's passive selling
on the highs. So you got two
participants stuck is the way I'm seeing
this. You've got someone absorbing here.
You got a buyer absorbing this and
you've got a seller absorbing this,
which is why you're just getting this
with no continuation. If this buyer
leaves, they should complete this. If
this seller leaves, they should complete
this. At the moment, there's nothing.
There's literally no trade to be had for
in my mind until we leave this value.
Exactly. Barcoding. Yeah. Well, that's
it. This gray box, right? It's just a
barcode.
the fact that we're rejecting this.
We should should not necessarily will we
should complete rotation to here, but it
hasn't. I
I don't know why. Why are they being so
weak? If you're going to take control,
take control.
Spy man can't get below its 20-day.
Can't get above PDC. It's so ugly. It's
so ugly in balance.
Yes. Uh Tom. Yeah. Current New York
profile on the right, my friend. Yes.
Back into gray box again.
Uh the big buy delta is at 18. So we're
probably going to come back and test
that big buy delta. They should have
held that on the dip back down. They
didn't. Do they resell against it? This
is the 18s. They're getting back above
it again. So are we going to go all the
way topside? I have no idea, folks. I
don't know what they're doing with this
right now. SPY coming back to VW up
again. So it held dips into its 20-day
again. It's coming back to VW up again.
Again, I will be interested if we can
start to get closes and bases above 40.
I was interested in dips into 18s, but
we didn't hold. We just flushed straight
through. So, this delta 18s is not doing
anything right now. We have a 269
or sorry, 334 lot at 18s and a 255 lot
at 20's buy side. So, if they protect
that, they're in the money, but they
should have already protected it. We're
going to go back to 40. So, rotation
still happening. So, top of this range.
I'm interested over this. I am
interested over this. If we base over
this for a squeeze back out upside
at the moment, this feels like
yesterday. Well, yeah, it's just like
yesterday. Yesterday, just selling the
highs, buying the lows, selling the
highs. So, all they're going to do is
keep us in this 60 point range. I'm
good, thanks. I'm not playing a 60 point
range. I like 100 plus point players.
Wool is 610. QQQ.
Uh, well, we're over 610. Oh, you mean I
see what you're saying. You mean the put
wall. The put wall was 610. Is that what
you're trying you're saying Julian
market would be like this till January?
Um I think it's really it's waiting for
the carry trade which is the 18th and
19th of this week. Yes, I think once we
get out of that be all right. And
remember it's OPEX week. It's uh roll
over. You've got all the options
expireies. You've got roll over and
you've got the carry trade. When you get
out of that it gets much easier. Like
this week's always a piece of [\h__\h]
because uh you're moving contracts. Look
at this seller coming on the book 880
lot at 350. Now
these guys coming in with size here at
20s again. Make your mind up. Make your
mind up please.
Spy failing VWAP again.
Very tight here. Nothing to do here
today unfortunately folks.
Such a shame. But we had a great
afternoon yesterday. Okay, we had a
really great day Monday. We had a really
great day Friday.
Well, it's like 98% chance that Japan
are going to raise their rates.
So, if that happens,
it is very well, it's not very likely.
Historically, let's let's put this in
perspective. Historically, it's likely
that they will start to sell their
positions in the US market, especially
their growth positions, i.e. stock. If
they do that, all right, then you might
get a cascade because if they start
aggressively selling, you're going to
have a liquidity issue where everyone
else starts selling. The only thing that
I would say that I have in my mind is if
everyone's looking for that trade, it
won't happen. because people are more
prepared for it after what was it August
two years ago it happening people are
more aware of it now so I don't know how
we react I just know that it's something
that I'm going to watch I want to see
what happens
yes sir uh yes I do I just have it on my
other monitor I can only show can't can
only show you so much but yes I look at
footprints so all the buyers stuck up
here and we've had some sellers stuck
down here but the end of the auction is
actually buy side at the moment which is
uh not too good which means it probably
has Not finished auctioning lower
other than what is this low down here?
Yeah, it's not amazing excess down there
back to value area low on the session.
Are we going to go edgeto edge or are we
going to finally come for previous days
value area low?
Yeah, Josh. I mean, that would be the
hedge, wouldn't it? That would be the
hedge. And that and the reason gold's
moved up is that has been the hedge for
two years, right? Asian markets have
been moving out of the dollar. Here we
go. So, maybe now we have an imbalance
down here into 60s again. and sellers no
follow through. Still a passive buyer on
the tape down here. Sellers no follow
through.
They need to see follow through. You
really if if we're going to leave value,
right? If we're going to leave this
value, current day's value, I know it's
developing and point of control, they
need to come and tag this. This is to
complete the rotation. Why are they not
doing that?
Must be pacifying.
buying trying to step up here is 17 and
75. They should just flush him and go
down to 40 now. I wouldn't be surprised
if he pulls his bid.
110 lot here.
He's leaning on that old uh 285 delta
sellside that was there. We're probably
going to flush in there. Yep. Here we
go. All right. So, we're moving lower
now. Here comes the 40s.
They can't reclaim 70s. You've just
worked so hard to get under 70s. Come
down to 50s and 40s. Here you come.
Come, come, come, come.
Now on Ninja Trader, I have previous day
point of control down here. Just so
you're aware, folks.
Here we come. Okay, finally seeing that
aggressive move. Can spy leave 78.
Here we come.
Can we get down into previous days value
area low? Now, that's really the
question to complete the rotation. They
took so long, but they've built out
enough liquidity. Now, if you did take
this, uh, your cover points are where
you are right now. Previous day value
area low. This is your old naked point
of control. Previous day low is all the
way down here. I don't know if you get
that if I'm honest. I would imagine they
will try and defend this area here. So,
just I would be very, very careful.
You're into we're still within
yesterday's value. Okay. So, this is
your cover point. If you can get this,
this is your initial balance low. If you
can get this, fantastic. Right. We're
tagging into it now. So, make sure
you're paying yourself here, please. You
must be paying yourself here, please. If
you did take this break away,
yeah, Nvidia, like like we talked about
right earlier, like it's it's losing key
levels. I did talk about the price
alerts I had going off on it. Here's
previous day value area low. Make sure
you're paying yourself here, please. You
must must must be paying yourself. And
then your runners beyond this. Big
sellers coming in here at the lows of
this. They might get themselves caught
here. Just be careful if you get down
into this old point control. It's 180s
as your target.
[\h__\h] hell. They took all day to do
that. They took all day to do that.
Okay, into this green box. This is your
next target. 180. If we flush 180, then
you got previous day low. But I would
imagine, they don't have to, but I'd
imagine bulls will try and defend here.
So, I would be covering I'd be down to
like 20% of my size if I was you into
this level.
Really close to that PC. Remember, this
is a big level from yesterday. They took
so long to leave value, but really nice.
I mean, did any of you take that? Like,
congrats if you're a range trader and
you took this. We left volume. They took
so long to do it. There's the breakaway.
There's your cover point one. This is
cover point two. This is cover.3. If for
some reason they want to absolutely yank
this, then you got a 800s today. But I
doub I doubt they do that today without
news.
You see that? Starting to get reaction
in this green box. Make sure you're
trimmed. Nice. Lots of you got it. Oh,
that makes me really happy, guys. Those
of you who join here, who are new here,
you might be like, well, you didn't
trade. I don't trade range, guys. I will
call range for you all day, every day. I
don't trade range. I like expansion
models, but I will do my best to call it
for you.
Short ENQ, thank you for the commentary.
You're welcome.
Nice, Chris. 600 for Chris. Sloth with
the win.
Got the short in my M2K. Nice work.
2,000 out of the micros. Nice.
Sold. Sold now. 304 flat. Nice. Great
kitty with the win. Ronald with the win.
Chad hit two good shorts. Thanks, bro.
Nice work, folks. Lots of you getting
it. Myron, John Dennis,
George Bart,
Calypso, Ty Turner. Nice to see some old
names in here that I recognize.
You got approved for the payout this
morning, Richard. I love it. I love
seeing my students get paid. Nice work.
620 on that. Nice work, folks.
Okay, naked point. Well, it's not naked
anymore. Old weekly point of control.
This is a big cover point. All right,
around here,
around here, around where we are now.
It's a huge cover point. If you see
continuation, you can think about
previous day low. But, uh, like I said,
I would have maybe 20% left now if I was
you. If you took this break or leaving
this liquidity, I'd be having some more
off here and then waiting to see if they
want to come down in here. We are now.
There are two two trades set up now.
This very hard right right now. If we
reject value, we can trade lower. The
hardest thing is knowing how thick a
level this is. I'm going to make this uh
obvious to you guys.
This is possible. This is where we're
trading at. You see these two nodes?
This is current year's profile. Big
node,
big node. All right. I'm very aware of
these players.
So, that's the only thing.
All right. Here you go.
basically at that white line. Make sure
you're paying yourself. Do not be a dick
or a tick.
Nice, Richard. Nice work, my friend.
Really nice.
All right, white line is the old point
of control. Doesn't mean we can't keep
selling. Uh spy might really want to
come to 675 now, which is probably the
next gamma level. It doesn't mean we
can't keep selling, but you don't want
to be short down here at low of day. You
need to see a back test really of at
least previous days value area low and
maybe really even the shelf that we've
created. So I could argue right now, you
know, sellers.
It's hard for me, aren't you? You're
going to let me draw it. Sellers really
need to defend this. I'd even argue down
to here, right? Sellers are in control
if they defend this. Really, if they're
looking for expansion, they'd want to
defend this. If you see this, all right,
this trade here will happen. And if they
get through it up to here, right? If we
look below previous day value and
reclaim current day value, this trade in
here and here. So if you're desperate to
take the long, that's your look below
and fail level, right? So sellers will
need to lean on previous day value area
low. Buyers will want this to be a trap
underneath it.
Try and see what do we have on the tape
down here at the lows. We do have some
sellers
caught down here under 92s right now.
[snorts]
Is it worth trading the week of
Christmas or New Year's? Uh,
[sighs and snorts]
it really varies year to year, mate. I
would say, you know, let's deal with
that as we get into it. Um, it the
reason I'm saying that I don't know
where we're going to close this week.
Right now, we've hit my main target for
the week is is right where we're at now,
right? This white dotted line that this
was the main target for the week. We
need to see how we close this week. Um,
and and we can only really think about
what's coming ahead once we see where we
close the week, what liquidity we have
left to search for, and how we act. I
would be it would be irresponsible of me
to say yes or no. Is volume likely to be
lighter? Absolutely. It's likely to be
lighter. Does that mean there isn't a
good trade setup? It does not mean there
isn't a good trade setup. There might
well be some really good trade setups
for you, but I don't want to say it yet.
It's a little bit early. We have plenty
of time yet to develop what's coming
next. All right. Someone just tried to
sell 170 and got themselves caught. So,
you have some sellers down here starting
to try and aggressively sell outside of
170. They're retesting them now. Do they
get follow through is the question.
We have a buyer at 160. So maybe we're
going to come to him. Here we go.
So here's the trade to 160. Now question
now is do we see expansion into previous
days low?
Do we see expansion into previous days
low? Very possible. ES uh sorry spy got
another one and a half bucks to get into
75. We are seeing some excess left down
here, but sellers are very aggressive. I
would not bid on this market right now,
guys. We've left yesterday's value.
Until we return back inside yesterday's
value, there is no buying opportunity in
my mind. This is probably covering
opportunity, but no buying opportunity.
The buying opportunity will come right
if we do something like that. Right back
inside yesterday's value. This becomes
trap sellers, but right now we're
probably going to come into this level
at the moment.
Previous day low is at 25,72.
every pot being sold into. Still some
more uh limit covers here. Passive
players. 160 155 150. We probably fill
all of these guys on a little flush
155.
So here we go. that they're bidding
lower and lower. So, they're trying to
drag this market down. They're probably
going to come down into this.
This was probably it. It's kind of
nasty. It wasn't much of a push, but
that was probably the retest to sell.
This wick here, I missed it. It wasn't
enough for me, but uh there we go. Not
going to get everything. So, this is
your next target. 2573. If they're going
to go mega mega heavy, you're we are
talking about 24,800 today. If they're
going to go mega puke day, you're
talking about 24,800
to make you aware of what is potentially
available today.
At the moment, I'd say previous day low
is probably the target that they're
looking at.
They keep bidding and moving their bids
down, which is going to help this market
sort of look for expansion lower right
now because it's going to just search.
It's searching for value and it can't
find it. So, it's going to keep going
down all the time. It's searching for
value and it can't find it. It's going
to keep auctioning lower.
It's what you're getting at the moment.
Constant auction lower.
[snorts]
They're still auctioning though. And
they're still looking for value. There's
some bids here at 120. It's still going
to come lower. It's got no reason to
stop right now, right? There's zero
reason to stop at the moment. This is
very, very heavy.
Only thing, [sighs]
why is NQ done? This is a habit of it
doing it recently. All I would have
liked to seen today for this move was
just a poke into here. All I wanted to
see today is a New York poke into there.
And that they didn't do it. They are
They've become buggers recently. All
right, you're going to get your final TP
here. You're into blue box. This is
where we found the man before. This is
previous day low. If we snap underneath
that, you never know what's next. If
they snap underneath that, folks, you
just never know what's next. But I would
be trimming my positions if I was you
right now.
You can't rule out 24800.
You can't rule it out. They're still
searching for value. We have not found
value. ES, by the way, has taken
previous day low. SPY has not taken
previous day low yet. QQQ has taken
previous day low. NQ hasn't. So, we got
divergence. Just so that you're aware,
we are starting to see some divergence
across the indexes right now. Just
trying to make you aware. Um, there's no
reason to bid on this market in my mind.
We are breaking outside of value now. We
are trend trading lower. searching for
value. There is no reason to try and bid
on this market right now.
You are if you try and bid on this,
you're counter trend. No reason.
Every pop still being sold. There'll
probably be some relief at some point.
Maybe once it takes previous day low,
unless they cascade it. There probably
be some relief, but you know, I would
not bid on that. Why bid counter trend
when we're leaving value? Here
we go. Liquidity here. 195. Still think
they will probably trade underneath
that.
Once it snaps that shelf, it's probably
going to get pretty nasty pretty quick.
I'd imagine
it's where buyers keep trying to step in
and they keep getting passively sold. We
haven't hit that previous day low yet on
ENQ. We have hit it on all the other
indexes now other than SPY. ES has hit
it, but SPY hasn't.
So maybe a bit of relief here up to 150,
maybe up to 170 for them to resell it. I
don't know. I don't think they're done.
I do not think they're done.
You got the dappy.
You bugger.
You bugger not giving me the FBO.
They're going to come fill this guy at
150 probably and then see if they resell
it here or 170. There's probably options
right now. Here's the 150 or the move
into 150. It's a it's an old imbalance
here. Here's 150. Do they get if they
get through this, they're going to go
170 and then they're going to see if
they sell that.
This is 150. It's an old imbalance.
So, this is counter trend squeeze up and
uh if we get through here, then they're
going to check 170. All right. I'm just
looking at the imbalances on the tape
and the delta on the tape.
It's still for me it's still a sell.
It's if you're going to [clears throat]
trade upside, you're playing counter
trend. I'm just telling you the levels
it's likely to go and back test right
now.
ES did sweep previous day low, but I
still think there'd be one more attempt
to move lower here.
So, back under the 50. They're checking
this 50. They're checking buy side
imbalance now. 43 and then what's this
level here? 35 and then 20. So, here's
the one more attempt to move lower. If
they fail to move lower now then maybe
more relief but uh like I said I think
sellers are still remain in control of
this market.
Sounds a loss somewhere. Yeah.
[laughter]
His satnav went off, didn't it?
Japan stole him, I would say.
[laughter]
So good.
Oh, okay. Okay, there. So, there there
we go. There's the push and fail. We're
underneath this uh old weekly point
control. This is the target. They still
want to take this out if they can.
That's what they are trying to do. I
don't think the auction's finished,
folks. When I look at the lows,
I don't think this auction's finished,
but we'll see.
Bit of a wiggle here. Still don't think
the auction's finished.
I think we're going to trade lower here.
They're trying. They're trying.
[snorts]
Here we go. They're going to try and
sell this down. This is what I was
saying. I didn't think it was finished
yet. There they go. So, they just poked
above the 50. What did I say? 50 was
probably the level. 59 they got to. If
they got If they closed above that, they
were going to test 70. So, probably new
low of day coming here, folks. There's
some covers into 100, but you're
probably looking for previous day low if
they flush 100. So, it be interesting
how they act here. Can they get back
through this 100 mark?
Back to the 100 again. There still
there's someone front running this 100.
I think we're going to sell through it
honestly. And I think you might get a
little flush here. If you're still in
the short, you want to cover some onto
the next flush because it might be
excess.
And if you get lucky, you get all the
way down to previous day low, but
definitely want to be covering some if
you're still short in this into the next
flush. Big sellers keep trying here, not
getting their way. Be careful. I think
it will come, but I don't know it will
come. You should be runners only really
now anyway.
So, they're front running that 100. I
still think they let go of that 100, but
it might just take some time. They might
need more relief.
Buyers are trying and trying and trying
and trying here. I think they're going
to get hurt. Here we go. Back to the 100
again.
They can't get through this 100. So,
there's passive buying. Front loading in
front of 100. I'm very surprised we
haven't broken it yet. It's probably
coming 108.
Here comes the 100. Check. And we will
probably snap underneath this. You must
be covering un in into this region here.
Huge level.
Here it comes. Here it comes, folks.
Make sure you're covering some onto
this. There you go. Here comes previous
day low. All right. Be careful now
because the auction can end here. I want
to be make that very, very clear. The
auction can end here. So, previous day
low is your target. Below that is a
bonus, but we don't know how far down
this goes. Maybe you get the 800s.
Really nice. Congratulations all of you
who took that. Please make sure you're
paying yourself here. I don't know if
they end the auction here because we
expect that flush to wash everyone out.
I don't know if you get some divergence
and uh I'm just looking at spy as well
right that was the level we said they
pinned it there yesterday and absorbed
maybe we reflush through here's previous
day low all right you should be down to
very small size now looking for your
next level is 800s it is an absolute
bonus right it's 200 points away but if
you get that next level it's here but
just hold on to your runners now for
this because this could really really
pay you if Any of you managed to get
that retest up here or you're still
holding? You've hit basically every
target. Now it's just like do you get
lucky? Do we get a big expansion model
down into this? But you've hit all your
targets there.
You've hit all your targets there. Your
big money should have been made today.
All right. You've hit all your targets
there.
You do you should not how should I say
you should not expect more downside. If
you get more downside,
fantastic.
Do not expect it. Manage your positions
accordingly. All right, while this is
happening, I'm going to use the bathroom
and get a refill on my coffee and I'll
be right back. And hopefully when I come
back, we've puked to 800 or something
and then you guys can tell me how rich
you are. It'd be great.
All
right. How we doing, chat? We there yet?
Still selling. Nice. Still selling. All
right. W's in chat if you absolutely
murdered some of this today. Hopefully
you did. Again, like I said, there's no
reason to bid on this. All right. My
thesis, like I talked about
this morning, we needed to really hold
here for buys. Once we got inside here,
I became uninterested. That's
yesterday's value. Once we reject
yesterday's value, it's a sell down to
here or here and here. And if they keep
selling it, they keep selling it. We are
leaving value. There is no buy
opportunity right now in this market. We
are in a strong sell. The only buy
opportunity will be when this leg has
finished, right? and for whatever reason
they feel like they need a pullback and
maybe they trade back into kind of here
and you know that will be your counter
trend buy for them to probably resell
unless they reclaim. All right. So,
just be aware of that. If you're going
to play buys now, you are playing
counter trend because we're leaving.
Look, look, we're leaving IB. We're
leaving previous day value.
Okay, there are I will tell you this
now. There's sellers came in aggressive
into 2550 there. Um,
I would say really
a potential small squeeze can happen
back over 100. That would be like the
level of that countertrend squeeze where
it could take place would be back over
100. But I'd be very careful about
thinking about any longs in this market
environment. But there were definitely
some sellers caught down underneath uh
56s, but I really would not be touching
this long. I think it's very very risky
to touch this long.
Nvidia now 3.26% down. That thing's
breaking those key levels we talked
about.
Half W. I didn't murder it enough to
clear consistency rule. Thank you so
much. You're welcome. Yeah, lots of you
getting it, which is awesome.
I love to see it. Well done, folks. Well
done, folks.
Okay, watch uh you can set us a price
alert on spy. I'd watch that 75 over
under.
Uh if we fade that, I know that there's
gamma at 70. It's a [\h__\h] long way
down. Another 50 points for ES if we get
there.
I don't know if we do it today. It's
exposure for the end of the week.
Yeah, I know. It's mad, Adam.
Vick's trying to take out previous day
high. Not there yet.
So, we just had to wait for that chop to
end. Still more selling here.
Still more selling here. I'm going to go
back to that daily level. Got to have a
look here. We're coming right into the
edge of this shelf. All right, the edge
of this daily shelf is basically 25 and
33. Maybe they bleed it a little bit
extra. I'm just looking at the volume
profile on the daily. All right. Um,
that's for the yearly volume. If we lose
this, let me get you over here. This is
what I'm very aware of. I wouldn't be a
new seller down here. This node, this is
this is your volume from the whole year.
This is a big node. If they lose that,
the next one is at well, basically 25K.
There's a tiny little node at 25K. If we
lose that, we're thin all the way down
into this. Oh my god. Let's just move
this out a bit. We're thin all the way
down into that. All right. So, I'd be
watching. Either buyers come in now or
they come in at 25,000 basically even.
If they don't, well, we get that 800
move I've been talking about.
So, they're trying to come in now.
They're like, "Fuck, please.
Please, Santa, come back. Save my
swings. [laughter]
Oh, that's all right, Troy. Look, all
that matter like that means you're doing
the right thing. You're sticking to what
you need to be doing, right? You're
sticking to your rules. You're sticking
to the rules placed upon you by uh the
prop firms that you are trading with.
Big selling delta came in there at 56 is
where we are right now.
Are they going to offer a little bit of
relief there? Because they just caught a
few people there. The answer maybe yes.
Where can they relieve up to 77s and
95s?
What is the exact pair? I'm trading NQ.
It's not a pair. Just trading ENQ, mate.
Not not trading forex.
Willow Williams, the volume nodes
concides with SPX 67750. Really
interesting. Here's the relief that we
just talked about. You might have heard
me just whisper it. If they get over 57,
where are they going to go? Probably 77
and then above that 95. So, we're just
in like a little liquidity building
phase of this market because we've done
a strong move down, right? Strong move
down. They're going to have to build
more liquidity before they decide what
next. We can't just move one direction
all the time. All right. They have to
rebuild people into the levels to then
play use their pain to play with
Yeah. Well,
it needed it, Peter. When you look at
that walk up on zero volume from uh
uh the holiday week, it was done on zero
volume and everyone's like volume
doesn't matter. It [\h__\h] matters, man.
It matters.
It matters. And this is what you get. Um
so AI fears, uh carry trade fears, you
see the numbers yesterday, they weren't
good. All right. every single month
since January, unemployment has ticked
up. Every single month, uh, average
uh, wage fees has gone down. So, and job
creation is down. So,
it is bleak out there. I've been saying
this for a very, very long time, right?
You got to know what's under the hood.
What's under the hood doesn't look good.
doesn't mean the markets can't um move
higher,
but uh in terms of the the economy, it's
not good. Eventually, you will see this
news start to make it out into
mainstream media. Uh my concern would
be, I would imagine, um Donald and his
compadres will do everything they can to
make sure this news does not make it out
into mainstream media before the
midterms. because if his whole uh what
should we say strategy was based on I
will save the economy and he comes out
going uh yeah it's not looking so good
he's going to be in trouble
he's going to be in big trouble right so
that's the one thing I'd be aware of the
political factors we all know he's going
to put a new uh
head of fed in we all know it's going to
be a puppet master even when he was
interviewed a couple weeks ago and they
said, "What will you do?" And he said,
"Whatever Donald wants me to do." I
mean, you're supposed to be neutral.
[laughter]
But I think what you're going to see is
a crack in the economy. I think you're
going to see some major flushes coming
Q1 next year. Um, and then I think
you're going to see a rush for the Fed
to cut. I think this whole we're going
to cut one time next year bollocks they
will [\h__\h] panic and they will go into
three or four cuts and big cuts because
they will feel like they've got to
inject some capital back into the
economy and and I think you'll see the
range that we created this year could
very well be retested a little bit. It's
been a big big year. Remember we're up
50 60% off the lows of year. you know,
your job, your job, but the way I see
it, if you're a swing trader, if you're
trading a a lowrisk like IER account, if
you're from the UK or 401k or whatever
it's called here, um your job is to make
10% a year. That's the average growth of
the S&P and the Q's, right? 10% a year.
10% a year is decent year. Uh if you
bought the lows, you're up 50 60% of the
year. So, it it needs to calm down,
folks, right? It needs to calm down.
Everyone got a bit AI trigger happy.
[snorts]
Okay, so we're going to come and test
these 94s now by the looks of it.
So, so far underneath previous day low,
starting to reclaim previous day low.
We're in inside this little volume node.
We're probably going to test sort of 94s
and if this is an old sellside
imbalance, which we're coming right into
now, and let's see if they get through
that, we probably go back up to value
area low on the day. But if if they
resell this, then they're going to
retest the low. So, there's a node 94.
Where is 94? somewhere around here,
right? Sellers will want to retest this
and if they do, they get a break. Buyers
will just want to get this move back
into this level for the day, right? Be I
would be very skeptical.
I was going to put this those who have
traded with me a long time will know.
Easy money trades gone, right? Low
hanging fruit's been taken. Um if you're
going to trade long today, you counter
trend. Maybe you catch a bit of a
squeeze, but the easy money was the
short back down once we left value.
[snorts] Here's the 100 test or this 94
kind of test.
And you're also watching ES into
previous day low here. And if they sell
this or not, do they sell this or not?
Otherwise, they let it back through to
value. And if we get back through
current value area low, then I'd be
watching that 170
value area lows here, by the way. So,
same area. Sorry on Ninja Trader. Valer
low is 130 right now.
130 on Ninja Trader. So here is value.
This is value low on Ninja Trader based
on tick. So do they fade this? Do they
fade this? Or do they just go [\h__\h] you
for the rest of the day? We'll find out.
We are about to find out.
Oh, I'd love prices to come down too. I
I want to get net long, but uh I want to
see like a 20 30% decline in the market.
Okay, there you go. They're reselling
that against 107. They didn't even make
it there. And buyers will want to hold
now into 73s for relief.
into a little bit of a shelf here.
Little bit of a volume shelf here that
sellers are trying to lean on. If they
don't lean on this shelf, we're going to
go 30s. They're trying to lean on this
shelf for sellers. We've reclaimed
previous day low. Now, I'd say this
weekly point of control becomes pretty
key up here.
Make sure you're zoomed out. All right.
So, think about what we're doing right
now.
All right, two leg.
They didn't take this high, which is
naughty of them. They've sold it. We're
going to repric. We might well build out
some liquidity here, which will offer
either this trade down or this one back
up. Um, which means, you know, today and
tomorrow we might just go into a rebuild
of liquidity unless they're going to
really hammer this thing.
I can't believe
that they left that [\h__\h] high at 517.
That is naughty.
That is naughty of them to do that.
I mean, it's not that big a puke. It It
feels big, Peter. But if if you think
about what we've done, if you think
about what we've done, um all we've done
is to trade into previous day low,
right? And all VIX has done
is to trade just shy of previous day
high. All right? So, it's it's in it's
in confluence with the move, right? It's
not like we've broken out previous day
low. We do that and we start breaking
out previous day high on the VIX. Give
it time.
Right. Buyers will want to hold this
little shelf that we've started to build
here in the previous day low. They will
not want price back below this. These
counter trend buyers sellers will they
want to absolutely tank this now. They
will want to make a new low.
Buyers doing a pretty good job there on
that last dip in. might see some relief.
They got to get back through 22s here.
That's value area low on the session. I
know it's not on uh Trading View, but it
is based on tick. 22s is your level.
They buyers need to get back above 22s.
If they get back up there, they're going
to go 170s. All right. This is uh value
area low on the session. It's just
delayed across here. 22s
somewhere around there. All right. That
high, that's your value area low.
Show you here.
That's what I'm looking at. That's value
low on the session. Just be aware of
that.
So if we're going to see expansion,
sellers are going to defend this. So
this is now your rotation. Buyers
defending this, sellers defending this.
Build out of liquidity. Whoever wins
gets the next move. Bit like earlier,
right? Build out of liquidity. But we
know it's high time frame demand down
here. And we know we've hit lowhanging
fruits to the downside.
Just joined. What is the ticker on the
screen right now? ENQ.
Yeah, CPI tomorrow. Carry trade 18th to
19th.
Back up to value. So, the buyers are
trying to get back inside of current
value. That last spite defended. Well,
this is the key level. This white line
on your screen. It's there for a reason,
folks. This is value area low on the
current session. Buyers need to get back
inside of value if they're going to see
a rotation. Otherwise, sellers are going
to defend that level and look for
expansion lower.
[snorts]
50 minutes left, folks. We're going to
do an Apex giveaway as well.
Thanks for all the new uh new people
joining the stream. Hopefully, you're
learning, getting some nice trades as we
go. Not the easiest model today. They
made it a little bit tricky not taking
the liquidity at the highs and fuffing
around in that gray box for so long, but
we are now starting to see expansion.
All good, Joe. No, look, there's no
stupid questions in this stream, man.
Ask away. No stupid questions.
This is the level we just talked about
that buyers need to defend this little
shelf. And this is the rotation we just
talked about. So if we just just put
this in here. Buyers are trying to
defend this.
And I'd say 57s,
right? They don't want it below 57s. The
reason I'm saying that is it's all
sellside delta underneath that. Buyers
need to defend that gray box there if
they've got a hope of going higher. I
wouldn't be buying this today. You
counter trend even though low hanging
fruit's gone. But if they're going to
buy, that gray box is where they need to
buy under that.
Like I say, good night, sweetheart. Or
any of my older English friends, maybe
you watched that back in the day. Great
show.
Your value area low is 263. Well,
that's 100. And even if you were on
here, that's considerably higher.
Previous day value low is 222.
Current day value low, which is
adjusting based on tick, is actually
115. So, this has got to catch up, but
it's actually here 115. Here you go. So
buyers are failing to take control of
the market here. We're testing that
delta level I just talked about, the
edge of that gray box, 56. Underneath
that, it is all sellers that are stuck.
If we get acceptance back into there, we
will probably make a new low.
They are not done with this. They are
not done with this by the looks of it.
So value area low was defended. This
white line on the screen, you can see
how accurate these levels are. white
line defended back into gray box. If
they resell this gray box, we will
probably make all a new low because all
the sellers who are stuck here are going
to be let out.
We just got to watch here. Big sellers
came in here at 49. So 56 and 49 are the
levels for sellers now to defend. They
will not want a reclaim of those levels.
Big big seller came in here 89 s 4950.
We're testing him. He will want to
resell this down. He will not want to
get caught here selling the lows. I
mean, I would not be selling these lows.
It's psychopath, but they are trying to
sell these lows.
Do we have divergence there to ES? I
think we do. Yes, we do. So, ES made a
new low there, folks. So, slight
divergence there be aware of.
If we don't go lower, do I think we go
back to 300
uh today?
unlikely. I think we probably make a
B-shaped profile.
I think what you probably get like a
double distribution, I would imagine. If
we don't go lower, I think what you
probably get is like this distribution
here and this starting to thicken up and
something like this and like a rotation
for a day.
If we don't go lower, if we break, then
obviously we're going to leave the shelf
and this is still the target down here.
So, what did we say? 25,000 is a big
target. whole number and it's the uh
little sort of uh high volume node, the
micro high volume node. Think about the
daily profile based on the year. We have
a little thing like this and then we
have nothing until we get like this. All
right, so if this was a yearly profile,
this is what it would look like. So we
can mark this out. I'll put a little box
in here. Sorry guys, I've got building
worked outside my house right now.
Hopefully that's not too loud for you
guys. It's pretty annoying, right?
Right. So, I'd say here is a high volume
node on the yearly
and here's the break. So, sellers taking
control and now they're going to look
for 25,000. Like I said, I would not be
a buyer in this market. Like your
counter trend if you're buying today and
how they act into here will be key. And
if they break that, there's nothing
really until we get down into here.
I still watch Good Night Sweetheart now.
Great show. Shame they never bought it
back off the the one-off episode in
2016. I never I didn't even know there
was a one-off episode in 2016. I'd love
to watch that. Maybe I'll check that
out. Okay, here we come. 25K coming up.
And under that, really only looking at
800. I don't know if any of you
reshorted uh this move into current
value area low on the session, but
here's your 25,000. So, you better be
covering some into 25,000. If you get
800 today, I'll be very, very happy. I'm
going to have to find a way of getting
involved if we're going to do that.
So, a little reaction here in front of
that 25,000.
Sellers got caught down there into the
lows. They missed 25K by like 10 points.
It's pretty big reaction here.
So, sellers came flying in 14s and 10
here. I still want it to hit that 25K.
Come on, market. Down you come. Come and
take out all the liquidity.
Thank you for being so detailed oriented
oriented.
Why can't I say that? You're welcome.
It's the only way to be with trading. We
can't uh you're not detail orientated. I
don't know what you're doing. Kind of
risky, but I'm sure there's plenty of
YouTube out YouTubers out there who uh
are not. No sellers down there under 14.
Still stuck right now. I still think we
should trade lower, but uh look,
can only say what I'm seeing on the
tape. I still think we should trade
lower, but what I'm seeing right now is
there were a few of them caught at 14.
The big sellers came in at You can mark
these levels above you. 20,50 20,56.
That's where the big sellers came flying
in. So, they don't get squeezed out
until we get above back above them,
right? So, sellers still in control. We
can very well come and test where those
big sellers came in, which is what we're
trying to do now. So, we're going to
come back up to 50 and 56 and see if
these sellers reload here. If they if
they get squeezed out here, we can go
back up towards value area low on the
date, which is basically just above 100.
So, we're testing those 50s and 56s
where those sellers last came in. See if
they refresh sell this. The answer
currently is yes, they are trying to
refresh sell it. We have not seen much
liquidity.
Watching the book to see if someone
jumps in here. Not seeing much yet. They
might get squeezed out here. Here's the
56s.
This is where they need to defend. These
sellers will need to defend this level.
There we go. They come back in. There
you go. So, it was a ride to 56s.
Couldn't been more accurate if I tried.
We got to 58. Sorry. But you can see
that's where they needed to defend. 50s
to 56s. So, there's still a passive
seller up there right now. Willing to
defend that level.
You are seeing uh positive cumulative
delta trying to come into the tape off
the lows here. We had divergence at low
of day. So delta didn't make a new low.
Price did make a new low.
Think about that in terms of who's
passive, who's aggressive. You're seeing
more aggressive buying up here and we
are absorbing it sell side at the
moment. I'd say those 56s is key.
Tapping back into it again. These 56s,
56s. Those sellers will want to defend
this. They will not want this over 56s.
If it gets over these 56s, you might get
some of those bigger guys forced to
cover.
They're trying to get over 56. There's a
little node here at 65s. I think over
that there's a squeeze. I would not play
this long. I'm just telling you what I'm
seeing. Like if you want to play it long
and you're a counter trend trader, by
all means, but I'm just going to tell
you what I'm seeing at this point. We're
tapping into that high volume node of 65
over that. There is a squeeze
potentially all the way back up to 100.
Here it goes.
Tempted to jump in a bit on an email,
but
here it goes, folks. So, over the 56s
all the time, we're over 50s. 56s. Those
sellers are a little bit stuck. I don't
think we finished the auction because we
didn't hit that 25,000. But here we go.
Sellers coming back in. So, let's see if
a buyer tries to absorb this aggressive
selling. No. Okay. Flush. Here we go.
There we come. The flush. So, you can
see that gray box held up. Previous day
low held up. Resell it. And now their
target is to make a new low of day. All
right. So, the relief was here to here
or 56es. Where was that? Here to here.
They couldn't get back through previous
day low. Previous day low. Sellers will
try and complete this rotation to here.
Defend. uh buyers will try and defend
this a little bit like here now folks
build out of liquidity relief resell
right build out of liquidity relief can
they resell for a new low or do they get
caught this is the target there's no
doubt about it all right this is a big
node on the yearly profile after that
here if you're joining late I can show
you the nodes I can show you why
the yearly profile where are you here we
are all right you can see this node
right here. And then we have a little
node. If you just see this little bump
in the road here at 25,000. So, blue box
and then 25,000 right under that all the
way down to 800. We thin out very
quickly.
Every pop still being sold into.
Hey, first time on the stream. I just
caught 50 point move from 261. Nice,
man. Nice work.
Do I notice more traffic on your channel
at alltime highs or big down days? Um,
well, the last month it's been growing
at an insane rate, the channel. Um,
I don't know. Maybe because I've I don't
know why. I can't tell you why. I don't
know why. YouTube suddenly has realized
that I know what I'm talking about.
Maybe. I don't know. Maybe the 400 extra
of you here have got sick of watching
traders pushing codes and not teaching
you anything. I I don't You guys tell
me. You guys tell me what why it's
growing while you're here. I I don't
know, but I'm thankful for it. I'm very
thankful for it. Would it be a valid
break and retest of 110 to go back
upside 110 110 110 110? Um yeah, yes it
would be. It would be if you see a break
above and a hold of it nihow then yes uh
if we can leave these participants all
trapped you need to wait for it remember
right now we're under previous day low
you're going to need to see this and
this and you'd want this little nugget
here and this here to hold if you're
looking for that break upside just for a
reprice right but we've had a big dump
right since the last pullback right if
we think if we're going to get relief if
we just think about the swing points
right then we can expect some relief
maybe to 82s which is the look at that
the 50% retracement is right to the old
naked point of control based on the
current low of day. Let's just move this
out to 25 cuz I think we might come down
to there. But yeah, there there is
potential for a relief rally. No doubt
about it. Timing it will not be easy.
Counter trend trade is probably the
hardest trade in the book.
Here we go. So, relief up to the 70s.
We've got a little bit of a shelf here.
You can see that. And then we thin out
to 106s.
And you're watching ES for a retest of
uh previous day low. SPY is already
retesting it. And the 50-day SPY is
retesting that 75 level. Remember that
gamma level at 75 we talked about. Maybe
you get a little bit of a squeeze up to
that value area low which now is at 93.
All right. So value area low has moved
down to 93.
All right, just remember Trading View is
lagging slightly.
It reads volume slightly differently,
but value area value area low on the day
based on tick volume is currently at
9293.
So maybe they retest that and you have
to see if sellers defend it again.
Lots of things to think about here. Uh
VIX, by the way, took out the previous
day high and has traded back inside the
range. Just be aware of that. We're
building a shelf here into and around
17. If VIX loses 17s, we trade back down
to 1650. That is the moment you will get
relief on the market. The VIX is like,
"Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, calm down.
Calm down. Calm down. Calm down.
Sorry for us new joiners. Your thesis
for the day is shorting down under 25."
I would not want to be short under
25,000, mate. No, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no. That is a cover point. It is a
cover point. The thesis,
all right, most people in here that made
big money
took the breakdown under here once we
left this volume or they would have
taken this retest here and the cover
points were here and here and the runner
is here. And if you get really lucky,
it's here. I would not be you're not a
new money short down there. Think about
value on the day. All right, there's
value area high. There's value area low.
There is point of control. you are
currently at deep deep discount. You do
not want to be a short seller and
discount.
It is more likely that we're going to
see relief at this point. It's a shame
we haven't taken that out, but it's the
same as we didn't take the high pivot
out this morning. And ENQ's just being a
little bit of a [\h__\h] recently when it
comes to uh taking liquidity out of the
game first. But there we go. Okay. Value
area low here. This white line I put on.
Make sure that's accurate. Uh it's at
89. Sorry. 89 right here. There we go.
If you're wondering why it's just
different on here. All right. So, I'm
having to look at both screens, but I
trust the value areas uh on Ninja Trader
because they're based on tick. All
right. So, bulls now. Well, if I was
going to defend bulls, I'd want dips
into 65 and 57s to hold. And I'd want
reclaims. And I think it was Nihal that
was talking about the 110s break above
110s and a hold. I would also want that.
So here's the squeeze testing value area
low. We still have sellers here on the
tape right now passively selling spy
back through previous day low and 75s.
ES is not quite there yet. All right, ES
is coming up to test this same level.
This is where they keep selling ES over
and over and over again. You might see
some relief here as we squeeze back
through value area low
and see if they come and passively sell
this. There are dips being offered at 20
40s. That's a bit low, man. You don't
really want it down there.
So that's the pop above value.
If buyers are going to step in here
again, I would not be personally today.
I would not be a buyer. But if you are
adamant on playing the counter trend,
you would want this to hold 57s and then
you'd want to get back above those 110s.
ES can't get back above previous day
low. Right? So, this gray box here,
you're starting to build out a bit of a
node here. Um, if I was a buyer, what
would I want to see? If I really thought
we were going to squeeze back up today,
I'd want this to hold a reclaim, a pull
back inside, and I'd be looking for this
drift back into value or or at least
into here into here was 50% of the
today's move. So, 180 is maybe a
possible target if they are ready. All
right, you're going to need to see some
compression down here, right? You need
to see something like this and that's
the relief and expect sellers to come
back in and sell that. Okay? So you if
you're trading the buy today, if you're
going to be adamant looking for the buy,
this is your sell, that's the counter
trend. The expectation is that they
resell that. Do not be trying to, you
know, buy high in this session or
expecting too much. You are, you're
going to be a buyer, you're a counter
trend buyer, you better be locking in
profits.
What indicators are you using for order
flow and the bands? Uh the bands are
just my flow zone pros. These are
rolling Fibonacci EMAs.
Um
and uh for order flow, I'm looking at
bookmap above and the footprint chart. I
have footprint chart on Ninja. I also
have it on here when I need to show you.
All right. So you can also have it on
trading view. As you can see at the
bottom of this auction today, we have
some sellers caught down here, right? We
didn't quite make it in. So, Delta
flipped and they've tried to sell here
aggressively a few times. It's why I'm
saying you wouldn't want it back below
this. You'd want this imbalance here to
hold. All right, buyers would really
need this to hold. If you if you see it
back under there, buyers are failing to
take control for that rotation
back into this gray box. All right, this
is where buyers will need to step in.
failing to step in. We just go back down
for a new low. Remember, 25,000 hasn't
been tagged yet.
Question, accidentally bought Apex
Rhythmic instead of Apex Trader 8. Is
there any way to see both in Ninja at
the same time? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah,
you can. You'll just need to open our
trader um and connect that to Ninja
Trader. You can use both.
So this is the level bulls need to hold.
ES rejecting harsh rejection of previous
day low again.
SPY back under 75s again. VIX finding a
bit of a bid there at 17s into those 5m
minute flow zones.
Be careful. Like I said if I would not
be a buyer. I'm going to make this
clear. You guys trade your accounts as
you want. I would not be a seller down
here but I would not be a buyer either.
I would not be convinced that we have
finished this to the downside. But each
to their own, here comes the flush.
Like any buy today is counter trend. I
think that's the worst trade in the
book. Personally,
more follow through here. They want they
want that 25k, you know, they want that
whole number. They want that fib level.
They want that little volume node.
We're not seeing I mean we're not seeing
higher highs and higher lows in this
market. We haven't seen a pivot yet.
It's not to say we don't get relief and
it doesn't come. But at the moment we
are seeing a trend day,
right? And we are seeing a move outside
of previous days value, outside of
initial balance, right? We're not
reclaiming any of these levels. So
you're going to be long your counter
trend of everything that's going. That's
not to say, right, that at some point we
don't see
something like this, but that's your
counter trend leg,
right? And I expect them to resell that
[snorts]
market. Will there be less volume? Um,
yeah.
Traditionally, yes. Traditionally, yes,
less volume, but we have some bit.
Remember, the government's been closed
for a long time. We're finally getting
the data out. We're going to have that
uh JP carry trade. Um if we have a look
20 year, 30 years, sorry. Uh
we pull back inside. We pull back
inside. I mean, everyone's watching that
420 break.
building liquidity here for a higher low
for 420 break. Everyone's watching this
knowing if we do this QQQ
down. All right. So, traditionally,
yeah, I'd say like lower volume, lower
volume, I think you'll find quite a lot
of people might stick around at the
moment
because they're going to need to manage
positions into end of year. I think the
rotations happened out of tech into
small cap. I think MM are uh they're
like, "Well, we're not going to make our
money on the cues, so we're going to
have to find some way to make it." And
they're probably trying to make it in
safe names and in some of those sort of
small cap names. Probably playing some
nasty squeeze outs.
One of you short from 57. Uh 57's
leaving the edge of that. It's not bad.
It's risky because you're you're near
low of day, but it's not bad. Just make
sure you're covering some into here.
You're uh
this last candle sellers came flying in
at the lows. You're starting to break it
now. You should get a low of day now
after this last candle. You I wouldn't
want to repric here. You should get a
low of day now. I would just watch 14s.
All right, that on that low of day
candle. That was your PC on that candle.
That was where sellers got stuck at 14s,
right? So, I'd be watching 14s. Flush
14s. You should get 25k
[snorts]
72 off sweet says trimmed one target for
25k. Nice mate. Yeah, nice.
I think I think you will get there. It's
just like because your entry your entry
isn't a terrible entry, but because if
we think about the whole swing, right,
the best entries are all the way up
here. Because you're entering here,
you're just going to have to be a bit
more careful managing your position. But
we are leaving volume. We are rejecting
this. We are rejecting this. We never
reclaimed uh value on the day. This
should happen. And under there, I would
say again a bit like on this move that
we talked about, was it this move here?
I forget where it was. And I was like,
you've got to cover on the snap. If we
snap here, you must be trimming, right?
If they do a liquidity run here, you
must be trimming because you got to be
careful of that move because your entry
is a little bit later. All right?
Because you've entered from 52s. the
snap of 25,000. Cover some on the flush,
right? If they're bidding here and they
flush it, you must be covering some in
into their wash.
It's so much like a small cap right now.
It's insane.
Probably a week after a week into
January normally, I would say, mate. A
week into January.
Here we come. But these 14s I keep
talking about, that's that old PC from
this candle. The PC on this candle is
14s. So I'll be watching 14s. And can
you trade under 14s? If you trade under
14s, you should hit a new low.
No new uh you got a new low by one tick
there. That's gross. I think you'll get
a new a newer low than that. You should
trade lower. This is gross. They
absorbed. I think you will get it, but
you just got to be careful. Uh I think
your entry was 50, wasn't it? So you're
okay. Think it's coming. They're trying
to resell this.
Big buyer stepping in here. Big seller
just clobbered him. Refresh selling
passive. Retesting 20s. They need to
resell this at 20s now.
Big buyer stepped in again here at 20s.
Do they reclobber him?
Don't like what I'm seeing here. They
need to sell it now. They need to move
away from 20s for you. Back to 14s. This
is good. Now you look better. Much more
comfortable now. 25,000 coming up. And
then 985 is on the bid. So if you break
25,000, you've got a new lower day here,
which is good. 25,000 coming up. Make
sure you're covering some into the wash
under here. All right. Make sure you are
covering some into the wash. [snorts]
You tapped 25K there. Make sure if you
snap 25 or you should have covered some
anyway into the gray box like I said.
But if you snap this gray box, you must
be out the majority of your position.
Back into a shelf here at 21s now.
Relief here. Relief here coming. So they
probably trade up to 40s now. Maybe even
up to 55s where you got in. I think
there will be one more sell opportunity
that not opportunity, but they should
try and resell this one more time.
Looks thinned out quite a lot here. So
up to this 56 we go. the same level as
before. This is why you have to cover
those lows.
Flat now plus 800. Really nice. Really
nice. What do I mean by relief? Uh well,
if everyone's selling down,
if everyone's selling down, the relief
is this move here. So, relief rally,
right? We're going to test 56 is
probably same level as before.
It's where all that delta came in. So,
we're going to test it, test it, test
it, test it. right into it. There we go.
So, can we poke through this now? And if
we do, we're going to go back to value,
which is 77. Sellers will want to sell
this where we are now. And if they don't
sell it, then all those guys at the
lower day are going to get caught.
Yes, still sorry. SPY still not through
its 50 days. Still not through previous
day low. VIX is turning back down to 17s
again.
What was the edge of bottom of that
auction like? Let me have a look.
Uh 80 lot, 60 lot, 21 lot.
Not huge excess. Not bad, but not
massive excess at the lows.
So, they couldn't get back through the
56s. They poked it, but no close above.
Buyers will want to defend 30 now.
Sellers still want a new low. They want
to take out 25,000. That is what they
would really like to do. Here they come.
So imbalance here into 30 and through
that should go lows.
Should go lows. We're through the
imbalance. Should go lows now.
Wasn't that much excess on that last
run. I think once we dump under 25,000
that's when you get a bigger stop run.
They are defending it with all their
might. So 6,800 ES 25,000 NQ
is the level. You know, I would expect a
stop run under these. I really would
absorption down there again though.
It's gray box to gray box rotation
again.
sellers still in control of this market.
They've still got targets below, right?
Liquidity is at 25,000. They're going to
snap that and they're going to cover
that or they don't have to. That's what
they're looking to do. They've had two
attempts now. This needs to do it right
here, right now. Um you would want not
want to see this hold. You'd want to see
this flush it right here, right now
because they've just poked back up to
value and failed. Here they come. So,
they're going to have one more attempt.
Again, if you have been short in this,
you must be covering into the wash,
which hopefully for you guys is about to
start coming. I've got to move book back
up. It's moving so quick. I can't see
it.
You do not want a defend of these 20s.
We've got a little node starting to
develop here. You do not want that to be
defended. You want a wash and a cover
into here. If you get really, really,
really lucky, they give you another 200
points. But, uh, where are we down for
the day? 1.40%.
Not convinced.
Nvidia now 4% down. That thing is
getting merckked. Absolutely mercked.
Come on sellers. You need to come and
wash this out.
Here we come back to these 20s. Got to
let go of this shelf. Under 20s we
should just snap load day. Got to get
under this shelf. This little micro
shelf of 20 to 22. They're absorbing
there again. Sellers doing a pretty bad
job down here. I'm going to be honest
with you.
Still think it comes, but they're not
doing a very good job of it. And the
longer they're here without snapping,
the more of them that are going to get
trapped on the relief. So, you want to
see this wash and wash soon. Big buyer
coming in here
being starting to absorb these 15s. I
don't think he's going to last very
long.
Back to the shelf again at 20s. It's big
level. It's a big level.
Think 25,000 is coming. It's a big big
level
under the 15s. We should go 25,000.
They're trying to aggressively sell this
low. Someone's absorbing here. I think
he's going to get hurt. Someone is
absorbing 15s. There you go. It's
absorbed again.
No follow through for these sellers.
They need to get back under 20s and 15s.
They're unable to do it right now. I'm
still I would not bid on this market
right now until we've washed out, done a
huge stop run, left lots and lots of
excess of the low. I would not be
thinking about the counter trend. I know
a few of you are looking for that
reversal. I don't think it's ready yet.
Rejecting those 20s
back to the 15s. They wash 15s. We go
25,000. Under 25,000 is your cover
point.
Just watching this develop. I need a
pee, but I've got to sit here and watch
this. The worst timing.
22s. They're trying to reclaim 22s.
Relief through 22s. There you go. Uh,
come on sellers. You got to do it
because we're not going to get a long
for a counter trend rally until you take
everyone out.
Okay, they were there too long. So, they
get relief now. Too many shorts.
Couldn't get their way. And there's the
relief. They should have broken down
there. this little ledge right here. So,
they've repriced this low volume node.
They should have broken down there. They
had numerous opportunities. They might
not still be done, but because they all
got caught here, we relieve back to this
gray box. Right. The rotation is here
now. Right over here. Rotation up under
here. They should snap this. This is
your cover point for all your shorts.
But this is uh I would be slightly
concerned here.
We made a new low on Delta and we didn't
make a new low on the chart which means
we have passive buying taking place here
because we had aggressive selling and we
have passive buying down there. Someone
is starting to absorb this take down in
front of 25,000 because Delta made a new
low and price did not. So you've
definitely got absorption under there
right now.
Uh I wouldn't say so Troy. I mean I mean
we only missed it by a tick, right? Or
did we actually hit it? Look, 25.25
25,000 25,000 and one tick.
The concept behind relief. Um
it's Yeah, absolutely. Okay. So why
why did we get relief here? Why didn't
we roll over here and do this? Because
at this level here, right, we've got
aggressive sellers, market sellers
trying to hammer the market down. But
what we also have is someone in this
region, probably an institution,
passively or limit buying. And he's
absorbing and absorbing and absorbing
and absorbing. And once the first one of
these starts to cover, it's a rush to
cover. And that's what gives the relief
higher. And then what you get is
probably this guy here who becomes a
limit seller up here because the best
trades to take are passive limit limit.
The guys that get stuck are the guys
trying to sell the lows on a market
order, right? That's why you get relief.
It's when one side stuck and you get a
rush to cover. Imagine you've got one
guy thousand lot short, another guy
thousand lot short, another guy thousand
lot short. All on market order, right?
Once the first one covers, it's a rush
then because you got three 3,000 lots
which need to cover and you get that
rush up.
Yeah, like I said, um is it Nihow, I
think. Yeah, Nihow.
The last month's been amazing. Um, I'm
not sure why, but I'm very thankful
because I've been tra I've been live
streaming since September last year now.
And uh, sometimes it's hard when I give
give out so much edge and to just not
see the growth, but the last month's
been really good. We're growing really
fast.
I bet Yeah. Uh, the dude 2004. I bet it
has, man, because those gamma levels
have been coming in clutch.
I bet it has.
Okay, back to 65. So that your value
area low now is right.
No, it's not 65. It's 71.
71. All right. This is value area low,
which is also previous day low. That's a
big overunder. Right now, you're
starting to develop like this coiling.
Look, three attempts to move lower here.
This isn't good for shorts. One, two,
three. Higher, low, higher, low. If we
start doing one of these, you will see
relief probably back into this range.
All right, so shorts are starting to get
themselves caught at these lows. If they
don't get a breakdown soon, they will
find themselves caught at these lows.
They've had three attempts to move
lower. They need a wash for their exit.
Imagine if you are a short seller, your
target is here. If you've been short and
short and short and short and you don't
get that target and your average is
here, you're going to start to cover,
which causes the squeeze. All right? And
then they're going to resell it from up
here. So, just be aware of that. If
shorts don't get a breakdown soon,
I would be very very uh concerned for
those of you who are have been short and
holding a runner. You want to see this
breakdown soon. If it doesn't come soon,
I would just get out of it.
Heath Edger. Yeah, I know, man. It's
It's mad. It's mad. I'm very very
thankful.
Joe Bag night.
009 ditching trader TV. I mean, if you
if you trade futures, you're better off
to be here. What I would say is I
absolutely love Sean.
I I love Sean. I think he's a good dude.
He's a cool dude. If I'm if I go to
Toronto, I really want to go and say
hello to them. But yeah, you will you
will learn more technical analysis with
me than you will over there. But I do
think Sean's a good dude. [snorts]
Fourth test. Yeah, they're try. They're
try they are trying. They are really
really trying. We're not back inside of
value on the day we haven't taken out
25,000. They're going to have one more
attempt. They really need that. We're
going gray box to gray box. Remember the
cover point is under here.
I I'm desperate for a P. Do you reckon I
can go for a P and make it back in time?
I'm going to try. Let's try.
They done it yet. They still not done
it. Very close. Gray box again. It will
come now. There's no way they come down
here and don't do it again. It will come
now. They will snap 25,000. You if
you're short, you must cover into this
wash which is about to come. You
absolutely must be covering into this
watch. They're going to snap it.
They
maybe they defend 20 here. They should
snap it and you must cover into the
wash. I cannot believe that they defend
this. No, no, no, no. Cannot believe
that they do this.
Got to defend 20 here. They don't defend
20 here. There's a shove all the way up
to 40 very quickly.
I think they will defend 20 and wash
this back down.
Trying to defend 20. Oh, they've got
stuck. Where's the passive seller? Is he
back in? There he is. Took a minute to
come back there.
Break 10's here. You go 25,000 in flush.
Oh my god. Some some big player has just
come on the tape and he's trying to
absorb it up here.
He's not [\h__\h] around. He's throwing
numbers through. Here you go. [laughter]
He was not messing about, mate. Back up
to 40. Like we said, if they don't hold
20, you're going to go 40 real quick.
That's what just happened. Back to 20
instantly.
And now you might get it cuz they've had
one more attempt. Now it's coming.
There's no way it doesn't come now.
Surely,
surely, surely, surely that last shove
was enough for them to get a breakdown
here. All they're looking for is a cover
under 25,000. So, all they want to do is
to get a cover of under 25,000. Here it
comes. Make sure you're covering. It's
going to come right now. Make sure
you're covering on this wash. It's
coming right now. There it is. Cover
some here. Please hold your runners. If
you get really lucky, you get 800. But I
think that is a good chance that in the
next couple minutes, we see the end of
the auction. All right. So, even there,
I called it for you. Even before this
happened, I said, "Whoa, there's a big
buyer has just turned up. He's probably
going to go 20 to 40." Boom. Boom. All
right. That's all he wanted. Job's done.
Now, you can hold runners for bleeding,
but I would not expect it. If you get
down into the 800s, amazing. It's more
likely that they use the next trade
inside as the point at which shorts get
trapped trying to play the 25,000 break.
But you're going to if you're going to
play the long, you're going to have to
wait for it.
Pretty new here. Appreciate the insight,
man. Just curious and serious question.
How do you see find your gamma levels?
Uh well you can use actually the tool on
uh trading view for options. Um you can
use anything like mental Q. You can use
uh
uh tide on
why can't my brain work?
Tide on on on
someone help me out.
Tide wave. There's loads of them. Uh,
tide is from
have to scroll through to try and find
it. Spot gamma. There's another one.
Uh, unusual whales. That's tied. They
all do the same thing, right? They all
do the same thing. They're just pulling
pulling data. Okay. If they reclaim
here, be careful. You had big sellers
coming at these lows. 49 lot came in at
85s.
All right, like I said, if they start
reclaiming 25,000, you will probably see
this be the end of the auction and we go
upside from here. So, here we go. They
are trying to end this auction for a
trade upside right now. I'm not saying
it it is it, but that is what they are
trying to do.
So, if there is not a break and a new
low and they reclaim 25,000 here, you
will potentially see relief.
They've helped 25 good there. Actually,
it's a good hold. Let's see if they
break lower. What's left to go for?
That's the only thing. Reclaim 25.
They're going to try relief. I think if
they get through 20s, there's a bigger
squeeze to 40s. If they get through
that, it's 64s.
So, potential trigger long counter trend
or the end of auction trade. Here's the
move to 20s. If they get through this,
you go 40s. Here we go. Here we go.
Don't say I didn't [\h__\h] tell you. I
don't want to hear anything like that. I
can't call this out ahead of time
enough. Okay, so here's 20s to 40s.
Relief here.
Old imbalance right now is at 48. So
they might come and test that. I would
tell you now if we start popping through
65, there is a bigger squeeze on on the
table here. So I think that is a good
chance that we've made the end of
auction. There's a good chance that this
can be the end of auction. Look at the
volume here. Look at the delta at the
lows. Look at the squeeze out. Watch
this node here.
It's up to you if you want to trade the
counter trend squeeze, but I'm telling
you what I'm seeing right now. We're
into a low volume node. If we start
getting through this and we get through
50s, we're going to go value area low.
If we get through that, we're going to
go straight back inside value for the
day.
If you're if you're going to trade
counter trend, you must move stops into
the money aggressively based on pivots.
All right.
Is that the NASDAQ? Sorry, I'm new here.
Yeah, NQ. So futures not QQQ but yes.
So this shelf here I would say sellers
are caught under tens. If they defend
tens
relief is possible. If they defend tens
relief is possible.
Uh for here I do it as two ticks, row
size two. But if you want it as number
of rows, I would do it as a thousand.
Right? So you could do it a th00and.
It's up to you. This would be the same.
There you go. Same same. Right? But I I
tend to have it um set to ticks.
Two ticks because that actually matches
what I have on footprint. It's the main
reason.
Okay. They're not defending 10. So they
need to defend these lows. They don't
defend the lows. We will break down.
They need to defend 25,000 now on a
retest. Failing to do that will break
down new lows. Like I said, if you're
going to play counter trend, hardest
trade in the book, you're going to have
to be aggressive.
lock money in with my account setup. I
trade options on QQQ based off your
chart. Bit different game, but stop
losses and profit targets because Greeks
and whatnot. Yeah, I mean it's the same.
It it's exactly the same, right? Like I
watch the cues. I'm watching it right
now breaking down around those 603s. I
know if we break under here, we've got
the 602 and the 600 level. And I I also
know on spy 670 was a huge level of a
huge put wall 670. So uh fix looks like
it's going to go again. So we might get
a new low here folks
and they are adding bids downside for
covers here. So maybe still breaking
down. Like I said I don't trade counter
trend squeezes but uh even that pop over
what did it offer you there? 35 points
not bad.
If you're going to play counter trend,
you'll be uh very very careful,
especially in a washy market.
Not much excess here. That's the only
thing. We need a wick like this
underneath. What would be really nice is
a nice long wick like this with massive
sellside delta in down here. That would
be really nice. And then this and this
and then you get that move. It' be
really, really good. Just kind of what
uh ES looks a bit more like.
25,000 again. They're reselling 25,000.
It's starting to look a little bit messy
here. Oh, it's not surprising we're
getting into lunch. Might get a
lunchtime sort of relief.
You know, if they've all been slamming
puts all morning, do they cover them
into lunch? I don't know. I don't know.
But be aware of it.
trading today in this community was a
thing of beauty. Thanks. So, you're
welcome, Green L. Five consecutive
lower high, lower lows. Lower time
frame, you mean in here? Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. I mean, it's still it it is still
breaking down. It's just whether they
they wash and reclaim. I wouldn't be
short here now, though. You've hit every
single The only thing left is if they
really want to go for this, but you've
hit every single target. I would not be
short down here. No. No. No. No. No. No.
No. Okay, because we are deep in
discount on the day. We are deep in
discount from previous day. We are deep
in discount. Previous day discount is
also weekly discount. All right, we
don't want to be short down here. You
can be short from up here and and
covering down here, but you are not a
new money short down here. You will get
stuck. I promise you. Unless you get
very lucky and it does this, but we
don't trade based on luck. We trade
based on stats. This is getting tighter
and tighter and tighter. At some point,
they will come topside. All right. At
some point, too many are likely to get
stuck and they will come topside. Do not
short low of day. No, no, no, no, no.
Sound like uh what film is that from? Um
with Sir Ben Kings Kingsley.
Uh I love that film. Sexy Beast. No, no,
no, no, no, no. You can't you can't I
won't repeat what else he says.
[laughter]
That's still good though, Joe. This
morning I did shorts. Got about halfway
to where we are now. Hey, like it's
still good. It's still good. You're
still sat at your desk trading, right?
Relief here. I'm If they get through
20s, there's still that move to 40s. If
they get through that value, I'm very
tempted to start joining here for that
relief rally higher.
It's starting to come now.
We're leaving buy side imbalances. It's
really they're getting aggressive here.
If they hold bids, if they hold the next
flush into 17s, this thing will squeeze.
They've got to hold a flush into 17s.
Small size in this just in case it
really wants to go. Here we go. Here we
go. Here we go.
Beautiful.
[snorts] See if they hold a dip here
into this low volume node. If we get
through this, I think the squeeze out
into this gray box. Value area low right
now is 60. They will need to hold dips
into sort of 20s and 18s for me to
consider adding otherwise not
interested. Already paying myself along
the way. I'm not looking for too much
because it's counter trend. Right here's
the dip. So you want this to hold 18s.
Now if they're really going to give
relief they have to hold 18s. You would
not want this little You can't even see
it on here. It's annoying. You There is
a little shelf at sort of 20s. You don't
want that to give. This is actually
here. Here we go, folks. Nice. And let's
see if we can get up to 61s here.
There's a little sellside imbalance here
at 50. So, if you want to cover some
into this or sell some into this, you
can. We're looking for value area low.
Remember, it's counter trend squeeze.
Once we get over value area low, if we
find acceptance over 60, we can actually
think about a trade back upside. Um, if
we get acceptance over 60, right, we can
think about that move up here. And then
we can think about reselling it up here
back down.
Getting stuck at these 50s right now.
Big the big seller trying to come in. I
don't think he's going to get his way,
but we're into a big node. So now I want
it to hold 40s really. I don't really
want to go in that low volume node. 37s,
let's say. Don't want it under 37s on
this runner. And I'm happy to add back
in if we base over value.
Coming in. You're going to take me out,
aren't you? You prick. Okay. So, it's
going to go back down into these 20s
again to pick up this imbalance that it
left. Can always add back in if I want.
But this is why if I'm going to trade
counter trend, I'm very careful.
Then come back into these 20s to 17s.
You're holding this shelf. You don't
want it to fl if it flushes under this.
Do not sit in this trade because it's
counter trend. Cannot tell you that
enough. We're still under current days
value
[\h__\h]
[laughter]
You [\h__\h] And we're into lunchtime.
We're going to do Apex giveaway here as
well. Give me just a second for this
just in case I want to pick it up again.
Not liking what I'm seeing now. Let's
just see.
Waiting to see. There's a there's an
imbalance here that I'm looking at. I
still don't love the excess, but there's
an imbalance here. So, if they do this,
I'm interested. If if they slice through
it, there's no play for me. They're
coming into it now. Now, I want one more
little bit to fill, which they've now
filled. If they slice this lower day, so
they need to absorb right here right
now. Don't like what I'm seeing. No, no,
no, no, no, no. Leave alone. Excellent
still involved. We can wait for a
reclaim.
Yeah, you guys are early. [laughter]
You typing the code in for We haven't
even said it yet. We can do it now. I'm
like I was out of that trade. It like I
said probably go lower a day now once it
lost that imbalance. They had a chance
to hold that little shelf. It's really
annoying. You can't really see, but if I
show you
22s basically on the tick, there's like
this here. All they needed to do was
hold that and they failed. So now this
is looking more and more likely. We
still don't have huge amount of excess
here. So we did catch some at the lows.
Like the sell candles was 356 delta, 134
delta before we turned around. We're
into lunchtime now as well. So, you
know, main trend is down on the day. The
easier trade is lower, but I don't want
to sell lower day.
I'm already out. Like I said, if it if
it I was out. I was selling into that
move of 50 and I was fully out. If it
couldn't hold that imbalance in 20s and
the teens, like I said, if it can't hold
it, I'm not going to hold on to it. It's
gone. The trade's gone. Been and gone.
Yeah, Peter. Yeah. Yeah. The last stop
today would be this down here. Um, let's
go over that now. If they if they're
really going to do that move, I'm
somewhat surprised, but if they're
really going to do that move, that would
be the last stop. Let's just put a fib
in as well. Just make sure we see where
this 61 is as well.
All right. I'd watch 900.
What's the edge of this shelf?
I'd watch 940 and 900 900 to the 61 of
the daily swing move from so from the
low of November to the high that we put
in that peak high. I'd watch that move
where we are now all the way down to
909. If we fail that, I'd be watching
this node. Okay, so those are the two
levels. So you could mark it out. So I'd
mark out 900. I'd mark out 992 and I'd
mark out 809s. Just call it 810s. That's
what I'd mark out. Those are the those
are the sort of areas that I think you
could think about. Um you know how
just want to measure this. Sorry folks.
Give me a second. So we're rejecting
that 20day strong rejection over 2%
down.
So really strong re. Why couldn't they
just poke this up for us this morning?
So, we could have sold the 500s.
Would have been kind of them to do that.
All right. Uh, let's get this back on
and let's do a giveaway for you lot.
Did you break that low? Did you have
excess there? Yep. 58 93. That there was
excess on that low. I'm not going to
touch it. Let me do the giveaway for you
guys. Let's do an Apex giveaway.
Give me a second. Don't type it yet.
Please don't type it yet because it it
won't include you. I haven't said it
yet.
A [\h__\h] Now they put excess on. Look
at that whip like I talked about. You
little pricks.
[gasps]
All right. Not you guys. As in market
makers. Not you guys. I wouldn't call
you guys that.
All right.
We're going to give away. The first
thing we're going to give away is an
Apex account. Those are 80% on sale
right now. All right. So, they've moved
it to 80% sale. Still has the cheap
activation fee, uh, which will last till
the 23rd of December. So, if you want to
load up for next year, now's a great
time to do it. Just type code FZT once
in chat. Only once. You don't need to do
it more than once, otherwise it pulls
you out. All right? And, uh, we'll pull
a winner shortly. So, just type it once
in chat.
Look at all these people. I love it.
Oh,
is this market now going to go? You
little prick.
Now we have Now we have excess.
All right. Now we have excess. Delta
starting to try and flip here. Yeah. Oh,
you bugger. You bugger.
Well, the good news is now we're getting
more and more people on stream, I will
be able to go back to the prop firms and
get some more codes to give away, which
is awesome. So hopefully we'll be at a
part where we can do more and more and
more giveaways soon, which would be
awesome,
awesome, awesome because I love helping
you guys out. Who was it on chat?
someone this week, earlier this week,
who had won a free giveaway on Apex,
passed the account and had turned it
into his first payout this week. I
Things like that make me happy. Make me
really happy.
Okay, 30 more seconds, guy. This is
starting to really relieve now. Oh god,
I can't believe I was one go early and
then as soon as I started talking to you
setting this up, it's gone. I was one go
early.
There you go. It was TJ. Yeah, I mean
that was awesome. All right, let's pull
this winner.
Eight Wool, are you here? Eight Wool.
I will ask Johnny. I'll do my best. I
I'll ask all of them, honestly. Um I've
got three funding next accounts to give
away. 8wall. Awesome. Awesome.
Congratulations, 8wall. All you've got
to do uh email me
info@flowzoneontrader.com.
In that email, I just want you to send a
screenshot of you logged into your
YouTube. I'm going to make a note of it
now
8p
apex account. All right. So,
info@flowzonerader.com.
Send me a screenshot of your YouTube and
I will pay you. I won't pay you. I will
give you a code so you can have any size
account you want. All right. Uh let's do
one more giveaway. I'm going to do the
uh
uh introduction
course. If you don't like my course, do
you get your money back? Mate, I'm I'm
not being funny. I'm not giving you 20
hours of education and uh like Discord
for life and private lessons and giving
you your money back.
No. because you could just say I don't
like the course and you would have
learned lots. [snorts]
No worries, April. All right, let's do
one more giveaway. We're going to do the
very uh introduction to markets course.
It's only like two hours long, but if
you've never traded before, it is a good
course. All right, it's only two hours
long, but if you've never ever ever ever
traded before, it's very beginner
friendly. uh this is the course for you
to if you have done the beginner to
advanced course or you've done the
orderflow course or any of these ones
and you don't want to do this you have a
choice you can tell me to reroll it and
we give it to someone else or you can
just give it to a friend and family
member for Christmas you can also do
that all right so what you got to do
stop typing in chat what you got to do
is type course in chat all right just
type course in chat just type it once
And it's up to you if you if you don't
want it. If you want to give it to a
friend, you can. If you want me to
reroll it in chat, we can do that as
well. I give you guys a minute to do
this. We're starting to hold down here.
You can see this liquidity is starting
to really be built down in these levels
here. I'm getting quite envious that I'm
not in this at the moment. I'm going to
be honest with you. We've caught uh
sellers twice at that low of day. So,
I'd say 25,000
we've caught and
25 uh 24985.
We've caught twice.
We have caught them twice down there.
Probably going to get some relief
coming.
I'm probably done for the day, though.
you guys. 30 seconds more.
And as there's loads of you in here, we
can talk about
some of the things I have available for
you lot.
Tom, I've just seen your email. As soon
as I get off stream, my friend, I will
get you set up. Just seen it now. I've
just seen it.
Sorry about that. Must have missed it.
Can I give you a rundown of the screen?
I'm used to volume bars on the bottom
and don't have the order, but uh bars
top right. How do you read them? Okay,
give me we give this away and then I'll
give you a rundown joke. No worries. All
right, let's choose this winner.
[laughter]
[gasps]
Nacho Libre, that's Miguel, right?
Miguel,
do you want the course for a family
member or someone buddy for Christmas?
Give it to your wife. Okay, awesome.
I'll hit you up on Discord then, buddy.
We We're chatting Discord. I'll sort you
out.
I'm happy you won. That's really nice.
Miguel's a longtime member.
Okay, so who is it? Someone asked for a
read on on what we're looking at. Uh let
me just scroll up to see what he was
saying. Can you give us a rundown of
your screen? I'm used to simple volume
bars on the bottom and don't have the
order book bars on the top right. How do
you read them? This is volume profile.
Right. So this is
h how and where
order has been placed based on price not
based on time. This is volume based on
time at the bottom. This is based on
price. So all we do for this right this
is uh just a tool you come to this one
here 1 2 3 fourth one down right and
you're looking at anchored volume
profile and you click on it from 930
okay I have it set to go to the right
hand side my settings are right here for
you right so I use row size two and
where is it uh to put it to the right
and placement to the right okay there
are free videos on my YouTube explaining
all of this how I use it how it gives
you your levels, all those things. Go
and check them out. It doesn't cost you
anything. Okay? So, there's a few that
I've done on like volume profile
mastery, how to set it up, all of these
things. They're quite popular videos.
There's a whole section on my YouTube,
completely free, all about volume
profile trading. At the bottom of the
screen, what you're seeing here is
delta. All right? So, this is delta per
bar. Not cumulative delta, delta per
bar. So, what I look for is things like
this at the lows, right? If I want a low
of day, I'd want a nice long wick. And
in here at the lows, I'd want it to be
all sellside delta. And the way I would
really see that and it doesn't look very
good. You out. See you later. All right,
darling. This actually doesn't look very
good for an end of auction because this
is buy side delta at the low. We don't
actually want to see that. What we want
to see is this sellside delta all the
way down to the low. So just Well, I
just had a little peek at that now. So I
would say this auction probably has not
finished yet. It probably may well have
more in it lower. Um, which is good that
I finally had a chance to look at it.
What else are you seeing on your
screens?
All right, the flow zone pro indicator
is this. Right, all this is are rolling
Fibonacci based on the time frame you're
looking at and daily and weekly levels.
All right, so previous day high,
previous day low, previous day close,
previous week high, previous week low,
previous week close. Everything else are
horizontal lines that I am putting on
the screen like previous day value
areas, previous week value areas. Right?
That's what we're looking at when we're
seeing this.
Is the footprint on trading view? Yes,
my friend. Trading view. Right. So,
right here, this button here where you
normally would have candles, you want to
come down to volume footprint. You will
need, is it called the pro account? I
can't remember what it's called. Pro
account or whatever it is. Um, so it's a
little bit more expensive. They often
have Black Friday sales. that is the
time to get it. Um, they might have a
Christmas sale. It's worth looking. Um,
but yes, that volume footprint chart is
on Trading View. I also have it on uh
Ninja Trader.
Jose says, "I just passed my Apex 25K
eval. I can vouch for the course."
That's awesome, mate. Congratulations.
Thanks for joining. Looking forward to
working with you more and more and more.
Any Tradeifies to give away? Not yet. I
will. Like I said, now we've got lots of
members joining all the time. I will be
able to reach out to Brett and um ask
for a bit more support from them. All
right, so Apex have been very good, but
we will ask for some others. We are
still trend like in this sort of awful
downtrend. I wouldn't be selling low of
day here. I'd be looking now probably
for the bare trap.
My what I would be looking at now is for
a bear trap for a squeeze back out and
I'd look to resell probably either this
edge or all the way up here. All right,
I wouldn't be selling down here. You
need a price higher to sell into. Now,
you're deep deep in discount on every
single time frame. Remember, I just want
to remind you
remember on the daily, you cannot lose
sight of where we are, right? On the
daily,
you are deep into discount here. We went
over these levels. You are coming into
your 61. 900s is the 61. 800s is next.
We're already into discount. Doesn't
mean we can't keep going down into
these, but if you're short here, you
want to be short on some pop up which
creates liquidity. You do not want to be
short at the low of day down here. You
are going to want this to trap some
bears, encourage bulls to get in, repric
higher. I'll be looking at these levels,
right? Where does it want to stop? Where
is the swing point from this morning
since we left this range? Where could we
price back into?
Right. I'd be really interested in a
price into sort of 150 160. Where's high
of day
and 200. So I'd be looking at 150, 160,
and 200s. That's if I was going to
resell it, that's where I'd be looking
to resell it. I wouldn't be selling low
of day. You're going to find relief.
Shorts will get cooked down here. And
you're starting to see it right now as
we're talking.
Hi, Alex. I just passed 20 accounts on
Apex. I truly appreciate your guidance.
Mate, I can't push those buttons for
you. That is you doing that job.
Congratulations. Nice work.
Does it work better on Trading View than
Ninja? Um I really like the this on
Trading View. I think it's really really
clear. It's so easy and clear to use. Uh
on Ninja Trader, I use a third party
because I don't love the order flow that
comes free with Ninja, but there are
plenty of third parties which are really
good.
Setting a swing limit order on CFD for
24800. Let's see tomorrow. Done for the
day. Oh, not Oh, I see what you're
saying, Peter. Well, fingers crossed,
mate. [laughter]
Yeah, I mean yes, basically uh simply
put uh dogee yes I I think what is
likely to get to happen is we will get
relief like I said right we will see
some form of relief if we think about
this is selling continuation
this is not selling continuation this is
likely to see a relief up which is then
sold back down all right so I think
we'll probably get relief up and then I
think you'll see sellers step in. They
won't. Smart money will not want to sell
the lows. They just won't.
All right. This is not a selling
pattern, is it? Right. It's not a
selling pattern. This is going to get
tight and you're going to see sellers at
the lows get caught and then sellers
come and then buyers probably chase too
high and then that resell. That would be
my anticipation for what's probably
about to come and it's already starting.
We've been talking about this for god
the best part of an hour probably and
it's finally starting to develop. that
kept saying under 25,000 I would be
covering my positions. You are not
seeing acceptance under it. You are
going to see relief higher. All right?
They're going to squeeze this out
higher. Imagine you were short at 25K.
You are about to get squeezed out. Then
you're going to see buyers come and join
in too high and then sellers come and
slam this back down. That's what you're
going to see. I would anticipate.
Ninja's horrible. ATAS is good. found a
prop that gives you a free license to
use that. I mean, each their own. I like
Ninja. I've had I've had a couple issues
with the uh setting a few bits up
recently, but I'm happy with it.
The one hour chart showed ES6806.
I played shorts to there and now I'm
long. There you go. There you go. It's
playing reversal back up. And if you
look at VIX, VIX can't get through high
day. So the other thing I'd be looking
at is why you have to pay attention to
what's going on across the board.
Previous day high, all right, poke
above, fail. If we start to lose this
and trade back into here, you will see
QQQ and SPY go upside. All right, so
just watch this break on VIX. If they do
that, you'll see more relief in the
market. All right, folks. I am out of
here. Uh, congratulations. Thank you for
joining me. We will be back tomorrow.
Remember, big big news prints tomorrow
morning. Big big newsprints tomorrow
morning.
I mentioned order flow on Trading View.
Yeah, I just I just showed it. Maybe you
missed it.
Joe bag me from six months ago would
have been screaming confirmation and
buying near the top of the [laughter]
creation of liquidity for for today's
sale. There you go. So, you've changed
immensely, which is awesome.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. It it has it has
footprint, mate. Yeah. It has
everything. They launched it about uh
it's probably about a year ago now. 6
months to a year, something like that.
What's the name on Trading View for
order flow? It's up here, mate. And we
just went over it. Come to your candles,
your types of candles, and come down
here. Volume footprint, right? Volume
footprint.
Yes, Joe. Uh, 9:15 New York time,
Eastern time, Monday to Friday. Right.
Monday to Friday, 9:15. You will always
catch me live there. It's important,
well, I would say it's important you
join at 9:15, not at 9:30 because it's
from 9:15 to 9:30 that I talk about the
setups I'm looking at and why. All
right? So those first 15 minutes can uh
be good for identifying those key
levels.
How much is activation for Apex account
again? Uh let me have a look. It's like
40 or 60 bucks at the moment. Hang on.
Bella did text me this morning. For 25k,
50k, and 100k fees. Lifetime activation
is currently 65 bucks.
Thanks, Rosco. Means a lot. Thank you,
mate. Thank you. Thank you everyone for
supporting.
Futures are open for the rest of the
week, right? Yep. Yep. Yep. Open the
rest of the week. All right, folks. I
will see you tomorrow morning, 9:15. Do
those in Discord. I look forward to
trading with you there. If you've
enjoyed how I trade and uh you want to
learn more, please go on my YouTube
before you do anything else. Go onto the
free education on my YouTube before you
spend any money at all. Make sure you
learn everything you can for free. All
right, keep your cost down. If you enjoy
how I teach, all the different courses
are on my uh website,
flowzonetrader.com.
All right, so if you want to do more
advanced stuff, if you like how I teach,
you like how I trade, everything is
there. Go on my YouTube first. There's
so much you can learn for free on my
YouTube. Here comes the relief, folks.
So, if you were long, I'd start paying
yourself a little bit. All right, peace
and love, everyone. Thank you for
joining me. Really appreciate all the
kind words and support. Trade safe in
the afternoon. Remember, we've taken all
the easy lowhanging fruits. Now, we're
going to build liquidity. Don't get
trapped the wrong side of it. Take care.