Please, no more tech issues. Come on,
YouTube. Wakey wakey.
There we go. Okay, so starting off on
the daily as we always do, we can see
like we talked about yesterday. Friday
we left the old balance range. Yesterday
we back tested stayed heavy and
overnight you would have seen my uh
level traded into uh now that level
adjusted
is 25180.
All right 25180 that's the naked point
of control that we were looking for that
trade into which on the old contract was
25 930. So we've tagged it overnight and
uh we're starting to try and bid back
up. So what are we watching? Really
simple, isn't it? We're watching this
transition point here. All right, this
transition point here. This transition
point here. If we go in rotation, we're
going to go inside here. We still have
this low volume node here. All right,
and that really needs to act as
resistance for bears. Very very simple.
They must must must
protect this. Failing to protect that
from bears, right, will mean this whole
area here will get bears caught. And if
we start coming back up, we can come and
test. Well, yes, obviously 570s, but
into the six 650s and old range. And if
we get acceptance in there, we'll be
looking for a breakout to the upside
because this will be a look below and
fail back into range and upside. If
you're saying, why have I shifted? Well,
I haven't shifted yet. But what I would
say is down here, I said if bulls are
going to defend, this is where they're
going to defend. That is the buying
opportunity. It happened overnight. And
if we move on to the hourly charts, I'm
going to show you how and why. All
right, this was the level. This red line
in the green box was the level I felt
like the market would draw into and then
it would be up to bulls to defend it.
So, we've drawn into it so far. They
defended it. I would question right
right now, very simply, can bulls defend
this box here now, right? Can they
produce in the New York session a higher
low over this box? If they can produce
that, their next job is to get back
inside previous days value area low. If
they do that, they need to go back to
the upside into previous days value area
high. I doubt they're able to do much
more than that today. But if they are,
then the next job is to base up here to
get back into previous week's value. All
right, that is the bull's job. All
right, this is all counter trend. All of
this counter trend until we get
acceptance back into previous week's
value. Just so that you are aware,
bear's job's quite simple, isn't it?
They want to stay underneath yesterday's
value. There's yesterday's value. All
right. They don't want acceptance back
into yesterday's value. If they defend
that, they'll be looking for a New York
test of this naked point of control. If
we sell that naked point of control,
then look out below because if we look
on the daily, right, if we're going to
sell that, the next real level that we
can think about is probably this high
volume node all the way down here. And
that is what 800s.
Is that on the old contract? It's not
adjusted, is it?
How do we hit low here? Oh, it is
adjusted. Okay, 248.
248. All right. So, we can mark one down
here.
All right. That's the next level.
[snorts] So, that's what we're watching
for. All right. Do bulls hold the
rotation or do bears defend previous
day's value? If we get back inside of
yesterday's value, then we're going to
look for rotations inside previous day's
value. All right, very very simple. So
bull's job will be to defend this. All
right, that's the bull's job to get back
to here. Bear's job is first stop to
defend this, right? And get down to
there. Those are the rotations early
morning. Once we make our mind beyond
that, either we're going to melt or
we're going to get back into range if we
find acceptance back into value. Bull's
next job is to get back to the top side.
Bears will desperately want to defend
this. The rotation can take place there.
If there's no rotation, there is a
squeeze potential. That's what we're
looking at in the market today, folks.
All right.
If we come up to uh 5m minute above, you
can just see how we've built that
liquidity. All right. So, yesterday we
participated in that big sell. All
right. There was a rally back. We sold
that back down. Overnight we came into
key level. We've gone sideways or we've
gone lower, but we've gone sideways and
potentially build out a base here. Too
early to say if we've successfully built
that out, but that is what the market is
looking at.
And if we get into
five minute chart, let's have a look
across the board right now.
All right, ES same kind of job right
here. Have to adjust some of these.
Right. One thing with ES to understand
is if we go onto a daily,
right, it's yet to leave that balance
range. Today's actually the first day.
So if you think about the daily, there's
the attempt to move higher. There's the
crack yesterday. If we can't get
acceptance, I'd say 900's your level on
ES. All right, we can set a price alert
there. 900 there or thereabouts, that's
the edge of the range, right? That's
where ES is trying to get back above.
Right. If ES gets back above that, we go
into old range, maybe they do a rotation
in here and can finish the year strong.
If they come up and they keep like
selling into this, then we're looking
for downside pressure. We've got some
imbalances here to come back down and
fill.
Okay, if you're struggling with the
levels today, make it easier for
yourself. All right, just go to the uh
ETFs. All right, really easy. Go to the
spy where you can see the box. We're now
trading underneath it. Go to the cues.
We can come to a fiveminute chart,
right? Just plot the levels on the spy
and the Q's. You can see there's top
side, there's the bottom side that we're
trying to leave. Same on the Q's, right?
You can move this down.
This is current resistance. Just make it
easy for yourself. Just have the spying
a cues on a side monitor for the
remainder of this week until we've got
enough data. [snorts]
All right. Interesting. Dixie
puked out on that uh 8:30 and then
reclaimed it. the complete opposite to
the market
VIX right now.
Where we at?
Just trading in a range for me. But um
like I said, when we come down here, we
historically into these areas, we often
find nasty moves out of them. We're
starting to see that. Bitcoin's found a
bit of a bid. All right, let's go
through the mag.
All right, gap down on Apple after that
news. Uh they are really pushing for
Apple to be punished for uh its
treatment of apps. So if they fail this,
there is a rotation back down into here.
All right. So if they start losing that,
so that's the level on Apple uh Amazon.
It's tricky into this. That's that look
above building liquidity here. And it
doesn't look ready to go either way yet,
but that's what it's starting to do. Oh,
we're gapping down. We're flat on
Amazon. So, no real edge on Amazon. Most
of these look kind of flat. Google, uh,
slight gap down, but still inside
previous days range, right? There's your
previous day range on Google. Microsoft
gapping down again inside previous days
range. You're going to see that a lot.
We are just in a rotation right now,
building the next leg. Um Micros
Microsoft did we just do that? So Meta
and Microsoft doing the same thing.
Microsoft actually looks a bit weaker.
Nvidia
inside yesterday's range pretty much
opening flat. All right. Yesterday
failed to reclaim this pivot right here.
It tried, it failed. We're in a range.
They're building liquidity. We can set a
price alert at the low here.
Just zoom out.
and Tesla
still looks good holding on. Tesla's
fine all the time it holds this. All
right, there's your sort of W breakout.
It can afford a pull back towards this.
Doesn't have to get that far. And then
it's looking for continuation. an
alltime high at 88. [snorts]
Looks all right. It's just pulling back
a bit. Looking to see if they can find a
bid on it.
Thank you. What is it? H now remember
what that is. There we go.
All right. So, those are your adjusted
levels if you want to look. Can I look
at gold? Uh, yeah, I can look at gold
quickly
on a pump.
Trying to get to back to the top side of
its range right now. All right. So, it's
trying to hold a bid. Gold's very
simple. It needs to hold a bid above
this. This is your supply. This is your
double top supply. All right. It's
building out a range here. Breakout will
try and take it up to here. You need to
be aware of failed breakouts. All right.
look above and fail will be if we come
back into this dance here. Right? So,
you're just playing edge to edge, edge
to edge, break out, edge to edge, edge
to edge, break out up into here, and
then see if it goes. If they fail this
range, you're coming back into the old
range. That's all you're doing.
Very. And probably it's all we're going
to see in all these markets until uh uh
Christmas and the new year right now, I
would imagine. Anyway,
okay.
Book map looks a bit of a mess as well.
Well, let me just check. [sighs]
I'm going have to adjust all these. Give
me a second. 451s.
See if I can get this done quickly. 451s
value low. 333s somewhere around there.
These are going to be rough today. I
don't really trust them all.
3s point of control. 419s. Seeing some
weakness coming here. 419s and then
previous week 718s
there
eight
and then
seven
basically 26. All right.
Sorry, folks. Give me a second. Have to
redo all the drawings. It's the most
annoying thing about uh roll over week
and to redo everything.
What's this down there?
226 215
retry.
[snorts]
One minute left here, folks. Sorry,
playing catch up a little bit here. This
is what happens.
And then next level was 800s, wasn't it?
New down here. Okay. All
right, 30 seconds.
Market about to open.
There we go. Just about set.
Oh no, don't shoot me errors.
All right. [sighs]
So, let this wiggle out, I would say,
this morning. Everyone's rolled over to
the new contract. Give it a bit of time.
Finding a beard off that green box
straight away, by the way.
They're trying to hold that edge from
overnight. You can see it's where we
broke out from. That's why I've got it
marked off that into the blue somewhere
around here. Buyers will want to hold
this. All right. Buyers will want to
hold this and get back into there.
That's their first job. Sellers will
want to defend that. That's their first
job. Give you a readout on the mag. All
of it is red right now other than
Amazon. Uh Tesla half a percent, Nvidia
0.15% down, Microsoft a third of percent
down. Uh Meta approaching a third of a
percent down. Google 1% down. Apple
0.12% down. Amazon actually up on the
day. comes up in the day. Smash that
like button nice and early for me,
please. Folks, do me a favor. Smash it
nice and early.
And let's see what we get here.
I'm just going to grab my water bottle.
Dry mouth.
Okay, reminder. It's the last day for
the Apex sale today. 90% sale. Today's
your last day to buy it and it's the
last day to pass them. Unfortunately, if
you want that cheap um activation fee,
unless they roll it over, I haven't
heard anything yet. As soon as I hear, I
will let you know. Right, here's the
approach back to previous day value area
low, which is right next to your point,
your uh previous day close.
So, bears will want to defend this and
if they don't defend it, it means we're
getting acceptance back into range. You
can see they're holding this box here.
Might have been a very quick long
opportunity this morning into those 200s
100 point scalp to be fair in the first
minute. Kind of crazy.
Let's just get this time to settle in my
mind. Amazon holding up. Meta's gone red
to green. Nvidia's gone red to green.
Let's develop for a minute.
Hey, Alex, the VP levels. Is that an
indicator? It's just drawing it on.
[snorts]
Um, these are manually drawn on. I do
them more manually.
Pop and fade. Yeah, it could well be a
pop and fade if they defend previous day
value. Like I said, the rotation right
now is between sort of this edge here
and this edge here. All right, so bulls
want to defend this, bears want to
defend that. That's your first rotation.
If they get acceptance back inside,
these are the rotations. All right, so
it's from here to here, here to here. If
we lose this,
then this is possible.
Sorry, folks.
Please, Lord, do not let me have another
cold before Christmas. I've just got
over CO.
[snorts]
Okay, so we're above that New York open
so far. Let's have [snorts] a look about
Google the weakest one right now. Market
looks like it's starting to bleed here,
folks. Market is starting to bleed a bit
here as in the mag.
Definitely starting to bleed a bit here
in the mag.
Why is it [\h__\h] my footprint up now?
[snorts] I got to reload it.
Oh god, that looks awful. What's
happened here on footprint?
Oh my god. Well, that's not useful, is
it?
I can't [\h__\h] see my charts right now.
[sighs]
You got to hate roll over. Let me save
this and reload it.
I don't trade top step. I've made that
very clear for many years for that
reason. You trade top step, you're
giving Michael Pekki cash. I don't agree
with his business ethics. Said it many,
many times.
I don't think he's a good man,
unfortunately.
Otherwise, you wouldn't have the issues
you have. He wouldn't be trying to
create a monopoly. He wouldn't be
controlling the backend data. He
wouldn't be selling and sharing your
data and he wouldn't be trying to move
it to a brokerage to take more of your
money out of you.
It's not the first time X has been down.
It's probably the millionth time this
quarter. Oh my god, my footprint is
absolutely [\h__\h] here. What is going
on?
This is a shame.
New version of footprint is now
available for download. Yeah. Okay. What
are you doing about it then?
Oh, no footprint for me.
I'm trading blind now.
No, my footprint is not on the other
contract. It's on the new contract. The
The problem is not the pricing. the the
footprint,
[sighs and gasps]
mate. Two days in a row.
Two days in a row.
Uh, [sighs]
anyone else having an issue using CDI
for Ninja Trader? Is it just me again?
You're having issue with it on quant
5 minutes fine. My one minute's
absolutely fooked
is absolutely fooked. Let's see if I can
make a new chart with that.
All right, here's your drive into
previous day value area low. So, if
bears don't defend this, they're going
to go rotation top side.
Yeah, top set X is down apparently.
Mate, my charts are [\h__\h] Like,
they're overlap. Look at that. All the
That's not even with footprint. It's
untradeable. Completely untradable.
Don't know what to do about that.
duplicate new tab. Let's try this.
Sorry folks, this is two days in a row.
It's frustrating. I'm really sorry about
that. I would love to be trading this
right now. Can't literally can't see in
my charts. All right, so bears are
trying to defend your previous day value
area low. If they successfully defend
this, they're going to look for VWAP and
then your New York open. If they fail
that coming all the way back down into
here,
at least I give you the move beforehand,
right? The drive was from green and blue
box to value area low. Bears will want
to defend this. That's your snapshot
opportunity.
Going to snap. I'm trying not to snap.
Two days in a row of dealing with
[\h__\h] nonsense. I'm about to snap.
Don't snap, Alex.
Honestly, institutions don't deal with
this [\h__\h] We shouldn't be dealing with
this [\h__\h] Drives me [\h__\h] mad. People
making money out of this stuff.
A USA
Ninja Tra is [\h__\h] man. It's
completely frozen on me now.
It's not even quart to 7. I'm already
dealing with this [\h__\h] Oh, you got a
lot of roll over week. Why [\h__\h] do
it?
You can hear the error messages now
coming up. Great.
Okay, there's your rotation. Congrats if
you took it.
Congrats if you took it. Oh my [\h__\h]
lord.
Yeah, my [\h__\h]
Nice, nice work, Tyson. Yeah, just
really clean rotation. So cover points
are now into view up and New York open.
If you fail New York open, all right,
then it's possible they come and test
sort of the these edges here. 217s, I'd
say two 17s, probably this edge here,
281. So we can clean this up a bit to be
honest. This can be a bit more like
this, right? I'll be watching these kind
of edges here and then
lower day
down here.
All right.
I still can't move my mouse on Ninja
Trader. The whole thing is [\h__\h] Wakey
wakey.
Okay, let's have another go at this.
Oh, I keep getting a message. Um, I
don't know who's trading on city saying
an F5 update is required.
And there's no update to do when I
check. And now it's got all my value
errors wrong. This is marvelous.
Okay. Well,
let's start.
You must select.
Okay, there's your VWAP. Sorry, folks.
All right, I'm there or thereabouts now.
I've just I'm trying trading a little
bit blind when it comes to the value
traded, but I'm there or thereabouts.
So, there's your New York open
[snorts]
market has all rolled over. Like I said,
all the mag started selling. So, that
previous day value area low was your
rejection point
like we talked about.
Yeah, I've got some sellers getting
caught these lows down here. All right.
240s. So you might see a pop back up off
this and we can maybe create new range
today. Let's just mark this out the 930.
Okay. So there's your rotation. We
talked about this premarket. People
said, "What was I looking for?" I I told
you premarket. All right. Bears must
defend this for a rotation down into
this. Balls must defend this for a
rotation up. That's the market condition
you're currently in. And Ninja Trader
has started to wake up now.
which is a start, I guess.
Oh my god, it's running so bad.
Back down to where these chap sellers
just were.
into this sort of gray greeny box.
There's your New York open. If we trade
under there, this is where bulls must
defend uh down here. So, we just
rejected point of control on the day.
Everyone's top step down, guys.
Everyone's top step is down. All you
guys asking, right? It's why I don't
trade on top step. You're literally
asking for problems straight in there.
Honestly, the guy's an [\h__\h]
Something big's coming. Yeah, something
big to [\h__\h] you lot over.
Okay, into this box. I'd say all the way
down to here is where bulls will want to
defend 180s. I would imagine if they
start losing in 180s, there'd be
problems. All right, so overall we're
bearish. We've just rejected value, but
we know overnight
um from sort of 230 to 180 is where
bulls will want to defend. We know that
from overnight. Okay. [snorts]
Never had that before. Oh well, you must
be new to them because they have issues
all the time.
Okay, so they're defending that box like
we just talked about. Green box. They
can defend all the way down to here.
Back to point of control on the day.
They're now trying to cause a squeeze
back up higher.
Here comes the squeeze. They go right
top side now. And if they can get there,
they go
all the way. Grabbing [clears throat] a
piece of this from point control
and looking at this ledge 320s now. See
if we can get three 320s or not.
Really nice. Nice squeeze. Beautiful. So
from one side, we just talked about the
rotation
from one side to the other, from one
side to the other, from one side to the
other. How we act now becomes important.
If we get back inside value, then
they're going to attack up here. Okay?
If they reject value, you're going to do
the same rotation back down or at least
back down to the midpoint. It's just a
rotational day. We've talked about it
numerous times already on stream
out [clears throat] of this. Now we got
to the 320s. You can hold a runner to
see if they can expand back into
previous days value.
Can I get back into previous days value?
Here is previous day's value. Tap tap
tap. I'm out of a bit now, by the way,
folks. So, I just took as soon as we
broke through here. 70s about 50 point
move or something. Not bad. If we get
into previous days value, all right, we
have supply overhead from
uh 380s to 400. And then above that, we
have the point of previous day point of
control and value. All right. So, we
have supply overhead. I should probably
draw this out
380. So, that's that peak to 400. I'm
going to leave that actually. We can
just put like a little pin in here so we
know where the liquidity is
there. But we're in rotation until it
proves otherwise. Here's the attempt to
get back through value and close the
gap.
Having to look at my footprint on
trading view. I'm struggling here. All
right. What I'd say is bulls will now
want to defend 295
to 263. All right. 295 to 263. If they
can defend 325, they leave some bears
stuck. But we have a big old imbalance
up there. All right. So, I would be down
to small size here.
Mag did rotate there a little bit. So uh
Nvidia, Microsoft and uh Amazon all
caught a bid.
[snorts]
Very stupid question. Is today the last
day to pass Apex Eval special? The
website doesn't say so. Yeah, it it is.
And it and it will say on the sale ends
this date. That's means that's your last
day to do it.
Okay. So, they're reaching in to this
previous day value gaps now filled. We
know there's supply overhead up here.
All right. The rotation
if they want to let come back down for
some of this imbalance. They will trade
they will trade back into this ledge.
All right. And bulls will want to defend
this ledge if they've got an ambition of
doing this. Bulls will defend this
ledge. Lud this ledge. We go right back
down to the lower side again. Remember,
we're just in a rotation. That's all
this market is in right now. There's the
squeeze. Beautiful. So, now you're
looking to take out this high. So, if
you're still in it, you look good. And
once you take out this high, you're
looking for previous day point of
control, previous day value area higher.
That's a really good squeeze there,
leaving those bears trapped at the 330s.
And they've just got trapped again into
370s. So, I'll be taking some profit
here into this box if I was you. And
then holding runners to get to the top
side of the rotation.
Yes, we've rolled over. We're on the H
contract. You'll be able to tell by the
numbers.
More money on the H contract. Really
nice. Gosh, I wish I held a little
something.
[snorts]
Could have, would a, should have.
Could have, would a, should have. It is
a 15-minute order break, but if you
using orderflow, you could have seen
that the sellers got trapped from uh 300
up to 324 on that 947, 948, 949, and in
the 10:00 candle, they got trapped at
3:30 to 3:15. So, you've left them all
trapped. I just be careful now because
you've had very, very aggressive buying
stepping in, and you need to pull back
and make sure it can hold a base because
all you've done now is sweep this
liquidity that we just marked out. All
right. So buyers now very simply got
they've got to hold above previous days
value. All right. They've got to hold
above previous days value. They've
created a ledge and this will be the
completion of the rotation.
Right? So buyers need to hold this.
Failing to hold this then you just get
back that whole squeeze.
And we can mark out other levels here.
Get those in. [snorts]
All right. So, some strong selling
trying to come in here. Like I said, you
need to hold previous day value
there or thereabouts. I'd say you don't
want to trade under 313s. That's where
the sellside delta got caught. So, let's
just call it 300s. 313s. Ideally, you
hold over 313s. Otherwise,
it can get a little bit weak back down
into here. Okay,
was a squeeze out.
Looks bullish overall. It's just whether
they can hold it.
3 330s to 316s, possibly down to to
297s, but you don't really want it down
there, I'd say.
They'd want to try and catch a bid here
to cause a resqueeze higher. In my mind,
they've got the opportunity to do it at
the moment. That's what they would want
to do.
So, here's value. Here's the gap fill.
They lose this. This little shelf here
is the area. They would not want to lose
this. That's your area. they lose that
you can repric this whole big big
squeeze candle [clears throat]
because you need to find acceptance into
previous days value otherwise it's a
look into it and a failure isn't it
right you need to find acceptance into
here otherwise it's a look in and a
failure here's the level they are trying
to bid off it they are attempting to bid
off it not very successfully yet but
they are attempting at least
Can they get back through and go top
side? Here they go. They got to get back
above it. They are trying. They got to
get back above this and squeeze back to
the top side. All right. So, they're
trying to put in a higher low here. I
might sort of wait to see if they do one
of these.
My charts are absolutely [\h__\h] I'm
literally trading blind right now.
Here they go. It's a good hold. So those
sellers remain trapped under 320 right
now.
This is where the strong selling sort of
stepped in where we are now. So, if they
can get back through this, new highs can
be available. They just got to make sure
they don't retract buyers up here, which
is what probably just happened here.
There is a potential move higher here
coming.
It's a really good hold of value like we
talked about. Any dip back down into
there that holds again will probably be
gobbled up and then go for a new high at
this point.
>> [cough]
>> It's my flow zone pro. It comes with the
beginner to advance course or you can
buy it on the website. The indicator one
of you asking. Okay, coming to fill this
cell side. We need to see one more dip
back in would be really good. And see if
they can hold that dip. That would be
really encouraging. Do you want to give
it to us? Are you going to be kind and
give it to us? Apparently not.
They're going to go for it, aren't they?
Come on. Come back down. Just one little
retest somewhere down there. No, they're
going for the squeeze. They're going for
the squeeze.
So, let's getting caught here at 64s.
One more dip in just to here to see if
we can hold for this be ideal looking
for the moment.
Here we come.
And can we accelerate now then?
Good.
And my chart's frozen. Oh, Ninja.
Ninja. Seriously,
charts fully frozen.
I'm in this long and my charts are
frozen.
Here
we go. Back on.
I don't know if I can trade like this.
All right, let's see if we can take out
this high.
Just missed me there. I'm going to cover
one into this.
Don't want to see it come back down and
lose 70s. Now there a seller up here
refreshing at 85. Want to be careful if
he tries to slam this back down.
[\h__\h] me. I can't trade like this. Like
I'm I'm making money. I'm in long from
60s, but uh
didn't give me a chance to put my uh
limits out there to get filled.
Yeah, they're holding this buy side
imbalance. They need to hold 70s. So,
I'm moving my stop into 69. They need to
hold 70s in my mind. Otherwise, I'm out.
Almost got tapped there. 70s is the buy
side and balance. If they don't hold
this, we can rotate. And I just want to
see if we can get up to point control.
Okay, out of this. Now I'm going to have
to do a reboot here. I'm literally
trading completely blind. This is
absolutely ridiculous.
This is to give you an idea. This is
what I'm currently dealing with it
freezing doing this. It's
okay. Just try and open this one more
time.
Really nice. [\h__\h] sake.
Oh my god. It's two days in a row
calling it like really nice and can't do
anything about it. Okay, so I would be
now if you took this long for this hold
of this dip. All right, you're partial
one here and then you're looking for
these. Okay, so you're partiing out into
this. So TP1, TP2, TP3 up here.
Let's just hope my Ninja Trader reboots
here and I can see what it's doing
properly.
[sighs]
You can see I'm getting agitated now.
It's two days in a row.
Yeah, it's not the cash unfortunately.
I've tried it. I wish it was that. I
mean, I could try it again because it
wouldn't be harm in doing that.
You look good into TP here. All right,
here's TP
into here and then here and then runners
for up here. You look good. So, anyone
who joined me yesterday, we talked about
that buying level. I want to see higher
time frame buyers coming down here.
Well, they've done it this morning.
That's a really nice drive out.
Oh, it's not working. This is not
working.
It keeps coming up saying a newer
version of City Footprint is available
for download.
Do I just need to do this?
Okay, [\h__\h] sake.
Nice. Nice work.
Yeah, still long and strong. You should
if if you're in this, just be long and
strong. You can see it held the dips.
Every dip we talked about, this one and
this one are starting to hold. And these
are the levels for you to TP out into.
I'm really trying not to snap here. I'm
really really trying not to snap here.
[sighs]
>> [cough]
[snorts]
>> Okay, that was your TP. They're starting
to pull back off it.
I can't even [\h__\h] read this site.
It's German.
Okay, so you're failing current day
value. You squeeze back it up into your
TP. If they start losing,
right? If they've swept and they start
losing this and losing this, you'll go
back into rotation. Easy money was made
from here or here to here.
Um, I'm trading blind right now, folks.
So, you're going to have to bear with
me. I'm doing my best to fix this Ninja
Trader so I can see what the [\h__\h] is
going on again.
Every time I log in, it's going back to
German. I'm give up. I [\h__\h] give up.
I give up.
same blue box is holding. All right,
you're still holding value.
These are the levels balls must defend
if they want to complete rotation. If
bears defend this, you complete rotation
here. You're inside previous days value.
So, they have the ability. I mean, you
did tag this. They have the ability to
try and get up into previous day value
area high and this if they're going to
get going. Mag looks okay. Tessa 0.76%
up. Uh Nvidia half a percent. Meta 3/4
of a percent. Google half a percent.
Amazon's just gone red to green.
Microsoft 0.15 down. Apple 0.43 down.
[sighs]
This is what tilt looks like because you
have technical issues. One of my big big
tilt factors is technical issues.
Yeah, close the trade. Yeah. Yeah. I
like money's not a problem. It's that
I'm trading blind and when I open Ninja
Trader, I've got like these awful charts
and then when I'm going to Twin Peaks,
it's showing me everything in German
even though I keep telling it English.
So, I can't I can't navigate [laughter]
the page.
Mine and profile, which I guess means my
profile. Um, but yeah, like this
just someone up there's been taking the
piss out of me this week. They're just
like, "Fuck this guy. Make sure he can't
make as much money as he'd like."
Yeah,
I'd literally give up.
Oh,
this is what I'm dealing with. That is a
one minute. What the hell am I supposed
to do with that?
Blue box holding. You're probably going
to get value area [snorts] high now,
folks. You will probably get value very
high.
I can show you to show you like I'm not
too stressed. It's just I can't [sighs]
I can't trade it. Oh god.
It's not Ninja. It's Twin Peaks. It's
not Ninja. It's it's it's the uh
Twin Peaks. But hopefully I don't know.
We'll see.
[groaning]
Okay.
Right. You need to see if they're going
to hold value here now. So, basically,
you want to see if this turns into this.
Uh and you want to watch this shelf down
to here. You don't want them to lose
this shelf. All right. So, I would still
be bullish technically on this, but
you've lost prime position. Prime
position was here and here. All right,
this retested this low. Remember, this
is the area higher time frame bulls
needed to hold. They've tested this
twice. If they do this, they should
complete rotation. All right, I'd be
very careful being long up into this,
but it it is potentially available. If
you start losing this, that is the
rotation back down. And you're seeing
delta flip from buy side to sell side
now. And oh, it's woken up. Okay,
fantastic. I have a screen. This is
good. All right, I can actually read all
the flow for you now.
All right, so Delta was last caught
offside at uh 337 here. So, previous day
value low. So, that looks like the same
spot that bulls want to hold. Failing
that, then probably down to pro uh point
control and VWOP down here. So, this
level here needs to hold for that. Fail
this, they wash back down into this.
At least that's how I'd be treating it
right now. So, you'd want this kind of
level here to hold. This is where big
sellers came in. If they don't hold this
and they resell it, then uh volume point
control and view up very very possible.
And we have that old imbalance down
there from uh 9:48 this morning.
So, it's a good attempt to hold this.
This is the key area, the previous day
value area low, like we've talked about
numerous times today.
And you have a battle on here.
Be careful if you start breaking this
shelf, this blue box, cuz we can get
straight down, straight down into the
300s very, very quickly,
which is what they're now trying to do.
So, we want to see if they look below
here and fail and catch uh sellers
caught or not,
which is what they're trying to do. But,
you won't re-trigger anything until you
get back above value. But that is what
they're attempting to do at the moment.
They're trying to trap shorts down here.
We have a shelf all the way down into 93
that they can actually trade down into.
And below that, they can come back down
into point of control. So, let's just
see. Here we go.
The bulls need to reclaim that value
area low right now
if they're going to leave these shorts
down here caught. Here they go. They're
attempting to do it. They're looking for
this bear trap in this little low volume
node is what the bulls looking to do.
They need to reclaim this and then start
to squeeze. So here's the attempt of the
reclaim and can they start to squeeze
this big question. They're back testing
value area low. If they can get back
above and base above, they will catch
those shorts in that low volume node we
just talked about.
Big big battle here now. Seller just
reloaded here at 36. Can bulls get back
above this to catch those bears in that
low volume node for a short squeeze back
up? That is the question.
That is the question. Sorry, I was
distracted this morning for the first
No, what's it been? 40 minutes. Thank
you. Very frustrating when you have
technical issues stopping me trading.
Okay, so nothing's changed. This is the
area. Bulls are trying to defend this.
Use that as the trap. Can they get this
move? That's what they're looking for at
the moment. Bears will want to just get
complete this rotation back down. So,
we're just trading in range today. All
right. It was identified from this box
to this box. So, we can make this back
to blue uh to red now because we didn't
hold it. All right. That's your range on
the day currently. Or you can just look
at the profile. You can see the range on
the day.
Waiting to see if bulls can get back
above and hold value or if we're going
to dip further down and start moving
into that cell.
VIX is going absolutely nowhere. It is
also caught in a range. Let's have a
look at ES. ES is now back to VWAP.
Still inside.
That's definitely changed. [\h__\h] me.
wishes galore here today.
There we go.
One day, folks, one day we'll come to
the charts and not have these issues.
I'm waiting for that day.
[snorts]
Top set back up. Okay, nice. Well, good
for you guys. You're brave if you trade
with them, honestly.
Okay, they're reattempting. Remember,
bulls want to get back above this level
to complete a rotation. Bears just want
to rotate back down to value low and
VWOP.
And you just got to probably let it
build out here for a minute.
God, that's strong, Jess. O, strong
coffee.
All right, so I'd watch this low volume
node here. 07s to 97s. All right, that
could be a trap level. Otherwise,
bears are starting to take control here.
Right. If they force this lower high, if
they start to rotate, it's a problem.
Balls
need to do
this move here. That's what bulls are
looking for. It's a battle right now.
Lower time frame. She knew I need to do
it. Yeah, he's probably right.
Either that or she's drugged it to be
like, "Shut this guy up." He's well
annoying.
[laughter]
Just tapping on that value level. We're
in sort of no man's land here. We need
to get back inside if Bulls are going to
have a shot here. They're having another
go. They're trying to get back inside
and bears are defending this
aggressively.
I do think if bulls are able to get back
inside value, there is a potential move
higher today. But we did defend this
400.
We know that was a big level yesterday
into here. But if bulls can reclaim, I
think we've got liquidity here we can
aim for. I think they could maybe could
do that rotation to value area height.
It all depends if they actually want to
turn up today or not.
Getting very tight here. You can see
very very very tight.
If we lose value, we have to like sort
of be willing to flip and think about
shorts because it means we're rejecting
value. So, but the way we've built out
structure this morning is going to make
it a little bit more tricky to think
about that at the moment.
Apple starting to lose a bid.
ES back under its New York open under
VWAP coming into its 20day. So, weakness
in the ES here.
There's that bleed across the markets.
RTY red on a day
testing towards that what we talked
about. Bears have taken control now and
how far can they force this rotation is
the new question.
Yes, very very very weak here.
Right into its 20k does not look good
for the ES right now.
So previous day value defended by bears.
So we go back into rotation of current
day value. All right. So bears have
taken control. They didn't let it back
through point of control. They've
defended. All right. So, bears didn't
let it back through point of control. So
far, they've defended value. This is
their TP right now. And then they're
looking for run as an expansion under
here if they get it. Bulls, well, they
will want to defend this level here
intraday. Failing to do that, they'll
look to defend this. But really, they
need to reclaim that. Otherwise, they've
got no shot. They have no shot because
higher time frame bears are in control
at the moment.
That's why you're seeing strong selling.
ES is very very weak here.
Coming into this value area low and VWOP
top set down again. Like I said, I
personally wouldn't trade with them.
I've made that
pretty clear for quite a few years or
definitely months and months and months.
Definitely all of this year and part of
last year.
I mean, you even had a guy who was up
like 100k a couple weeks ago. Platform
went down. He proved it went down. He
has videos of it going down. He has
videos of their log not exiting. He lost
all his money. And instead, they said,
"Oh, we'll offer you a few resets.
Oh, whoopy [\h__\h] do.
Michael protect, ladies and gentlemen.
That's
why bother. Do you know what I mean?
Why? Why give him your money?
Okay. Value area low here. VWAP here.
Globeex here. If they lose this, we go
back into these green and blue boxes
below. Uh ES is very weak. Like I keep
saying, very, very, very weak. It's
coming back down for its low of day.
probably going to start to see this
market melt at the moment. It does not
look pretty if you ask me. Does not look
pretty right now.
just in a rotation. Edge to edge, it's
all we're seeing at the moment. Edge,
it's an edgeto edge day.
Yeah, definitely carry unwind into
Thursday and Friday. I mean, it was been
in the newsletter. We've talked about it
a lot.
The other side of that is
I do feel like everyone's looking at the
same trade and that always worries me as
well. You know, when everyone's looking
at the same thing, it often means it
doesn't happen or at least doesn't
happen when people think it's going to
happen.
No, I'm not sure. I'm not I'm not
anything right now.
I have to wait at the moment. enough to
calm my nervous system back down
after being very annoyed of not being
able to trade again this morning
properly.
Be watching if they hold this value
here. We go rotation back to this this
edge here. This is where bears will now
need to defend
this block, right? So, we can go edge to
edge. Bears will want to defend or at
least this low volume node to force this
rotation lower. ES is trying to find a
bid down here near the lows. You'd
imagine they're going going to go and
dunk it, but all I'm saying is be
careful
coming into this edge. And if they lose
that low day is possible.
Definitely possible.
Yes, he's about to do it.
Few
sellers got stuck down there just then,
folks.
They need to get back under 65 here. The
sellers, otherwise they're going to get
caught. Few sellers just got caught
under 65. They need to get back under 65
otherwise they're going to get caught
for a little squeeze.
It's a passive seller up there at 80. If
he moves out the way, this thing can
squeeze because it just caught a few. So
65 to 80 is your current like M1
rotation.
They're going to go back to test 65. If
they get under 65, sellers take control
again. They're testing it. You see, they
just found a bid there again. So there's
a passive buy there for now. It's only a
15 point rotation here while they make
their mind up. You've got a few people
on the tape battling. Sellers are caught
under 65. There's a passive seller at
80. So sellers want it under 65 for a
wash. If they get back above 80, they're
going to get squeezed out.
You would imagine we're going to trade
lower because ES is very close to lower
day, but they need to see the set. Here
they come. So they step back on the
tape. There you go.
They almost lost control of that for a
for nancond. Yes. Almost current day.
Big starting to spike as well. Starting
to get motoring into the 17s. Here's
the lows in. It goes boom
into those lows.
Yes, new low day. All right. So, here's
your New York open and then green and
blue box is what they will ideally want
to defend. If they fail to defend this,
then you can't rule out GlobeEx low.
There's no way you can rule it out.
Market staying heavy. Most of the mags
lost its bid now other than Meta and
Nvidia. [cough]
Yeah, once it lost, you're right. Once
it lost the shelf, right, once it failed
previous day, uh, in control a couple
times and it lost this, it really
started to wash and wash and wash and
wash and now we're moving into a sell.
So, we're outside of yesterday's value.
So the bias now remains short and you
just be covering into these. [snorts]
Uh we're in we're if we reclaim today's
value, you just want to be careful that
they just don't do a whippy rotational
type of day. Let me just check the
daily. I mean still we're an inside day
on the daily. So you want to be careful.
It's an inside bar on the daily.
You want to be careful spy looks below
and fails.
Where have we traded into 78? That was a
big level on spy.
The way we built this, we they might
want to come and test this point of
control and if they get through that
back through here and then they might
try and resell it or they might just
keep dumping if they've got inventory
like this. We'll see.
Aggressive. Aggressive. Aggressive.
Probably 75 I imagine is the next gamma
level on spy.
Zoom this out. We're losing all bits
here on spy. It's starting to lose its
uh box here. Yeah, 755 75 is probably in
the next level. fighters.
Jack, thank God we don't listen to you
every day you're here.
You can't listen, my friends. You can't
listen. If we leave this,
we're protrend. We have to reject this.
We're protren. But we're going to
respect this. Rotation can happen in
here. Can happen in here. But like I
said, we're protraed outside of this.
Oh man, I tell you what, Jack, very
close to permanently deleting you from
here, mate. Cuz you're just you're just
annoying.
You're just an annoying character.
[snorts]
All right. into this box where we found
bids overnight. All right, this is the
edge of it. This blue level that will
probably be probably be their first
cover point
and we see if they really want to go for
expansion. Uh ES starting to come into
75s.
[cough and clears throat]
Imagine I would imagine there's a bit of
a gamma level there. VIX starting to
really start to break out now. So, next
level for VIX once we get through here
will be a test of 1786.
Starting to get very aggressive on the
tape here.
Any of you that are short, I'd be
covering into this level like I talked
about. All right, that's the sort of
break and retest level or at least
covering some of your position into this
level. This blue box here, this is where
they will try and defend. It doesn't
mean they can defend it, but you would
imagine they'll try and defend. And then
beyond this, we'd be looking for a
breakdown of GloEx. And then under here,
the next level's all the way down at
800.
All the way down at 800.
Nice. Yeah, really nice, man.
Still getting aggressive here. Whole of
the mag other than meta now turns
green to reds.
Yeah, exactly, Josh. It can move down
into that into this box if we lo if we
lose the bid up there. Absolutely. It's
the next level.
If we look at the daily and the yearly,
yeah, there's no profile really till we
get down there. So, you'd be watching,
you know, previous day low into 25s. All
right. And 25,000 whole number and that
sort of 960. We start to lose that, then
yes, I I would agree with you. I would
agree with you. It's possible.
I think we might need to build a bit
more liquidity. This is getting very
very aggressive. So, need to wait for a
back test to see if they uh remain heavy
on it because they've done a big move
here. Might not look big, but this is
likeund and something point move from
losing this shelf without really much of
a back test, I guess, for a couple
minutes here. So, just waiting to see if
they offer a back test.
ES coming into GlobeEx. It's found a
little bit of a bid there at GlobeEx
spying to its 20-day. [snorts]
And you're starting to see some relief
here on the edge of the blue box.
So, it's a cover point. Like I said,
likely to be a cover point down here.
Doesn't mean they can't go lower. It's
just likely to be a first target. If I
was short off the rotation here, right?
If my Ninja Trader was being kind and we
lost these shelves, all right, this
would definitely be a cover point where
I'd be taking a huge amount of my profit
off, which is why it's highlighted the
way it is. All right, so you're starting
to see some relief now. We're going to
come up to that New York open. That New
York open will be key. It will be key.
Buyers getting aggressive up here. They
might get themselves caught. They keep
trying to buy the high of this candle.
They don't get through that New York
open. They're going to get caught buy
side delta here. Here into the sellside
imbalance. Can they get continuation?
Here's the New York open.
And they're going to look to squeeze
probably back up towards value here. And
then if I was them, I'd be very careful
about thinking about more than that.
Unless we get acceptance back into that
range again, in which case,
oh my god, it could be rotation, but you
know,
make sure you listen to Mr. Noby in chat
instead. Okay,
here we go. Testing current value area
low. Testing this shelf here. This is
where bears will have to defend.
Big buyer coming in here. He might get
himself caught hit. He might well get
himself caught hit. He's coming in with
size right into a key level.
Yeah, Rosco, I don't know like I don't
know if it was Ninja or or or uh I
thought it was my um volume footprint,
which is a third party, but seems that
this last reset has got it fixed. Okay,
so retesting this level I just talked
about.
Lots of big buying coming in here. They
need to find acceptance through this
level otherwise they will get themselves
caught. I would imagine shorts will try
and defend this now. That's marking out
with the 20-day on ES as well.
SPY found a bid on its 20-day. What did
we say to SPY? 75 probably. We're going
to trade back up to 78 now and see if
they defend this. And if we get back
inside this, we're going to go back in
rotation. They need to defend this. The
bears, this is the level for them to
defend. Point of control on the day. VW
up for the day. If they want to take
control of it, they need to take control
of it here. They want to look for lower
prices. This is the area they want to do
it from. Right? If they want to cause a
lower high, they need to do it here. And
they will not want All right. If they
want to cause a lower high, they will
not want bulls to defend this area. All
right? Otherwise, they'll be done with
it. And then we're going to go back
upside. Same if we do this. We're going
to come and rebalance this out, which
will not be nice.
Starting my nervous system starting to
calm down now. Can feel it starting to
come back down to a regulated level.
Okay, VW up and point of control here.
Like we talked about, this is the level.
This is your overunder for sentiment on
the day I would say for now.
Right, this is the level right here.
They must defend this bears otherwise
we're going to go back into current
range and we're going to squeeze up to
320s and above.
[clears throat]
I was a bear, I'd be trying to make sure
that this is not going to find
acceptance back into side inside the
range. And at the moment, they're not
doing too much of a good job about it.
And the mag's gone starting to go green
here, folks.
So, you can see this is the level.
That's why we've paused there.
Where are sellers offside? 273 and below
is where seven sellers are offside. 273
and below. 270s. They need to get back
underneath that. Basically, we have big
offside delta there at 270s. If they
don't get back off underneath 270s,
they're going to get caught. So this is
the attempt to get back under it and
stay under it and they failed. Look. So
all these sellers into 270. We can see
them on bookmap. They are caught right
now. They need to get back underneath
that otherwise they're going to start to
get squeezed out.
So you can see the delta 273 272 271.
That's where they need to get back
under. You see every time into there so
far there's been a passive buyer. They
need a snap just to make sure that they
stay safe as a seller. Otherwise, I
think they might get themselves caught.
There's this decent amount around this
level here. They're desperately trying
to get a close underneath this now.
Here they go. Good. So, they've taken
control. This is the sellers now trying
to take control. Can they get a close
though? How long we got left? 10 seconds
left of this candle. This is uh around
value area low on the day. They will
want this to just make a new low. They
will not want bulls to defend. If bulls
defend this and they start reclaiming
these 270s, these bears are going to get
very, very caught cuz they come in here
very aggressively
back to these 70s where they've got
offside delta again.
It's a lower time frame battle here.
Bulls have the chance here.
They got to get back above 73 and drive
out. So, if they do that and create a
new high, I think you might get a little
short squeeze. If bears hold this, they
can rotate back to this low of day. So,
we just I'm not I've got no position
here. I'm just watching the tape. I can
see how big the delta is here. It's very
very offside into these 70s. We are
below that right now. So,
we will see. I think if we get back
above 73
and definitely above 93, there's a
squeeze. All the time we're below 273,
bears have control. Lower time frame.
[snorts]
Yes, I rolled to March. Guys, everyone,
everyone asking questions, all you have
to do is look at the side of the chart.
Look at the numbers on the side of the
chart. That will show you that I've
rolled to March. Okay,
more volume on the March contract. Now,
like I said yesterday, likely that I
roll over by Tuesday.
Oh my god, lots of new people here. I
think volume on the right is your New
York anchor. All right, this is volume
since 9:30. We're back over the 70.
Squeeze is on here, folks. Squeeze is on
here. They've got to get back over 93s
now. So, the transition is 73 to 93. If
bulls get over 93, this thing will
squeeze.
Feathering into this long just to see if
we give it a chance here. So, I'm going
to put my stop just under 73. If they
close back under that. Oh, look at that.
Am I going to get stopped out instantly?
Possibly. Balls just got caught into 81.
Okay, out of this. [\h__\h] me. That was
quick.
They reclaim and go here.
[laughter]
H. All right. They're defending 73s.
Okay. I was going to say if they reclaim
and go there after a good stop, I'll be
very upset. Here
they come. So downside we come now.
Defended 73s on that retest. That's a
good move.
Okay. Okay.
We've come to bears.
They need a break and a new low here.
Bears.
What was that auction like at the low
88s?
[snorts]
And VIX doesn't know what it's doing.
VIX does not know what it's doing right
now.
So I say bears in total control all the
time. Price is under 270s.
Total control all the time price is
under 270s. Bears have taken control
there.
That's their pain point.
I had a little stab at that and
instantly cut it. Lost like 10 15 points
on that very quickly.
They should rotate here. They should
have the power to rotate here. Entry for
a long. No, for me,
not right now. It hasn't proved itself.
Right. We've just lost value. We've lost
this shelf. You haven't [snorts]
reclaimed any level for a long. Yeah, we
we know there's bid support here, but
they had the chance there and they
failed. Like for me, no longs right now
in this market. I I was willing to give
it a shot once they reclaimed the 70s
and I had the door shut on my face very
quickly. So, probably should have waited
for the candle to close. That's probably
my fault. Which probably says
still maybe not fully calm down my
nervous system after the ninja issues
this morning.
So, what would I say? Area is not too
bad into here for the longs, but
location's terrible. Uh, location's
okay, but momentum's terrible.
Yeah, I jumped in there too soon. That
is an error for me. Not letting that
candle close.
Nice, Carla. Yeah, I think shorts taking
control there. Totally taking control
there now in this level. See this shelf
built built out. I should have just lent
on that. That's that's screaming to me
that um
I'm like
maybe a bit tilted from what happened
earlier. That's two days in a row.
That's probably
I have to really question whether I take
a trade now today.
To really question whether I take a
trade now today, I think
If I look at my journal, I know my
biggest tilt factor by my well two tilt
factors. Break too many break evens in a
row and tech.
Too many break evens in a row in tech.
Today I had tech. Yesterday I had tech.
So be carrying a bit of that over.
What do you mean? We're testing previous
day value at a high. Are you Are you Are
you okay? We're We're definitely not
We're well below that, Albero.
Okay, this New York level is being used
as an overunder right now.
Bears failed to break down here. Bears
must get a new low here. Bears fail to
make a new low here, they're going to
get very upset. They've done the hard
work. They need to get a new low. These
bears.
Here they come.
Failed again.
They're coming again. They're going to
have another go. They need to get a new
low. These bears here.
They will get very upset if they don't.
They've done the hard work at 270s.
They need a new low.
If we break this uh well really you're
looking at low of day globeex low 2574
and then you're really looking at 800s
and VIX is just rotating in range. It's
very ugly.
No sustained breakout. It's literally
sat in the middle of its range right now
on the VIX. [snorts]
[clears throat]
They're having another go for the
breakdown here. The Bears, they're
flying in here. They're getting more and
more pissed off that they haven't done
it yet. They need that breakdown. They
need a new lower day. Otherwise, they
don't get their cover point.
Definitely a little bit of absorption
down here, but again, it's a bearish
momentum right now. They've taken
control from those 270s. They should get
a new low of day here. The bears
failing to do that will be a problem for
them. Here they go. So, they're coming
for it now.
Took long enough. They took long enough.
spider's back to that 20-day mean
reversion.
VIX is trying to find a bid. It's got to
break out though and make a higher high
here. The VIX I'm not convinced of this
chart over here right now.
That is uh what are we doing? What are
we doing? It needs to get going here and
break out.
Can see this edge down here keeps being
defended by high time frame buyers
again.
They might come back up here. If they
don't get this cell versus this little
ledge, they might get caught again. And
that would be the uh failed break lower.
Oh my gosh. Bears have failed. They fail
the rotation. They need to defend this
uh blue line, this New York open.
Otherwise, we're going to come straight
back to 260s.
They need to defend that New York open
otherwise we're going 260s.
They're not doing a very good job here
into low vol node and we're probably
going to go to 60s now.
There is a little note here. 40s. And
then let's just make sure this is lined
up properly. They need to defend this
here, this blue level here. If they
don't defend this, we're going to drift
high. If they defend this, then we can
go, they can slap this back down. But
they've got to come in, and they got to
come in soon because a few of them came
back in at 197 and got caught. So, if
they lift this, we're going to go 60s.
And VIX has failed again. This is the
one worry I would say for these bears.
The VIX has just pushed and failed
again.
Here we go. So, back up to the 60s then.
And if we get back inside 60s, they're
going to get really upset. And if we get
back above the 70s, the all the bears
are stuck up there, right? We talked
about that. 70s is their level. This is
where they came flying in. Remember,
this is where I lost that trade. I was
looking long here without waiting for
confirmation and instantly got slapped.
Right? So, we're revisiting this shelf
now. And if we get back above that, that
would be a failure to make a new low.
And this will be the trigger long
back inside of a range rotation, believe
it or not,
in an inside day.
70s are going to be visited here. We
know bears absolutely hammer 70s. If
they get stopped out at 70s, this thing
flies. Here we go. Here's 70s.
If they get stopped out here, this thing
flies. So, this is a huge level for them
now. and 93s will be their pain point.
All right. So 70s to 93s is that old
rotation
[clears throat]
same levels. What I would say now though
is bears failed to make a new low.
So, it's possible we come up into 316s.
Once we get over 70 and pop 90s, it's
possible we come up into this shelf.
So, it's back and forth today. Why is it
back and forth, folks?
Is it because it's Jack's big trend day
lower, or is it because we're in an
inside bar and maybe rotating? Just
wondering.
Are we underneath initial balance?
Not yet.
Nice, Carla.
All right, here we go. So 90 is being
popped. So we might go straight up to
sort of the 310s
320s now. So
try to help out here.
Hopefully you can see it when I'm
calling it and it makes sense to you
guys. Over the 90s is a squeeze back out
to this next red block. All right. So,
if it if it can get over the 90s,
there's a squeeze out to that next red
block.
I'm going to get a refill on coffee.
Come right back.
[cough]
>> [snorts]
>> All right.
Yeah, it's it's trying to go, folks.
This thing's trying to go.
Yeah, hopefully it helped you. I mean,
guys, these are these are days like
these are days where you have to be
playing the edges. Like if we just zoom
out,
we're likely to try and rotate back
inside of this. All right. So, if we
can't find expansion lower, remember
here, right, was the naked point of
control. Here is like
into discount,
right? Trying to short down here is not
ideal. Not without structure. Your short
this morning came from previous day
value area high, right? So
or value area high, previous day point
of control. The short, the first short
was a snapshot here, right? Then they
held this. Okay, this is telling you
bulls are going to defend this level
which we had already identified
overnight. We came back in one, two,
three. Can't get over previous day point
control failure. All right, maybe here
is a nice short. Maybe here is a nice
short. But it's down into a rotation,
right? That's all it is. And back inside
we go.
So, you got to be somewhat careful. Um,
and if we look at
the shelf which we're protecting today
where we're trying to get back inside
previous day's range, the shelf we're
protecting is 25,000.
If you go to the daily, there's a shelf
25,243
on the adjusted chart. We're trying to
get back into yesterday's range until we
reject yesterday 280s. All right. Then
we can see expansion again lower, which
they're trying to do now, which is the
280 level. So that that's the battle of
like, are we going rotation? Are we
going lower? Are we going rotation? Are
we going lower? But you don't want to be
like too biased in one direction right
now. We had a big sell day yesterday. We
had a big sell day overnight.
If they're going to sell, they need to
sell from here. And they need to see
follow through under here. And right now
we don't have it. So intraday
we're still in this. Right? Think about
your opening 15 minutes. Look above
fail, look below fail. That's your
rotation for the day. Right? If we get
back inside here, we're back inside
previous day's low. If we get back
inside here, we're back inside previous
day's value. You want to be very careful
being too biased one side. We can be
biased once it really starts to break
away and shows itself, but even the mag
can't make its mind up right now. just
night like days like today. Nice and
easy. Did big wash overnight. Remember
the the level we wanted. I'll show you
my Discord because they they they take
the piss out of me. Like these guys know
cuz I wasn't here last night. I was out
for dinner. These guys know. All right,
if we come up,
Alex's moved down happening in Asia.
Right, we already hit the target right
here. Right, these guys know what
they're looking for. Mo correctly
identifying it. We hit this target,
right? And I showed them last night.
We're trading into discount now. So, you
want to be careful and you just follow
follow the process and let them build
out liquidity. Remember, like once we
once we liquidate a big level, all
right? Unless you get a cascade effect,
they're going to build more volume out
to then go for the next level and go for
the next level and go for the next
level. They have to build volume out
each time. We don't just move straight.
So, even if we want to think about
Right?
We've basically done this for a few
weeks. We've leaving this volume Friday
last week. We left the volume. We back
tested yesterday. We've crashed down
into a big level. We're coming back
here. The chances of just like doing
this are slim because these legs here
are what builds out volume. So, if we're
going to move lower, we're going to need
buyers in here. And if too many shorts
get caught at the lows, then we're going
to back test higher up. That's the kind
of day we're in today.
Right?
Those of you who are orb traders, like
you're not even outside your orb. You're
not outside your initial balance. You're
not outside current day's value. We are
outside previous day's value.
So potentially drift back up and defend,
but I'd be very careful because we've
had one, two, three, four attempts to
break in underneath this box. Remember,
this box was identified
from GlobeEx, right? This was this is
your naked point of control. This is a
huge weekly level.
Got a weekly weekly level that we
drifted under and then reclaimed. This
red line is the point of control. We
reclaimed it.
I can't draw it on the chart because
we're on the new contract. So, I can't
show you where it came from because the
uh candles don't exist on the new
contract. But if you look at the old
contract, if you look at 930s on the old
contract, you'll see what I'm talking
about.
you'll see what I'm talking about. Uh,
Discord is just for members, I'm afraid,
my friend.
But, uh, it's a it's if you do the
beginner to advanced course, it's a
onetime fee. Um, it's just for members.
It's talk about this all the time, but
it's just so we all trade the same
direction. All right. So, you're
starting to try and break up to here at
the moment. So, there's a low volume
node here that that uh bears
[clears throat] want to defend. Failing
to defend this will cause a resqueeze
higher. This can be a buildout. There is
no doubt about it. Right. This can be a
buildout of liquidity to break lower,
but it can also find acceptance up here,
right? It can do both because we're
inside value.
It is a range rotational day.
Unfortunately, that is what we are being
dealt with today. So, edges are what's
paying today. Where are the best trade
locations today that have happened? The
failures up here and the failures down
here. All right, we're going to go edge
to edge and everyone in between is
probably going to get hurt. So, this is
the red box test. So if you're long,
this is your next TP. And now you can
look for previous day value. And if we
get back inside previous day value,
guess what? We're rotating previous days
value if we get back inside it. All
right. So make sure you're locking some
profit here.
And I'm trying to calm down, folks. I'm
trying to like I'm only human. Two days
in a row of not being able to trade
effectively is uh mega frustrating,
believe it or not.
Okay, so buyers will want to defend that
low volume node. Now, I would imagine
sellers will want to defend previous day
value. Buyers will want to defend this
little nugget here, right? Buyers want
to defend this to cause this. And if we
get inside here, we're inside previous
day's value. That's going to find
acceptance higher. Then that's going to
basically say that all of today and all
of last night was a look below and fail.
All right, so coming up to value area
high on the session and previous day's
value area high. If buyers get through
this and find acceptance into previous
days value, we can rotate and look for
previous day point of control again and
above that uh previous day value area
high.
Correct Eddie? Correct. Until it proves
otherwise, right? Range day because
that's what we've built. If we think
about this profile, this profile does if
this profile looked like this,
then we can say we're in a trend day,
right? And we could be looking for lower
prices. But we've got a bell curve.
That's a balance.
And the day before it's balance here.
So, we're trying to get back above
today's balance and get into yesterday's
balance. And bears will have to defend
that. If they don't defend that,
because at the moment, if we get back
inside, this is what I'm looking at,
right? Make this simple. If we get back
inside this, then what it's saying is
we're not accepting lower prices. And
Alex's level here of the naked point of
control was the dip by. And if you
joined yesterday, you'll know that we
said this could be a high time frame dip
by if they want to rotate it. Big if.
So if we get back inside here, this is
your look below and fail, which will
leave short sellers trapped. So then the
rotation is to here. And if they get
back through that, it would be nasty.
Doesn't have to do that. I'm just
telling you what's available is
[clears throat] someone said yesterday
or you you say two things because
there's always two sides that are
tradable when we come into key levels.
is how we react at the key levels. So,
back into these key levels up here now.
Value area low from previous day, value
area high from current day. If they play
the edge, they will try and sell this
back down to here. If they can't, if
bears don't successfully defend, and I
would even argue we can move this now
because it's not that thick.
And we can look at these levels up here.
Is the 20our course updated with the
latest info? What? What do you mean, my
friend? Um,
do you mean the volume profile course?
It's a separate course. Yes. So, if you
want to do volume profile on order flow,
I launched it yesterday. There is a
discount code. You can use capital
letters L. Uh, just type in launch with
capitals. You'll get $100 off.
Okay. So, back testing where we just
came from. So, this shelf here, you can
see the rotation. This shelf here
is your level.
This value up here, we can adjust this,
make it into this little node here. All
right. This is now the rotation between
these two levels. If they lose blue,
they come back down between blue and
green. Right? So, the current rotations
because we're in a rotational market is
between here. If we lose this, it's
between here. If we get above this, it's
probably between here. [snorts]
Market's trying to find a bid, I'll tell
you that much. And offside delta is at
93 and 73.
Offside delta is at 93 and 73.
Oh, which one's in the Discord channel?
a beginner that you have to do the
beginner to advanced course, the 20our
course. That's the only one that offers
Discord.
The volume profile course is is like 6
hours long and gets added to, but uh I
still use um teachings from the beginner
to advanced course in it. So, it's like
a supplement course, I guess, is the
best way of saying it.
An additional info, a topper upper if
you like.
Okay,
let's see. Last big sellers came in at
uh 336. So, back above that and they get
squeezed out.
Feels like they're looking to send this
at the moment. Just depends. They've got
to make a higher high here otherwise
they get caught in this red box.
[snorts]
Does that course have all your trading
view settings or is the volume profile
course? Trading view settings for what?
If you want order flow
like footprint and bookmap, do the
volume profile and order flow course. If
you want a 20our knowledge of everything
I do, which also has volume profile
stuff in it, do the 20-hour course.
I mean, GG, you can um I talk about my
volume profile even on free videos on
YouTube as well. So, you don't need to
buy the course if you just want the
settings. If you go to my volume profile
master, I think it's called or m
something like that. It's a free video
on YouTube. I give you my settings on
there.
Okay, so retatting into previous day
close and like I said, I think they're
going to resqueeze this. And if they do,
if they find success inside of value,
then they're going to come and try and
get back up into here, the high of day.
So far, buyers keep getting caught up
here in the last few minutes.
I definitely just got caught up there
above low. So bears are trying to defend
it. Aggressive buyers definitely just
got caught up there. They need to find
acceptance above, which needs to be a
close above, a pull back into it, and a
hold. So acceptance above will be a
hold. That's true acceptance. Or if they
just drive really hard. But like just
tapping and tapping and tapping, that's
saying that there's a passive seller
here, isn't there? Because we know that
this is a shelf. And if they lose this
shelf, then back down to here they come.
Where'd you get the buy and sell
signals? Uh the flow zone pro indicator
Danny. Yeah. So the H1 right now, you
see the green box? We keep dipping and
holding it. If if you have a look at the
H1, what you're looking at right now,
why it's a rotation, think about
I'll just do it on here.
All right, think about yesterday. Let's
just take this off.
Think about yesterday. All right, so
Monday, that was the overnight session
expansion. Yesterday built the liquidity
expansion, right? overnight.
Now, we need to build liquidity.
Look at these H1 guys here. If you were
short in here, right, you're caught. And
this is why I was saying this is
probably the level today while we put
the blue box in. This is the naked point
of control. So, H1 back testing supply
but holding demand. So, build out of
liquidity in here. And eventually, maybe
today, maybe tomorrow, maybe end of
week, we don't know. We will break out
of this. And if we do this side, then
we're going to come up to here. If we do
this side, then we expand into this box.
Right? So, this is why I'm saying today
is more likely to be a rotational day
because we've done that move overnight.
We're pinned in between yesterday's
area.
These are the days where I'm like, got
to be careful. Got to be careful. Like,
it's not like this day where we've done
the back test and we're going to sell
the open or where they've created the
liquidity overnight and they're selling
back down to this. Remember, this is the
magnet. So, we've now hit my magnet and
we're holding it. All right, look below.
Fail, hold, dip, hold, back to here.
We're stuck. This is why I said today is
a rotational day
until it proves otherwise.
Hopefully that helps make sense.
See, we're just stuck up here for now.
So, if we lose this shelf, back down to
280s. If we lose the shelf and the edge
of this shelf, let's just draw this in
your little gray box.
This is the tiny little rotation right
now. It's happening right here. There
you go. Starting to lose it. So it might
come 280s now down into this. Very very
possible. We do have a bit of an
imbalance down here into 300s where we
just broke out from
this little nugget here. 300s.
[snorts]
Yeah, exactly Danny. Well, really good
for like well done in identifying this
is not the condition you like. Like I
said, that's honestly like you improve
your profit factor. Not by trading more,
by trading less, by by seeing what you
don't want to trade. So, that's really
good.
Nice indeed. Yeah. If you've made money
and you don't like days like today, then
uh be happy with it and walk. Um we will
do a giveaway here, folks, in in about
an hour. We'll do another Apex giveaway.
Maybe we'll give away a little course as
well.
So, let's get those likes up. 400 of you
watching at the moment. Let's smash that
like button.
Okay. So, what would I be watching? Same
thing. Same rotation. All right. So,
we're starting to get stuck under this
little blue box. All right. Bulls need
to reclaim that for a squeeze. If they
keep selling against it, the rotation is
to here. Like I talked about, this is
this rotation. If we lose this box, this
is this rotation. If we reclaim this,
this is this rotation.
Mag is looking a bit better. I'll give
you a readout. Tesla 0.22% up. Nvidia
0.40% up. Meta 0.81% up. Amazon 0.34%
up. And then you have Microsoft almost
flat on the day. Apple 0.16% down. And
the bigger loser is Google which is a
third of percent down. So they're trying
to find a bid. And again, VIX has failed
to break out. Like I talked about, I
didn't like the look of that VIX for
shorts. It's failed to break out. It's
come back down towards its lows. It's
drifting under or it's under the 17s.
It's at 1667. It's got a PDC which has
already back tested once today at 1650
and VIX is looking like it's starting to
sort of float lower which might help
market catch a bid. But right now ES and
SPY can't get through their VWAP. So
that's why we're stuck around here on
the market.
And you're just going to see that
transition until one side's caught.
They're building the liquidity.
Yeah, exactly. Uh I'm not sure how to
say your name. Na na n N N N N N N N N N
N N N N N N N N N N N N N N N N N N N N
N N N N N N N N N N N 9577.
That's exactly it, right? So like any
trend
even on a lower time frame, right? If
the protrend is down, let's just imagine
this protrend is is down, which it is
technically. All right, if this is the
protrend is down,
right? Then this is a rebalance. And if
they resume this, the protrend will be
down again, right? Assume there's
nothing down here. All right? And this
can be like assume this part is the
daily. This is all huge daily. So when
we're playing protrend, what we're
looking for is to time the lower time
frame to get an alignment. So if we've
had a huge sell on a daily and the 30
minute is doing this, it's repricing
some of the daily sell and then you're
looking for that lower high. But what
you need is a lower low because if we
don't get the lower low, which is what
we saw here, this is where shorts get
get trapped, right? Because they attack
the lows, right? So this is the main
trend. This is the pullback. They look
for the continuation. If if the
continuation doesn't happen, that's
where they get stuck, right?
So now you're seeing that rotation back
into this level here. All right. So
bulls will want to try and defend this.
Now if they fail to defend it, we go for
the next level down. And you're just
going to see rinse, repeat, rinse,
repeat, rinse, repeat, non-stop. That's
what you're going to see today.
Yes. One minute. One minute. All right.
So catching a bid off the 80s. All
right. Now maybe they test this little
shelf here at 300s and if they get
through it they come back to 320. So
it's just the same thing over and over
and over and over again. Level level
level. That's all we do. Test test test.
Who wins? Who wins? Who wins? Who's in?
How much liquidity have we got? Have we
got someone stuck? Yes, lift or yes
dump. Right? That's all we do in a
rotation.
Understand the difference. They are very
very different markets.
Buyers getting stuck here. They keep
trying to get this lift back into this
blue box and they keep trying and keep
getting stuck in these last few wicks.
So this level here 302 looks pretty key
right now. Buyers buyers are stuck at
300. They've come in twice or three
times actually up here and not got a
close above. So they need to get back
above that. they get back above that,
they're going to go and test 317s.
That's where they want to test. There is
a little imbalance into 305s. But so
this level here is where they keep
flying in. They need to get a squeeze
back up, otherwise they get caught here
trying to buy the dip, these buyers.
So here's the little sellside imbalance.
And it just got resold instantly, the
305s.
I don't like rotation. No, Indie. I I I
try and sit out rotation as much as
possible, especially rotation early
morning. Like if if it's nice early
morning and it's a fresh test of a
level,
fresh test, fresh test, fresh test.
Fine. But as we go through the day, it
gets more and more messy. I'm less
interested and I'll just let let
everyone else get trapped and then come
back tomorrow or the day after when we
start leaving the value, leaving the
volume that we've created. And then we
get days like yesterday and Friday where
we can be aggressive because it's market
is directional.
He's trying to step back up in here and
they keep getting caught.
They keep getting caught so far. There's
passive selling here. They keep getting
caught. They need to get closes back
above and we're going to see this
rotation again. So, this technically now
would be red,
right? So, sellers will want a lower
high and a dump and buyers will want to
reclaim it.
How do you know if there's enough folks
get stuck for the counter move? Well, it
you need to also understand what time
frame you're looking at when you're
calling talking about the counter trend
move. Um and then you need to trade in
and around a key area and you need to
look for participants on volume profile
or on bookmap whatever you're looking
for to get stuck or even even like here
right if we've been here long enough we
couldn't break out we create this shelf
like I said like once we leave the shelf
we're going to come to here all right if
too many sellers come in at the low of
the shelf and they reclaim the shelf
then we're going to come back to here
the easiest way to see that though for
me in my opinion would be
I'm going have to change this on a uh
NQ.
All right. Would be in this.
And like I said, the buyers kept getting
stuck here. Here's that little
imbalance. Right. So in that last move,
this is all market buy side and they got
stuck and we flipped to sell. If we look
at the highs up here, buyers had
numerous attempts to move higher
and failed. And then we go big sell and
this is where sellers came in. This why
I'm saying buyers need to get back above
this otherwise they're caught, right?
And that's the easiest way to see it for
in my opinion would be using orderflow.
If we lose this, like I said, we can
come straight back down to that New York
open and value area low on the day. And
if buyers can't defend that, then we can
break.
ES looks very weak. Very, very weak.
This feels like uh Friday now
and yesterday. Same kind of thing.
There we go.
And this kind of becomes gray now to be
honest. That's your rotational zone.
It's so thick.
I think it does, Richard. I don't I'm
not 100% sure, but yes, I think I think
that is the case that it will end today
unless they extend it, you know,
unless they extend it. Yeah, I think
that would be the case.
I don't know uh 100% but uh yeah, I
think that that that is normally the
case with Apex. When the sale ends, the
activation fee ends.
I don't know, random guy. Why does your
one minute chart look different? I I
don't know why your one minute chart
looks different. Maybe you're looking at
a different instrument. Maybe you
haven't rolled over. Maybe I have no
idea. You tell me. I can't see your
chart, so I can't tell the answer to
that.
Positions get built, losers stop loss
propel the winner's direction to the
next liquidity more or less. Yes, ex
exactly that. That is literally it.
That's the game you've just described
there. That's exactly it, my friend.
Looks heavy here. and the rotation
continuing with losing this gray box
here. If we lose this gray box, New York
open value area low on the session. If
we lose that, dip down into this higher
higher time frame demand level. If we
reclaim this box rotation here again,
you can see this is where we've spent
most of the time today. This is the area
you do not want to trade in in my
opinion and how I trade. This is the
area I would not want to trade in. Would
not want to trade it in that gray box
area. Very very uh messy in and around
that area.
>> [snorts]
>> Delta's starting to get pretty heavy
down here.
They're starting to slam this or attempt
to into value very low on the day is
what they're trying to do.
Google losing a bit.
Probably coming for that value area
lower in New York open now. And if we
lose that fade back down again
just looks very messy this market
to my eyes anyway. I don't look look at
this and think yes I want to trade it.
Quite the opposite. This morning I
thought yes I wanted to trade it. Not
now.
Not now. We can wait for us to leave
range and then maybe uh something more
tradable.
back into these lows where buyers have
stepped up. You got to think at some
point they're not going to be able to
step up. We're seeing so much momentum
here. Spy getting very aggressive now.
So, is NQ going to follow suit
and take out the lows, IBOWs, or are we
just going to find bids off this same
area? The momentum is very heavy. Like,
I would not be brave enough to be a
buyer now. Let's put it that way.
Right, we've just rejected value area
low again. So, we're outside previous
day value. We're inside current value.
But if we reject here, then you would
expect them to try and complete the
rotation. The only thing is we have
tested this naked point of control in
the New York session and found a bid.
So, it's hard for me to be too biased
directionally right now, I'd say.
What's the difference of volume profile
of session and day?
Well, session would be the session
you're looking at. Day would be the
whole thing.
Correct, Max. I agree. Absolutely agree
with you.
Absolutely agree with you. All right.
So, buyers are trying to defend the same
level. I don't think they're going to
have too much success down here. They've
had many, many attempts. It's possible
because we're in a rotation that they do
it, but uh it's kind of
gh kind of day. You got to have balls of
steel if you're going to defend this
three, four times over is all I would
say right now. Balls of absolute steel.
Vo up at VWAP. So, probably back tested
this gray box again where I said you
probably don't want to trade around
here. So sellers right now failed to
break down, but this can be a lower high
if they defend this big if. How long we
got left? 40 minutes. These are not
trades I'm going to take. Sellers will
want this. Buyers will want this. Right,
that's the level. Sellers will want to
defend into that. Buyers will want to
reclaim it and go squeeze. And the VIX
is the VIX does not know what the [\h__\h]
it is doing right now. It looks
terrible,
which is common for rollover week. very
common for rollover week.
So, last lot of sellers came in, I'd say
from 64 to 73, which is where we're
coming up to now. So, they bid off that
green box again and now we go gray box
again. Like we talked about the
rotations. This is the next rotation.
So, we're doing the rotation. Now you
have to see does the sellers defend the
rotation or are they exhausted now and
thinking, "Oh my god, we've had so many
attempts to go lower. Why have we not
gone lower?" I don't I don't know what
they're going to do because we're in a
rotation. Literally anything is possible
in a rotation. Sellers should try and
defend to like force this market lower
at this point, but they've done a pretty
[\h__\h] job of it this morning so far, I
would say, which is uh not surprising.
And like I said, VIX is literally in no
man's land.
because it can't break down under PDC
and it can't break out under over PDH.
So, it's just stuck right in the middle
of its range right now. The VIX,
come on sellers. So, maybe they defend
this now.
When I look at weeklys, I I just do the
whole thing. When I look at weeklys,
when I look at previous day, it's RTH.
When I do weeklys, I just draw the whole
thing because it's it's so much data
that it's not going to make a difference
if there's like a little bit of GloEx in
there in my opinion.
All right. Well, here's the rotation for
this phase of this market, right? So,
this is the rotation. Once they make
their mind up, someone should win.
Can I use the bathroom while you guys
watch this? I'll be back. I would uh
look, my opinion on this, I would lean
short on it right now because
if I had to pick a bias, we've defended
that. We're defending this. We should
break down. But this level here is a
cover point. Not just because of this.
It's because it's the old naked level,
right? And below that, if you get lucky,
you get GloEx. That would be my opinion.
But right now, so far today, they've
done a pretty pretty [\h__\h] awful job
in um doing that move, enforcing that
move. But that's what I'd be looking for
is can they break down underneath into
that sort of uh red line.
That's what I'd be looking for
personally.
[snorts]
All
right, big Apex news folks just came in
for those of you who just asked. Sale
ends today. All right, sale ends tonight
at midnight Eastern time. 90% sale, but
they have extended the lifetime PA fee
to December 23rd. So, any accounts that
you buy before midnight tonight, you
have until the 23rd of December to pass
at that uh cheap lifetime PA fee, which
is awesome. So, you guys don't need to
rush it because that's probably why some
of you are asking, which is really good.
I'm glad that they've done that. That's
really good, especially over holiday
season.
Yeah, there you go. You just saw the
same thing. Yeah, which is great. Which
is great. Okay, sellers still defending
this gray box. They're still trying to
force. They want this bare flag and a
breakdown. They're looking to defend
this gray box in rotation.
Hate it when it does this. They're
looking to defend this. They need to get
under New York and then they're going to
look to swipe these guys out. That's
what they're looking to do. Whether they
can do it or not is another thing
because this is the edge of value. So
value buyers keep trying to bid off
this. But like I said, I would stay with
the shorts at the moment because we've
started to lose control of some key
levels.
Can they sell it?
Just having a little look around. You
got to watch uh spy into this low day.
Can see expansion. How long we got left
or lunch? Not got too long left either.
35 minutes. Value still holding up.
Still holding up. Buyers still coming in
here. Sellers just want one snap. I
think once sellers get one good snap,
they can get out of their positions and
they'll be happy for the day.
Yeah, I think it's good that they've
done that, Otus. Like it means people
don't have to force, you know, when they
when they say it ends today probably
makes you force trades a bit more. So,
now that they've extended it, I think
that's really good. Gives you a bit more
time to do it. Okay, testing this level
again, again, again, again. Aggressive
selling coming in again. Seeing some
absorption. I think we've got a snap
coming any second now. They keep trying
to absorb it. Here they go. They're
trying to drive it now. They're looking
for 215s on the tape. Still seeing
absorption here.
Still seeing absorption here
into 230 225. Once this guy moves, you
get 215s, but he's still absorbing and
he's trying to walk up. Once he moves,
he might get a wash, but he's not
willing to move right now.
Soaking the bid here. He is really
soaking the bid here.
And he's walking up with it now.
So, I think 230 225. That's his pain
point.
He's flashing 225 now. He's he's lifted
and moved. Let's see if we drop under
him. No, he's trapped and soaked. God,
he's playing some games here. Why so
many games at this level in the New York
Open?
He's bidding. Rebid. Rebid. Rebid on the
limits. Pulled it. He just pulled it.
Does he come in and soak like he did
last time and trap? Yeah, he's trying
the same move again.
What are you doing, buddy?
Now he's gone back on the tape at 30s.
Does he pull it? Now he's pulled it.
There we go. Now we're washing through
probably to these 15s now, like we
talked about. Here we go. So, coming to
15s and then 200s.
Weird dude that buyer the way he was
acting there. Bit weird. Weird.
So you need to defend that level. We
just broke down from 30s. That's where
he was absorbing. If they reclaim all
the 30s, he just gets back in the money.
So he's back in the money at the moment
for now.
And he stepped back on the book above
20s now. So he's lifted he's moved his
his bid from 15s to 22s.
Mate, what are you doing? You are
playing games. You are playing games.
Now he's at 20s. 150 lot. He's trying to
absorb 20s. If they snap this, you're
going to go 200s, I think, cuz he's
moved from 215s.
There you go. There's the break of it.
There's the break of it. Now, can you
see follow through? Because you had a
big seller there at 220s, 150 lot. He
might get caught there at 220s. Like I
said, he paired off. You can see him
there. 205 lot at 220s
just got absorbed.
And if we go back upside then we're
going to go gray box or at least we're
going to go 243s and then maybe gray
box.
Oh
news at 230. Could they reach
day L 2580 by passing 25150 otherwise
25400?
What you say Matt? 20
5080.
I mean, that's definitely possible. It's
inside a GlobeEx. Definitely possible to
get down there. Does Apex allow
scalping? Yeah.
Yeah, they allow scalping.
That seller right now has caught
this guy on map. right here is caught
246 lot of 220. He got himself caught so
far.
He tried to sell through and he didn't
get the follow through. There was a
little snap and then he got absorbed.
Especially level to watch where his pain
is.
Back inside value we go.
Oh, I'm so uninterested. Will bitmap
work good enough with Ninja Trader level
two data or should I buy global? Uh I
have global but um
I don't know. You used to be able to
link it. I don't know if you can. Um I
would email them like I don't want to
give you the wrong answer there. Otus.
Just shoot them an email. They're
they're normally so quick at bookmap to
reply. Just shoot them an email.
If you're paying for I I don't know if
you can do it with data from the prop
firms. I I just pay for it. I just have
it. But uh if you can email them, it
save you a bit of money.
VIX is trying to get going now back
through the 17s, but still in the mid
part of the range. Like if we look at
VIX again,
nothing's really changed here. Stuck in
the middle of the range.
Still boxed in. Just in no man's land.
Not aggressively breaking out, which
will help the short. Not aggressively
breaking down, which help the long. Just
stuck.
Bears really want to get this move, man.
They're really looking they snap into
this. They've got this liquidity built.
Once they use this,
it's possible that we can see expansion
if they are able to use it. Right now,
they've done not a very good job.
If I'm mainly looking at hourly and
daily time frames, what would the best
areas to set up
to set up profiles? I would say uh go to
a 30 minute if you're going to set up
profiles.
You're going to use daily and hourly.
You want 30 minute profiles because you
my opinion is you want where the where
the volume comes in. Where does the
volume come in? 9:30 open. So what I'm
always interested in is 9:30 to 4:00.
9:30 to 4:00 is where the volume is. So
that's what I'm interested in. If you if
we're going to measure volume, we look
at the difference overnight.
This volume, no volume, no volume, no
volume volume. All right? So if we think
about support and resistance, right? We
need to know areas which were traded
with high volume or low volume. We need
to know the areas of low volume, but we
don't need to know as much these areas
here.
if you're looking at profiles.
Okay, so they failed to break down and
we're going to squeeze out probably back
towards this gray box. Now, we've just
got above this node here. We're probably
going to come all the way up here and
you're going to see this rotation we've
been talking about happening again.
Right. So, first rotation was
here to here, here to here, here to
here. Failed this box down to this box.
Failed under this to green to gray to
green. Might well go to gray again. and
then it may be up here or maybe back
down here again. I don't know because
this is a rotational market. Like I
said, I don't know what we do in
rotation. You can only play the edges or
you can be like me and just not play at
all.
I don't
I don't know if this is the same pattern
as yesterday. I'm going to be honest. Uh
trader tilt. Yesterday was Friday's
pattern,
right? For me, there's a big difference.
This is the difference. Yesterday, we
left value. We went into sell. That's
the repric. That's your sell point to
try and get down. Uh Friday was the
same. We left value
with a big sell. That was the repric. We
sold this to go down. Today,
we're not really aggressively leaving
value in the same way. It doesn't mean
we can't go lower. But if we look at
today's action, look at the sell this
morning. Where's the big sell this
morning? It's not really is it? It's
it's it's a it's a creation of volume
this morning. Right? You could say the
sell from here, but the difference is
we've created structure. Whereas
yesterday and Friday, we hadn't created
all this structure, right? We were big
cells into open land. Big cells into
open land. That's the big difference for
me is we've created some structure now.
So, I'm
would have to say I disagree with you
in terms of what we're doing.
Not not to be a dick. I can easily be
wrong. Like I said, I'm happy to be
wrong. Hopefully, I'm wrong if you're
positioned for the sale because I'm not
positioned in anything. But I would just
be careful thinking about that. I think
today's market is not the same as
yesterday and Friday's market. For me,
they're very different.
Uh, no li lifetime dogee. I can't
remember what the rebuild is. It's like
50 or 60%.
Something like that. So, you want you
want to pass them by the 23rd of uh
December or whenever they've just
announced it. You want to pass by then.
Okay. So, back up to uh VWOP and point
of control 72s into this gray box up
into here. All right. And do they defend
this gray box or do we find back
acceptance back inside? And we go
rotation back up again. All right. And
again, VIX doing a terrible job. Like I
talked said about, we're not seeing VIX
break out to the upside, which is
hurting people looking for shorts,
looking for continuation lower today.
There hasn't been a continuation lower.
We haven't broken down outside overnight
value.
I don't know what to think about the VIX
expiry.
I think VIX is positioning for a really
nasty move, but I think we can position
here for months.
Um, I haven't checked the uh OPEX levels
to be quite honest with you.
Uh, a lot, Patrick. A lot. A lot of
people do.
Um, because they don't understand,
like the guy that comes on talking crap
in here every day. They don't understand
when we're in a trend and when we're
not. And so, they get caught. It's why I
avoid it, right? Once I see this,
especially as we go into the like
further into the day, it's like for me
it's why do I want to trade this? Why do
I want to trade this when we like Friday
and Monday was so good? Why trade why
why trade the day where it needs to
build out? Why not f for me? Why not
focus on the day where we use the people
who have been caught? Those are the days
that I like to focus on personally. But
it's each to their own. Some people love
trading rotation. There's nothing wrong
with trading rotation as long as you
understand that's the condition that
you're in. If you don't understand
that's the condition you're in. That's
where the pain comes
into the gray box. Selling the gray box.
Now, what are they doing? I don't know,
folks. I don't know what they want to
do. I have no idea what these folks want
to do,
but at least you can see the level to
level. Hopefully, it makes sense like
even me plotting the boxes out for you.
Hopefully, it helps you understand like
where we trade to and and and how and
why. Beyond those levels, I don't I
can't tell you beyond those levels what
we're going to do until we get through
it, right? Until we get through it.
So, we come back down. Look at the node
that we developed here. All right. So
bulls will now try and defend this. If
they fail to defend it, then maybe they
just got caught up here. We can check
again.
Right. So we have some buyers in that
last big candle.
Yeah. So sellers need to defend 50s now,
right? And then they can look for a
breakdown lower.
Hopefully that helps. Trying my best
here folks while trying to keep a calm
head.
back to value area low again after a big
big sell. This is where they just bid
off. And if they fail to bid this time,
then maybe you get initial balance low
if they go for expansion. You might get
a snap because that was a decent tug
down, but you might need one more
rebalance first. I don't know. Time will
tell.
This guy's bidding at 200s again. Is
there anyone underneath? Not really. Not
at the moment.
blue account today. I'm sorry to hear
that. Sorry to hear that. Uh, use it as
a lesson. Use it as a lesson. Try and
understand why did you blow the account?
Did you chase? Did you fail to
understand the market conditions?
Did you not know it was in a rotation?
Did you oversize? Did you not stop out?
Did you add into a loser? Like, make
sure you understand why you blew the
account. Because if you just blow
accounts and you don't understand why,
um, then it's a waste of money. But I do
believe if you blow an account and you
learn from it, it's actually money well
spent. As as painful as that might
sound,
yeah, Patrick, we've talked about that.
I mean,
all I would say is I've consistently
said do not trade on Project X. Do not
trade with Topstep. Do not trade on
Project X. I've consistently said that
for for many, many
months.
I'm really sorry to hear that you're
having those issues, but it it's not
uncommon on there. and they have shown
absolutely
no uh
no motivation to get it fixed. Let's say
that they've shown zero motivation,
zero ethics
to do anything and everyone celebrated
last time after there was like a stopout
and they gave people free accounts. They
didn't give you your [\h__\h] money back,
you know? So, there's a reason all the
other firms as well, like they've
stopped working with the other firms.
They're trying to monopolize stuff. They
are greedy. They will take your money in
my opinion. So, just be careful.
Yeah, the indicators repaint.
There you go. They repaint. You just got
to zoom into them. But yeah, they
repaint. It's It's an option. You You
have the option on the uh in on the
indicator.
Uh
where is it? Somewhere on here.
Somewhere towards the bottom. You can
choose repaint or not.
Okay. Market back in a dance.
Meta 5. Didn't Meta 5 get closed down
though? Didn't they have like issues of
fraud or something like a few years ago?
Oh, Jack's back in here talking [\h__\h] My
broadcast is 6 seconds delayed. So,
do you know what, Jack?
Today's your lucky day, mate.
Okay.
Uh yeah, unfortunately for Jack, he's
gone beyond time out. Jack Jack will no
longer be able to be here. Um I gave him
weeks, weeks and weeks and weeks to stop
being a [\h__\h] And um he was
unfortunately unable to look at himself
and was just too disruptive to too many
people for too many times and was just
started to annoy me. And you know, I do
this for free, so I don't need to put up
with it. So unfortunately, we will not
be seeing Jack here again. I tried I
tried to give him a chance. I tried to
be nice, but uh there we go. Um,
[laughter]
sorry, Jack. I tried mate. I tried to
give you so many chances. What are my
thoughts on Traderify? Yeah, I really
like Traderify. I think they're really
good. Um,
yeah, really like it. I like how you can
uh
do the same day payouts and stuff now.
Lucid as well. I'm going to do I will do
a video um I want to I want to do two
videos for you going into 2026 like the
top five prop firms that I think you
should use and why and and do it based
on your trading style. And I want to do
a video on like how I would trade if I
was a new trader going into 2026.
Up 1,000 on new I'm calling it a day.
Appreciate your analysis, Alex. You're
you're welcome, Chris. Hope you're good.
Thanks, Greg. Yeah, I'm sorry to hear if
you're on top step. Yeah, I mean, look,
I I recommend a Apex, but it's a it's
Apex is very different to a lot of the
other firms, right? You have to treat it
differently. Um, Apex is great for
scaling. If you want to make big money
and scale the accounts, Apex is great.
If you're also low on budget and you're
a newer trader and you just want to feel
it out, Apex is great. But you have to
understand the rules. Trailing draw down
is a [\h__\h] So
once you get into the PAS, you got to
take your time, right? Build your buffer
out. Once you build the buffer out, Apex
is the same as everywhere else. Like you
can make good money from it, but it it
depends. Can can you It's It's actually
a really good test. Do you have the
discipline and patience? Because I I'm a
firm believer trading is about being a
sniper, which means being disciplined.
You've seen me today like I wanted to
trade and fade the market this morning
on the first push. Ninja Trader or or my
whatever it was, the footprint wasn't
working. So, I'm annoyed. So, I'm trying
to fix it and then there's lag and then
I can't get out of the trade or I can't
I can get out of the trade. I couldn't
see the trade. Get out of the trade,
fine, make money, but it doesn't matter
for me about making money. The process
is I'm now pissed off that two days in a
row I've had an issue. So what am I
doing? Back off. I take one trade. It
was a bad trade, right? I jumped the gun
thinking someone would trap. Didn't let
the candle close. Jumped the gun. Ate
the loss on it. That for me was an
instant cue of Alex, you're probably a
little bit on tilt here because you
didn't wait for the closure. You've been
pissed off this morning. You were pissed
off yesterday. best thing you can do is
go into capital preservation and just
chill out and come back and also market
conditions now are anyone who's joined
me for months or years will know these
are the conditions I try and avoid like
the plague um so apex with that where I
was going with this will build that
discipline into you because if you are a
trader which oversizes you're going to
blow up accounts if you are a trader
that chases you are going to blow up the
accounts if you are a trader who doesn't
use stops doesn't take profits at key
levels you're going to blow up accounts
But if you can move from that to a
trader who trades with the right amount
of size, adds into winners, takes profit
at key liquidity levels, trades A+
setups and A+ setups only, you're going
to be fine.
Yes. Uh you can copy trade 20 accounts
on Apex and you can copy trade all the
other stuff together with it.
on Apex it says $65 all in is the
activation
fee now free on activation? No. So what
it is do uh it was going to cost you
$1960
or 65 cent something like that for any
size account right now. Right. For any
size account and then uh the activation
fee will take it up to $65. You've got
the the sale ends today but you have
until the 23rd of December to pass. All
right. So, so you can buy 20, 30, 40,
50, 100 counts, however many you want at
$19 today. You have until the 23rd to
get the cheap activation fee, right? So,
you've got
what are we at? 16th uh 178 28 21 22 23
7 days, but not all of those are trading
days. So, you got like five days
basically. Five days.
What are your placing orders on?
Somebody needs to do a video on
execution.
What are y'all placing orders on? Oh,
like what software? How do we do it? Uh,
Ninja Trader uh ATM strategy
on Apex once challenge would pass. Is
there recurring monthly fee unfunded?
No. As long as you pay for the um
lifetime activation fee, which currently
is like 40 bucks, no monthly fees.
Exactly, TJ. Exactly that.
You want a course on psychology? There's
a honestly guys there, if you go through
my videos on YouTube, there's some
really good courses on psychology.
That's what I did at university. I got a
bachelor of science with honors in that.
So, let me try and post some of them.
It's worth doing. Like, it's it's free.
There's some stuff in in the beginner to
advance course, but like I I post so
much stuff for you guys for free. Um,
but you have to go through it all. Let
me find it for you. I haven't done one
for a while, right? Trading psychology,
understanding tilt and self-sabotage.
Let me post this for you guys.
Right, there's one here.
Try and find some more for you. I know
I've done a few.
There's one here.
These are all going back a while before
I had really anyone watching.
There's so much There's so much on here
that I I did for free. There's one on
here.
There's four video. I'm going to give
you four videos. We should probably make
a slate for these, shouldn't I? And
there's one here.
Right. Those are four completely free
psychology videos. They will hopefully
they will help you a little bit.
[snorts]
Fiser got hammered, did it? Uh, let me
have a look. Uh,
10 minutes, guys. I'm going to do a
giveaway. Uh, D. My brain cannot get in
gear this morning. Finnbiz. God. Sorry,
guys.
I mean, the whole He's saying Fiser is
getting hammered, mate. The whole market
is getting hammered, right? The whole
market um the the breadth
actually breth.
All right. Healthcare all down.
Energyy's down massive.
It's funny. The only things holding on
are heavily weighted in ENQ. Nvidia,
AVGI, AMZ, Amazon, and Tesla and Oracle
and Palanteer and Meta. rest of the
market. If you look down here at the
what's in the spiders, healthcare and
energy and finance, all clobbered, all
absolutely clobbered.
Where is the sectors for this?
Okay, there you go. So, reclaiming gray.
All right, so Bears did an awful job.
Like I talked about, bears needed to
defend this and get back under the New
York open and underneath value. Failed
to get under it. We go back to gray.
They have one more attempt. They get
caught there. Now we go from gray to
red. We get through this, we go from
here to here. If we get through this,
they get relief. All right, these are
the trades. This is how it's setting up
today. It's just rotation, rotation,
rotation, rotation. And I know I am a
stuck record, but hopefully by me being
really annoying and being a stuck record
to you guys, hopefully it's going to
start to sit in your brain and you're
going to start to recognize it and be
like, I get it. I get the level to level
now.
Can you reset a PA account or do you
have to start back? No, you have to
start back at Eval. Uh, the only ones I
think you can reset a PA account with
are
Take Profit. Maybe there's somewhere
else, but I don't know if there is. But
I know take profit can.
Hi, Alex. Appreciate the patience today.
See you tomorrow. Hopefully top [\h__\h]
would be back up. Yeah, I hope it's up
for you guys, man. And I hope Michael
does the right thing by you all. Any of
you who were in profit and couldn't
close out, he should give you your
profit. You know, like that's the right
thing to do. And I [\h__\h] tell you
what, if he's going to open up a
brokerage, he needs to do right by you
lot because they can't pull this [\h__\h]
with real money. And that's the [\h__\h]
thing that I think is dangerous. If they
can't [\h__\h] run a sim, how are they
running real orders? That would worry
me, guys.
Um, [gasps]
do following you. I've greatly ramped up
the number of my trades. A good thing.
If I go for Apex 50K account and I want
to pass in five days, that means trading
one to two minis, not micros. Would you
agree? Uh,
no, not necessarily. Uh if you break
3,00 3,000 down into five days, you're
looking at $600 a day. You can easily do
that with micros, but it will depend on
the range available to you. Um we've got
a volatile market right now. So, you
know, if you're picking edgeto edge, I
think you could do it right now, but
it would depend on the market
conditions. Would really depend on
market conditions. Spy keeps failing
VWAP, folks. Spy keeps failing VWAP.
Cannot get over it today. Every little
push in is getting sold into.
Yeah, take profit's very expensive to
reset the pro account, but you can do
it. That's all I'm saying because
someone asked, can you reset it on Apex?
I was no,
I'm close to passing 30 Apex accounts.
If all are activated, I can only trade
20 simultaneously. Could you please
clarify? Yes. So, what you want to do is
uh you will be able to activate 20. 10
will be on standby. Windows 10, you
might need to pay you'll have to sign
the dock, but I think you'll you'll need
to pay for the monthly fee until you
need them. I think that's how it works
with that.
So, if you're paying 19 or $30 a month,
you continue to pay $30 a month for the
10 you're not using until you use it.
Traderify said there are resetting
today's P&L on all accounts. Yeah, see
that's the difference. Tradeify do right
by their traders.
They do right by their traders. Like
they did it last time. Like they had to
eat [\h__\h] for top steps error, but they
do right by their traders. And I I
respect Brett for that, man. Cuz it's
not his fault. We all know where the
buck ends.
[snorts]
End of day trading. Which one is better?
Uh end of day is easier to manage for
sure.
end of day much easier to manage than a
trailing draw down. Much much easier.
Okay, back into uh point of control and
we up right back into this gray box
again. It's the same story. Bulls need
to defend this to go continue higher.
They failed this red box again. We
talked about this here, didn't we? We
talked about this move from here to
here. We talked about this move from
here to here. And we talked about this
move from here to here being the new
rotation. And if they lose this, we go
back into this. If they hold this, we go
back into this. Okay?
Does everyone understand that? Because I
know I've said it a lot of times today,
but do you do you can you see it? Does
it make sense? Can you see what I'm on
about? That's all that really matters is
can you see it?
Next week we'll be outlining the plan to
migrate all the accounts from PS to
trade away. Yeah, Brett Brett had enough
a long time ago, man. Like [snorts] I
think they all did. The other ones that
had handled it really, really, really
well was Lucid. The moment there were
issues, they were like, "We're done with
these guys. We'll move you all for free.
We'll we'll we'll deal with everything.
We'll give you your money back. we will
honor everything. That's if you're going
to trade prop, you want to know that if
something goes wrong, they're going to
do right by it and that they're going to
fix the issues. We're not talking about
a new [\h__\h] company here. Not don't I
mustn't go on a rant here, but we are
talking about one of the the biggest and
the best and the we do this like no what
you do is you don't fix project X ever
since you launched it ever ever ever
ever. It's never been stable.
Enough said. You can't be the biggest
and the best if you can't do the very
basics. If you can't do R&D and fix
stuff, you lose that right to have that
name in my opinion.
Do right by your traders or get the [\h__\h]
out. You want to have a broker. Do you
understand what this is all about,
folks? Like, do do you understand why
all of this is happening? They're trying
to start a brokerage. Here comes a
rotation. Gray to red. If we get through
red, we go to this red. If we get
through that, this is your next target.
Um, they're trying to start a brokerage
house.
Can you imagine if you had a broker if
you had a brokerage account with them
and they go and it and it fails and you
can't get out your position. Oh,
what's going to happen? They going to
bail you out your money?
Don't think so.
What's my chat interval? I don't Oh,
chart interval. This is a M1 M1 chart.
What's the gray box around VWOP? Uh,
this was the rotation. All right, we've
thickened up the rotation, but basically
basically earlier in the day, we were
like this with a bell-shaped curve,
right? So, this is balance. Red line is
point of control. So, we know this is
the under over for the day. So, if Bulls
can stay over this, they're going to try
and get over or into previous day value.
So far today, they've found no
acceptance in here. They drifted up to
previous day point of control. But
bull's job today, they want to get back
inside here, which will leave short
sellers trapped under here. Bear's job
today, they want to defend this and try
and break lower, which they failed so
far.
3 minutes and then we're going to do a
giveaway. Um, how many likes we got in
stream? We've lost about 100 people,
which means everyone's made their money
for the day. But if you stay here, um,
let's get this up another at least
another 50 likes. Let's get up to 250
likes, folks. There's 36060 60 plus of
you watching. I want to give out, um,
some free Apex accounts.
The bands around the VWAP are set to one
standard deviation or what interval?
There's no bands around these. These are
uh, EMAs, mate. They're not they're
nothing to do with you.
Yeah, on Ninja Trader, uh, as long as
you have a copier, your ATM will copy
across across everything else. So,
here's your previous day value area low.
This is what bulls are trying to find
acceptance back inside. ES is trading
back into its VWAP now. So far today, ES
cannot find acceptance over VW up.
You're coming into lunch. Uh if I was
long, I would be taking some of my money
off here and holding to see if bulls.
All right, if they can complete the
rotation. Oh, they will need to get back
above previous day value, find
acceptance, get to point of control, and
previous day value high. That's what the
bulls are trying to
am I trading auction market theory?
Yeah. Or market auction theory, I would
call it. But yes, I am.
Nice, Max. You took you took the
rotation. Nice work, buddy.
Good morning. I'm new here. I like to
trade volume profile. I think that's a
great tool. I agree with you. It's very
useful tool.
The gray box around VWAP,
the gray box around VWAP are set to what
interval? One standard deviation or what
interval? If you know, sorry, fourth
time asking. Yeah, I said the gray
standard dev these are just your
standard VWAPS. There's no there's no
interval on this. There's no band on
this. There's no standard deviation
above or below this. This is standard
New York VWAP anchored to the start of
the day. All right, the gray box is just
an area of rotation I was interested in.
The red line is your PC. There are no
standard deviations on my VWOPS. There
is nothing. I am not playing any bands.
I'm not looking for expansion on bands.
Good day trading today. Well, if if you
like it, [laughter]
each to their own, Nihow. Each to their
own. There's opportunity for For sure.
Like I always talk about there's there's
opportunities for range traders. For
sure. For sure.
[laughter]
You must be a range trader. Neihow.
Yeah, just co coincidence, Mark. Just
coincidence. No, there's nothing there.
It's just coincidential.
[laughter]
This is the great thing about trading,
right? This is why you have to
understand like it's each to their own.
Like for some people, if you if you are
someone that loves playing edges, all
right, if you're like, I'm buying value
area low, I'm selling value area high.
Right? Look at the opportunities you've
had today. Right? If that's your game
plan, right? Then this is like probably
an A+ day. If you're someone like me
that likes looking for higher time frame
narrative to line up with lower time
frame narrative for expansion or traps,
there's nothing really to do.
I always think it's like sport. Like
some people I don't know most of you are
American here. Like if you're the Bills,
maybe your edge comes in playing in in
snowy, freezing cold conditions because
you know if the Rams come to town, well,
they're [\h__\h] because they're used to
playing in, you know, beautiful summer
heat. All right, so like that's your
edge, right? Your edge comes from the
conditions. It's the same as this. What
condition do you like playing in? Snow,
heat, altitude.
It's why it's you need home home
advantage. Home advantage for me is not
this, but home advantage for you might
be this. And this is why I always say, I
will teach you what's there, but it
doesn't mean I will trade it. My edge
comes from leaving [\h__\h] alone I don't
like. Here comes the expansion. Here's
previous day close. Um, if you can get
through this, you're looking for
previous day point of control. Just
remember, you're coming into lunch. But
if you can get through this, oh, sorry,
folks. And if you can get inside
previous day low, all right, if you can
get acceptance back inside, if you can
find acceptance back inside. Oh my god.
One more time. We'll try it. We can find
acceptance back inside of here. This is
the move and then we will leave all
shorts caught. All right. So, you look
good right now, Max. You look really
good. Just make sure you've lot Oh, you
already have lots them in. You did say
you had lots in. So, this looks good.
Previous week low is 375. So, I'd be
watching that. We have some sellside
imbalance here. We're starting to tap
into. And you just want to see if we can
expand up into higher day. Now, ES is at
VWOP. Watch ES carefully.
Yes, we're going to do giveaways. Hey,
James from Dublin. Love the channel to
go for my second 50K tomorrow. Top man.
Hey, nice James. All right, guys. I'm I
tell you what, we'll set the Apex
giveaway and I'm going to grab a drink
and then when I get back, we'll announce
the winner. Um, don't type anything yet
because I haven't done it yet. Don't
type anything yet. Uh D. Nightbot,
don't [laughter] don't type it yet. And
you're all typing it. Don't type it yet.
Don't type it yet. Okay. Uh
giveaways.
[laughter]
Yeah. Did we get the likes up? I didn't
check that actually.
We needed 250 likes. We did it. Well
done, folks. Okay. [snorts]
All right. So, code FCT, it's your best
code for Apex and most prop firms will
get you the best deal always. Just type
that once in chat. We give away an Apex
account. You are now looking for those
of you who are long, you are looking to
support and expand this out. You need
this area to hold for you. For those of
you who took the long rotation like Max
and your targets are up here, right, I'm
going to use the bathroom and get a
drink while this does what it needs to
do. And then when I come back, we'll do
the giveaway.
>> Well, we will announce it.
Okay.
Pick this winner.
Henrik,
are you here? Henrik.
Mhm.
Just shoot me an email. I'm going to
make a note of you now. Shoot me an
email. Uh, info@flowzonerader.com.
Henrik. Copy your name so I know it's
you. Just send me a screenshot
of you logged into your
uh, YouTube account so I know it's you
and I will sort you out with a free Apex
account, my friend. And you will have
until 35 97. You will have until uh
February to use it. February to use it.
All right, folks. Um let's go over your
plays for this afternoon. Um for those
of you looking for this, I'm just going
to zoom out here. Let's go to a 15minute
chart
and take this off for a second.
Okay, you can see the buildout of
liquidity today. Right. This is very
different
from this yesterday
and from this Friday. Okay, remember
we've had two big move downs and even
overnight a big move down. The target
for the week was this here. All right, I
know the numbers are different to what I
give you in the newsletter, but it's cuz
it's a new contract. But this
is the 930 level, right? That was the
target for the week. This is the weekly
point of control, the untested naked
point of control. We've done that move.
Now, this is why I think we probably
need to build out liquidity because if I
was a higher time frame bull, there is a
good chance I would start buying from
around here. You can see we built
liquidity, we broke down, we bid back
over, we've been holding it. This is why
I was saying I don't think today is a
trend day, right? Woke up, woke up, woke
up, early market, and all we've done
since is test each side of this. This
will be a buildout of liquidity. It
might be that we develop a trend day
tomorrow or later in the week where we
do this. Very well could happen. It
might also be that they say, "Hey,
enough. We need to repric a bit. Let's
look left. We want to come back and
visit here." That can also happen. And
it's what happens in here that creates
the liquidity to do that. This is your
edgetoedge day. You had trend day one,
trend day two. You had last night as
well. Sorry, Friday, Monday, last night.
Don't expect it every single time.
Right? Understand we lack liquidity.
Now, what you what you have to ask
yourself is why are we moving lower? Why
if we're here, are we moving lower this
morning? If there's if there's no way
there's no one to abuse, we've got like
really light volume here to move lower.
So, we need to build volume out into
this. Even if we're going to move lower
or higher, we still need to build volume
out. So, that's what I'd be looking at.
If we zoom in, it's just the same levels
of rotation. Okay. Your edges
are here,
here, and your bullish. I mean, it's
looking worse and worse. Look at this
fat old profile. This is
screaming rotation. All right, because
we're starting to lack low volume nodes.
They're just building the whole thing
out. This is probably just going to do
this all day. If we break above and
hold, we're going here. If we break
below and hold, this and this. Other
than that, you're trading edge to edge
or like me, you're leaving it alone.
leaving it alone. Um,
no, only one only only one winner. Only
one winner. Um,
if you uh
are interested in learning how I trade,
right, if you're new here, because
there's lots of new people here, right?
First of all, go on my YouTube, do all
the free stuff, right? There's tons of
stuff on my YouTube. Go start on
YouTube. Start on my YouTube channel.
There's tons of free stuff. There's even
a free course on here that you can do.
If you're interested in more, there's a
20our course here. It's onetime fee,
$649, and you get uh a version of the
flow zones, and you get Discord included
in it, one time free. If you want to
learn volume and order flow trading,
this just uh launched this week or
yesterday actually. All right, with the
uh code launch at checkout, if you go
buy now, hit launch, it will do it for
you for $299. That offer will end in
January. Okay, so zero pressure to do
it. Like I said, start on YouTube, do as
much as you can for free. If you like
how I trade or how I teach, then think
about everything else. Um, I am probably
just going to set price alerts and let
this do whatever it is it wants to do
today and build out. Don't get chopped
up, guys. All right, we are into
a stage of the market where we need to
build out liquidity. We are into OPEX.
We're into rollover. We are into end of
year. A lot of traders have probably
already checked out. Honestly, I think
you'll find lots of traders like, I'm
out of this now. And just whatever
happens happens. So, don't be uh don't
be ruining your year or your month or
your week or your quarter or your day by
fighting and fighting and fighting and
fighting. All right? Just if there's
something in front of you that is your
setup that you like, by all means, take
it. Otherwise, just be chill. Just be
chill. We wait for the next day.
No, but Matt is not required to trade my
system.
All right, folks. Um, peace and love.
Those in Discord, I'll pop in there
shortly. And um, everyone else, thanks
for joining. I'll see you tomorrow
morning. 9:15 Eastern. We go again. Same
thing. Hopefully we move out of range
tomorrow. All right. Trade safe. Use
hard stops.