Hey team, welcome back. Welcome back.
Welcome back. Uh if I'm distracted this
morning, I am sorry. Uh,
Ninja Trader have kindly um shut down my
access uh to all my Ninja Trader and all
my Trader 8. Um, so I can't get into my
account, can't get to my prop because
they say I'm missing a W8 form and it's
not linked to the account when I've
emailed them about that being an error.
Um, but there we go. So, no trading for
me today until they fix this this uh
problem. So, hopefully I don't miss out
on an absolutely amazing setup today.
But let's get you guys prepared no
matter what. All right, what are we
looking at here?
We can see that for a few weeks we had a
range. All right, this was our range
and we left that range. Inside this
range, we have a very high volume area
right here standing out.
All right, very simply, we need to
maintain control of that volume area.
Um, I would still be looking at the old
contract now for now probably until
tomorrow for those of you aware. So
anything I'm going to quote you will be
old contract uh levels not the new
contract levels. So very very simply all
right you would be looking at Thursday's
low here to act as uh resistance or
supply and this low volume node here.
I'd be very careful once we start
reclaiming sort of 480s 500s. All right.
But if this reacts, all right, then we
expect some selling here and a move back
down into this kind of level here. So I
think from 500, right, top side 500 into
300, maybe even 200 is a possible
rotation today. It would not surprise me
to see sort of an inside bar be built
because this was a big move, but I would
expect the rotation to happen. Uh
absolute max, you don't want it
reclaiming 560s and definitely not 600s.
All right. So, anything here, you're
looking for that move down into here. I
would say that's the protrend move right
now. Any reclaim of this, well, then all
bearish thesis is off the table because
it means they've lost the impetus. We
are at the mean, right? 20-day, 50-day,
5day above after a couple days. 5day
will come here. Eventually, we'll get
very, very tight. So, I'd be watching
for this drift up into here to be sold
into for a retest of that. That's your
target. You just you're going to be
taking money off the table. sort of 300,
280, 200. And you know, if it breaks
down, great. You're positioned for it.
But I'm not, my expectations is not a
big breakdown today. It's not like we
have major major news coming today. So,
I'm probably thinking about an inside
bar.
Uh, let's have a look on the hourly. We
can look at some key levels that this
might come into. Let me just pull this
down for you. Make this a little bit
bigger. There we go. All right. So you
can see previous week value area low and
the week before value area low around
these sort of 450s. It it must not
reclaim that. All right. It really must
not reclaim 450s. Uh I would see this as
a pullback leg after leaving the range.
Here's the balance. We left the range.
This is a pullback or break and retest
we can call it. All right. Uh we're
already reclaiming previous day value
area very high which is not a good look.
But let's just see. I would be watching
these weekly levels up into here. All
right. If we lose this and then and we
look above if we look above previous day
value area high and we stay heavy
against previous week value area low.
All right. If we do something like this,
that's your short for the rotation back
down. Very simple. If they reclaim this
and especially if they back test
previous day value, all right, and he
holds inside this, then they will look
for that rotation up here. Um, you have
previous week point of control.
Has that been adjusted?
That don't look right.
Okay, that light up. All right. Yeah,
previous week point control up there,
which you might want to aim for.
Technically speaking, this is naked
because it's Monday and we've not
retested it. We we traded under lots of
times last week. technically technically
speaking it's naked. Um so that's what
I'll be looking for today. Um all the
time we're against we're staying heavy
against this possible short. If we lose
previous day value area high possible
re-entry and your cover points are 240s
and 150s and if it breaks down under
there great you're positioned for it but
I wouldn't be having expectations that
it does. on the other side of it.
Conversely, if we start basing above
previous days value area high and we
reclaim previous day value area low and
it's not a look above a fail, right? As
long as it doesn't do this and it does
this, then there's a trade back inside
and we will be week three in here, which
is not what we want, but have to be
aware of what what is possible.
Okay, moving into lower time frames
and we can have a look at some of the
other indexes.
All right, ES here
doing the same kind of move. It's uh
never really let go of balance.
That's uh a little bit different looking
over there on ES. So even if we just
have a look
That's not great.
That's quite big divergence. That's not
great. And you can see it held those
800s. So testing I've just measured out
just since we've been up here in
balance. Testing the top side of value
here. So 470s. I'd say 490 is a max.
Claim reclaim that. And uh well that can
still start squeezing. You've got
divergence there. It's very possible
that that starts squeezing, but I
they've made that tricky. I'm going to
be honest. Um, they need to hold versus
900. All right. And that rotation back
down. And ES needs to do this breakdown
for
uh everything to line up. If we start
reclaiming that, then this move here is
on. And remember, we've seen a rotation
out of big tech recently, which is why
you're seeing this, which is why RTY put
in a new alltime high last week. So, it
is possible backside here if it can't
get back above and come back down into
some level of sensibility. Um, let's
have a look at the Dixie. It's trying to
find a bit of a bid there, but it's
bearish, but it is trying to find a bit
of a bid. Gold
pulling back. Failed to reclaim that
level so far, but still looks pretty
bullish.
Vicks, all right, dancing in range. You
can see no acceptance outside of this
range. There's no acceptance on the top
side. We're dancing in range. That sort
of leans into the thesis that probable
inside day right now. Uh Bitcoin.
And this is what I was talking about. If
it can't reclaim this box here, it
probably revisits some of this. And if
it loses that downside pressure, if it
holds this, it will have another attempt
at it. Let's have a look at the mag
here.
Slight gap up on Apple, but no change.
It's just boxed in.
No acceptance above, no acceptance
below. So, let's set some price alerts
here
each side of the range.
All right, Amazon
slight gap up there, but it is trading
near these lows from previous week. All
right, so previous week lows needs to
hold above here. Failed to break, failed
to break, wash down. All right, you want
to be careful of this look now on
Amazon.
All right. So, it needs to reclaim 228
228 229. Failure to do that. Um, I'd say
some weakness there. Google, similar
kind of story, but it's a little bit
ahead of Amazon. There's your neckline.
All right, there's the fail break, wash
down, failed to reclaim, break down, and
it's back testing this kind of level. If
it stays heavy, we go back down into the
300s right now. If it can hold a
reclaim, you know, maybe it can try and
build here. I wouldn't be surprised to
see rotation between here for a few days
now.
Uh meta
flat. Nothing happening there. There's
your big break. Two leg failing to
reclaim. Same same kind of story. Basing
at the bottom until we see a break
either side or a failed break either
side. Same story on Microsoft. Looks
exactly the same. Big weakness. All
right. Spent Thursday trying to get back
up. All it was was a reprice for them to
sell back into Friday resells and we're
opening up inside a Friday. Uh Nvidia
exactly the same as we just went over.
All right, failed to reclaim big slam
down and I'd say 179 180 is the level in
Nvidia. If they stay heavy versus that,
it's probably going to break down. Uh
massive strength in Tesla. We talked
about this last week. All right,
relative strength in Tesla. It is
breaking out. All right, is breaking
out. It's very, very close now, right?
Some supply up here, but you can see
this little trap underneath this swing
point rebalancing some of this. This
wants new alltime highs. It wants 500.
They're trying to push for 500. It is as
simple as that. It's very, very strong.
Um, I would expect it's OPEX this week,
so I'd expect there's some stuff up here
at like pro the probable levels 75, 80,
90, 500 I would expect on Tesla. So,
relative strength there. Oracle, let's
just have a look at these ones that had
earnings last week. Opening up slightly
inside and slightly down and EV AVGO,
same kind of story. Still sort of has
not found it base yet. It's trying, but
you know, you can't rule out another leg
down yet, right? Maybe some relief and
then base and then leg down. We just
have to see into end of year.
And just going to check the bonds move
30 year
10 years breaking out. 30 year trying to
break out. Yeah. I mean you know my
thoughts on these. I've been saying it
for a long time. Right.
That would be a problem. I'd say over
twos over over 42. So that's what a lot
of people will be will be watching right
now.
All right folks, that should have you
prepared. Um just go easy. This week it
is OPEX week. Um we have roll over. It's
uh contracts in futures likely to roll
over tomorrow I would say as in the
volume will move over tomorrow.
That pullback holding previous day value
area high is very strong right now but
maybe coming for a retest up here. So we
will see. We will see. We will see. Good
morning everyone. I'll try and get
through some good mornings here if I
can. Uh can't read everyone's names
unfortunately. Get my glasses on. Good
morning JMM.
Uh Evan Sylum John Jade inferrisk fall
forward. Uh Miguel Francesca Toby
Richard. Pull this up.
Larry, Marrick, Troy, Green, Mark, Noah,
Amalabi, Brandon, Dave,
uh, Azvid, uh, Rosco, the other Dave. I
love that you've changed that. Sergio,
DL Smith, uh, Bart,
Steven,
Gray, Kitty, Loet, Christhorne, Random
Guy, Firewater,
U, Prrisca. Gosh, I'm losing a lot of
you here.
The dude, Jeff Stewart, Thumper, Enq,
Hates Noah,
all these names changing, Hercules, uh,
Dojon,
Rich Crawford, Chad, Moi, Abby. Good
morning, everyone.
All right, 30 seconds left. Let me just
share this on uh
on Twitter. Hopefully, I get a reply
from Ninja Trader. I'd love to be able
to trade today. I can't even log into
Trader 8 at the moment, unfortunately.
He's just sending me on a loop. So, that
needs fixing ASAP. Uh, smash that like
button. I would like to do a giveaway
today. We give away an Apex account.
There's your morning chef.
Okay, so watching these levels here,
here and here. If you start losing
value, we go inside previous days value,
the rotation is point of control and
previous day value area low. If you hold
value, they shove it up. You'd want them
to sell against that. You do not, if
you're a bear, you do not want to see a
reclaim um or previous week value area
low up here. uh a reclaim of that will
be a major major problem. Means we're
just going to go back into the exact
same level that we spent the prior two
weeks in.
Oh, I'd love to be able to trade. Are
you going to let me trade today?
seems not. Oh, that's frustrating. Let
me move this down so I can read price
action for you.
Sorry, guys. It's very frustrating. What
you going to do?
All
right. So, you're underneath New York
open. You had some big sellers come in
at 70. They got caught. All right. So
far, you're in a balance. uh pre-market
you had some buying of over 400. They
got caught and you're just trapped
between the two right now
and you're watching this level. If you
start to lose value, all right, if you
look above and fail, the the things I'd
be looking for today are a trade back
under. If it loses value,
if it loses value, at least this to view
up and previous day point control and
close the gap and you can have cover
points there and then covering the rest
here. If we base above value, I mean, I
don't love the long, I'll be honest. But
if we do this up here, maybe they come
into this and then I'd be looking for a
look above and fail, trade back down to
value and lose a value again. Uh, if
you're going to long this, you've got to
remember the cheap long was down here
overnight. Uh, we're now above previous
day value, underneath previous week.
This is not a great long area. I'm going
to be honest with you. Actually, got
overhead supply. Maybe you've got two
weeks worth of supply up up above this
or in that and above.
Oh man, this is
very frustrating
way to start the week all over a W8 form
which is I don't even need to do. It's
on an old account but it's obviously
linked and it's caused a problem. Now I
can't get into any of my accounts. What
a pain.
Okay.
All right. I'm going to get water here
real quick. Forgotten that. Oh, I've got
bottle here. All
right, there's your loss of uh previous
day value error low. So if you stay
heavy there, you will see the rotation.
And I'd be watching spy an ES interview
up etc etc.
Tesla's on a ripper straight up through
the 75s into 80s. I'll give you a
readout on the mag. Tesla up 4%. That
thing's in a hurry like we talked about.
Nvidia up 1.34%.
Apple up just about 0.20%.
And rest of the market down.
Tesla failing into those 78s not quite
making it there.
you are getting hammered. It's like I
said, once you lose value, you'll come
into a rotation. All right, so the next
level I'd be targeting if I was you was
these 300. So as you start to drift
down, you can pull some money off the
table. If it stays heavy now, right, if
it stays heavy versus there, this and
this are possible. And then this is the
edge of the range. You would be covering
on the way down, right? So if you're
already short, great. Otherwise, you're
looking for a turn back into get short,
cover one, cover two, a little bit into
this whole zone, cover three, and
anything beyond that is uh well, you're
looking very good at that point, aren't
you?
Where should I enter? I don't think I
could have make this made this clearer
today. Underneath value, I don't
understand what you guys listen to. When
you lose this, we go rotation. I've said
it about I must have genuinely said it
about five times this morning. I'm not
even taking a piss. Like,
what is a WA? It's a tax form if you're
from the UK um and uh working in
America, but I don't need to do it
because they have a green card. So,
that's why I didn't fill it in for them.
But, it's just their system
because they know I'm from the UK
originally. So, it's just stupid error
on their system. But, there we go.
Okay. ES trying to find a bid off VWAP.
SPY's lost his VWAP. So I'd be watching
SPY for a back test which will be around
the 8470s. So as long as 85, same level
as last week, folks on the spiders. If
85 stays heavy, we rotate to 82. If you
lose that, we rotate to 80. QQQ just
coming back up to its VWAP as well. The
New York VW up. So I would be looking
now, there's two trades here. You would
be looking for them to sell this level
here for that rotation back down.
That's what they need to do, right? If
they reclaim that level, I would not be
sure. If they reclaim this level, they
will look to move back up to here. But
all the time we're under that, I'd be
looking short side or this move down
into here. TP1, TP2,
TP3 if you get lucky. Any reclaim of
that, no shorts. If they reclaim that,
no shorts. The one thing you would have
to watch because it's been a pain the
last few days is Tesla, right? has been
very aggressive this morning again. It
was just like uh Friday. It did the same
thing. I think it was Friday. Yeah,
Tesla just going the other way to the
market. So, give you an idea. Tesla's up
4.11% right now trying to push back
through 480. It's currently trading 477.
Rest of the market is either flat or
down other than video is like one and a
half% up.
Okay.
So, here's the retest of value and view.
And if they sell this, you can look for
a lower low.
I would say you don't want them to
reclaim 70s,
right? In 70s, we had some sellers get
stuck there at 9:30 this morning. We've
broken down under them. They're
comfortably in the money. So, there you
go. There's the sell point into this
level. And you just want this to break
down now.
So you want to see some follow through.
And ideally Tesla stops pumping because
that's going to make your life very
hard. If you're looking for this move
and Tesla keeps pumping, it's going to
make your life hard. Give you an idea of
what I'm talking about right now. This
thing is uh in a hurry again.
Straight up. All right. On Tesla, it's
going for that breakout we talked about
pre-market. So already taking this
liquidity now at 80. What's the next
level to go for? 88s. All right. So,
just be aware of that on Tesla. It's uh
if that's flying, it's obviously trying
to drag the cues up with it. That's the
only thing I'd be very very aware of.
Rest the market does not look like that.
It's a one stock doing the damage. You
are still rejecting previous day value
area high. So, I'd still be my bias
would remain short side right now all
the time. You're protecting this kind of
area.
I'm not trading today, folks. I want to
make that clear. I'd love to be trading.
I cannot get into any of my accounts.
I've been booted out my accounts right
now. So, all I can do is call price
action for you right now, unfortunately.
Okay, really nice sell versus previous
day value area high there. So, you're
looking for a lower low. Just watch this
24-hour VW up, this green line. And if
you snap that, all right, your next
cover points are 35s down into 213. And
so you've got another 100 points down
here if you start losing. So you could
take a little partial into this if you
want. And really I'd be targeting this
down here. But if you want to take a
partial into that because it's early on
a Monday, I wouldn't blame you. But
here's the lower low. Don't say I didn't
give this to you nice and early. I don't
want to hear anyone in chat saying when
does he enter? Blah blah blah. All that
nonsense. Literally laid that out for
you. There's a nice winner for you to
start the day. That's a 50 plus point
winner already. You're welcome.
So, you should be smacking this right
now. And I want W's in chat. Here's your
VWAP. So, I would pay myself a little
bit here probably. And I would look to
see if they start to sell through this.
And you should see that move down to
previous day point of control. Um,
Globex and PDC if they sell VWAP. So,
this is a key level here. The big
question is, do you see this snap down
into this? All right. So, make pay
yourself a little bit here. This is the
main target. If I got down into here,
I'd be taking a huge amount of my
position off.
All right, and there is your trade for
your Monday morning. All right, so you
should be up 50 plus points and you
might get 100 plus points here. And that
is all you need. This is why I'm a
little bit upset that it's not letting
me trade here. It was a nice setup this
morning.
There you go. Yeah.
Lots of you making money. Nice W's in
chat. 1,100 across 10 accounts. Nice
work, folks.
There you go, Johnny. Nice work. Nice
work. Nice and easy, isn't it? It's nice
when the market behaves properly. It's
good.
Um, what I would say is you got some
sellers caught there under 290. So,
they're trying to aggressively bid this
back up at the moment. Um,
out the way so I can see the delta.
So, they're trying to flip to positive
delta. Uh, last sellers came in at 45.
So, I'd say now really, you want to stay
heavy versus 45 if they're going to see
that continuation.
Tesla did peak above 480. So, I've got
my one eye on Tesla. It's still good to
move lower here. I'd be looking for
lower highs and lower lows for that
potential gap fill unless it starts to
reclaim everything. But, you should have
paid yourself some money.
You need this to start getting
aggressive beneath 300 really.
Nice rejection of VW up there on ES.
Looks good. Looks good. It's just Tesla
making this harder. Honestly, if Tesla
stops pumping,
it's currently up $13 or $14 since the
open.
Honestly, I don't know how people trade
that. I must be so wild this week,
especially into OPEX because I know
everyone loves zero DTE on Tessa. My
Tesla breaking out new high day. This is
why Q's is not rolling over right now.
If Tesla loses a bid,
this thing will start puking. There you
go. Big rejection there into 81. Already
pulled back $3 in the last 10 seconds on
Tesla. Wild, wild move. Apple's breaking
the low. So, I just got an alert on
that. So, that's going to drag this mark
market down. Right. So, remember I set
an alert earlier on Apple. If if we
start losing this low on Apple. There
you go. It's starting to break this low
that we looked at pre-market, which is
why I set an alert right here. Right.
So, maybe Apple comes and trades into
here now. So, it needs to find a bid
here. If it doesn't, it trades to this
low side. Market will get heavy with it.
So, your shorts look good all the time
that this is happening. You just want
Tesla to do the same thing now and
you'll have a really nice trade. You
just need Tesla to start playing ball
and Nvidia as well by the way which is
uh now starting to look okay. You look
good. Continuation short here looks good
in my mind.
You just need a new lower low. Right. So
Apple now 1% down. Amazon half% down.
Google quarter% down. Microsoft 0.20%
down. Um Nvidia 0.77%
up. Meta 0.64% up. Tesla 4% up starting
to have a pullback here. This 5minute
candle is important. It's got another
one and a half plus minutes left in it
on Tesla. But
let's see if they roll Tesla. I think
you're kind of going to come into this.
All depends what these zero DTE are
probably doing on Tesla. I'd say
come on Ninja Trader. I'd love to trade
today. Please, can you reply?
[\h__\h] me.
What a way to start the week.
Looks good. Tesla starting to lose a bid
here. You look good. It's going to trade
back into 75 and see if they hold it.
And if they don't, if this is a carbon
copy of Friday where they pumped it and
lost the bid, then the market can roll.
Here you go, folks. So, you're looking
for a lower low here,
right? So, all you guys in shorts from
up here,
right? I said shorts from up here, you
want to see this move and this move into
here would be fantastic. If you get
this, you should be covering 80 plus% of
your position into this move here. If
you get a wash down into it,
what I would say twice now, they've
tried to aggressively sell 290 is you
need a break down here so that these
shorts are comfortable because they're
flying in and not getting their way.
There is some absorption taking place at
290s right now.
You want a breakdown. You need a
breakdown. Tests are going to test these
75s like I talked about.
SPY rejecting VWAP hard there. Hard
rejection of VWAP on Spy
and it will probably trade back into the
82s here on Spy. Maybe gap fill and you
might get a bleed. They just got to stop
absorbing this. If they stop absorbing
this, you're going to get a nasty, nasty
snap down. This is the third time now
shorts have tried to sell underneath 90
and they're being absorbed.
But you should be comfortable because
you should be short from up here, right?
So 70 points higher right now.
Feels like they're going to snap it now.
They're having another go at these low.
There you go. So, new low day. Can they
start to really sell this now? Big
sellers coming in. Huge selling coming
in. There's some absorption on the tape
here. If this buyer gets out the way, it
[\h__\h] pukes.
There's another 100 or 80 points in
this. If this buyer gets out the way,
he's trying really hard to absorb this
tape. Big seller coming in here.
Aggressive selling.
You look fantastic team. You look really
good. There you go. Beautiful starting
breakdown. Now, you do not want this to
reclaim these sort of 80s and 300s. Now,
they've just put a lot of work into
getting that snap in this candle, and
you should be targeting this.
You guys are all making loads of money
while I'm sat here unable to trade.
Do not want to reclaim. They just worked
really hard to get that breakdown.
Really hard they worked there to try and
get this breakdown.
So, try and sit in this. You do I would
say definitely don't want want it to
reclaim 92 93 must not reclaim that.
Nice follow through on spy.
Tesla's trying to find a bid. So spy
really really weak here.
Can this market rotate with it? So I'm
going to give you a readout now. test.
Uh, Apple 1.37% down, Amazon over half a
percent down, Google quarter of a
percent down, Microsoft quarter of a
percent down, Meta 0.41% up, Nvidia
1.11% up, Tesla 4% up. So, that's the
problem right now. You've got a bit of a
mixed bag here.
Spy is trying to find a bid here. I'd be
taking a little bit off the table. You
can always add back on if you haven't
paid yourself yet. You should have
already paid yourself, though. As long
as you don't trade back above, what did
I say? 92s. Yeah, I think 92s 90s to
300s is key. As long as it stays heavy
versus that, you've got gap fill
potential. They reclaim that, I would be
out.
Remember, we expected an inside bar
today. That's what we're getting.
It's meeting our expectations. If we're
very very efficient, we're going to come
down into this bright yellow line. All
right. If we want to do a full rotation,
we're going to come down into there. It
doesn't have to. Right. So, we're
probably at the midpoint. Previous day
point of control is uh we're coming into
the top side of that area. Now, to be
honest, if we go to like an hourly,
we think about where we got congested.
You got your 20-day here. All right. So
that's your return to mean your previous
day point of control and you've got it
like this. All right. So I'd say this
whole area is pretty thick. I would
expect the market to probably try and
get a bid from there unless they get
very very weak and they're like no we're
selling this big today. I'd expect the
market to try and find some sort of
balance in here. Remember I said rewind
to the beginning this is technically
naked because we're opening up on a
Monday. So, it might want to revisit the
naked PC and then go for a rotation back
up to 330, which might be taking most of
my position up as we trade into these
levels.
Lots of buying coming in here. They're
trying to flip delta.
Tesla's try trying again to get back
above its 480. See if they sell it
versus 480. Like I said, you're still
good. Sort of 92s to 300s as long as
they're selling versus that for your
runners. But if they reclaim that, I
would be out of it. You can always add
back in.
Uh TJ, uh Dece um December contract
probably until tomorrow. Not enough
volume has flipped over yet. Probably
until tomorrow. I'd say normally between
Tuesday and Wednesday it will flip to
the new contract. the volume will be
bigger on the new contract. Yeah, it's
harder to read the tape for me this
week. Um because I'm currently watching
a December contract, so I'm going to see
like the levels will look thinner and
obviously if they're playing the March
contract, I can't see them. I can't look
at two things at once. All right, I'd
probably cut this now, folks. You can
always get back in.
And it's Tesla doing the damage, trying
to break out for a new high.
Did they really just poke above
Yeah, I'd leave this alone for a minute
while they made their minds up here.
Tesla's going to be a pain for you. But
hopefully most of you made lots of money
on that.
Most of you made lots of money. So, it
is possible. They do a little look above
here. They just trapped some bulls there
on that last play. That was gross that
they poked through. What did I say? 92s
to 300. 92s
to 300. This kind of level here is where
I would have cut the trade.
If they get back up below this, this is
still possible. Like I said, you can
always get back in. That's how I think
about these things. Can always get back
in.
I don't think this auction at the bottom
is finished. There the the low of day
has buying on it, not selling. I don't
think we've finished selling. It just
needs Tesla to stop. There you go. That
little naughty poke above there.
Shouldn't have gone above 300 there.
They let it above. It should not have
done that. Got back above the old PC.
P at 1041.
340 943 was 300. Yeah, I didn't want
them to revisit above that, but they
did.
Sells still look good here now as long
as they're rejecting these levels. So
now I would say you need it to stay
heavy versus 290. If they sell versus
290, there might be a continuation
trade. If they reclaim that again, I
wouldn't touch it. But flow zone still
in a cell. You're underneath the VWOPS.
We've got gap fills to go and do. New
low of day on SPY. Everything looks
good. It's just
Mr. Elon holding the market up, basing
out at highs right now. And those are
very close to alltime highs.
There you go. Comes the sells. They're
trying to they're trying to aggressively
slam this down to 200 now. Here you go.
So re-entry.
There's the lower day. That's lots of
selling at lower day. They want to close
this gap now. Finally. Naughty people
putting above 300. Naughty, naughty,
naughty. Here goes ES. Really good. Very
clean on ES.
Spy coming down into those 82s that we
talked about.
You should get GloEx and gap fill here.
Feels like a magnet. VIX is trying to
break out of that 1650 level as well.
Tesla turning back inside still. Five
minute is bullish. Tesla Tesla needs to
stay below 76s. If Tesla gets below 75
76es or VWAP and starts to sell, we
really pick. Here we go. Really nice.
Now, all right. Covers into here,
please. If you took that re-entry, must
be paying yourself into here. All right.
This is your target for the day. If you
get lucky, you do a full rotation. You
must pay yourself into this level here.
Please. This is fair value from last
week. All right. So, anywhere from where
we are now down to 212s, I would take
80% of your position off.
Right. Most of my position would be
covered here. I'd be runners down in
case we got into there, but I don't
necessarily expect it.
And that's it. That's your uh trades
done for the day. If you traded with me
this morning, you've traded for 23
minutes and entry one was versus this.
So 65 and we've covered some into view
up. So that was 65 points. We got
knocked out. You would have got back in.
You should be covering some in here
again and in here. And that's, you know,
I've probably netted you over well over
100 points, 150 points with thesis,
telling you what to do beforehand and
why. And that is what separates
me from guys where you're like, "When
does he enter? When does he do this? Did
I see you all this morning saying it?" I
told you when and why. I told you the
exact reason why. And that's the
difference. You've got to learn to stand
on your own two feet. People, I will
teach you to fish. You want to turn up,
I'll teach you to fish. You want to
learn how I do it. You really want to
learn and you can't decipher it from
what I'm telling you here. Do the
course. Join the mentorship. Join join
the crew. Um,
I can't give it I can't explain it
better than this. I'm doing the best I
can. And remember, I'm getting nothing
out of this because I can't even trade
today. So frustrating.
So frustrating.
They still haven't emailed me back.
Uh, Alvaro, at the end of the course, if
you scroll down towards the end of the
course, you'll see like there's a tab
that says Discord. It tells you what to
do.
Thanks, Green.
Yeah, exactly.
>> Give me your money.
Still got gap fill potential here. Still
got gap fill. That bright yellow line.
All right. So the orange line is
glowbacks. The yellow line is gap fill.
Looks like we're coming for gap fill.
And if we fail gap fill, right? Then I
think we're going to go here. Right. So
this is your cover point. And this is
runners. Previous day low value area low
is runners.
If we get expansion under there, I would
find that unlikely today. I'm going to
be honest. But we're not going to rule
it out. So if we do something like this,
we can look for an expansion model down
into this old naked point of control
that we talked about on Friday and
Thursday last week. All right. So, but
really I would imagine I would imagine
because we lack news today, we probably
do an inside day. So I'd imagine this is
a rotational day and at the moment it's
telling me we want to rotate because we
lost value area high and we are coming
to gap fill and point of control. We
might do a back test to this. We might
do something like this. Right. I'd
imagine we stay kind of within these
confines today. I can't imagine really
that we move outside of that unless they
go into panic and they, you know, they
start getting out of their moves before
the end of the week because they're
worried about that carry trade, which is
what I talked about in the newsletter. I
think that's the big red alarm this
week. Okay, gap fill almost there,
folks. So, technically your gap fills
into 14 somewhere around there.
No, you're good. It's no dis It's no
disrespect, mate. It's not
disrespectful. And it's not just you. I
get hammered with that every day. My
channel is is full of it. It wasn't an
attack on you or anyone else.
It's just the big thing, the difference
between here and watching
some of my peers who might just be like,
you know, like Danny trades. Okay guys,
I'm long. I'm long. Oh my god, I made 10
grand. Oh my god. Based on nothing. I
will tell you what I would be looking at
and why.
Okay, so gap fill coming coming up here.
[\h__\h] me. Why Why Ninja Trader did you do
this to me? We're in such an easy setup.
Killing me. Killing me. All right, you
can see them. There's 182 lot. He's just
jumped up to front run this. So, he's
trying to absorb here. So they're trying
to just they're trying to cover their
positions into this gap fill. Someone
was worried he wouldn't get filled. So
he just jumped up from 12 to 20s to get
filled, which he's now filled. 180 lot,
180 lot, 180 lot. He's trying to get
filled. 181 lot. There you go. He's
filled. All right. So that's an
efficient market. We've now filled the
gap here. And the next level really is
this value rotation. So your runners
now, I would be out like 80% of my
position, I'll be honest. And I'd be
holding 20% for here. And I'd be
covering some as we get down into this.
And this will be the best move of the
day, folks. You have absolutely nailed
this. It's a beautiful move. I mean, if
you didn't get knocked I would have got
knocked out. I'm telling you, I would
have got knocked out and had to
re-enter. But if you didn't, there's 150
points. And if we get full TP, 210 and
250 points all for free just from
watching some old fart on YouTube.
Yeah, ex exactly Indie.
Um the differences uh this time in my
mind is we are so
if if you go from January and you look
at what the market's done since then,
we're so overleveraged. Um and if you
look at growth names and tech stocks, I
think I talked about it in the
newsletter. Um my opinion is Asia in are
in big leverage products. There's a
reason crypto started freaking out,
right? Other than the fact we've gone
through the cycle, right? We're in
liquidation mode. There's a reason
everyone's really worried about AI that
the valuations are massive. Um it's very
speculative. It's it's probably going to
work out the speculation, but when we
get things like um Japan increase the
rates, they're going to have to derisk
their risk on US assets and then you get
a liquidity crunch because you get a
race. You get a race to sell. So if we
if we've seen weakness since Friday,
which we have, we've seen like the
Oracle and um AVGO scares. Okay? So
everyone started like, okay, I'm going
to start taking profit. We've had a
massive year. We need to start locking
profit because if we don't lock in
profit now and that Japan trade comes in
when it's 1:00 a.m. in the morning and
everyone's asleep and we wake up to a
market and gap down, uh, it's going to
be a rush then for everyone in profit to
be like sell sell. You're just going to
see waterfall, waterfall, waterfall and
then you get liquidity problems and not
just liquidity problems on the day like
multiple days.
Okay, Spy is trying to just complete it
gap fill here as well. It's very very
close. 80 82 or just under 82 will be
gap for 8176. So it's hitting those 82s
now. Remember this is gamma level on
spy.
And if we stay heavy, we probably trade
the 80s on spy. So really nice. So now
you should be out 80% of your position
now. The only thing we're looking at now
is previous day value area low and
previous day low. So previous day value
low, previous day low. I would say 20%
of your position left for this move into
here. I would be covering almost all of
my position here. just holding a tiny
runner in case just in case it wants to
come back down into this naked point of
control today. I would find that
unlikely, but if it does it today when
I've been able to unable to trade, I can
guarantee you I will grab one of my
monitors and bend it off my knee and
have the biggest fit ever. I will be
very pissed off if it chooses to do this
trade. The one day where I'm not being
allowed to trade.
As long as we stay in balance, then I we
can save that trade for another day.
All right, some excess down here. Like I
said, I' I'd be out majority of my
position. SPY just closed it gap. ES
closed it gap. Tesla's come back into
VWOPS trying to find a bid. You should
be out most of your position now. All
right. Anything more you make today is
an absolute bonus. You've absolutely
murdered this in the first 30 minutes
today. All right. Just be happy. Be
happy with what you've made today. It's
a Monday morning. We're probably going
to have an inside day and you guys have
destroyed it.
What are you guys saying? Oh my god.
Oh my god. I made 10 grand. Yeah.
Honestly, guys, I'm done for the day.
Thanks so much, Alex. Another great one.
Nice work. Nice work, Eric. Thanks for
the call outs.
8:50 on your call outs. Thanks so much
on the clarity of why things happen.
You're welcome, everyone. You're
welcome. Done for the day. Yeah, lots of
you are done. Like, it's the way to
trade.
If you're old, I've got one foot in the
grave and the other on a banana pill.
No, no, no, no, no. Okay, I feel old. I
mean, it's my first year at 40. Let me
say I'm old. Midlife crisis year. Um,
high flow saving up for the course. You
are very good at this. Nice. Well, look
forward look forward to working with
you. Jeff W. Big one on that. Thanks,
Alex. Great call out. Uh, all out 25
220. 25 220. Yeah, nice. Very nice.
Nothing wrong with locking in. Just
passed TS top step. Is that TS 50K eval
on that short? Thanks, man. What you're
doing here is really amazing. You're
welcome, Luke.
I guess today is the day to ask for
money from everyone.
Oh, it's all right. It's just one trade
day.
[\h__\h]
I can't believe it. I know what I know
it's over the W8 form. It's so annoying.
And uh when I go to fill it in, it
doesn't let me because it knows I can't
do it and then it just sends me on a
like a circle loop. What I don't
understand is why I can't like, okay,
Ninja Trader doesn't let me in. This is
my like funded account if you like my
your personal account, but I can't get
in the props either. So, it's all
because they're all linked. You're
seeing more weakness come in here. They
want to sell this through. VIX is like
starting to spike now. It's through
1650s. It's starting to break out. Next
level on VIX I'd be looking at is the
17s. This is getting very, very heavy.
They want to get to value. You're going
to You might well hit your last TPS
here. Anything below this on the day is
a bonus. I would not read short here.
The only way I would read short if I was
you now is if we break below all this
and we do like a multileg here and build
and build and build and then look for
that snap. I really hope they don't do
that today. Alex will be a very upset
man if they do the A+ trade today.
Yeah, I know. I' I've emailed customer
support and I've emailed my contact
there. Obviously, I work with them a
lot. Um,
but it I can't teach and do it. So, in
my mind, the moment I get off stream,
I'll get on phone to them if they
haven't replied. They've they've emailed
me acknowledging that I've emailed them.
So, they've seen it.
Yeah, one good trade. It's all you ever
need. And that's the way you need to see
the market. Like, remember, we came to
the market today and we thought, well,
we we might have a queen queen setup.
All right. If we're playing Texas
holder, we might have a queen queen
setup. We failed the New York open. High
day was New York open. We traded
underneath. We back tested previous day
value area high. This is what I was
talking about this up here. Once we see
this, this is confirmation. All right. M
maybe maybe king king. Maybe we can say
king king. All right. Maybe we move the
new hand is a king king. So it's like
it's unlikely market's going to get an
ace ace and beat us at this point.
Right. So we get king king. We're like
okay well let's see the flop. Okay. the
flop comes in and it's like a two, a
four, and an eight. And we're like,
well, we feel pretty [\h__\h] good about
that. And now we're like, we're not all
in, but we're like, we we'll take that.
Thanks very much. We've made our money.
Everyone on the table gave us their
money. Now, we just wait, right? We wait
to see how many idiots want to give us
more money. But we've made
80 plus% of our money. All right? And
you should have hit your daily goals on
these breakdowns. Look at the
continuation. just bare flat, bare flat,
bare flat, bare flat. The only one that
annoyed me was it this guy here that
picked over 90 to 300.
I know structurally it was fine, but I
was watching basically in here where
everyone was trapped. What you didn't
want them to do was let these guys out.
They kind of let them out and then
resold it. So, you can see the reaction
here now as we trade back into previous
day point of control. I'm going to put
some volume on here for the current day
now. We've been open a while, right?
We're retesting value. This area is key
now for sentiment. All right. This area,
this is value area low on the current
session, previous day point of control.
Right? If they hold this, they might
rotate. If they reclaim this, then the
rotation back upside's possible with VWA
up and previous day value area high. So,
I would say your money's been made. Your
money should have been made here this
morning.
You turned 62 on Friday. Happy birthday.
Happy happy belated, my friend.
One good trade is all you need. Alex,
what is a good way of differentiating a
stop run from an actual move? Uh, for
me, it's it's it's like it's never how
can I put this? It's a question of
liquidity and what we do afterwards. All
right. So it's we can always have levels
on a chart, right? Every level we look
at is pretty much near enough always a
horizontal level. Otherwise, it's a
trend line. What we do afterwards is
important. So we've built all this
liquidity here. All right, if we just
poke up and have no reaction, not not
able to base, all right, then that can
be a stop run and a rotation. However,
if we start getting up and we start to
base, all right, and then we start doing
that, that will be a reversal back into
or into here for example. Same as when
we talked about this morning,
right? If you think about what the stop
run was this morning, it was shorts
leaning on this and buyers breaking this
out, right? And we went, yeah, yeah,
yeah, we're going to go high. No, we're
not. All right, that's the stop run. The
difference there being did we base
above? For me, it's always like are we
breaking a retest or are we all the
market does let me just move up here. If
we where can I draw it? If we just think
about basics,
right? If this is support and this is
resistance, right? If the market does
this, right, it's a fail breakout. If
the market does this, right, then it's
not a stop run. That's a stop run.
That's a continuation, right? Do we hold
the level? And think about this as like
blocks, right? They're not necessarily
tiny little thin lines. Do we hold a
level or do we just poke through it and
instantly reject? And then what happens
in here becomes important on the
footprint. Right? For example, these
last 1 2 3 4 five candles. Buyers,
at least on that last candle, buyers,
there's a lot of buying activity here
and at the very top of this. And we're
rejecting this level. Remember what we
just said? If we reject this level here,
there is potential continuation trade
lower. It's value area low on the day
and its previous point of control. If we
reject this, this can happen. If we get
above this, this can happen. This is why
for me, I would wait. If I wanted to be
long today, I would wait to see a firm
reclaim of this. And ideally, it will
happen after we do that. You want them
to stop run this first. At the moment,
we're short bias.
Heavy selling here. Not getting their
way right now. All right. From 98 to 91,
they just tried to heavily sell this.
But just be aware of this level.
No worries, Ero.
So, if you look at Spy, Spy is trying to
reclaim.
Um, it's it's uh PDC. It's just hanging
around at PDC. Tesla drifted back down
into uh VWAP, went under VWAP, back over
VWAP. It's trying to build a fiveminute
flag. Tesla looks just like Friday.
Honestly, it looks identical to Friday.
Uh VIX rejected, right? We talked about
VIX maybe trying to get back 317. All
right, it drifted up into it. It's uh
got sold into there. So, we need to be
aware of that. It's still trying to
base. Can still do a 5minute flag. It
filled a little imbalance, but I'd say
we're going into like balance for a
couple minutes while we make our
decision. There is still lowhanging
fruit lower previous day value low,
previous day low. As long as we stay
heavy versus this level like we talked
about and we can see a continuation into
this. So, if you're still, some of you
might still be in this looking for
these. If we break down under here,
well, I'll be very very very upset
because it means we will be coming for
that old weekly naked PC underneath us
into uh 24,900s
and I'll be upset because I can't trade
today and this is the trade I've been
waiting for and that will just as we'd
say in the UK that would be sod sod's
law. All right, here's the trade into
value.
trading into value here.
So, this is your TP.
So, here and here. And then runners,
if you do this, I'll be upset, but I
would say I'd be out 90% of my position
into this.
90% of my position would be out now.
Uh, it's anchored volume profile, so
it's not visible. This is anchored
volume profile from 9:30. It doesn't
change when I move, right? It doesn't
It's not a visible range. It's anchored
to the 930. So, for me, just call it the
New York print. New York print.
Why do I get the feeling?
Why do I have this nasty, nasty, nasty
feeling we're going to trade into 24,930
today?
Better not. We better not.
Do I think it would hit previous day
low? Um, I really don't know, mate. I
don't know.
Um, if they protect it, they're going to
protect it where we are. Right? If they
protect it, they're going to protect it
from here. If we look at this,
all right, we went higher low, higher
low. We had excess under here. All
right. If they're going to take that,
then they're going to really want it.
Means they're going to want this move.
In my mind,
I don't know. I don't know what their
ambitions are. All I know is we had a
high probab probability sell from up
here to here this morning. I I can't
tell you if they're going to do that. I
wish I could. I wish I was Nostradamus.
All I know is that it's it is possible.
I wouldn't rule it out, right? I
wouldn't rule it out. But you're
you should be managing a position from
up here or here. I would not be entering
short down here because we are at
discount based on the previous day right
based on previous day. This is premium
from from Friday. This is discount from
Friday. If you enter short here, if you
get this, you're lucky. Uh the short
should be from premium, which is up here
to here. You should be covering into
this. That's all I know. I I don't I
genuinely don't know if we're going to
take it out, mate. And I wish I wish I
did. I wish I could tell you yes, but I
I don't think it needs to. Um
I don't think it needs to based on what
we've done, but
I predicted this move on Friday. Yeah. I
mean, even if you think about what did I
say in the newsletter this week? I don't
know if we even got high enough to back
test the levels.
Um,
where is my newsletter?
See what we said in the newsletter this
week.
Bears bearish playbook is relatively
straightforward. Bears must aggressively
defend 25380 to 25475. Where did we open
up this morning?
There's the defend
of 380. All right. Bears must
aggressively defend 380. Their initial
objective is to break down to 25145
which will open the door to attack
24930. A sustained close below that will
level would firmly shift momentum in
favor of bears setting up a move towards
the high volume node on the year to
24,800 with an extension target to
24300.
And that area also aligns with daily
Ballinger band lows. A decisive break
and acceptance below this zone would
trigger a multi-frame break multi-time
frame breakdown and mark a meaningful
shift in the broader market. I'm not
expecting that, but
what was the target?
Defend 25 380. Get to 25145.
Hello.
It was in the Sunday newsletter, which
is completely free.
Completely free. Landed in your inbox
Saturday morning. We're about to hit 45.
So,
I don't know what to say, folks.
Even if you don't do the course, you
don't turn up here, it's it's staring
you in the eyes. I spend countless hours
doing that for everyone.
So, job one of the newsletter just got
tagged. All right, we've hit 45. We've
come under it.
So, if you're a long trader, if you're
uber bullish in this market, I'm not
uber bullish in this market, but if you
are, what would you want to see? You'd
want to see something like this. All
right. And you'd need to I would not be
long until you regain stuff. All right.
Are we due a push? Yeah, probably. All
right. We've built a lot of liquidity
here. This is a very strong trend. All
right. Maybe it drifts under here and
then reclaims and then comes up into
here and then fails. This feels like
Friday, folks. If we look at Friday,
it's kind of similar. We just had to
wait to come out of the range. All
right. So, once we left the range,
right,
it was just melt time, wasn't it? And
then we get one of these, which probably
gets sold into. So, I would be thinking
about the same sort of scenario here.
I'd be very, very bearish overall. For
me personally, I wouldn't be taking
longs because we're outside of range.
But if you are adamant on taking the
longs today, I'd be looking for a failed
breakdown. Ideally, at this point, it
takes previous day low, right? Ideally,
you do something like this. And where
would I be long? I'd want really to
reclaim current day. Um, but you can see
all the covering into value is starting
to happen. So, you should be out so much
of your position now. Anything beyond
this is a absolute gift. Like I always
talk about, it's a gift.
I cannot cannot cannot believe they've
done this to me on this day.
No, it won't. It won't. I can't even get
into my trailer v, guys. It's on It's on
a loop.
Oh, I might be in.
Have they just let me in?
You up there are playing [\h__\h] games
with me. You've let me log in once the
move's gone.
You're being cruel.
You're be You're being [\h__\h] cruel.
They just let me in after we attacked
previous day. If that's a sign to never
touch this [\h__\h] market today, that is
the biggest sign I've ever seen. You lot
are taking a piss up there, whichever
one of you it is.
Oh,
you've just got to laugh, man. Like,
you've got to laugh at life in the face
sometimes. It's just
[\h__\h] seriously
It's all you can do, right?
Always look on the bright side of life.
All right, targets are hit there. Right,
that's your previous day low. You've
just Well, it's trying to shift point of
control down here. So, we're going to
build out a lot of volume down here.
Now, I would be out of 90% of my shorts
now. Okay, because if we're going to go
if we're going to go rotation, we're
going to do it from here or hereabouts.
All right, so let's have a look. There
was an excess on that low short side. So
that's the one thing I don't like. We
have flipped uh to a bullish bias. Oh,
there was on Ninja Trader. Okay, we have
167 caught at the bottom there. So maybe
m may maybe the rotation might start. I
don't love the excess here. I would like
to see like a little bit more down into
this a little bit more sellside delta.
But if we look at bookmap, there was 167
lot at that low court. We're starting to
reclaim value already. Remember I talked
about this earlier. Look how we've just
shifted value lower. So, if we're going
to go into a uh a range rotational day,
it will happen around here. All right.
So, if they're going to sell it, they're
going to need to do this. If they do
something like this or something like
they're doing, they're starting to
rebuild here, then I would expect into
previous day point control. By the time
we get there, it probably be VWOP. That
would be the rotation. I wouldn't be
long. I want to make this clear. If
you've joined me enough times, I hate
playing rotations. I don't like playing
reversals. We're outside of range. But
if they are going to do it today, they
will need a failed breakdown, a reclaim
of value, and a trade back inside. It's
probably due in the next 20 minutes. If
they're going to do it, if they stay
heavy outside of previous day low, then
this has been my target for months down
here. If you're asking why, it's an old
naked point of control. It's been left
there now for Oh, let's have a look
together. Right. It's been left there
since
the 24th of November. All right. So,
this is where we last found balance,
right? This is a failed break above into
a twoe balance range where we're leaving
this balance. We didn't even have the
power to back test it today and we're
starting to get weak. This would be my
ultimate cover point. All right. I would
expect higher time frame bulls if they
if they have ambush ambitions of saving
the market market higher time frame. If
they have ambitions of saving the market
higher time frame, I would imagine they
will come in there somewhere in here.
They might not have ambitions to do it,
but it would be a strong cover point for
me is what I'm trying to tell you. Every
part of me saying don't even boot up my
Ninja Trader now because the move's
gone. I just feel like I'll probably
lose now.
You don't think it tagged it? Uh, did it
miss it by a tick or something? Let's
have Oh, you might be right.
It's there or thereabouts. 19s. It
missed it by one point. Maybe it still
comes for it. Yeah, you might be right.
I mean, ES hasn't come for it yet. ES
has got a long way to go.
Um, notice how this morning I'm going
to, especially for those in Discord,
look at SPY. First five minutes trades
down. Second five minutes fails to
reclaim what? 85 gamma level. From there
we trade at 82.
At 10:05 we trade under 82. We trade
back into 82. We reject it. We're now at
80s. We lose 80s. I don't think there's
a whole lot below. This is what I was
saying last week. All the exposure were
cool walls higher. There weren't many
put walls. This thing can start going
into freeall if
Oh my god. Here it goes. [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] coming to here without me. Are
you [\h__\h] kidding me?
Okay, now we have excess. I'd watch this
candle. So, I would say this candle
becomes key. You guys who are uber
bullish, you don't want to be bullish
until you reclaim this. Right. This
candle has strong selling in it. You
need to wait for there to be a passive
buy. I've not seen it all morning. This
is the one of the biggest delta candles
we've had all day. They are absolutely
tanking this thing right now.
Let's see if I can get back into ninja.
Do I even want to do this now? I've
missed the A+ scenario. Do you really
want to do it, Alex? Let's see if I can
even get in.
24930 is like an order block or supply
zone from a couple weeks ago. Yeah, it's
just it was the most traded level. All
right. It was the most traded level. So,
it's deemed fair value. So, if you look
at uh the week starting Monday the 17th,
it was a value area high. All right,
that's where we had to break out from.
We failed to we broke out and we failed.
We came back under and then we retested
it on Monday the 24th and we built out
so much volume there that it's
considered fair value. So, that is this
green box is acting like a magnet. Oh,
great. Ninja Trade is now working. You
absolut.
See you next Tuesday.
I just have to like manage this in my
head. Am I on tilt if I trade pro?
Probably.
Probably if we reach this. Probably. My
location has gone. The A+ trade is
playing out.
Cruelty levels. Cruelty levels.
Blame Bitcoin for all this. I mean, it's
not Bitcoin's fault. We're If you
understand why Bitcoin is selling, why
tech is selling.
Bitcoin Bitcoin is a they're heavily
leveraged in it. If you understand why
that's happening,
um why it's leading the pack
might help.
That's not me being a dick. Like, I'm
I'm genuinely saying, do do you
understand why? I can tell you why. If
you don't,
it's in the newsletter.
Hello, first time here. Thank you for
your live. What is the name of the
indicator with the delta candles?
This one. Do you mean at the bottom?
This is just delta. This is on Trading
View. Volume delta, if that's what you
mean. Uh, if you mean
this, this is a footprint chart
and that's your footprint chart. I'm not
sure which one you mean, but hopefully
that helps.
Yeah. Yeah. So at the you know at the
end of the newsletter it's all this is
all about the JPY carry trade. That's
what the weakness is coming from. People
a lot of people don't understand this.
All right. Buyers last got stuck at 91s.
Right. You can see this low volume node.
Sellers will want to hold versus this.
This is now your overunder. If you're
still short in this, this is your
overunder. All right. This is no reason
to long yet. Nothing has been reclaimed.
This is like a giant magnet right now.
Oh, Miguel, I'm sorry to hear that, my
friend.
This is the trade we've been waiting
for.
That pink and blue
just above the delta from Trading View.
You mean this? This is Satis's volume
stat. It's just a volume chart. It just
shows you or gives you an estimate of
the selling or buying within that
candle. So it's like sort of matching
the delta.
Yeah, no worries. NGC, it wasn't, like I
said, it wasn't loaded. It's just do you
understand why? All I was saying is do
you understand why crypto is selling?
Other than the technical selloff, other
than the fact, you know, technically
speaking, if you look at Bitcoin, it
always does about a one 1,000 day bull
run. We finished that bull run this
year. Um, I don't know if you were here
for that when I was saying, you know, I
expect Bitcoin to start going into a
sell to 70s and if it cracks 70s, it can
do a 70 plus% sell. It normally does
that after its bull run, especially if
this market front like follows it. We're
going to do a rate hike in Japan. We've
got uh major issues with debt in
America. It's going to have to refinance
its debt early into next year. We're
coming for that [\h__\h] point of
control. I cannot believe you up here.
Yeah, I'm definitely on tilt. Can't
touch this.
So cruel.
So cruel. I can show you that I haven't
taken a trade. The only trade I took was
yesterday. All right. I've just logged
in. That was last night. I took that
trade. [\h__\h]
Oh, it's cruel, man.
Yeah. Nice, Miguel. Nice, Miguel.
Also, I look back at the BOJ rate
hike after 1989 has contributed. Yeah,
exactly. Sometimes up to 35%.
But the the main thing is is how
leveraged we are. Um I'll try and show
you what I mean. Guys, you know the
levels, right? If you're still hopefully
some of you are still managing your
short, watch this volume built out here.
If you're short, you do not want it to
trade back above this. This low volume
node must act as resistance. If you
reclaim this, you must be out of your
shorts. All right? If you if you poke in
and and they sell against it, fine. The
level I'm going to put this on your
chart so that we can see the exact
level. The level I'd be aiming for is
right here. This line here. All right.
Runners are into that. That is the
dreamboat level. I would expect
if higher time frame bulls are going to
come back in this market, this is a
level where I would expect this market
to try and make a higher low. All right,
if we think about this just for a second
so you can understand this,
this was a low volume drive.
All right, through the holiday season.
Look, we're almost lining up to 50%. All
right, it's looking pretty good, right?
If I was going to be a bull my first
attempt on a on a higher time frame, I'm
talking about institutional money. This
is a level I'd buy off then here. If we
failed this, I'd be I'd be out. I'm
talking about if I was an institutional
buyer, I'd be looking for a trade into
here and a return back up there or a
trade into here and a return back up
there. So, this is why I would be
covering my shorts into this position
and potentially higher time frame bulls
will want to step in there. potentially.
It doesn't. Remember, we have to wait to
see if they step in. How are we going to
wait to see that? We're going to have to
see some form of trap level. Okay, look
at this. So, this is the revisit into
here. If they reclaim this, I'd be fully
out. All right. If they reclaim this, I
would be fully out if I was you. If they
start reclaiming value area low, if they
start basing above 90 or 88, that's
where they came flying in there. We do
have a good auction here where we've
left lots of shorts trapped in these
lows now. So this is looking much much
better for a potential relief rally. So
I would say if they dip and hold 85s,
bulls will take control of this. I
wouldn't be long in this personally. I
cannot make that clear enough. But for
those of you who like playing reversals,
that would be your first thing to see.
You'd want a dip and hold of 90 and 85
and then you'd want a reclaim of value
area low on the day and previous days
value area low. And if you get that, you
might well see some squeeze relief. So
here they're going back up towards value
area low from yesterday from today sorry
and this is yesterday and if they
reclaim this we have washed remember
this has been a straight trend this has
been walked down all right they can come
back into at least this node and then
possibly up into this low volume node
right this is possible this trade here
is possible you should be out shorts now
in my opinion I would be out of shorts
now personally that's how I would trade
this you're starting to uh
potentially repair some of this. And
really, if you got this short, you're
not missing too much more down here. I'd
be pretty happy with what I got. All
right, I guess
if they hold this, I'd be out. That's
what I'd be saying to myself.
Hopefully that makes sense. This is
using volume, order flow, and even flow
zones. Personally, I wouldn't be long in
this, but I know some of you are
desperate to get long. When the updated
course comes out, will the current
members be grandfathered in? Uh,
have a look in Discord, my friend.
So, we talked about it yesterday.
Okay, I'll tell you now. Uh,
if you've done the original course,
there is a 50% sale and a private
discount for you in Discord. Right? So,
if you've done the original course, for
everyone else, the course is actually
now live. Um, I have got a uh discounted
price
Let me have a look for you.
I wasn't going to talk about it today,
but seeing as you guys are asking,
uh, code launch will get you $100 off.
No, Alvaro. No, because you'll still
you'll still get the extra cheap price
for for current members. You'll still
get it.
Yeah, if you can I can show you guys if
you want.
So, bulls starting to hold this volume
node we just talked about. All right. If
bulls defend this,
there's lots of sellers trapped here.
They will look for relief to point of
control and value area low. If they
reclaim value area low, they're going to
look for relief up into here. So if
you're bullish really you need it to
hold over 153s and then you're looking
there's a 100 point move back upside
there for you if you're desperate
desperate desperate desperate desperate
to play the counter trend. I don't play
those like I always talk about. That's
not how I play. But
all right, I'll show you. I'll show you
guys. Give me a second.
I'm do so many things at once. Only so
much I can do.
Okay. So, if you come to here now,
volume and orderflow course, it is
available here for you to buy. All
right. Haven't shot the video for yet
for it yet. Be a week or two. If you hit
buy now
and you put in the coupon code,
what did I say it was? Launch,
right? You'll get $100 off 299,
right? Limited time only. That's running
till probably till Jan. Right. So, those
of you who were waiting for it,
it is out now.
It's just a soft launch.
I was going to talk about it later this
week, but seeing as a couple of you just
asked,
so it's available for you now. Those of
you who are already Discord members, or
those of you who have done the full
course already, go into Discord, have a
look.
No, beginner to advance is a totally
separate course, buddy. Totally separate
course.
You need to do that first, really. So
you've got a good basis of
understanding. You've said you've bought
it. So just work your way through that.
If you want Discord access, go to the
end of that course and there's a module
on how to get Discord access. All right.
So here they come. They're going to come
and back test this level towards these
90s that I talked about. They need to
hold this if uh these bulls have a
chance of repricing.
Yeah. Thanks Aaron. God the CO set me
back so much. You'll hear it in some of
the early modules. I'm like,
so I might redo some of them now. My
voice has come back.
Yes. And I will add modules, Richard.
Like like today,
I would have loved to have recorded this
trade, but uh I'll go back and and
record the record why this trade worked
and put it in and then I'll just quote
because you can see that I would have
traded this live if I had access to my
Ninja Trader this morning. Okay, so it's
a good hold of 90s kind of area so far.
So there's going to be a battle here.
SPY didn't quite take previous day low
yet. We did take it on NQ. The rotation
now is starting to take place. They've
repriced this lower this low volume
node. This is the area bulls will want
to defend to leave this seller trapped.
Right? So if bulls successfully do that,
they need to get back above previous
day's value area low for squeeze relief.
That could be a twole that they might
well sell back into. That is just like
Friday. If you remember Friday, I talked
about how personally I would leave the
bullish play alone, right, and wait for
it to peak out. And in Discord, we took
that move. So that's a really good hold
of this volume node we just talked
about. So those of you who are desperate
to play the bullish side, this is the
level, right? So this is the level bulls
are trying to defend right now. This
level right here.
Again, this is all playing out in
retime. Bulls must defend this level.
And I would say really they need to
reclaim this guy, right? Because if they
do that, that will be a look below and
fail and we can trade up. That will be
exactly the same as this morning. That's
a look above and fail. That's a look
below and fail. We can repric into here.
It's very, very possible that they can
do that today. I would love them to do
that today and leave that area that I
want to trade into for another day. It
would be fantastic
cuz I think I'm probably a bit too
emotional and tilty to trade now at this
point having missed what if I missed
like two 300 points out of this.
Optimal entry would have been around
here. Let's be realistic.
Yeah, I've missed 300 points. Yeah, I
probably can't trade today out of
discipline.
owe my misses some credit to do. Pretty
sure you were able after trading. What
do you mean
miss missing after trading? What do you
mean? Oh, like not giving her any time.
Definitely.
I saw a video. Has anyone seen that meme
video of the uh trader at his desk and
it's like uh the hot hot Latina walks
in. She's like trying to be all sexy and
like she looks at him and then like
walks out and it looks like he's walking
after her and he just slams the door and
goes back to his trade desk. Like yeah,
that's the trader right there. You're
distracting me. It'll [\h__\h] away.
Just one day should show my dom. The
dom's up here. The dom's up here.
I don't know whether to shut it down,
honestly.
Don't think we're done with short. It's
very possible we're not. Like I said,
this is the magnet
for me. Like I said, bulls would need to
defend this and they would need to
reclaim this. I don't I don't play
these. These are counter trends against
like the higher time frame. I'm like
just like Friday. Friday.
All right. I didn't play
this trade here. I ignored all this, but
I did play this, right? We did play that
breakdown on Friday.
Oh, don't do that. There we go. I need
that a little bit.
You can see like the bulls are trying to
defend this volume area. We do have
sellers track. If you look at bookmap
right now, you see this guy down here,
281 lot like trapped at the bottom. That
is the sign that an auction might have
possibly finished. Okay, so it not
guaranteed,
but if I get you on to bookmat,
right, auctions finished when the last
seller has sold. Well, there's a big
seller down here has sold so far. So,
you can see if we just analyze this
right now,
right, late shorts are caught here. We
are holding price above that. All the
time we hold price above that, there's
potential relief. And where can we get
relief to? I'm trying to look where the
big big guys came in. So I'd be looking
for relief to sort of 75 to 200 and
above. Hopefully that makes sense.
It's a big if button maybe if you're
going to take this. But that's that's
what they're looking to do. Uh if they
get back inside previous day's value,
that will be the key trigger. Can they
get back inside previous days value?
Is Discord behind a payw wall? Um, it's
just for course members. So, if you do
the beginner to advanced course, there's
no additional fee. I I talk about this
all the time. There's no like monthly
membership or weekly fee or anything
like that. Um, we keep it for people
that do uh the beginner to advanced
course. It's not to try and prevent you
guys from having access. It's to try and
I've been in a lot of communities. Um,
and normally what you'll find is if
they're
on a subscription ba subscription basis
or even if they're free, you get lots of
traders arguing because they're seeing
different things, trading different
ways. What I've tried to do is create a
small community of people who are
trading the same way, looking for the
same thing, because I think from a
longevity point of view, that will
create a good ethos and good support
system. If you think about if you were
actually going to trade at a prop firm,
you would have a risk manager and you
would have like a sort of trade desk
leader who would sort of get you in and
out of trades. Everyone would be trading
in the same direction unless you had one
guy hedging against them all. You would
not have them all arguing, I'm taking
this, I'm doing this, I'm doing this,
I'm putting you off this trade, blah
blah blah. And that's what I'm trying to
avoid. Okay, where would I say big
sellers above came in at 150s. So I'd be
watching that level. or if they start
reclaiming that then maybe we go back
into value. So we're going to poke up
into previous day value like I talked
about. So this blue box just held like I
said potential rotation to here. They
will need to find acceptance in here for
a squeeze. Otherwise this can be a
two-leg which is resold into right. So
this is counter trend relief and how we
act into and around here becomes key. So
you can see the key levels.
You have to manage how you want to trade
this. Do you want to lean on this short
when it's finished peeking out? Or are
you the trader that's looking for a
failed breakout
outside of value? Are you looking for
this into here? Or are you looking for
something like this all the way back
down? That's what you have to think
about. Both of those are possible.
Yeah, I see that. It's It's dirty on the
It's annoying, isn't it? Divergence
playing out there.
Oh, thanks. Sucks. I already trade
pretty much the same. Not buying the
course. Yeah. So, sorry, Johnny. Sorry.
Like, I get it. I like I totally get it.
It I wouldn't spend if I was you, I
wouldn't buy the course either. Like,
um, but I will be here every day and
most of those guys are here every day.
So, you know, you get three hours with
me and it won't cost you anything.
But I to I I totally
I totally understand. I would be exactly
the same. And I spent when I was
learning, I spent
thousands and thousands and thousands on
garbage courses and garbage uh discords
and stuff like that whereas 150 a day or
a day a month or 300 a month and it was
just shite. Um so I've tried to do the
opposite of that. So here's the relief.
Okay. So maybe even if you didn't take
this, maybe this is helping you see this
in the future. We had excess on this low
like we talked about. They protected
this which meant leaving these sellers
stuck. We have a strong trend down on
the day which they can repric because we
haven't riced it. We've come back inside
previous days value. So we've reclaimed
current value. We've left short stuck.
We're back inside previous days value.
How they act now becomes important.
Friday we did this kind of thing. today.
Is it possible that they hold value or
hold here and go for relief? Is it
possible that we rotate in here for the
day? It is because I think we're
probably doing inside day today. We've
moved outside, but we haven't sustained
an auction lower. For me, this right now
is a failed breakout. All right, you're
seeing relief now. So, for those of you
who like the rotation, that is it. And
hopefully you saw it ahead of time.
Uh, do it in capitals. Uh, you might
need to do it on capitals. Let me double
check that. It should work. I just put
it in my side.
It's only working on the uh, it's only
for the volume orderflow course. Go buy
now.
It would need to be in capitals. Sorry,
I probably said didn't say that. That's
probably my fault. Yeah, it works.
You've got to be in capitals.
Nice, Johnny.
Um, where did you where did you uh
how should I put this? Where where did
you find your consistency from? Did was
it for other people in chat? Was it just
time on the charts? Because I think time
on the charts is the biggest teacher. Or
was there something that really helped
you? What helped you click and move
over?
I only watched 15 minutes of YouTube
stream
and what sold it for me was Alex telling
someone not to buy his course to try the
videos for free. But it's important,
isn't it? Like it's so important because
it's guys, it's an expensive um thing to
start out on. And like I've tried to I
think I priced mine fair. Like I don't
think
personally I don't think 650 is a lot
for 20 hours discord
uh an indicator. And I still do private
lessons in Discord. It's not like the
education stopped. So I try and price it
fair. But if you don't like me or how I
teach or the sound of my voice or any of
those things, then there's no point in
doing it because you just you're not
going to learn. Like I talked about, I
remember being at university and college
and having teachers which I just hated
the way they taught. And I my grades
just got tanked. And it doesn't mean
that they were bad teachers. Just their
pedagogy didn't work for me. The way
they taught didn't work with me. It
rubbed me the wrong way. Okay. And there
was other teachers who my psychology
teacher in my first year I will always
remember Dr. Pink
awesome awesome awesome at Brunell
University West London. [\h__\h]
unbelievable coach and like he hooked me
in. I traded I changed my modules to
move to sport psychology because he was
so good. And then he left and I got
dealt a different mentor for the next
for my second and third year at uni and
he was [\h__\h] and he did well in my
opinion he was a great uh writer. He had
lots of stuff out in like you know um
sports science journals and stuff but
his teaching methodology rubbed me the
wrong way. like shouting stuff or just
yelling
[\h__\h] without explaining to me didn't
work for me and my grade suffered for
it, you know? So, it's it's the same
with with anything, right? Especially
those of you who have kids probably know
this more than anyone. I'm sure like the
finding the right teacher for them is so
important.
not clicking for you here yet? I'm sorry
to hear that. Um,
have you finished the course? Is there
stuff I can do to help you? Because I
want it to click for you. Let me know if
there's stuff I can do or lean on the
guys on Discord as well.
Yeah, that's key, Mike. That I think
that is everything liquid. This this is
a game of liquidity. If you think about
if we just review today. All right,
let's just review today. Let's just
review what's happened. Let's just take
this this off to start with. All right,
let's just review just based on value.
All right, this is your pre-market high
in this morning push. What happens?
Right, amateur bulls come flying in. So,
you've got people short against this and
breakout bulls in here, right? But this
is expensive. This is premium. So they
chase the market higher and the shorts
get popped. So what do we have here? We
have market buy orders because if you're
a breakout buyer, you're a market buy
order. If you're a short seller and you
get stopped out, you're a market buy
order. That gets paired off with
selling. If we look at Well, we can just
probably do it in here.
Move this over. If we look at the
opening drive this morning,
we got to go into one minute 5 minute.
Let's have a little look.
Maybe at the right place up here. We go.
Right, we leave
pre-market. There was a buy side
imbalance. We repair that and sellers
hold the market. Buyers come in big
here. 84
to 71. Do we ever let these buyers out?
No. The next candle doesn't let them
out. That is your failure. You can
probably see it even more in a one
minute. It's going to play bull. Here we
go. Zoom right in.
All right. So, early participants
get caught. This is actually an unusual
auction at the high to be honest. But
you can see it's these guys that get
caught 401 to 405 and then this candle
here 95 to 80s and I was concerned about
these sellers being stuck. Right? So
these became a level which we had to
watch closely but once they resold this
you can see here aggressive buyers
stepping in the market at at uh 936
trying to get back through these strong
sellers failed which means there's
passive selling here and since then all
we've done is go lower. So what have we
done? Failed breakout.
Failed breakout. Trapping liquidity.
Where have we attacked the other side?
If we look at the auction at the low
who got caught at the lows
sellers. All right. And someone
somewhere in here was a previous day
low. Uh
what was previous day low? Put this back
on.
Right. 119. So 119. Remember 119. Was
that right?
2516.
I've got to move this over. That's why
this is a problem. It's the old
contract.
Okay. Right here. 116
2518 20.
This is not moved.
here. This guy here. Okay. So,
everything that happened beneath that
had the potential to catch sellers
and we leave sellers caught here, but
mainly here. And the delta flips from
here to positive. You can see all this
aggressive buying. Okay. Now we know
sellers are caught down here. Then we
reclaim sellers tried to sell underneath
previous day low again. So sellers
caught here and here. That is exactly
what we're talking about and we auction
away from them. So how we act here
coming back into it will set the tone
and sentiment for the remainder of the
day. Now the one thing I would say here
is this is looking like Friday
two leg. How we act here now becomes
important. Look at the node. Look at
VWAP. We repric. We've done the damage.
If they start failing value here, they
can come backside back down to this.
It's possible, right? Because this is
your second leg. We've failed VW up.
We've failed point of control. Now we've
built out a shelf. If if they sell
versus sort of 50, 60, 70, 80, maybe
even 200. If they sell versus this,
that's a backside move. I would not be
long now until they show that they want
to reclaim that because the main trend
is lower. But what I would say is we've
taken liquidity both sides. This is
where I become uninterested.
Hopefully that makes sense. Hopefully me
sort of talking you through that. But
that is the game of liquidity. Take
liquidity from the high. Take liquidity
from the low. Trap liquidity here. Make
sellers come in versus this. All right.
If if bulls can hold above this, they
need to rotate and get above this. If
they're going to sell this, they're
going to trap versus this. They need a
continuation underneath these lows. and
they're going to need to let out these
sellers who are stuck. Your lowhanging
fruit sell has gone. The easy money sell
has gone. This is why I'm like probably
can't trade for the rest of the day. Can
we come down here?
Possible.
But I'd almost like this to build out
more liquidity for a little bit, trap
lots more people in, and then use them,
which is just like Friday. If we go back
to Friday, it was the same game.
I think about Friday. Difference with
Friday is we actually caused compression
at the low. This is what we've done with
the whole trend today.
All right. Relief second leg peak out
into key area backside and repric.
Only thing in my head I thought I think
today would be an inside day. So I've
got this kind of like niggling thing in
the back of my head being like maybe
they hold
Let's see. Can go both sides now. Uh ES
just failed VWAP. All right. ES just fa
failed VWOP. Spy just failed 82.
Remember that's a massive level. Big
gamma level. Uh if anyone can have a
look if anyone's got the gamma levels
up. What are the put walls below? I
would imagine 80 7875. But is there
anything standing out huge so far on
this Monday morning? Uh we've got OPEX
as well this week.
Time on the chart says the only way to
digest what you learn then it's down to
mentally being able to control the FOMO.
Absolutely. When I learn agree,
go to Coop's corner and join the
challenge and sign in on the Saturday
morning conference call. It will help.
Several guys in there can answer. There
you go. Yeah, Richard helping you there.
Coup's corners in the Discord.
It's a It's part of the Discord.
Gold's indecisive.
Well, gold would be the hedge for what's
probably going to happen this week.
Back end of the week. It's It's fine.
It's fine. Look, all the time gold's
basing above here.
It's fine, right? High time frame. It
wants to come and take these out. So if
it keep peaking and holds and peaks and
holds and peaks and holds, these are the
levels. All right, it's going to be
boxed in here. Once it goes for a break,
it will swipe these. If it loses this,
yes, it will come back downside. But
it's it's a catch-up trade to silver
right now. But if they sell, all right,
if they sell uh NQ and SPY, etc., etc.,
uh because of the JPY carry or the JP
carry then I expect this will probably
happen here because this would be the
hedge versus USD
big ifs and buts and maybe we won't we
won't know until Friday and Sunday
Alex, am I on Trading View Pro? My
volume footprint looks like nothing as
detailed as you. Uh, I am. It would just
be how you set it up though. If if
you've got access to footprint, do you
have access to the footprint chart?
Like, can it load? And then it's just
depends how you set it up. I have mine
set for uh delta.
So,
right. So, I'm looking at row size to
display profile and delta. That's how I
have mine set up.
So, bold trying to step in here. We have
offside delta at the low of day. We're
now just trading around that previous
day value area low. The big question is
can bulls all right find acceptance back
into value. All right. If we can't find
acceptance outside of previous day
value, we probably come back into value.
Where were the playboy? Well, previous
day point of control will be where they
want to test. If we get back above that,
then we're going to go right back up
here. If we fail this, then we retest
value again. If they fail that low of
day again, fail that old point of
control again. We're into a rotational
market uh to build out liquidity because
we've done the main rotation. Remember
here to here was the main rotation. Now
they have to build liquidity to make
their mind up.
Yeah. So lifetime dogee it would just be
in the settings my friend. So just open
it up. I would I changed mine to manual
uh two tick row size um profile chart
and delta. But it all depends what you
want to look at. Everyone's everyone's
different. All I ever care about really
when when I'm looking at footprint
charts is the delta. Uh if you're using
it on a 5, 10, 15, 30 minute chart, it
might be worth having the volume on
there as well
because then you can see the shapes of
the profile. All right, sellers buyers
just got caught up there into 59.
Someone just came flying in and got got
myself caught. I'm going to use the
bathroom here for a second, folks, and
I'll be right back. Stay with me. We're
going to do an Apex giveaway in about an
hour and uh we can keep going through
some lessons because I don't think I'm
going to be able to actively trade this.
I am starting to chill out now because
it's if it le if it leaves if it leaves
this for another day, I'll be very
happy. Very, very happy. So, that's
Please, please, please. I'm going to get
coffee, use bathroom, I'll be right
back.
This will be what round five.
Okay.
at least 20262.
>> No, no.
I'll give you
all right team. Sorry about that. Had a
call as well. I didn't realize that was
coming in. Uh what we got then? Okay, so
you are reclaiming.
So failed look below previous day value
area low right now. Reclaiming previous
day value area low. Previous day low. Uh
current point control on the session.
You might well see a drift up into here.
All right. So maybe second leg comes up
into here. And what they do here becomes
important for sentiment of the rest of
the day because if they're going to go
rotation, they're going to need to sell
this back down. If they fail to hold
sellers, okay, sellers have done a
really good job today. Remember, all low
hanging fruit's gone. That's why I've
become less interested. If they're going
to offer a sell, it needs to be here. If
they can't offer that sell, we're going
to come right back up to previous day
value area high. Uh
so, those are the rotations.
Sorry, folks. Sorry, sorry, sorry.
Didn't want to be gone that long, but uh
some of you know I've got some
some family stuff going on at the
moment, unfortunately. It's part of
life.
Part of life. But
looking okay is
fingers crossed.
Are any of you guys in long in this? Did
any of you guys take either long from
the blue box or long from previous day
low reclaim or any of that? It's not a
trade I like, but it's a valid trade
setup. Just because I don't like it
means doesn't mean it's not valid.
Thanks guys. I appreciate it. It's
Yeah, I won't talk about it on here. I
don't want to get emotional. It's a lot,
but uh it's not
it's not looking too bad at the moment,
which is good.
I wish it was uh something as small as
that.
At what point on the day does value area
high low become more important than
yesterday? Oh, you mean current days
building? Um, I'd say really from now
10:30 in, but you know, it doesn't mean
we can't repric. Like we can see we've
left volume above
um
every level is valid. Every level is
valid. What I'd be thinking about is
like
have we expanded lower? Have we hit
this? No. So it's possible we might want
to go back for that. Have we let left
left sellers trapped down there? Yes, we
have. So maybe they finished ex
expansion down today. Have we reclaimed
current value? Yes, we have. All right.
So was there a long back up here?
Possible. Yes. Was there a long here
possible? Yes. Like I said, both of
these were valid trades. They're not
trades I would take, but they are valid
trades. What I'd be looking at now is
look how thin it gets above this little
shelf here, right? So, if they're able
to pop this shelf, we can probably come
straight up into this level here.
Remember, that's previous day close,
GlobeEx, previous day point of control.
So, big big big if butts and ws. I
wouldn't imagine bears will want them to
be allowed to rotate above these areas.
All right. So, I'd imagine they're
allowing some relief. If we even think
about this New York session, we're
probably what, 30 or something? 33s.
There you go. So, 38. So, if we're going
to allow 50% retracement, if they're
going to allow 50% retracement,
remember, walk down, walk down, walk
down, walk down, walk down, walk down,
big expansion trap, higher low, higher
high, higher low. How we act in here for
me and in here becomes key, right? So, I
I don't trade the longs on stuff like
this. Doesn't mean you can't. I'd be
waiting now to see I don't like this.
So, I'd want to see it peak above, fail,
come under, stay heavy, ro like rotate,
and I'd be covering here, here, here,
here, here, and holding for a runner. My
expectation is not now how it was
earlier because now I know
in here we have lots of trap sellers.
Whereas when we were walking down
before, we didn't have that. Now we have
trap sellers which means what? We have
demand. We have a support structure. So
if we're going to play for a
continuation, we're going to respect
that just like Friday. It's guys, it's
carbon copy from Friday. This is why
learn to see these things the same way.
Where is Friday? Mr. Friday. Here it
goes. Right. So the relief took a while
on Friday.
There's the little blowoff top. All
right. On volume. And then we failed to
print it back above. There's the lower
high. And we cover into these points. We
respect these points. And if we get
lower, it's great. But we always respect
those levels.
I agree with you Johnny. That's that's
exactly how I feel my friend. That's how
I feel. I that's why I don't play the
counter trend because the main if we
look at VWOP
VWOP trading downside, right? VWOPS are
down, EMAs are down, higher time frame
are down, point of control is here. I'm
with you, my friend. I don't trade these
trades, but it doesn't mean they're not
valid setups. It's just it is not I
would rather let this peak out and trade
that. I'm exactly with you, my friend.
That's that is my preference. But if it
peaks out and it doesn't want to let go,
you know, we can't rule out that move up
there. But, uh, it all depends what the
Q's do today on the MAG. So, let's give
you a little readout on the MAG. So,
Tesla right now
3.83% up, Nvidia 1.28% 28% up. Meta
0.36% up. And then you've got the
weakness. So Microsoft 1% down. Google
uh 3/4 of a percent down. Amazon 1.16%
down. Apple 1 and a half% down. So mixed
bag. If we look beyond that, AVGO 4.09%
down. Oracle 3% down. Um all those sort
of I would say B and C list high gamma
exposure names they all got clobbered
this morning. So RGTI 7 7.24% down. NVTS
5.82%. 82% down all those sort of chip
name AI names and NQ 6.16% down 8.20%
20% down, you know, so Netflix 1.19%
down. So the the bigger spectrum right
now is not in a buy. I am I am in
absolutely agreement with you, Johnny.
But I try and the difference is how I
trade and how I teach. I have to be
aware that some of you will like playing
these rotations. Some of you will be
looking for a scalp off this. This this
like we talked about, it's a valid
trade. It's not a trade I would take,
but it is a valid trade.
dead eyee. What am I looking at? Uh any
form of
bookmap, delta, footprint, like anything
like that. However you want to view it,
whatever you feel comfortable with. I
use all of them.
It's like we talked about footprint.
If we look at the lows, right, sellers
are at the lows,
right? So, they're stuck. So, that's why
we reversed off that level.
And like I said, if you if you rewind
the tape, I said, as long as they put in
a higher low versus here, they're going
to be okay. All right. So, they
protected these guys. These guys are
stuck. And now they've left these guys
stuck. All right. So, everyone beneath
this who's a seller is now stuck and
you're seeing relief to the upside
because of it. Right? But you don't have
to view that on there. You can see it on
bookmap as well. Like it it's like
horses for courses, right? However you
want to see it. Like we went over. If
you look at bookmap, look at this big
seller at the low of day. 226 lot, 220
lot here, 286 lot here, 24 lot there.
Above him, 242 lot. All these guys are
now stuck. Right underneath here is all
sell side. We look at all these
aggressive sellers. They're all stuck.
So, we're lifting. We're going to come
to this VWAP now.
Right. So, it's just it's it's totally
up to you how you view it. I mean, you
don't have to use any of this. If you if
you
Um trying to think how to explain this.
If you just like candlesticks, all
right, then you can think about this in
terms of structure, right? If you don't
want to be uber accurate and you're just
like, well, you know, there is your
displacement, there is a failed break
below, there's a hold, we break through
that displacement, all right, we're
going upside, right? That's the relief.
That's another way of viewing it.
I like to have like real data inside of
this rather than guessing based on
candles than
historically. I've always looked at
bitmap, right? I've only used footprint
more recently. I'm actually really
enjoying it because I find it arguably
even easier to read than bookm
uh
but it's the same theory. I'm always
looking the same stuff. We're seeing big
buying coming in at the moment and if
they can't get through these levels,
they're going to get themselves caught.
We see on bookmap 175 lot 56 lot more
coming in here and if they don't get
this breakout and push above they will
get themselves caught and we will
probably wash back down to 175. So
they're trying aggressively aggressively
aggressively to step in. We've got this
shelf hedge. Remember we said we we're
thin above this. If you rewind the tape
only like probably three or four
minutes. So we're thin above this. A
break here will probably cause a squeeze
out up here because look at the
difference. There's your volume build
out, right? Sellers needed to defend
this edge. you can see it and they
didn't. So, we're going to get a lift
off here and a squeeze. Now, if we lift
and we fell back into that, that might
offer the short back down. Maybe maybe
they don't want to do it today because
we've hit most our targets today. My
ambition today or my thought process
today, go back to the very very
beginning like 9:15 today uh New York
time 9:15. What did we talk about?
Where's my daily? We talked about
probability of having an inside bar.
We've looked we've looked underneath.
We're coming back to this shelf. Look at
this. We're coming back to this shelf,
right? Can they lift all the way up
here? I doubt it. I think we're just
going to sit in here today.
I think ultimately we're going to come
down here. I don't think it's going to
be today. I could be wrong. Could
absolutely be wrong. I thought we'd stay
inside today. We've already gone
outside, but we're back in. So, let's
look below and fail
for now. For now, it's early in the day.
Things can change. How we close today
becomes important. Here's the lift,
then. All
right. So, previous day point of control
here, current value area high on the day
here. So, bulls done a good job of
getting up here. If I was a bull, I'd be
starting to take profits into this area.
Lots of bulls trying to get this move to
300. I would be, if I was a bull, I
wouldn't be adding here, but they are
still trying to add and get this squeeze
out. a big buying delta. And if there's
a passive selling here, well, they'll
get themselves caught, right? And then
you see starting to get themselves
caught already into this level.
Didn't quite make value area high, which
is 42. So, previous day point of control
was 40. Value area high is 42s. This is
what they're trying to get to. This
right here,
right? This kind of area right here is
where they're trying to get to. And then
how we act beyond that becomes
important.
Right? So you can see the rotation now
has been developed.
Right? There's value on the day. Someone
asked when do I pay attention to value?
Now. Now I'm paying attention to value.
You think we drift up to repric? Yeah. I
mean, very good chance even on.
Sorry, I'm just looking at the hourly.
Give me a second.
Yeah, I mean three 300s, 305s, even
where we broke down from that shelves
320s. It's possible, but you know, it
gets worse and worse for shorts here.
The more they allow this to lift, the
more it looks like, are we going to do
that move we talked about originally?
Look above. Look below. Is that
possible? Yes. I would say it has to do
this to allow that to be possible. This
can still be
or at least back into there. Maybe they
can catch a bid if they fail that back
down. But I think we just tra we rotate
now for the day. We've done the damage.
I think we probably see a rotation.
We've just repriced an old imbalance
here up into 55s.
So, I'd watch point control now. If they
start to get heavy underneath that,
you might see uh this like aggressively
rotate back and forwards. There's lots
of big buying and lots of being selling
in the last minute up here. So, buyers
right now 35 37 sellers right now 31.
They're all sort of positioned quite
tight. If we expand through here, we
kind of get a bit thin up into 70s.
There was a buyer caught offside this
morning at 10 at 9:47 up into 72s.
Why is Tesla lifting so? It's just a
technical breakout and people have been
too short biased on Tesla and not
trading the technicals. The technicals
are staying higher. I'm sure there's
some ridiculous gamma exposure on it for
OPEX. Remember, it's OPEX this week. I'm
sure there's some ridiculous,
ridiculous, ridiculous levels it's got
to go and take out to make sure one side
loses.
No worries, mate.
So, into this red box.
Can they get over this red box? This
previous day point control. So, this is
fair value from Friday. We're now
trading at fair value from Friday.
And if they lift through here,
can't rule out all the way up back up to
there. Cannot rule it out for a range
rotation day. It's possible.
It's possible. Not guaranteed because we
can also fail back under here. Rotate
right back down. I have no no real bias
at this point. We've done the damage. I
would say the big damage has been done.
I would like to see them get stuck, but
uh we see we did definitely catch some
buyers up here.
Sort of above 40.
If BW holds her, I think we can hit a
new high of day.
I think it's asking a lot to go for a
high of day.
I think you'll probably see it like
stall out soon.
I think this is a multi-legg pushup. I
think what you're probably going to see
is something like this and then just
like sort of this for the day. I
wouldn't be surprised if we sit in here.
Really would not be surprised at all.
Remember, we don't have much news today
or anything. And um all eyes are on
later this week.
Have we got tomorrow? Is tomorrow,
right? Tomorrow we've got uh the delayed
report of US employment data. Do we get
the current? We should get the current
report. We get the US hourly wages. We
get UT uh delayed report of the US
retail sales. Um and that all comes at
8:30. Then we get PMI at 9:45.
Business inventories at 10:00. I think
we've got something else coming as well.
I'll have a look in a second. Uh
Wednesday, a load of Fed talk. And then
Thursday's obviously the big one. You
got jobless cranes CPI and the carry
trade coming into potentially
potentially coming into effect.
Where is big buy delta stuck? 319 if
they really want to get going. Been
asking a lot out of the market to do
that.
How long we got left there? Just over
half an hour. I just should do an Apex
giveaway. Uh I really want to set up
this Christmas giveaway as well. Haven't
had a chance to do that yet.
Mundus, did I take any trades? No.
Unfortunately, my Ninja was down today
due to a issue with my W8. But the
trades we called out on stream were from
here. TP1, TP2, TP3. And if you got
well, TP3 was in this area. And if you
got lucky, we would have got full thing
here. And then the second trade we
called out was from here, higher low. I
don't take these, but these are valid
trades for that relief back into here.
This is where you're now boxed in. All
right. So, you can rewind and watch it
all. You'll see me say up here, I can't
trade today. My ninja trader is down,
but this is what I'd be looking for. And
I guided everyone here and
lots of people here have made big big
days, two 300 point trades.
Really nice. But go back and um if it's
your first time here, I would say it's a
good one to watch. If you just go back
to the beginning of the stream, I leave
all the streams up. You will see me call
out where I'd enter, what I would do,
and the thesis way ahead of time. Way
way way ahead of time. Unfortunately,
yeah, unfortunately today, my friend,
for some reason, uh NTA is uh very upset
that I haven't done a W8 form, even
though I am now a uh well, I'm not a US
citizen, but I'm a green card holder, so
I don't need to do that. So, they
disabled my account thinking I'm trading
from UK, which I'm not.
Do I trade live or eval? Uh both, both.
Both both both.
I really like your trade style at
basement trades off risk and reward.
First- time viewer, but you seem to be
aligned with that. I mostly trade the
markets, Bitcoin, and gold right now.
Oh, nice. And uh Harlen, are you like an
intraday trader or swing trader when
you're trading that stuff?
How do I get the profile on the right
side of the chart? Uh anchored VWAP. Uh
anchored VWAP. It's a anchored V
anchored volume profile. And then here
you have to click here placement right.
Okay. So we're banging into that value
area high for the day at the moment.
There is some delta standing out offside
at 72s from earlier this morning. I
don't know if they let them out. So we
will see what's the Mac doing. Tesla is
trying to break out here, folks.
It looks like a bit of a cup and handle
for me on a 5m minute on Tesla and it
might get going.
Nvidia now 2% up as well. AMD 1% up. Uh
market equally weighted 0.84% up right
now. So, it's finding that relief we
talked about.
I don't know if it reprices the whole
thing today. If it's a look below and
fail and they repric the whole thing. I
don't know, folks. I wish I wish I had a
crystal ball, but uh we're coming into
an area where I think they might start
to get stuck. If they're going to get
stuck, it's going to need to be here or
hereabouts.
Is my doggy better? Yeah, she's doing
amazing. Thank you so much for asking.
Yeah, she's fully better. Um completely
off leash, running around like a lunatic
again. It's like I do you know what? She
had a bad leg for so long, I almost
forgot what it was like to have a happy
dog. Uh, it's so nice. I took her up on
the bluffs uh yesterday. Had her off
leash and just watching her run around.
So, so nice.
We don't deserve them. Honestly, we
don't deserve them. Best creatures ever.
Okay. Drift higher in effect.
How do you make it smaller? Uh, it' be
in your row size.
Uh, it' be here. So, I'd either go tick
ticks per row I'd do to two or if you do
number rows I'd do it to a thousand.
It's up to you how you do it.
But the reason I've been doing two is
because I have my footprint set to the
same thing.
Okay, some buyers potentially getting
stuck here. You might see a wash coming
in here. Can they take control? So, a
look above value and fail. Previous day
point, this area here is the contested
area. I like how we act here becomes
key. Are they going to keep drifting? In
which case, there's no short. If they
get stuck here, I think there's a short
down to 200. So, I think there's a
potential. Well, it's only 30 points,
but if they get stuck, it's potential.
If they hold this, they can drift. Even
if they come back down here, they can
still do this later. But they're
building this right now. I would imagine
they're going to wash them at some
point. We got to wait for them to let go
of 30. I don't like how we've built out
two nodes here instead of one. Never
like seeing that.
That's gross.
Yeah. Yeah. Uh it's not an indicator.
It's just a tool. Um it is in is it this
one? No, this one. Yeah. So if you go to
projections. So 1 2 3 four fifth one
down projections and then volume base
and you'll see anchored view up. Here's
the sell guys. This is we're getting
into an interesting area here. How they
act here like I talked about will become
important. Right? Buyers will want to
defend this. If they can't defend it, I
think there's potentially a wash down
into sort of 200. So, I'm watching this
area here.
Which indicator you using to show your
breakout high and lows? What you mean
breakout high and lows? I don't know
what you're talking about. Sorry, mate.
Let me know what you mean and and I'll
try and explain. I'm not sure what you
mean. I'm sorry. I've misunderstood
that. Back into the little ledge here.
If they start letting go of this, I'm
interested in a breakdown sell all the
way back down into 196 here.
We're just testing the edge of this
little range we just talked about. They
would need to leave this range, which
they are now starting to try and do.
Back to volume point control on the day
here.
So, we're going to try and find dips.
Are we at 22s? I don't think so. Don't
think you are. I think you're probably
going to get yourself caught here, Mr.
Buyer. Here you go. See you later. I'm
in this. Can we get follow through? I
want to see continuation under 22s.
Let's go. Let's go. Let's go.
Thank you. Covered a little bit there on
that last little wash. There's a buyer
trying to step in here. Seller getting
himself caught there. I think we can
wash down into this shelf. I'm just
careful because we're at PDC. So, I'm
short from here. Covered some into here.
I want to see if we can get down into
this guy here. Like I talked about
again, I gave you this beforehand. Once
we leave this, I think we can retrace
back into here. Here we go. Cover a bit
more here because they're getting a bit
aggressive here for my liking. Come on,
baby.
Finally. At least I got something today,
[\h__\h]
Pardon my French. Okay, so we're
watching this node here. I don't really
expect it to sell beneath beneath this
level. So, I've taken a big chunk off
because I'm playing this pullback. I
don't know if buyers step back in here.
So, like we talked about, once we see
this, I'm trying to play the pro trend.
I don't know if if they do this, I can
add back in, but I'm protecting
liquidity that we built air or I'm
protecting myself against liquidity we
built earlier because maybe like we
talked about, they do this, this wash,
reclaim this, and go higher. I don't
know. I know both are possible. So, I'm
positioned and I'm paying myself. Here
we go.
There's an imbalance here into 200. Here
we go. Here we go. I don't want to see
them defend this. We're going to get
continuation. We've got to stay heavy
under this.
This is the shelf. I've taken most of my
position off now, folks.
I don't know if they defend it. And if I
if I was a bull and I was going to take
us back to previous day value high, I'd
want to defend this level. So, I'm going
to respect them. Delta sellside delta is
down at 84. into here would be amazing.
Here's 94s. Can we get to 84s? Can we
get to 84s?
You're close. Give me 84s.
Eyes are trying and failing right now.
Come on, baby.
Let's [\h__\h] go. Let's go. Give me
eight fours.
You [\h__\h] You're not going to film me
there.
Oh my god. You've missed me by [\h__\h] a
tick.
These lot up here are just playing games
with me today. I swear to God.
Come on. You feel me? At 84s. If we come
84s now, I think we wash harder. So,
come on.
Come on.
There's delta right there. That's why
we're Yeah. Yeah. Okay. Tiny tiny tiny
size. Let's see. Let's see. Let's see.
All right. But this was the main trade.
Well, the main trade. The trade I
played. Once we leave this volume, we
leave these guys trapped. If you rewind,
we talked about this. This is just like
Friday, folks. Right. We built this
liquidity. These balls are now trapped.
We're coming back down into this shelf.
Bulls might defend this. So I'm down to
like tiny size. How we act here? Like if
we reject this and do this, then we can
add back on any reclaim of this. Then
there's no more shorts for the day. All
right. So this is why I think I forgot
his name. Was it Jonathan Johnny? I
think we were in alignment. We ignore
this and you know I wait to see this
pattern here. Previous day point control
value area high. We played back inside.
This is point control. We cover some
well most of it here. Um we see if we
respect this. If bulls respect that then
I'm done with shorts. If we sell through
this then we do have potential
continuation down into these 930s.
Really good. Really good.
So the next level I'm watching 170. I
haven't got enough size to cover anymore
now. So we just have to wait and see if
we keep watching and just move stop down
with it.
Beautiful. Beautiful. Beautiful.
Beautiful.
Let's go.
Okay. Cover point here. I would say if
you haven't taken any yet,
if bulls don't defend this, then we're
not back inside yesterday's range and we
can look for expansion again.
I'd be majority out here. We can always
read adding back in, right? Can always
add back in if it confirms.
uh watching bookmap here. This was the
level I've got that white line. This is
where they got trapped earlier. Okay.
So, just be aware of this. Remember, we
talked about this earlier. All sellers
are caught under here. So, I would say
you want to be majority out here because
we know underneath this horizontal line
I gave you earlier is where all the
sellers got caught. All right, so they
might well defend this line here. We
don't know. All right, we can only do
what we see on the chart. We don't know
if they're going to be able to defend
this, but what I would say is I would
not be a new money short under this
level. I'd be covering into this level.
And hopefully some of you have caught
this with me. I'm down. I haven't got
enough sides on here to do any damage.
I want to see this flush now. Otherwise,
I'm going to take it off.
You got to give me a reflush. Otherwise,
I'm covering all here.
Don't want it to print back above 57.
That's where they just tried to sell
that last candle. If they print back
above 57, I'm just going to cut it all.
Yeah, I'm out. Out there. I can always
jump back in.
So, a smaller trade, but a decent trade.
Decent trade that
are looking for long. I'm I'm not
I'm not looking for long. I'm staying
short bias until it proves otherwise to
me.
Thanks, Alex. Pass my buffer without TPT
on the last trade. Hey, nice work. Nice
work. Nice work. So, I've given you
probably two two bangers short side
today. Okay, I gave you the long if you
really really wanted it, but like I
talked about, I I don't like those
longs. I think they're very risky. Much
easier to stay protrend. All right, much
easier to trade this, isn't it? When we
trap volume into the key level, there's
the red box. There's your lower time
frame algo. All right, Mr. lower time
frame algo. There's all the buyers being
like, we're going to go back to highs.
And there's me going, [\h__\h] you. All
right, so just play what's in front of
you. All right, you don't want to be
long up here above this, right? They
would needed to base out and do it. They
couldn't. This is the bull trap. This is
the EMAs. This is VWAP. This is losing
everything. This is into shelf. If they
puke this now after knocking Alex out
and come straight down to here, I'm
going to have to find a way of getting
back involved. But we're back into range
for the day.
Remember, my thought process now is
we'll probably just rotate in here,
right? So, we rotated up, rotate to the
midpoint. If we get stuck here, maybe we
do this, maybe we do this. But I don't
can't really imagine we move outside of
this range now.
And if we are going to move outside of
that range, maybe we come down for that
naked point of control. But I don't
really imagine we move outside of this
range for the rest of the day.
Where was my entry? Uh, let me find it.
I started entering underneath that cell.
Delta 37's got a tiny tiny feeler on. I
entered hard at 28 once that big buyer
came in on the tape and got stuck. So
and then I started covering. I'd never
got I never got big size on
cuz for me the low hanging fruit's gone
right
trying to protect this note. That might
be it. It might well be it for the day,
folks. 20 minutes left. We'll have to
see. Maybe you get backside, but
they're going to make this tricky now.
So, if they fail this, maybe they offer
this, but it's much harder now because
they've built out this block. Whereas
here was the first retest up here,
right? That's the first test. That's the
trap. That's the trade inside. Maybe
they do this. Maybe they do this. I I
think they just rotate now. For me,
there's probably not another trade setup
today. Unfortunately, the easy trade
setup was that first one I gave you this
morning. It was the failure above value.
That was your money trade. That is an
okay trade. It's not bad. It's not as
good as this though, is it? But it's not
bad. And think about this. Why did I not
want to be long bias up there? What do
we talk about the reprice on the fib?
Right? Bang into the 61. Boom. Fail. You
had 61 value area high. Big level to
come and test back into confluence for a
potential short. just had to wait for it
to break down. Fails the lower time
frame algo. Traps the buyers at the
highs. We see the buyers get caught on
the footprint. We see them trapped up
here. You see the shift in delta, right?
You see them get trapped up here. Here
you go. You see the buyers get trapped
up here. Right? This is all aggressive
buying. We shift and they become sellers
and sellers and they just got caught
again here into 70. Right? So if we get
a breakdown here, you've just got a load
of new buyers. Just got caught here into
70s. We are trading into the level.
remember where these trap sellers got
caught this morning, right? So, I just
be aware of this level, right? This is
probably your balance until you find
acceptance beneath this.
Really nice. I'm out of this now,
unfortunately. [\h__\h] me. If they go to
90s now, I'm going to have to find a way
of getting involved.
Really nice. Uh,
why
why do I need to announce it? Are you
kid
I'm going to be really calm here?
Did I or did I not tell you what I was
looking for up here?
Did I or did I not tell you what I'd be
looking for? Did I not Did I Did I not
say if we leave volume, I'm going to be
looking to sell back down into this
range here. Did I or did I not say that?
Okay, then what what else do you need me
to say? Do you want me to hold your dick
while you go for a piss as well or or
shall I just tell you where the bathroom
is?
Come on, guys. Like, I literally g I
gave it to you. I can't click the button
for you.
No, no, no. I didn't say two different
things to cover myself. I said if we
base above here, it's a long. If we fail
under here, it's a short. Because the
market can always do two things. It's
what it does that matters.
[\h__\h] me, man.
Crazy.
all day. I even had a discussion with
Johnny. I think it's Johnny who might be
new here. Johnny was saying he doesn't
like the longs. And I said, I know I
will call the longs, but I don't like
the longs. I'm going to wait for this to
pee out. I think this is exactly the
same as Friday. I'd be looking for the
retracement just like Friday. I
literally talked you through. I've shown
you so many times.
I can tell when it's a newer trader
who's just like wants a signal. I even
basically gave you the signal other than
say saying to you, "Sell right now. Sell
right now. Sell right now." I gave you
everything.
It's upsetting, man, because I feel like
the amount of free education I've given
you for the last two hours, you will not
find in most courses. You will get
charged thousands of dollars for what
I've given you in two hours here for
free. And I'm getting questioned. Like,
it's
it's bonkers. It's bonkers. But that's
the internet.
That's the internet.
All right. Aggressive sellers trying to
step in here.
I'd be very, very careful. Like I said,
this is where shorts got stuck at the
beginning of the day. If aggressive
sellers try again and they don't get
their move, they're going to get caught
again and it would be the second time. I
would not for me all edge has gone now.
All right. Sellers got caught under here
like we talked about. We've shown it.
buyers just caugh caught up here. Here
is the edge of your day's rotation. It's
very possible that they rotate in here
for a bit. I don't know if they want to
come down here or come back above here.
The edge has gone for me. We've played
the two trades. There's the first one.
There's the retest. Like I said, I said
a million times, if this happens, I will
respect the structure we've created. If
this starts snapping without me, the
only other way I can get involved now is
if we come under here and we back test
this to stay heavy for this trade.
There's no other way of me getting
involved right now.
I didn't get enough size from up here to
hold it up, unfortunately. I'm being
very careful because Ninja's been a pain
with me this morning.
Yeah, one minute chart, my friend.
I understand that I have two days I
stumbled on this channel and I'm and I'm
effing learning. Nice, dude.
Yeah, I mean I can see validity both
sides, but for me I wouldn't be long on
a day where we're leaving value, right?
Personally, I would not play the
retracement longs. We're leaving value
just like Friday. We're leaving value.
And the target for leaving value right
now is down here, right? Same target
I've had for weeks. If they leave value,
this is where we go. Let's just like
remind you of what's happening right
now.
Here is your two weeks balance range.
Right? On Friday, we left value. On
Monday morning, we failed to get back
inside value. We are testing down. We
are looking at value created from here.
Right? This confluence area. This is
where I think they're trying to get to.
I would be very careful about being long
biased today. It's not to say that you
can't find a scalp for like that counter
trend play, but I would be very very
careful. It's probably the hardest trade
in the book on the hardest environment
to do it in right now. You will have to
lean on lower time frame shorts being
stuck. You need to maintain these guys
stuck. If they become unstuck and you do
this, this thing will absolutely puke.
I shorted
497 but got out way too early at 450.
That's still 50 points though, man. It's
Yeah, I mean it's still pretty good.
It's 50 points is pretty good. I would
say pretty good. 49. What did you say
you traded at? 497. Oh, are you on the
other contract?
What's uh where's the other contract?
trading out. I don't really want to do
this, but I'm going to have to look.
497.
Oh, they haven't flipped that yet. Uh,
what is it? NQM.
Is that new one? NQM.
ENQ.
Someone help me out. What's the new
contract?
Why can't I get it? March. There we go.
497.
Yeah. Nice. Look like See, failed.
All right. covered some. You covered
into 50s.
Yeah, you respected you respected that.
I I don't hate that, dude. I think
that's a good trade. It's a good trade.
Could you have held longer? Yeah, but
you don't know whether they find a bid
here. Like, you'll be you got to cover
at least like, you know, 50% into those
levels. I I'm in agreement like this.
Like, like I said, maybe we build out
here, they build enough out here. If we
hadn't done this earlier, this trade
down to here would be easier because
there wouldn't be shorts stuck in here.
But we have done this. So like I'm very
aware how many shorts are caught in
here. Right?
These guys are offside.
Right.
These guys are offside. They didn't get
their cover.
These guys are offside. These guys are
offside. These guys are offside. These
guys are offside. So for me, if I was
going to pin this, I'd be looking at
like the two levels. Can we find
acceptance?
Let's do this like really thick so we
can see it here and
here. Somewhere around here, right? And
where are we trading into?
All right. We're finding a bid there.
It's because shorts are stuck there from
this morning. Right. So you can see in
this level is where shorts are stuck. So
we're finding a bid here. So, I don't
think your cover was that bad is what
I'm trying to say. Like 50 points,
decent move.
Now, we're going to build out volume in
this area here. And how we act here, you
can see we've rotated here multiple
times earlier. We're going to rotate
here multiple times again probably.
Right? This is the difference between in
a thin market. Once we break out of this
earlier, straight up, we fail, we come
back into volume. We can rotate here, we
can rotate here, and it can take a long
time now. And we're getting close to
lunch.
Yeah, I'm still trading zed. I mean, I
I'll have to check if enough uh volume's
moved over to the new one, but uh
probably by tomorrow. It's normally by
Tuesday, but we can have a little look.
Let me have a look. Get it up in here.
Does this update in real time?
Hopefully, it does. All
right. So, yeah. So, more people were
starting to tra trade the March
contract. So, total volume in December
still 760,000,
but you're starting to see like some
more volume coming in the March
contract. So, probably by tomorrow, by
end of day today, it's probably time to
roll over, but we I will check at the
end of play. Probably dump for the day.
I don't use tick chart. I I I played
around with it for a bit. Um but I've
I've moved back off it. Um so I I I have
a 500 tick but I don't really use it if
I'm honest. I just time is important to
me. I know with most volume traders time
won't be important. I I actually really
care about those hourly exchanges and
4hour exchanges and even five minute
bars. Uh buyers just got caught again
there above 60 62s again. They just came
flying in there and got caught. Um
I think you're just going to go into a
bit of a rotation here for a bit.
More than 40% more volume in the new
more new contract. Yeah, like I said, we
just looked at it and we starting to
really push that new contract.
Trying to let these buyers out. They're
going to retest big last big sell delta
was at 84s. All right, 84s. But I think
the edge is gone from the market. For
me, I'd say the edge is gone at the
moment unless they build out a lot a lot
more. I think the edge is probably gone
now.
Alex, this is Oaken. I've traded for
three years and your approach to
combining market auction theory with
volume profile is by far the best I've
seen. Thank you. You're welcome, dude.
Thanks for the good energy.
If we can below 377 PL day on the H
contract and test and break lower, I
like the downside.
Kala, did I say that right? Kra,
I mean, yeah,
for me like I've maintained
where this market wants to come to, I
think, is here. I've maintained that for
a long time, right? based on weeklies.
This is where it wants to come to. And
where are we trading at on the daily
right now? Where's my daily chart gone?
We're just hovering around.
It's really important you guys zoom out
a lot. Right. We're just hovering around
this high volume node which we've
started creating. Right. And we're right
at the mean. All right. So, this is
zero. This is your zero line. Purple
20day. Two standard deviation. Two
standard deviation.
We have this volume node here. And just
above this,
well in this, all right, we have an
untested point of control. All right, I
think the market wants to come to here.
I do doesn't need to do it today. I
think the market does want to come to
here. What I would say now is based on
this yearly volume profile, look how we
have built this low volume node out and
we're starting to respect it. All right,
if we keep rejecting this, then what are
we saying? We're saying exactly what I
said last week on Friday. We're leaving
these buyers trapped. So, we're leaving
this balance range trapped. We're
leaving this balance range trapped,
which means we're probably going to move
lower. Until we reclaim that, I think
higher time frame bullish scenarios off
the table. Yes, there's an argument to
play dips into 9:30 swing dips if they
hold it. But,
you know, if you play that dip and then
Thursday, Friday, Sunday comes around
and that happens,
you're probably going to be waking up
down here. All right? So, just be aware
of that.
Oh, I had it's not ended, guys. Sorry. I
didn't mean to click that.
Scare a lot of you away. Right back to
the top side of this gray box we just
put in.
Hey, Alex, do I need to change anything
on top step for the new contract or
would it automatically do it? Uh, dumb
question. I don't know. Uh, I would
assume top set X will automatically roll
you. Um, I would assume it will
automatically roll you. So, I wouldn't I
wouldn't stress out. But if you want to
trade trade the new contract, you can
probably change it by yourself. I don't
trade on top set, so I couldn't tell
you. Oh, look at the gray box. Oh, he
didn't tell us what to do. Oh, the gray
box. Oh,
um, I'm sorry, but what is the bottom
volume indicator you have on your chart?
Uh, this one here. This is delta. It's
volume delta.
It's showing you delta inside each
candle.
Do I have a bookmap stream on my
Discord? Uh, I don't.
I could leave it up the day, I guess, if
that would be useful for people. I've
never really thought about doing that.
No worries.
And here's the rotation in that grain
box. What did we say? I don't know.
Maybe he didn't give you a big enough
signal. There's the rotation for you
guys who love playing rotations.
But you didn't hold my dick while I went
for a pee pee.
Be nice, Alex. Don't be rude.
Don't be rude.
Man, TJ, I'm with you. I am with you,
man.
There's nothing I hate more. But
I mean, if you like Edge to Edge, it's
pretty good, isn't it? But there's
nothing I hate more than a road, I am
with you, buddy. I could not agree more.
It's the opposite of what I like.
Looks like a head and shoulders. I mean,
yeah. I mean, if they build out enough
liquidity, you could argue it, but like
I said, all I'm saying is in here, this
level here and this level here, they're
short stuck. It really depends if they
let them out. You're going to need to
break away from here. And I think the
better trade really if you want
confirmation would be that. I think
playing in here is very, very risky. It
will rotate. It looked above. It will
rotate. It needs to leave buyers trapped
and it needs to let these sellers out.
The problem is now you've got to
understand what the market's done this
morning. Sellers are trapped here and
here. Buyers are trapped here and people
here are in balance. All right, so
here's your edge where sellers are
trapped. Here's where buyers are
trapped. Here's the balance, right? You
can see it. It stands out. All right,
that's the balance. Until you leave
balance, and I'd say leave where people
are trapped, you're just going to get
rotations.
Do you understand how the liquidity's
been built out? Because if you're just
looking at that and you're going to play
that, you might find yourself getting
caught because these guys need to cover
to get relief. All right, if they're
stuck and they dip down and they're
like, "Thank [\h__\h] for that. I can get
out break even." You go straight back
inside range. All right, this is the
problem. What's the lowhanging fruit?
Previous day low. What's the other hang
low hanging fruit? Previous day value
area low. Have we taken them? Yes. So,
if you're going to play short side, what
are you aiming for down here? The only
way to do that is this. In my mind, the
only way we get there safely is if we
reject here. I need to know that all of
this becomes trapped if I really think
we're going to trade down to there.
There's me giving you
ample education again.
No lie, I totally missed the tra the
trade because of a bathroom trip. Oh
man, I've been there. It happens. The
good thing is that the market's open 23
hours a day, right? So, it will always
provide you with another opportunity.
Like you would have seen me today all
that time Ninja Trader wouldn't open. I
had to email Ryan over there and even he
was like, I nudged him but I can't do
anything. And I got it open. When did it
eventually open? It [\h__\h] opened when
we were down here, right? And I called
this for you. So then I'm on tilt. So I
have to calm myself down. I have to wait
for it to peek out and then I have to
take like a scalp and that's all I can
get. And now I just have to wait. But I
know tomorrow is a new day and we're
going to get another great trade
opportunity tomorrow.
Maybe not tomorrow would be great. Maybe
Thursday, Friday would be fantastic.
Bro, I don't understand how people can
actually troll on this live.
This is like a university course when
the teacher actually gives you the
answer for the exam and all you have to
do is write it down.
Dr. Wall Street, I'm honestly surprised
you don't have a larger audience. It's
because I'm not
I don't fit the
what's the right way of putting it? I
don't fit the demographic. I think if I
was 20 years old and flashy and teaching
you bollocks, you'd they seem to do
better, right? Like
slowly slowly though, I have noticed the
last like month or so it started to like
grow very very quick.
Um
but actually like I'm I'm fine with it
just being slow and steady and a nice
crew.
F my favorite strategy uh Carla is a
multi-timeframe
breakout away from B Friday Friday last
week that's that's my money maker. Yeah.
Like
it doesn't matter which way it goes but
if we have trap trap participants in the
market
that's where where I'm interested.
two weeks trapped rejection we leave
them we play multi-time frame one way
same as we're getting today right can't
get back inside range we're going this
way it's why I'm focused on shorts
okay if we come down here and we base
for a bit and then we leave volume here
we can trade back upside into it then
it' be an A+ long um so yeah same as we
played when we left the shorts at the
highs same as here, right? This is was
an A+ trade for us a few weeks ago.
Volume's all trapped up here. We lean on
it short. We lean on it short, right? We
leave these guys trapped,
right? Which is why if too many shorts
come in, what would be really nice over
the next few weeks if they want to do
the long, I don't know, but if they do,
if they do something like this, be
really nice. If we can leave shorts who
are not respecting this, leave them
trapped. we play the reversal back up.
So that that's it. So the same on what
would that look like if I come up? I got
to come high. So like if I wanted to
play the long, I'd want the higher time
frame to be doing this,
right? And I'd want to play in here on a
lower time frame, which would look like
something like this, and leaving shorts
exposed to go back upside. But I'd want
the pro trend to be up. At the moment
we're doing the opposite because the
higher time frame is leaving volume
trap. So the higher time frame is doing
this, right? And I want to play against
this in the lower time frame which would
look like this. All right? And that's
why I want to join the trend which has
developed higher time frame. I want my
lower time frame, higher time frame to
be in alignment. Which is why you saw me
today say this is probable, but I won't
trade it. I'll let it peak out just like
Friday and play the downside because
this is where higher time frame wants to
play. I want to play in line with the
funds. I want to find a whale in the
market who wants to sell and I want to
get in his slipstream.
I found you on Friday exactly when you
were calling for the massive breakdown.
You earned my views for that. Oh,
thanks, mate.
I need to get a rented Lambo. Yeah,
man. The one the stuff that worries me
the most with with the community is like
the and I'm not on it or I have an
account, but I don't I've never used it
is the Tik Tok stuff. um these like
kids
don't know what they're talking about
and that
you just want that I just worry that
you're getting 18 year olds
doing stupid stuff. You might as well go
to the bookies and chuck it on the
[\h__\h] horses honestly with what what I
see being done. So, seeing this gray box
of rotations happening, we're going to
Oh, I didn't realize it's lunch. Let's
do a giveaway, folks. Sorry, I got
distracted there. Giveaway time. So, so
sorry. Let's give away an Apex account.
You guys have been great today.
Hopefully, those of you who were, you
know, upset I didn't give you a signal.
Hopefully, I would suggest you go back
and rewind this video. Re-watch this
video, right? Watch it on 2x speed, 3x
speed if you need to. I gave you the
signals. I told you what's going to
happen and where I will look to trade. I
might not say I'm buying now. I'm buying
now. I'm selling now. I'm selling now. I
shouldn't need to say that. All right?
I'm telling you before it happens.
That's the difference.
I don't have a laptop, mate. Um I I
trade off a off a big desk. Yeah. So I
custom built my PC last year. I built it
myself.
I'm not down. I'm not I'm honestly I'm
not down. I just I don't want people I'm
not down at all, guys. I'm good. I'm
good.
How many screens do I have? Uh, well,
technically five or four in a bit. So, I
can tell you over here I have We'll do
the giveaway straight after this. ES spy
and normally QQQ, but I have it on Tesla
today because I feel like we're on a bit
of a one-stop market. So, I've got that
on my eyes and the VIX. All right. And
then I also have I can switch between a
uh five minute footprint, a 30 minute
and and the VIX and the daily. All
right. So I can switch between them.
Over here I have what you're watching
this the NQ1. Then I have the five
minute underneath. Then I have my hourly
or 30inut chart and a daily. And then
when we start the day I have this five
minute chart as well and a daily
underneath this. All right. And then in
front of me I have my Ninja Trader which
is on a on a one and a five and a 30.
And then I have my bookmat. And then I
have the stream here.
Uh, right. Let's do this giveaway.
You're banned from Apex. Oh, no.
Let's hope you don't win then, mate.
Uh, set this up.
Uh, I never think you need like lot lots
of monitors. You just need like
enough to feel comfortable. Too many can
be overload. Like I think if I wasn't
streaming, I wouldn't even need this
many.
Um,
thanks 911.
Okay, so just type it once. All right,
FZT. That's the code that you need to
use for Apex and 90% sale. Type it once
in chat and we will give away a free
Apex account.
I don't trade crypto.
I like I might invest in it. Swing trade
in which case I just do it on Coinbase.
But I I don't actively trade crypto. One
of you asked that. I just saw it pop up.
Give you guys a couple minutes to do
this so you can see. Hopefully even now
you're learning to spot the rotations,
right? Thick volume, rotation, thin
volume, trend or trap, trend or trap.
You only need to type it once, guys. All
right? If you type it two or three
times, it will just take you out, right?
Just type it once. Spamming it won't
help you. It pull you out. Automatically
pulls you out.
Like 30 more seconds and we'll pull the
winner.
No, like I I met I haven't got any
family in Australia. I messaged uh
friends over there who were actually in
London luckily.
Thanks, bro. I learned more the last two
streams than in the course for $3,000.
E, that's nice to hear.
Indie. Yeah. Yeah. No worries. Just
here, mate. Right. So, I change this to
ticks per row. If you want it number of
rows, set it to a th00and. If you do
ticks per row, I do it to two. And then,
uh, style, I just move it over to right.
Width, I have it at 20. Value area up
blue. Um, up volume and down volume
gray. Value area blue. That's it. That's
all I do.
Okay, let's pull this winner.
Roman Roman F5T6K,
are you here? Roman,
I don't Yeah, I don't have a laptop,
mate. I I I use a desktop for trading. I
did say it to you. You probably missed
it.
Nice. All right, Roman. Congratulations.
Um, shoot me an email, please, Roman.
info@flzonetrader.com.
Just send me a uh screenshot. I'm just
going to make a note of it now.
Send me a screenshot of you logged into
your YouTube. Okay. So, I can see that
it's you. I'm going to make a note of
your name, FT
6K, and I will sort you out an Apex
account. You can use it for any side uh
size that you want. You've got till
February to use it, I think. So, no rush
if if you're already using it.
No, Roman's here. I can see Roman's
reply. Congratulations, mate.
Right. So, those of you that are
interested, I will leave you with this
today. The I wasn't going to talk about
it today, but a few of you asked. Um, so
the course is now on sale,
right? The new course is now on sale. So
if you go to
volume and order flow of course right if
you're interested you can buy this here
uh
if you use capital launch
it do this for me
of course it won't
right come into here
launch in capital
will get you $100 off all right
so if you are interested if you like how
I trade today. If you haven't done the
beginner to advanced course and you're
interested, I would advise that you do
that so you get a good like 20our basis
on what's going on. If you don't like
how I teach, you're not interested in
doing the course, don't do it. There's
absolutely no pressure for you to do
that. All right. Um,
everyone from Discord, I'll see you in
there this afternoon. I'm probably going
to take a little break for a bit. I'm
not convinced. I'm gonna be very honest
with you. All right. I'm not convinced
we get a whole lot this afternoon. We
don't have any news. All right. We've
done the move. The move really was from
here to
here. And this was a bonus. All right.
So, we've done the main move. That's the
move. I don't know if they really want
to let this go today for that. And
unfortunately, the RR there is not
great. It's not bad. What would we We'd
get 100 points out of it. It's not bad.
So, what I'm going to do,
you can do it with me. I'm going to set
a price alert for
two levels. All right. So, I'm going to
do
uh current
value area low. And I'm going to set
another price alert for
low of day, IBO. All right. IBL.
All right. And if we tag those, I will
get a notification on my phone and I
will run to my desk. Uh, I'm not going
to trade the upside, so I don't care.
This can lift as much as it wants. The
more it lifts, the better the trade
becomes for later in the week. That's
fine. I don't want to trade the
rotation. All right. I'm not interested
in trading the rotation in here. I'm not
interested in trading the rotation in
here. The only trade I would be
interested in is this trade back down
into this. All right. And then once we
do that, I'm interested in longs. Not
today. I mean, once we do that, I'm
interested if higher time frame
participants come in and look for the
longs. So, that is what I would be
looking at for the remainder of the day
for those of you who are interested.
What are you guys saying here before I
go?
The only one that gives you access to
Discord is the beginner to advance
course, the 20our course, right? That's
the one that gives you Discord access
because that's how we trade. That is the
basis of how we trade, right? That's the
one to do.
Alex, for clarification, is this
separate? Yeah, it's separate.
Is there a course and then indicators
sold separately? So, if you do the
beginner to advanced course, you get a a
version of this indicator, right? You
get a version of this indicator included
for free. Um, to get everything on this
indicator, there's like an upgrade
price, right?
Lifetime access. Yeah. Onetime fee,
lifetime access. Every everything I do
is lifetime access. No monthly fees,
nothing like that. No subscription
model. It's just you pay once.
See you guys on stream. Love the vibe
and chat. Alex, can't thank you enough,
mate. Second session in and I'm sold on
the course. Respect from Australia. Uh
oh, are you from Australia, mate? I hope
you're good. Are are you over on um
Sydney and Bondi? Hope I hope you're
safe. I hope all your friends and family
are safe. Really prayers go out to
everyone there. Very very sad situation.
Really sorry to wake up to that news
yesterday. Very very sad.
Richard, that green, this green box,
this is a previous uh week. If you go
back to
go back to the week starting Monday the
24th of November, it is an untested
point of control. Go back to the week
before that 17th of November, it is a
value area high. There's a lot of
confluence to say that the market might
want to come there. Okay, there's lots
and lots of confluence. So, I'm just
going to ask ask answer a few questions
before I get off here. Um,
what account size do I recommend for
Apex? What makes sense? 50K is easiest
to pass. It really depends what you're
looking for. 50K is easiest to pass and
easiest to get paid from that. And the
25K, right? They're the easiest ones to
pass.
Uh, I have the app on my phone, right?
So if I if I have it so this the
notifications
uh notify in app in the mobile app. You
see this here hopefully that's shown in
your screen. You need to tick this if
you don't already have it. All right. Or
if you use something else you can have
it hooked to your email or whatever. But
that's how I do it.
If you buy multiple challenges, is it
better to pass them all at once or do
you trade them at once at a time? Um,
that really depends on your success
rate. Are you comfortable as a trader?
How much of a rush are you in? Have you
got proven a proven uh ability to
pass accounts and trade well? If you
know what you're doing, stack them
together. If you know you're not fully
confident yet, one at a time. Why spend
the money doing 20 in one go if you've
not got a proven track record? Because
you don't want to blow 20 in one go. So,
learn to pass one. Watch I've done a
video on it. Pass one, get paid from
one, buy three more, get paid, do that,
buy two more, then buy five more, then
five more, then five. You don't need to
do it all together,
right? So, manage manage your your own
risk. Your risk with prop firms,
remember, is what you invest in that
account with how much you pay for it.
So, if your pass rate is high, you're
eliminating your risk factor.
Alex, does YouTube do commands you can
type in chat? Like for example, if
someone asks, "How do I get Discord? Can
you do a disc?" Oh, that's a good idea.
I don't know. Um, that's a really good
idea, Adam.
I'll have a look at that.
Ragnar Rock Gaming, I passed Fort Apex
today. Hey, nice work, mate. Nice, nice
work. All right, folks. I'm out of here.
Um, like I said, price alerts are set.
I'm going to take a break for a bit,
walk my dog.
get some food and um I'll see you guys
in a bit. Thanks for a great stream
and uh I'll see you all tomorrow
morning. Please don't force something
today. If you caught any of these trades
with me today, ideally you caught the
two shorts,
even if you took that long counter
trend, don't sit here expecting too much
from this market. Okay? Let the market
prove to you what you want to do. If
you've made good money, this is a
casino. We had, like we talked about
this morning, we had like pocket queens
or pocket kings and we played them and
that's where you made your money. Don't
now play with a like a three and a four
or something or three and an eight.
Don't do it, right? Wait until you get
pocket kings. It might not come today.
Might be tomorrow. Very might very well
might not be till Thursday now, right?
So please, please, please, please,
please don't be forcing and giving back.
All right. Peace and love everyone. Use
hard stops. Be kind to each other. All
that good stuff. I'll see you in a bit.