All right, morning folks.
How are we all doing?
>> There we go.
Get that light down. There we go. All
right, team.
Um, well, it's Groundhog Day. It's
Friday and it's Groundhog Day. Uh we're
going to start on the Friday on the uh
daily. Sorry. You can see we still can't
do the overcut on here. All right. This
level right into here.
Market's been unable to come and get
above it. All right. It wants to try and
get above it. It's failed. Why is that?
Because we've got trap buyers and uh
we've now had one, two, three, four
attempts in the last I don't know two
weeks between last week and this week.
Cannot get back into here because all
the buyers are trapped.
Yesterday we had the chance to break
down, right? We came under this range.
We think about it something like this.
An ugly looking version of this. Came
down, missed the 20-day and 50-day,
undercut everything that we've done
since
3rd of December. So, is that the lowest
print this month? Not quite, but
undercut 3rd of December into the low
volume node. Found a bid right in front
of this shelf. All right. I was looking
for it to come that little bit further
down as we know into the 200s. Didn't
want to do it. reversed, came back
inside, came to the top, reversed again.
AVGO came out with earnings last night,
fantastic earnings, uh looking for a
100% gain next year, and then they got
on the call and said, "Yeah, we don't
think our margins, etc., etc., going to
be so good. Credit issue." And wham.
Okay. And that is been the story of this
week because this move was caused by
Why is my brain not working?
Brain's not working. Another semi. I
can't think who it was. Oracle. There we
go. Well, wake up brain. All right. This
move was caused by Oracle. And then this
move here has been caused by APGO. Okay.
So, we're just stuck. It's as it's as
simple as that. All right. There has
been no change. If we want to think
about this, all right, this low volume
node here is resistance currently. This
low volume n n n n n n n n n n n n n n n
n n n n n n n n n n n n n n n n n n n n
n n n n node here is support currently.
And in between this, we have a range
rotation in here. All right. So, this is
no man's land.
Until something here gives, we're going
to continue to get what we've got. All
right. So, we have to assume these edges
hold until proves otherwise. We get
this. Great. We get this. Great. In
here, you're going to get rotation. And
we all know Alex doesn't really play
rotation. He tries to avoid rotation.
Right? So, that's where we're at and
that's what we have got currently. Uh
let's move into the hourlies and see
what's been going on
developing profile for the week. I've
had it on this week because we've been
in a range just to see how we act.
Normally I don't bother with a weekly
development. But as you can see yet
again, all right, yesterday
in the after hours finally broke out.
Did we take the highs? No. We failed up
there. Failed up here. Came back down
inside current week range. inside
previous week range. Came back into the
balance side. Failed to reclaim it. Came
back to point of control. Came back down
to the bottom side. Came back to point
of control. And now we're doing the
dance. It's the same dance we've done
all week, folks. If you're joining me
today and you've joined me all week, you
nothing has changed. You can literally
split this range into sort of two parts.
There's your point of control. And
here's the sort of lower side of it. And
here's the upper side of it. And you can
see above no acceptance, below no
acceptance. So we are doing rotations
really from sort of 725
to 640 down to 525. Right? Those are
kind of the moves. So we fail one side,
back test, back test, back test, flush,
back test, back test, fail the other
side, fail the other side, back test,
back test, back test, back test, back
test, fail the other side, back test,
back test, back test, back test. You get
the point. In here is that gray box that
we had on the daily. All right? Very,
very simple. So, just be careful. It's
Friday. I don't know what they're going
to do. I have no idea what their
intentions are. Do they have some puts
that they need to close that cause a
squeeze? Do they have do they want to go
risk off because they're worried about
what's coming next week? I don't know.
Uh and I don't think many people do. I
think you'll find anyone who's
predicting the market, I don't think
many people knows what's happening.
Otherwise, we wouldn't be in this. All
right. If we had good confluence of one
way, we'd be moving that way finally.
And we don't have that overnight. Let's
just have a little dial and see what
we've seen overnight. Right, the big
thing was the gap down. All right,
again, this market had we closed up
here. All it had to do is hold a
pullback and we could go. But we gap
down AGO call and Asia goes kind of
sideways and then London says [\h__\h] that.
We're not holding this and down we go.
The question now is, are we going to
take out GlobeEx at 700 and find a bid
or are we just simply going to reject
point of control like we keep doing and
come back down to the current value area
low? I don't know. Again, I don't know.
We're stuck right in the middle, folks.
Right in the middle. Let's have a look
at what's going on elsewhere.
Move up here. Go to a five minute. Let's
get rid of that ugly drawing.
And let's just check out the ES.
Probably a bit of relative strength over
there, I would imagine. Less affected by
some of these semis.
Yeah. So, opening up pretty much flat.
We compare that to the Q's
which are opening up on a gap down. So,
ES already relative strength. Remember,
less affected by tech. Um, what are the
opportunities here? Well, it really
needs to hold that gap. It really needs
to hold 890s. All right. A hold of 890s
gives it potential for strength because
we've seen fail breakdown higher low. If
it can hold this, maybe we can start or
at least creating liquidity for next
week for that move. All right, it's
possible. It is possible. So, we have
strength over there by comparison to the
cues. We just have to see how we open.
Dixie started to fail the last few
sessions,
right? Rolling over that sort of head
and shoulders. Where have we gone?
There we go. Right, starting to roll
over or a quasi. Right, starting to see
that breakdown. So, I expect Dixie to do
a bit of a back test here and then maybe
let go. Uh, gold and silver have been
continuing to break out. Gold almost
there. Um, remember silver's on just a
ridiculous pump at the moment. People
overexposed short side on it. BIX
continues to drift down, right? We're
now sub 15. That is usually very bullish
for the market. The only thing I would
say is every time we come into here,
right, this is where the danger starts,
right? So, we can come into here for a
long time, but this is where if we get
overexposed, over greedy. Think about
this. If this is fear and index, this is
starting to get overly greedy. It will
start to flip and we'll see some of
these when we're least expecting it, I
would imagine. Uh, Bitcoin,
well, it's into a key level. All right.
I would say if Bitcoin fails this uh
it's in problems because it will come
back down and liquidate. It needs to
reclaim this to have any shot. Uh not
trading it, not interested. But just for
those of you who are Apple slight gap
down here, remains in range. All right.
Yesterday it washed on uh that Tim Cook
uh announcement challenging uh I think
it was the European Courts over the App
Store and all it did all day was grind
back. So it's a look below and fail.
Back into range we go. You're going to
get the point here. It's everything's
looking kind of the same. Amazon. Well,
that looks messy, doesn't it? There's
your range. All right. Look below and
fail earlier this week. Look above and
fail yesterday and the day before. We
just have to see what happens. Again, no
edge there really. Goo.
Zoom out of this a little bit.
Still has potential for this to be a
continuation pattern versus this. It's
actually doesn't look too bad. If it can
find a bid, potentially it can get
going. Meta
starting to look a bit rough. There's
your box that they must hold. There's
the failed breakout. Failed to make a
new high. There's the short. There's the
turn back inside. There's the retest.
So, I'd be out my short now. Waiting to
see do we develop one of these or do we
develop this and find acceptance down.
So, again, I'm small position in Meta
from just 580s. Just trying to remember.
Yeah, 580 is down here. I'm small long
from here. I'm not looking to sell it.
I've got my stop breakers and I'm just
looking to see what it does in case we
base.
Microsoft
market's gone sleeping Christmas. All
right, that's it. Midpoint of that.
Gosh, not much out here to trade right
now. Uh, same story here on Nvidia. gone
to sleep. Tesla's got a chance to break.
All right, this has got a chance to
break. All right, so we got double
bottom here. There's your pin high.
There's the double bottom. And it's
trying And there goes my belly. Hungry.
Trying to hold to get back upside. Uh I
wouldn't be short on this until you
start to break down and then you can
think about it. Uh let's have a look at
what Oracle's doing. Right, there's the
big earnings news. We're flat here.
Uh wouldn't be long here yet. All right,
I am watching it for a long. I know
we've got a gap filled down to I think
it was 78 or something. Why can I never
remember that? Yes, 78. So, watching
that see if we do want to do a gap fill.
I'm not touching it until then.
Um, let's have a look at those names
which caused the move. Broadcom, AVGO.
Right. So, you can see earnings were
really good. What was the problem was
that was the call. All right. blowout
earnings absolutely ripped it up to 422s
and we've just given back over 10% here.
So have to see how we now this is a key
level for AVGO. If it starts losing that
then you're going to have you know uh
over a month's worth of trap buyers
above.
So we just see uh what did break out.
Well RTY I think it was RTY broke out
alltime highs right watching that. So
that is signaling
right a rotation out of tech
into small cap land. Right? So just keep
your eyes on that
daily huge breakout. There you go. All
right. So really nice recovery. If you
think, oh well the rest of the market's
lagging behind, go and look at some of
the times we've had uh major major
problems in the market quite frequently.
you will see RTY do this Q's not do it
and then all a roll. So, it's the only
thing I'm concerned about. I don't want
to be overly biased anyway right now. I
do want to be um somewhat aware of
what's going on. Um let me just check
move quickly before I forget.
Okay. the 10 year
five. It was the 10 that pullback held.
I think this is going to be a problem.
I've maintained this for a long, long
time. I think this is where the
problem's going to come.
A break over 42.
This is going to be a problem for the
market.
Just absolutely is. and uh US has got a
lot of um debt it's exposed to that it's
going to have to move come early 2026.
So maybe we don't see this play out till
next year. But uh
it's certainly not looking good if that
starts breaking out, folks.
I don't want to have a bias. Not right
now. Right. That's that's what I'm
talking about is macro stuff, bigger
stuff.
Right now, we just got to play what's in
front of us.
All right, might have time to do some
good mornings today. It's the first time
in a while. Good morning, everyone. Um,
Evan, Fall Forward, Mark, Inferris,
John, Dennis. Oh, thank you, John. Very
kind of you on a Friday as always. You
are the best. There goes my coffee and
brunch for the day. Market's getting
weak here, just be aware. Uh, Troy,
Jeff, Clint,
Haley, uh, the Bartell's, Julian, Sigma,
Brandon, Raphael, Noah, Niko, Sylum,
Chris,
Alan, Bailey, um, Steven
Bart,
Marosa, Toby, Green, Sergio, Locket.
Good morning everyone. Let me just post
that we're live on YouTube. Get it out
there to the world. Um, we will do a
giveaway today and uh when I do the
newsletter this weekend, I will try and
put in it um a big giveaway. We're going
to do a big Christmas giveaway. I did
mention it yesterday. I want to give
away some Apex accounts and some funded
next accounts and maybe some courses.
So, we'll probably do three giveaways
over Christmas.
All
right.
Move this down so it's a bit cleaner for
you guys. There we go.
Sorry guys, just making sure my copy is
ready. Okay, how long we got here?
30 seconds.
30 seconds. We're opening uh even in the
cues, we're opening up bang in the
middle. Right by the VW. Bang in the
middle. Um same levels I'd be watching
on SPY if you're going to trade that
today. 88s. If we lose 88s, you're
watching the 85s and 82s. It's been the
same level all week. If we get through
88s, 90s, and then the 700s, those are
the walls, right? So, here's the open,
folks. Let's see what we get.
Mixed bag on the mag again. Another day
of the mag being all over the place. All
right, so Tesla opening up just under 1%
up. Nvidia green on the day, 0.19% up.
Microsoft 0.83% down. Meta 3/4 of a
percent down, Google third of a percent
up, Amazon half a percent down, and
Apple third of a percent down. Just a
mixed bag out there. Complete mixed bag.
Currently sweeping that uh pre-market
low from 655
right here. Mark this out for you.
Right, swept it so far. Found a bid.
Right, big steep cliff here.
Will that roll over pre-market
and just letting this calm down as you
can probably tell.
Okay, lots of big sellers coming in down
here and we haven't moved lower.
I'll be watching that New York open here
as we trade back into it. I'm watching
these levels up here really the previous
week wave control and value area high
from previous day for me it's very
simple can we get over and hold above
those right same as yesterday for all
those wondering once we got above those
yesterday afternoon we traded long in
Discord right once we got above those
yesterday's afternoon we traded long in
discord um I just wait for us to move
outside of this range this is uh this
will be two weeks this is our second
week in a range which is basically
basically uh 466 to
750, right? That's the range. That's the
previous week range. The current week's
range is actually even smaller inside of
that. And we all know once we get out of
range, we will see something nasty
happen. It's always the way
watching ES at the moment. Not able to
reclaim those 900s. SPY coming down to
those 88s we talked about. Buyers
trapped above 70 right now. Sellers
trapped below 40 right now. The rotation
is continuing.
Let this settle down for five 15 minutes
here.
Apple gone red to green just about or
it's closed this gap. I mean, we're not
pushing yet, but Apple red to green.
Google
uh 0.43% up. Nvidia now half a percent
up. Tesla 1% up. So they've all caught a
bid. Amazon, Meta, Microsoft all lagging
behind,
Oracle down just a percent.
It's really the question like can ABGO
and Oracle start to hold a bid and give
them confidence in chips? The problem is
credit right now.
Let me I'm going to have to add a here
so I can just see what it's doing today.
As the day progresses
7% down right now.
All right.
Yes, just missed those lows but came
into GlobeEx finding a bid right now.
88's held on SPY like we talked about.
Came down just underneath it. Found a
bid back to VWAP.
I'm just going to let this play out. at
least get through this first five minute
candle which a minute left. But those
sellers got caught under 40s. Buyers
keep getting caught over 70s. It just
depends if they can hold up here. This
is just a rotation taking place early
morning.
If we reclaim these, it' be interesting.
Nice and calm today. Smash that like
button nice and early for me if you can,
folks. noticed the last few days we have
not had enough likes compared to the
amount of people watching. So, we need
to get those likes up towards 200 today
if we're going to do an Apex giveaway.
So, into this pivot into these 90s
pivots. Finding some buyers. Keep
getting caught up here. There's no
continuation yet. Delta offside at 580s,
but uh comfortably back underneath it.
Here they go. They're starting to try
and slam this now. would probably come
and test the 550s and see if they can
hold a bid there, which they just did.
It's all happening very quickly here
because they are not in agreement.
They're very angry both sides right now.
They are over that New York open.
So if you look at if you zoom out and
look at the current weekly profile, we
are literally trading right at the uh
value area low. Previous week point of
control is just above us as you can see.
So this is current value area low of the
week. This blue line previous week point
of control here. So we're just battling
between all these levels at the moment.
I would love to be long and strong but
uh you know how many attempts can this
market have at 900 and keep failing? You
got to imagine the next attempt we just
run through it. It's been there so many
times. But at the moment we are nowhere
near that. We're over 300 points away
from it.
Tes are really motoring here.
Really motoring here. I think it had uh
over 50s. It looks good. And it's
currently trading at 55. So, it's really
dragging this market up. It's
impressive.
Yeah, big squeeze. Jeez, Tesla's just
absolutely ripping. The next level on
Tesla would be 56.90. Might as well call
it 57. And that would be a big breakout
if we get through that. Then you're
looking at 5877
and then it's off to the races.
Attacking the top side of its range
here. Tesla, it is motoring.
Absolutely motoring. Dragging this
market up with it
into previous point. control VWAP above.
Just waiting to see if we can like
balance out a bit and start to find a
bid if we're really going to do this
rather than just one single squeeze. ES
or spy just failed at VWAP and spies
through it. ES isn't.
So, VWAP incoming, point of control,
big squeeze. Tesla's just broken out.
So, that's still going. That might uh
you might see a pull back on that soon.
Now, it's taking that first lot of
liquidity. And have to see what the
market does in response to that.
Buy looks good.
If we're going to go top side today,
we're going to have to get through uh
sort of the 640 area up here. This is
VWAP right now. Just be careful. I don't
know if you guys got long in that after
I said those sellers are trapped at the
lows. I haven't taken anything yet. I'm
just letting this figure itself out, but
this is we are starting to like really
get motoring here. My only concern is if
Tesla pulls back, this will pull back
with it, which is what we're starting to
see right now. And you'd want really a
hold now of 580s. 586's
um point of control is at 70s. You're
getting stuck at VW, stuck at previous
day point of control. I'll put our
current day volume on here now. Starting
to build out a little bit.
No, it's not what I want.
Okay. So, long as they hold a bid down
here,
market can hold a bid here and reclaim
this. This is the target.
Must hold a bid down there, though.
Tesla going again. So, a resqueeze here.
possible.
Amazon trying to go red to green. So,
the ones really lagging now on Meta and
Microsoft. Everything else looking
pretty good.
Question is, does this pull back come in
and are they able to hold? Yes, still
not through its VWAP. So, seeing some
divergence here across the book to be
careful. So, I'm still in nothing.
Waiting to see if it offers a join long
here.
Some sellers got caught on that last
candle. This is M just going to go
without me now.
Dang it.
Wait and see for that retest of 80. He's
never came. Dang it. Dang it. All right.
So, if you're longing this, you'd be
looking for this squeeze up to this blue
line above you now. Previous day value
high. I was just waiting. Just wanted a
bit more of a retest down here. Maybe I
was too greedy. Was waiting to see this
build down into here and then scoop that
up.
The last lot of sellers got trapped into
around 96 in here. So they held previous
week. They're not getting through
previous day though for that move there.
So maybe I'll get another shot at this.
I want to be careful now because it's
just squeezed out.
Lots of buyers getting aggressive here
and not getting the move.
Yeah, absolutely correct. Whoever said
that same trap zone as yesterday, it is.
It is. We're still in yesterday's range,
right? There's the top of the range.
There's bottom of the range.
Oh, move that. And we're going to need
that.
Can we develop some sort of higher pivot
here is the question. Can we develop the
higher pivot over this and use this then
to come and attack this? And if we get
lucky, we close this gap. If we fail
this, then everything's off the table.
We're a little bit thin under 96 down to
78. Just aware of that. There you go.
So, that happened literally as I said
it.
We're a little bit thin. Gone. Oh, we'll
have your thinness. Thanks very much.
Okay, so I'm just going to wait this out
a second.
Came straight through that point of
control on the session. Back to be what?
Oh my days.
This little low volume node now here
becomes important as you're over under
Just checking the news today.
10:00 a.m. Wholesales
Goulsby at 10:35. Right. 10 a.m.
Wholesale is worth being aware of. Okay.
Heaviness coming into this market.
So they failed to get back through those
point of controls. They had the ability
to put in a higher low. They haven't
been able to put in that higher low. So,
no dips available yet. Starting to wash
down. I'm still flat on the day, folks.
Like, no trades here. There's nothing
going on. Just waiting till I see
something I like.
Let's wait and see if we'd come into
here and put in a high low. We haven't
done that. All we've done now is had a
failed breakout up here,
failing to regain point control. And if
they lose this, then we're going to come
and revisit value area low.
So the rotations are continuing.
I don't use range charts. No, I don't
use range charts or tick charts.
Do I know if you can copy trade across
firms like Apex TPT at the same time?
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, you can.
This is very rare that firms don't allow
it. I think trade day was one that
didn't, but like everyone else allows it
pretty much.
Manipulation. I mean, I just think we're
in a a rotation. I don't think it's
necessarily manipulation. and we haven't
moved a bubble below a swing point.
Personally, that's how I would read it.
All right, just remember with if we zoom
out and think about where we are,
right? This is the previous week range.
This is the current week range.
We can't get back above the current
week's point of control or the previous
week point of control. We're coming down
to the current week value area low. If
we lose that, we come down to
yesterday's value low. If we hold that,
we come back. If we lose that, we come
down. We're just going like remember at
the beginning before in the pre-market
if you were here I talked about going
from level to level to level to level.
That's what we do in range rotations. We
just test one side, test the other. Test
one side, test the other. That's why
it's very hard for me to want to get
involved. Like I said, like if we come
down and we base out and we hold a dip,
I'll and I see something interesting, I
will absolutely play it. But it's not
what I'm seeing right now.
The blue is what and the gray is what?
Uh, blue is value. That's your current
value area, high, value area low. This
is outside of value. This is developing
though. So, this will build as we go on
through the day because we're only what,
15 minutes into the day. This is your
opening range low coming up here, folks.
The buy and sell indicators, they're the
flow zone pros. You can get those on my
website if you're interested.
I would be somewhat careful trading. uh
they are momentum players and trend
players. So be careful trading those
when we're inside a range though, right?
When you see them going up and down, up
and down, up and down, I kind of tend to
ignore these. Once we get into a trend
though, they're fantastic.
Like yesterday, they were really
powerful once we started breaking out
or even the breakdown last night.
This breakout yesterday once we got long
really nice even this long end of day,
right? So really good once we're in
breakout territory.
Okay, testing this low again.
Feels like we're going to sweep, but uh
feels like and does has not been
matching recently.
Where's spy trading into 88's on spy?
Remember key level 88's on spy. We lose
that. Um yesterday 87s was important but
I'd say 85s unless they uh move the gaps
levels 85 82s 88 9700.
Okay so holding bottom side of this
range we're probably going to go out and
test towards 70 now failing that New
York open that blue line on the chart so
far. This will become key as you're over
under. You can see how ugly this is
getting. If we develop liquidity here
it's possible right if we develop
liquidity here and hold here it's
possible that they rotate this. Can't
rule that out
again. Still flat for me. Just waiting.
We're still inside that opening five
minute candle.
Tesla is trying to build out here.
Starting to break down here now. Some
big sellers coming in at those 35s
though being absorbed.
trying to break down. It's a big delta
level here at sort of 34 standing out.
They get under that, there's a potential
flush, but at the moment they keep
getting absorbed down here.
Tesla is trying to go the other way.
It's trying to build a 5minute flag for
a breakout on Tesla.
And if it does that, it might drag the
market up with it. We will see.
Lots of selling at these lows, folks.
They keep reloading the selling at the
lows and they're not able to move lower
yet. They are trying. They are
desperately trying to move lower here.
There's the attempt again. Lots of
selling down here. Market orders flying
in. There we go. They finally getting
their break. Here's the move outside of
your opening range. Now, the question
is, can they get continuation? They
won't want to lose 40s. All right. If we
reclaim 40s, all the shorts down here
will get stuck. The rotation can happen
down to here if they really want. So,
they're looking to sell versus 40s for a
rotation lower. If they lose 40s, they
will be in problems.
Can they snap down to that value? That's
not breaking out yet, so it might give
them a chance. So many shorts piling in
here. Can they get a continuation? Here
we go.
So, first little scout. Big delta there
at at 300 at 500s. Be very very careful.
That's massive seller down there. He's
twice now he's got trapped. There's
someone on the tape down there
absorbing.
So I wouldn't want this to revisit uh I
wouldn't want this to reclaim sorry 40s
all the time. We're under that possible
continuation but it's all sellside delta
here. There's definitely absorption
happening versus 500. So watching this
now as we come back into the 40s. Do
they sell this in front of 40s? If they
don't, we're going straight back into
range.
And the selling really started at 47.
So buyers tried there and failed to
reclaim 30s and 40s. Now you're going to
get a lower time frame battle. There's
absorption at 500, but 40s becomes the
key level for me. I'm watching. Tesla
trying to break out as well at the same
time. Just be aware of that. Tesla
trying to do a fivem minute flag
breakout. It does that might drag the
cues up. Rest of the market's gone red
other than Tesla. Rest of the market's
gone heavy. Tesla's the only one. 250 or
58% up. Rest of the market is all red on
the day
and test the I really want this to come
up to 40s and show me
back to these 500s again. He's just
sitting at 500s trying to absorb Delta
offside down here. If we break that,
we're probably going to go down to 470s.
They're trying to sell this again to
Delta C again here. Can they snap is the
question. Otherwise, we're going right
back up to 40s. So, failed to break down
there so far.
If they snap, we go previous day value
low. If they hold, we go back to the
40s. Back to the 40s we go at the
moment. Or at least back to 20s.
That bid just pulled. So, he's moved
down to uh 487s.
Tesla looks like it's going to break
out. honestly be very concerned about
this that they can do a reversal here if
they want to be really nasty.
They're pushing for those 40s like we
just talked about. If they reclaim that
potential squeezes on 40s to 50s
that be a failed look below not even
getting to value.
That's currently value 65s.
Interesting levels here.
No snap. No push. Tesla's about to break
out here, folks. Be very, very careful.
And that will drag the market up if it
does.
They are bidding lower. It's like they
want to move lower, but they've got a
one-stop market right now trying to drag
this market up. We snap 500s. They've
got to play, but uh
yeah, they're coming to revisit it.
They're trying. There's just so much
delta caught offside down here. So many
sellers caught offside at 500 right now.
So many
So there's 20s,
here's the 30s, and here's the test of
the 40s I just talked about. And there's
Tesla breaking out. So that's why, like
I said, one stock market. It's it's just
how the cues have been for a little
while.
We test 40s now. And maybe if we get
through this, we're going to test 60s,
which is New York Open. Is it New York
Open? I don't think it is New York Open.
Let me check.
It is New York open. All right. And B up
60s. Okay. So, squeezes on here with
Tesla like I just talked about. So, all
that delta offside at the lows
and up we go. And the rotation
continues. No continuation trades. We
had We don't even complete rotations at
this point. We're not even getting down
to complete one side or the other.
That's how bad this market's got.
And there's the New York Open.
Tesla's still going. This is a one-stop
market. It's going to drag everything
else up with it. So Tesla's risk on
absolutely flying right now. Up 15
points on the day. [\h__\h] I don't know
how people trade that with zero DTE.
Absolute psychopaths.
Apple now gone red to green. Nvidia gone
red to green and this is all from Tessa
doing that hard work and spy trying to
trying to reclaim back towards 88. It's
not there yet though.
Not there yet though. And to New York
open we go.
And back inside the opening range.
What a [\h__\h] show this week's been.
Honestly, or the last two weeks
actually. Complete [\h__\h] show.
Is there anyone higher now? Yeah.
So, I'd watch Spy and uh
Why is Tesla ripping? Because he's in a
technical breakout.
So through point of control on the
session, we probably come and test uh
90s to 600s now, which is your value
area high and your 24-hour VWAP and the
lower time frame algo and the previous
week point of control.
So probably up to that other side of
this
and I don't know if they fail that or
not. All right, sweet. Didn't complete
rotation here. Didn't complete rotation
here. Stuck in between. They had the
chance to do this breakdown. They
failed. They had the chance to do this
breakout, they failed. That's the story
of this market.
But at some point, I tell you what's
going to happen. Everyone's going to bet
long here or bet short here, or maybe
not there, but at the extremes, and
they're going to get crushed because
they've got so used to trading the
edges. At sometimes those at some point
those edges will fail because we've been
there so many times now.
Big outlier here at 73 delta wise. Get
above that and it's a potential squeeze.
Looks so messy. Essa still looks like it
wants more to me.
Market's trying to rotate red to green
across the board now. It's trying. It's
not there yet. Nvidia is about to go
green to red though
point control.
Uh I guess question I guess technically
speaking they could try and put higher
low in at the edge of this shelf. Uh I'm
I'm just avoiding this now at this
point. I was interested in playing the
shorts. Uh, but I'm going to avoid this,
right? Because we know in here they will
build out liquidity. If we leave this,
maybe if we leave this, maybe I'll be
more interested. I'm going to try and
avoid this rotation in here for a
minute. We've still got lots of day
left. We've got news coming top of the
hour. We've got three and a half minutes
to get into that.
But what I would say is without a doubt,
Big Delta got caught at 30 and under.
And it really got caught at the low of
day. If I
should really just add a chart here,
shouldn't I? Let me just do this because
it's going to make me easier to teach
you. Where's my delta chart? Print.
Give me a second.
All right. Here's your offside players
down here.
All right. here. They got caught and
this guy and once we reprinted that, you
see this whole candle now stuck. All
right, so these guys are strong sellers.
They're now stuck. And we're playing the
other way
again. Same in this candle. They sold
the lows and they might get stuck here.
What bet did you lose with me last week,
buddy? I don't know what bet you lost.
Back down to these lows where those
bears just got trapped. Still in range,
folks. Still in range. So, if you enjoy
playing edgeto edge, this is your
market.
We've talked about this.
My uh profit factor goes up by avoiding
stuff that I'm
not as confident in doing.
Uh it's a footprint chart, but this just
a footprint chart.
That's what I see on my Ninja, but you
can have it on here. So, if you come up
to here where you have your bars, you
come down to volume footprint, you can
put it on.
Uh, it won't look like that. You'll have
to change a few things. I'll do a video
in the next in the next few weeks for
it.
Update my indicator. What do you mean?
market's gone still waiting for this
10:00 print probably which is coming
was it 10 wholesale wasn't it
wholesale yeah we'll see normally I'd
say unlikely to move the market but I'd
say recently the market just feels very
sensitive
okay es spy can't reclaim 88
keeps failing at 88 the spy. So 87 maybe
was a key level yesterday. What's the
five day at? Yeah, 85 is still the
level. we lose 88 is potent potential
for rotation to 85 especially if we
start breaking these 87s that pre-market
lows by 8650s
new course hopefully will be out next
week bud um and uh bookmaps in
Okay, starting to see some weakness back
down into these levels. This is where
shorts keep getting stuck. It's current
value area low on the day right right
here. They keep getting stuck into this
candle.
I just feel like we want to break down.
Oh, every time I say it, we do this
whip. But is there going to be
continuation though? We know bears got
stuck down here at the beginning of the
day.
500s is what they're protecting right
now.
So, new low of day on ES, new low of day
on SPY. Q's holding up. Uh Tesla are
about to come back to VWAP.
Massive weakness in the spiders here.
Back down to their higher time frame
algo. Huge weakness in the spiders. No
continuation through the lows yet. And
there you go. It's where the bears got
trapped earlier on ENQ. It's gross out
here, folks. So these guys on bit mapap
here at 500 is trying to pin this market
up. Do they get washed in? Buyers just
stepped in here and failed.
So divergence versus ES. So ES now
weaker.
Someone explained that to me when you've
got uh chips being weak. But uh
apparently Tesla matters this much that
we just uh don't respect levels the
right way now on ENQ because one one
stock wants to go one way and that that
just does all the damage, does it? Come
on, man. We can't live in a world where
that's the case surely.
So, do they reject here or we just going
to go full reclaim and squeeze these 87s
now on the spiders like I talked about?
They're going to become key. Is there
any continuation back down to lower day
currently? No on the ENQ. Shorts cannot
get their way. They can't get a break
down under 500.
And they're stacking these 500s. Not
seeing any aggressive bears come in and
snap it down yet. There was a buyer just
got trapped at 35. There is their
continuation now. They've got the chance
to do it now, but they're going to have
to break these 20s. They break 20s,
they've got a shot at it. Definitely
they break 20s, they've got a shot at
those 500s.
Delta keeps coming in here and we're not
moving lower. You can see on bookmark
they keep stacking. I think a flush will
come sooner rather than later. But do
they do absorb the 500s will then be the
next thing, right? Or do they absorb
500s?
You see this player here keeps
reloading.
Refresh bidding between 15 and 500. Do
they fill him though?
Yes is the answer. There's his 15s
filled. Flush coming here. And do they
come to 500s and break down now? New low
day on spy. Will ENQ follow?
Watch Tesla into VW up here. Be very
careful if they bid Tesla off VW up. Be
very very careful. We should complete
the rotation to previous day value low,
but we haven't completed it either side
today. So I don't want to sort of tell
you guys we're going to do it because it
hasn't wanted to do it. But we should
technically speaking come down into here
now.
Just be careful. Tesla's finding a bid
in front of that VWAP. We are L. We've
lost 88. We've lost 87s on spy. We
should go 85s.
Is Trump scheduled? Let me have a look.
I didn't see him scheduled
the 12th.
I haven't got him scheduled.
Gby
Hammock Pollson. That was it for today.
Okay, you're going to get that move
finally. Just be careful. Don't add late
here. Um, this is where they keep
getting stuck. But I think you're going
to get that move to previous day value
area low.
Lots of bears just came flying in here
at low of day again.
Shelf now developed at 18s. Uh if you're
short in this, you've got to be covering
some as you move into this previous day
value. If you get outside of that, you
can hold a runner, but right now it's uh
hasn't even got to value. So, just be
smart.
I think we're going to go 85s on spy.
That is my gut feeling. Here comes
value. All right. Don't be a dick for a
tick. Make sure you're paying yourself
some money here into value as we start
to reject this. Finally, this was the
move we wanted earlier. Finally, we're
now doing it right right here.
We're rejecting this. This is your cover
point under here. We can think about
previous day low.
Really nice. Just had give it time to
develop. Thank you, darling. There's
your value tap. You got to be paying
yourself there. Be very careful. Do not
get caught offside here.
I'll come back to your questions once
this is finished, guys. Let me watch the
tape and I see how we act into these key
levels. This is the edge where they've
been bidding off all week and the
previous week. But momentum is very
heavy here right now.
So for me, I wouldn't really want to be
long until unless we start reclaiming
levels. I always talk about that. That's
why I don't like trading ranges, right?
Because I wouldn't want to be long until
I see reclaim of this and then my risk
has to be down here. I would stay short
bias until there's a reason for a pivot
because structurally we're short bias.
Momentum is downside. We've lost point
of control. We've coming into a key
levels, no doubt about it. But what
happens if we lose this and do this? How
are you going to risk off it? If you
like trading rotation and you want to
front run this long,
do your thing. It's just not how I play.
I think Spy wants 85s. Like I said, once
we lost 88,
Tesla trying to find a bid at VWOP.
Should be very, very aware of that.
Trying to find a bit of VWAP.
Uh what you guys saying?
It should drop now. Is there any news
regarding gold? Uh I haven't seen
anything regarding gold. It would just
be following silver. Silver's at all
time highs. Uh we'll be gold. Remember,
gold is the hedge to what's going on in
the economy. All right. So, we've got to
watch that JPY carry trade that they
will be positioning themselves in gold
early in case that goes disastrously
wrong.
Still think you've got more downside
here at the moment. Retesting that low.
No breakdown yet, but it feels like we
want more downside.
It feels very, very heavy at this point.
Very, very, very heavy. I think you're
going to get a flush here. There's that
little flush. They're trying. Shorts are
getting starting to compiling in here.
If they don't get their way soon, they
will get caught here.
So there's both areas of value taken and
the next level would be previous day
low. So runners now would be here. We
can add back on, right? We can add back
on if we do something like this and stay
heavy. We can play this move otherwise
your runners. Here comes the flush that
I just talked about finally. So I say it
wouldn't be long based momentum is very
uh heavy right now. If we reclaim and
trap shorts, you can think about the
long or that's how I would play it. If
we trap shorts and reclaim, you could
think about the long, but structurally,
momentum wise, we're trading downside.
Tesla's now lost VW up, folks.
Still downside. Still coming downside
right now. So, if you retest value and
and stay heavy here, there's maybe an
add-on opportunity. Didn't even get up
to value there. Or did it tapped it
actually. That's a lie, Alex. It
actually tapped value, right? So, there
might be an add-on opportunity here. You
do not want to see a reclaim of these
levels. If it reclaim these levels, you
want to be fully out because it' be a
look below and fail.
Still melting here. Really good. Still
melting here. Here you go. Previous day
low your target now.
And I tell you what, if we get under
that,
we're going to start wicking out
a lot of liquidity.
And we can look for a move into 300s.
And if we lose 300s, we're looking for a
move, doesn't have to be today, into two
24,920.
Really nice. Heavy, heavy, heavy. Here
we go. Finally, we're getting some
momentum in the market. Finally.
Big offside uh at 44s there. 444s. Big
offside there. Be aware. Think we're
coming for 400s. But big offside bar at
44. So you don't want him to get back in
the money. Continuation. Lovely. Yes,
baby. Yes, baby. Let's go. Previous day
low. Don't knock me out of this. I don't
want you to reclaim. Big buyer coming in
here. Keep him heavy under 17, please.
Keep him heavy under 17, please. Keep
heavy under 17, please. I don't want to
like hold this too much longer. Stay
heavy under 17. Heavy under 17. Good
boy. Thank you. Stop now. Going to move
to 17 cuz there's delta offside there.
Might get whipped out here. Okay, [\h__\h]
it. I don't care. Whatever. I can get
back in, but I don't want to get caught.
All right. Really nice.
Really nice. Really, really, really
nice. We had to be patient. We had to be
so It's very much like yesterday. And I
knew it was going to be like this today.
And like, how did you know? You didn't
know. You didn't say anything. Well, I I
absolutely did. All right.
Maybe easier to join after 9:45 10:00
just like yesterday. All right. Let them
build. Just learn when we open up in
value. Let them [\h__\h] around. Let them do
their nonsense. Once we got the move.
Where was 9:45 10:00? There was 9:45.
That was the first opportunity. Didn't
work. There was 10:00. Did work. All
right. Now we're done with it. We just
wait. If they reject this, maybe they
come for this. If they reject this,
right, this is an area I really want to
see traded into. I really want to see
this traded into. It's an old naked.
God, I can't draw point of control on a
weekly. All right. I really want to see
that traded into, but doesn't have to be
today. Look below and fail will be this.
Okay, look below and fail be this. I
wouldn't really want to long. We're
going to do a look below and fail. I
want to see this. And I really want to
see us claim value on the day. And then
there's a trade up to here.
All the time we're outside of this range
though, there is a possible trend. Okay,
there's a possible trend.
Let's do this. Make this simple. There's
a possible trend if we stay heavy versus
this. If we reclaim it, it is a look
below and fail.
Big W. Yeah, W's in chat if you got that
with me. I'm trying to be a bit calmer
recently. Some of you know I've got some
really nasty stuff going on off the
street, off the uh screens at the
moment. So, it's definitely affected my
attitudes recently. Like I said, I
apologize. I'm only human. I can only
deal with so much. When family matters
get bad, it's very hard to stay calm
here. If you got that with me, really
nice. It's laid out nice and early.
Starting to see a rejection of this red
box
and bulls did come in there and didn't
get that way. So, we have a passive
seller up here, which is what we want to
see. So your target if you're going to
rehit this or if you're holding your
runners, your target now is to here.
Okay, that's your target.
If they reclaim this, I would be risk
off shortwise. Okay, if they reclaim
this,
that is the potential long. But uh I
would rather stay heavy and short on
this today. All the time it's going to
stay heavy.
Have we traded 85 yet? We're not at 85
yet. low of the day on SPY's 8550.
Like we said, once we lost 88, it's
probably going to go 85. Only reason I
said that is just because those are the
gamma levels. I normally don't look at
those, but this market the last definite
few weeks has just been all about those
gamma levels on SPY. I don't know why.
Well, I do know why. It's because it's
all about the hedge. They are very
concerned about what's going on in the
economy, as am I. So, they're hedging
against it using options.
you want to catch a Vshape. The only
thing I'd say, Peter,
um, traders are getting very, how can I
put this? Trying to think of a way to
teach this. When traders get very used
to one environment, the market will
often go the other way, right? So, do
you remember earlier I said traders are
getting so used to trading edge to edge,
edge to edge, edge to edge. Think about
how many traders are buying this right
now being like, "Well, we're going to go
oh well, we're going to go in recovery
because yesterday we did a Vshape for
example, right? Or yes, yesterday we did
a a Vshape off here or whatever, right?
Everyone's going to try and look for the
same thing. It's habit. Look for that
fade. What happens when we try it for
two weeks in a row and then it goes [\h__\h]
you, right? That's my concern right now.
These are not fresh levels. Same as
this. That's not fresh. Think about
we're just going to go to an hourly to
make try and teach this so it makes
sense.
All right, this is
one, two, three times down here. Maybe
it came earlier. We can include that
four times. We think about the high one,
two, three, four times. Right? These are
not fresh. So if that's supply, well,
we've chewed through it. And if this is
demand, well, we've probably chewed
through it. There won't be that many
bids left there. There won't be that
many sales left there at some point. All
right. Once the market's ready, that
will happen. Once the market's ready,
that will happen. That's all I'm saying.
I don't I'm not trying to say it has to
be today. But the market has a nasty
habit of luring you in to a pattern
which like I've seen this I've seen this
four times this week. I've seen it four
times this week and on the fifth time it
goes no. Right? So just be aware of
that. At the moment momentum is he all
I'm going to say is what's happening.
Momentum is heavy. We're outside value
on the day. We're outside value on the
week. We're outside value on the
previous day. We're outside value on the
previous week. This is a potential
momentum play lower all the time this is
being protected. That's all I know.
That's what I know. That's what it's
telling me. This is momentum lower all
the time it's being protected. This is
not a long not a long. That's all I know
right now. I can only tell you what I
can see right in front of me right now.
Hopefully that makes sense.
Where did I enter? Uh I came in
up on Ninja.
Uh we had one trade I took one trade
earlier into sort of 40s 540s downside.
Then I had that first attempt
uh for the breakdown
and that failed. So I was short around
sort of the
20s and stuff and knocked out break
even. And then the next time I saw the
momentum start to come in, I started to
hit it at around 88
93 and then I added heavy on the break
of 67.
And then my cover point, my lowest cover
point there was 17s. Lowest cover point
was 17s.
Can you explain the chart without the
indicators? I don't see nothing.
What do you mean? What? Without this? Is
this what you mean? Which indicators? I
mean, this is just showing you momentum,
right? So, this this is the flow zones
are just telling you momentum. Right
now, we're in a cell. Lower highs, lower
lows, lower highs, lower lows. We are
protecting the flow zones. All right.
So, this should be telling you, I don't
This is why I built this. I don't want a
long. I'm not going to battle against
this. It's another reason why I don't
like trading trading range rotations
because if we reclaim this, all right
then and it does do a Vshape. Let's say
it does do a Vshape, these will take
time to catch up and I'll be looking for
a lower high that might not come in and
might just go flying. But
I I've made money. Don't worry. Don't
worry. I've uh I've pounded into this.
Don't worry. I'm I'm good for a Friday.
I size down on Fridays anyway. I'm good.
And if it gives me another setup, I'll
take another setup. Don't you worry.
All right. Previous day lows your
target.
That that red box holding up really
nice. I'm currently out of this. I
didn't add in while I was teaching. So
maybe that's what you mean.
Watch spying to 85s. Okay. Watch spying
to 85s. you if you 85 will be an under
over you lose 85 on spy 82 is the next
stop you lose that 80 is the next stop
there wasn't much gamma to the downside
I can't imagine spy going underneath 82s
because the whole market will lose a bid
if it does that so
we're getting close to potentially the
edge of range unless we go risk off I
will give you a readout on the market
though so you can understand how the
market or the mag when I say the market
shifted so we've moved into a sell
overall in an equally weighted balance
we're now down 0.1 18%. Tesla's the big
winner today, but now it's only up
1.96%. It was up well over 3% beginning
of the day. We traded high of day, 463
on Tesla. We're currently trading 455
under VW up. If it makes a lower high
here into VW up and starts rolling over,
market might get really weak. Big if.
Um, let's look across the board. Nvidia
0.18% down. Microsoft 0.63% down. Meta
0.76% down. Google half a percent down.
Amazon 1.22% down. Apple 0.12% up. AMD
1.98% down. AVGO that's now 9.75%
down. That would be SSR. Went over 10%
down. Oh, Oracle is also SSR today. That
was well over 10% down in yesterday.
Right. All right. Found uh no, Oracle
was SSR yesterday. Found a bid. Um so
yeah, some weakness across the board in
tech. Um, the reason we took a bit
longer to flush than the rest of the
market was literally Tesla holding it up
because we got to remember the mag are
60% of the cues, right? Or even more
than that now. So, when you have
something with relative strength, it
just holds it up. So, we've talked about
this the last few days on stream. It
gets really easy with the cues when the
whole of the M go red. Like, if Tesla if
Tesla was in a red day today, guys, we'd
be [\h__\h] puking. We'd be absolutely
tanking.
Okay. So, you can see they're trying to
walk this down. There's a seller at 500.
He's stayed up there at 500. He's moved
some size to 480. Didn't get filled.
Tried to move down to 460. He's now
trying to chase it a little bit into
440s, 455. Juggling around.
The last two candles before this one
were positive delta. If we cannot break
above the high of that, those buyers
will get stuck. There is a big outlier
delta right here at 44s
and we should be able to see him. Here
he is 43 115 lot buy side all the time
we're below him but 443.5
then a buyer there's a big buyer stuck.
All right. So they need to get it above
that player and they're not able to do
that right now. So, if you look at my
VPD on my uh tape, we can go to here.
You can see this player is stuck. All
right. If you just focus, has it moved
to map? Yeah. What did I just say his
level was? Where's that 100 lot? Here he
goes. Look at these guys offside here
now. So, 444 is a huge buyer who's
caught 453 lot offside. And above that,
there's a 100 lot. Where's the 100 lot?
Here he is. 458 and above that there was
some more.
So yeah, 444 is stuck currently with
massive size. All right, with massive
size. So this guy here and this guy here
are stuck. And this guy and this guy and
this guy. So if we were going to draw it
out on here, these are your overunders.
These are buyers stuck in the market. So
I don't know if Miguel's on here with me
yesterday, but we talked about this
together, buddy. We see this guy here as
well. This is the big player right here,
right? See this big bubble here, 427
lot. So all the time we're under this,
these buyers are stuck. They become
supply. We break down lower. We reclaim
that. We go the other way. So I don't
know if Miguel's here. This is the
lesson we went over together last night.
That voice note. There you go. There's
the breakdown. So just playing the
continuation in front of you. Don't
guess what's happening. Learn to
actually read the tape in front of you
of what's really happening. Makes a big
difference. There you go. Big breakdown.
So, did that make sense, Miguel? Based
on our conversation yesterday. Sorry,
I'm giving priority to one of my
students here, but it's important. Does
this make sense? Right. Exactly what we
talked about like the higher time frame.
And remember the voice not said on the
lower time frame. Think about all of
this. How many green bubbles do you see?
All these green bubbles. Do we get a
back above them? No. And now we sell
them. We use their stops. They just
stopped out here. All right. So, all of
these guys used the low as the stop. So
this is why we got a big sell here
because these guys become a seller down
here and this becomes your over under.
Now 440 to 470 is your overunder on the
lower time frame range, right?
Oh, he doesn't know what he's talking
about. I'm just going to wait for all
these [\h__\h] comments to come in from
ICT traders.
He's a scam.
[\h__\h]
Yes. Sit, Tyson. Nice work, my friend.
You're natural Libra now. Okay, now I
see who you are. Okay.
Maybe I'll change mine to King King King
Scan.
All right. So, we're going to come and
test this area where the buyers were
stuck. All right. So, the big delta
level is 444.25.
So, 25,444.25.
All the time we're under that, sellers
are in absolute control of this market.
So, we can put a line on here if it
helps you. 444.25
right here. All right. All the time
we're under this, what should we do it
as? Like this little pink line. All the
time we're under this, sellers are in
control. But we get above that, we're
going to let buyers out.
Mr. Smart Bollocks.
All right. So, that's your level to risk
off. Uh I wouldn't be long. Uh by the
way, if we just reclaim that, I'd wait
to reclaim value. All of you guys who
are desperate to get long, I don't think
today's your day. But if you're
desperate to get long, ideally what
you'd like to see is previous day low,
this green. If you are desperate to get
long, this is what I think you want to
see. You want to see this, this, this,
this, this, this, this, this, this,
this. All right. And that is your long
trigger up here once you take this out.
But I would be very skeptical about
looking for longs. If we're on a Friday,
this is what I now know. This is where
my brain is. It's a Friday. We failed to
break out of the highs three times this
week.
Uh earnings report have been good but
we've sold. Guidance has been bad.
Everyone's worried about tech.
We're in a sell. No reason to buy it,
right? You don't need to buy weakness.
You want to buy strength. So, previous
day low coming up here for you. You guys
still short. There's your target. All
right. So, make sure you're covering
some here.
And uh well, now we really need to think
about next levels down. And to do that,
I want to take you back to the daily
chart. All right.
This is where we're trading into this
low volume node. We talked about it this
morning. If we lose this low volume
node, the high volume node starts at
340. 50-day is at 324. 20-day is at 241.
And the big level for me to trade back
into is uh what did I call it? The 900.
Yes, it's down here. All right. This
naked PC, if we lose this blue box, I
don't think it happens today. But just
in case, this is the trade that I want
to see happen. I don't know if it
happens today or if it happens next
week, but we lose this. This is one of
the biggest magnets you will ever get in
a stock market. All right, it's an
untested weekly PC. So, if we don't do
it today, we're going to do it on week
three, which means what? Think about
what we're starting to see. All these
participants, if we start breaking down
and holding these, these guys will
become trap volume. We will use them and
we will sell their pain down to this
point. All right, so this has not
changed. I've maintained this stance all
week. It's why I got very pissed off
earlier in the week when everyone was
saying, "Oh, it's very obvious bull
trend and I was like, it's [\h__\h] not."
And saying that is dangerous. So, but
we're into a potential
cover point here and you just should
just be runners only now unless we start
to really flip these zones. So, unless
we get under the if we get underneath
blue and we reject blue, then we're
coming to here. All right. So your only
trades left now for shorts are
if we get underneath this and we reject
this ideally with a two-leg then you can
think about this. Ideally they save it
for next week. I'll be honest. It' be
really nice if they just save that for
next week.
All right. So all of you should
understand what's going on. I've done my
best to teach it in a u
easier way to understand. Let's say hope
hopefully it's helping.
Hopefully it's helping.
Still don't feel 100% you know postco.
Nice TJ. I love to see that. Today I
made 23,639
on Apex account. I won here. So, you got
a free account from me and you're about
to take your 1K payout tomorrow.
Love that. I absolutely love that.
Congratulations.
Really nice.
Really nice. All right. So, I'd say a
few trap sellers coming in down here at
65s, but uh you know, momentum is
downside. It remains downside and you
haven't reclaimed previous day low yet.
We you haven't reclaimed value or
anything like that. Momentum's heavy.
You have taken the lowhanging fruit. We
are into this. Remember this right here
is that potential daily low volume node.
It's a high volume node outside of
value. It's basically in the gap for
those that care. It's in the gap between
Monday the 24th and Monday the 1st. If
you look at the gap between um value
area low and value area high there,
that's what we've traded into. But it it
is absolutely a low volume node on the
daily we just went over. We start losing
93s. We've got liquidity at 200s and
then we're going 900s. And it can happen
quick. I'm not joking. It can happen
quick. I really would like them to save
this for next week. Really? Ideally,
they save it next week.
Are you I'm not even ask like
what are you talking about then?
I'm not I'm not giving anyone like that
valid validity.
I've made it super clear.
All right. So, watching into the low of
this box. You got to be covering some of
the low of this box. And if we lose this
previous week low is at 193s. You can
think about that. But I'd really think
that we can maybe go down to the 900s if
we start getting really heavy today. It
will be a complete meltdown if they do
that. So, look at Spy now underneath
85s. It's lost 85s. We're going to go to
the 82s. If they lose 82s, it's good
night, sweetheart.
It would be nice, Peter. Um,
the 900s is uh what I think this market
really wants to get to. All right, we're
into the low of this box, right? So
there's a value area high from the week
of the 24th of November. All right. So
we're trading into that value area high.
If we lose this, we're going to go
search for value inside, which means
we're probably going to come for the
900s. If we lo if we lose this,
remember, it won't just be a break. You
need a break back test. Stay heavy.
Initial balance now set. Major puke
here. Tesla giving it back the whole
day. Coming back to previous day high
here on Tesla. It's given back its whole
day.
It's whole day.
All right, I tell you where you had huge
sellers come in was 59
59 360 you can call it. All right, huge
sellers came in
360 top of this box. All right, so they
tried to defend the top of this box
which shows how important these levels
are because this is where sellers came
in. They tried to defend it. became
sellers and we're trying to hold the
bottom of this box. All right? So, this
rotation here is going to become
important. If we reject this, reject
this, reject this, we're going lower.
This is a strong trend. So, I said to
you guys, I wouldn't be bidding this
market today.
Chris took my first ENQ trade in May.
Today, I finally cleared the TPT buffer.
I have my first payout. 1,500 coming.
I'm not going to lie. I'm going to cry
right now. I can't thank you enough.
Hey, Chris. High five, bud. High five,
bud. I love I love to see that. Love to
hear that.
Taylor, what's the meaning of the blue
box? If if you see a blue box, it's a
possible area of demand. It's like if
you're in a short, it's an area you
should be starting to cover some of your
positions. If you see a red box, it's a
possible area of supply, right? Those
boxes can flip. Okay? So, a zone will
flip. So, if we drop below this, right,
I would expect this to become red and we
stay heavy. Right now, we're trading
right to the edge of it. You can see how
important it is. We're finding a bid on
the previous week's value area or two
weeks ago, previous week value area low.
We just went over it, right? You guys
got to learn this here. This is where
we're finding a bid. Here's the volume.
Here's the previous week. It's actually
two weeks ago. This is current week,
previous week, previous week. Right? So,
from dating back all the way back into
here, right? We're trying to find a bid.
If we lose that, like I said, this is a
naked point of control. This is where
the market will rotate to. Anyone who
read the newsletter, which is completely
free, you will know these levels. You
should have them marked out on your uh
charts, right? I give these out for free
in the newsletters. What I'm looking
for, what the areas are to be defended
and why.
How do I draw the boxes?
It's just a rectangle, mate.
Just draw it on like that. Is that what
you mean? How do I literally draw it?
I'm not If I'm not understanding it,
just say.
Yeah, like we said, those big sellers
are at 360. Exactly right. Whoever just
said that, spot on. That's where they're
looking to defend the 360, the top side
of the box. If they don't defend this, a
squeeze back upside is on. Come and test
probably this area here. All right, this
guy
right here, right, is a level of
interest for a back test if they reclaim
360s. But in these 360s, we had uh look,
if you look at the tape, look at this
guy here, 626 lot sellside. All right,
so sellside delta
626 lot. We're now above them, right?
Which means everyone below is now stuck
as a seller. This is why I give it to
you. So, reclaim blue blue box. Watch
previous day low. If we squeeze through
previous day low, they're going to get
some relief to 433s. This is still not a
long for me. There's nothing in here as
a long for me personally. All right. You
for me personally, like I talked about,
you would need to take this liquidity
and come back inside this and defend
this. And then really, you want to
trigger would be that to there. I mean,
you are in a strong sell day. So, I
don't think there's a reason to be long
today. Personally, that's how I would
treat it.
Nice. Good work, folks. All you guys
passing making money.
Do I trade as well? Yeah, I've been
trading like I'm
I'm up. All right, I'm just waiting now.
If we get a nice deep ret retest, I'll
I'll think about adding back in. But
it's a Friday for me. I'm just nice and
easy size down on a Friday.
Alex, that concept that you showed on
bookmat or stuck buyers, that was epic.
Is that you teach? Is that how I teach?
Is that what you mean? It's all in the
It's all in the new orderflow bookmap
course. It's all like, guys, that's
it's just different ways of looking at
it. That's all I'm ever looking at.
Whether you're using orderflow, whether
you're using bookmap, whether you're
using candle structure, that the whole
principle of how a market moves is based
on who's stuck. That's literally
how the market moves.
Okay, sell is still in control. So, no
reclaim above that 360 peaked above it.
No reclaim of it. No close above, no
hold above blue box. Right? Notice you
are not seeing this. All right? You're
seeing a poke and a fail.
Right? If bulls are going to do this,
they've got to do this. And your long
would be on a reclaim. You don't want to
be long down here because you will get
flushed out on.
Right? If you're desperate to be long,
it's got to go and rebuild. And I'd be
very careful because for me any long
today will be counter trend. Why?
Because we're outside of value for the
first time this week. We're rejecting
value. Yeah, we've taken previous day
low. Whippy-doo. I know what you're
going to say. Low hanging fruit's gone.
But the draw can easily be down here. So
any long today, you know, unless you
reclaim this, right? Then this is
probably a counter trend which gets sold
into until they prove otherwise. That's
how I would think about the market. So
if you're long today, you counter trend.
I don't like counter trends. I try and
play protrends. I'd rather let this
squeeze out, right? Imagine we get loads
of bulls, chase, chase, chase, chase,
chase, two leg, fail, slam back down,
cover some, run us for down here just in
case it wants to do it. That's the kind
of thing I would prefer to look for.
Holding for naked PC. I mean, if they
get it today, what will that move be?
Let's see if it's actually realistic to
do in one day. Where did our closing
price from yesterday to?
Possible. It's a 3% move. Seen weirder
things. Where's the New York open?
Somewhere around here. Where's my blue
line? Yeah,
2.41% down day. It's possible. It's not
actually that much, is it?
It's a lot, don't get me wrong. 2 to 3%
is a lot, but it's not like it's a 10%
drop in a day is what I'm trying to say.
It's possible. There's validity to it.
It could happen. It could happen. Okay.
SPY retesting 85 here. This is a big
overunder for SPY. Remember, if it
retests it, we can go on a reclaim
squeeze. If they resell into this, then
I think 82s are very, very much possible
on SPY. So, these are the levels you
just had. Buyers just came flying in
here trying to support this bid for an
upside move now.
And where did we say these guys were
stuck? Where was the
I thought I put pink line on the chart
if I deleted it.
Have to find him now again. That's
annoying.
Zoom out this. Oh, he's way up there.
Okay. So, I'd be watching it into sort
of 425s,
425s to 460s, 470s. And you'd want
sellers to defend that max. Okay. Here's
the retest of previous day low staying
heavy. This volume node now staying
heavy.
Sellers came flying in here. 450 lot now
caught at 50. So, just I would just
personally I'd just let this shake out
for a minute. Let it shake out for a
minute. If you're looking for the follow
on short, I would just let this shake
out for a minute. You got a bit of a
battle developing here. Previous day
low. A big seller just came flying in
here and got stuck. Okay, this is your
volume node. If they reclaim this node,
this is potential resistance to here,
but it's very thin, so they might just
skip straight up to here. These are the
levels that I'm interested in shorting
versus. If we reclaim those shorts go
out the off the table, and we'll
probably go back into rotation. So, I'm
going to wait. Can we squeeze through
this little area here? Can we do like a
two-leg
through the low volume node. Right?
Either sellers defend this or we're
going to go straight squeeze to here.
And this area here I'm interested in
selling against.
Right? That area there. Chris, just a
small thank you for sharing your
knowledge with us. I'm looking forward
to 2026. Hey Chris, super proud of you,
man. Great work. Thank you. That's very,
very kind of you to uh
pay for my lunch for the day. You and
John, very very kind. Thank you.
Which one indicator showing previous
week value area high in New York VW
previous day high previous day low? My
one just showing volume profile and
value area high. Uh this is the flow
zone indicator. This is the flow zone
pro. It's available on my website.
Right. So if you want all of these
that's on the website. No pressure to
get it. I'm only telling you because
you've asked before someone says that
I'm selling hard.
I'm sure there are some if you just want
the daily levels, I'm sure there's
something out there for free. But, uh,
if you want all everything in here,
GlobeEx, opening range, initial balance,
daily levels, weekly levels, momentum,
flow zone, cloud, deep float, pull black
clouds, higher time frame algo, lower
time frame algo, and sentiment. Then
just grab it on my website.
All right, I'm going to get a coffee. I
will be right back.
Right.
What we doing, folks? Just building out
liquidity now. All right. The market's
taking a breather now.
Market's taking a breather. It's still
bearish. All right. Look, if we just
think about this, very, very simple. Can
we reclaim previous day low? No. Have we
reclaimed momentum clouds, flow zone
clouds? No. Have we got back above this
shelf? Have we reclaimed this low
volume? No. No. So for me, any build out
here is bearish. All right. Any build
out here is bearish. But you can just
really build a bare flag and and let it
do whatever it needs to do. Ideally,
you know, two plus leg pullback. Where
is my channel? Do I have one? Let me get
rid of it.
I'll just draw it like this. All right.
No, it's not what we want. Sorry, folks.
Let me try and help here. Right.
I don't really want to be a new money
short in here. Do I remember this is a
high time frame level. It's been on here
for two weeks now. This level. I don't
want to be a short in this box. All
right. I would much rather see this
market move out of this.
All right. Maybe into here. Maybe into
here.
and then offer a short here. Or if it
won't do that, if it's a nasty market
and it just does this and fail, then we
need to wait for a return in for a
continuation. All right? So,
if you're learning anything from here,
it's the important of the higher time
frames, right? It's important of
understanding when we're leaving value,
when we're searching for new value.
Remember, this market has been in value
in here for two weeks, right? Rotation,
rotation, rotation, rotation.
Eventually, it went [\h__\h] no. We don't
like the price up here. We need to
search for new value. That's what a
trend is. It's search for new value. The
moment it's found some validity here
because it's building out volume. I know
the most valued area is down here. I
don't know. It comes today. It might
come next week. It might never come. I
think it will come, but it might never
come. And we need to be prepared for
that. But that's the move that I would
love to see. That is also previous week
low right here. So, we're going to also
respect that.
So, the indicators mention in private
created ones. Yeah, they're they're
private. So, you can get it on uh the
website if you're interested. If you do
the course, uh you get a version of it.
Uh they're cheaper if you do the
beginner to advanced course because it's
a big part of how I trade. I don't try
not to trade against them.
Uh what are the other ones that you want
to know, bud? Uh this is this is just
anchored uh volume profile, right?
Anchored off the 930. That's all that
is. And everything else that you've seen
on the chart are just uh weekly um fixed
fixed range volume profiles, right? You
can draw those on. They're for free,
right? They're not uh they're just here.
Is it here? Is it this one? They're
here. Volume based, right? anchored
volume profile, fixed range volume
profile. So that's all these are.
They're just they're not indicators.
They're tools, I guess, is a better way
of putting it. If that's what you were
wondering. If I've misunderstood that, I
am sorry.
So, let's see if this can lift up a bit
here. Spy reclaiming those 85s. Didn't
quite get to 82s. I saw one of you
saying S&P got to strike price or
something. I missed that. So, I don't
know what price that was. Apologies.
VIX did peak out at 16, has failed to
close above 16, coming right down to the
1550s now. And we are into this low
volume node. So sometimes you will see
sellers try and defend this. All right,
but at the moment we might see a retest
of this. If they get through this,
retest this. If we get through this, I'm
not interested in shorts anymore. And
I'm not going to short. What I do not do
is try and guess where the top is,
right? I let it I don't go short short
short blow up. All right, we let it peak
out, right? Ideally, this move happens
aggressively. The slower it is actually,
the worse it is. What you want is
something like this and then that,
right? And you want buyers all buying
here, right? Delta to go high, right?
This delta you want to go high and then
to get stuck and then we use their pain.
At least that's how I trade it. So, this
is what actually just happened now.
Buyers just came flying in here at 94,
right? They literally just claim flying
in at 94.
So let's see if they get stuck. And they
do have bid support at 76 is here. But
they just got stuck there at 94. They
just came. So there you go. Why I'm
teaching it? It's starting. All right.
So let's just see. I'd say big buy side
delta is 94. And if they get above that,
it's 9008ish.
And they are now starting to find
themselves a little bit caught up here.
The problem now is is how we've built
out this volume. All right. Do they
respect this? It's why it's why you want
like a blowoff top and then that because
you use their pain to come lower.
Can I show that on bookm? Uh yeah, right
here.
Uh maybe to put that
these guys right here. All right. See
these guys? 57 lot, 5 lot, 142 lot, 107
lot. And the moment, if you just think
about this as like a little shelf, the
moment they got stuck, boom, they become
sellers. So, we're going to come back
and test them. If they stay heavy again,
if they stay heavy versus here, right,
they've just bought heavy into it again.
If they can't reclaim this range, we
move lower. So if they reclaim this
range, then we're going to try and move
higher and we can think about where
delta is stuck above. So 406s is a big
level. 408 is a big level.
416s is a big level.
They're trying to bid up now. And I
would say we go back to
this
and we're watching 410s and then 430s.
Those are really the levels I'd be
watching. 410s, 430s.
But we are starting to build out
liquidity. Now,
what you don't want to do is be short
above 460s, 470s today, because that
would be a look below and fail, right?
Be a look below and fail, which is what
we've had the last few days.
Okay, so Delta 409's, 416s, 420s.
Who's this guy? [\h__\h] hell, that's
huge.
544s is massive. 544s.
That makes sense in here. I'm going to
extend this out a little bit. I know
he's at 44 just so I can remind myself.
And the way I'm seeing that is
this guy here. Think about how much
buying took place here.
Right. It's this guy we need trapped.
All these guys, whoever was buying here,
that's who we need trapped. They need to
stay trapped for us to move lower.
Okay, we have some guys here as well.
This is all buyers stuck. All right, so
this guy and this guy up here. Oh, we
need to keep them trapped. And if we can
keep them trapped, we can have a go
lower. We need to be aware of where the
shorts got stuck here. 350s. Right. So
if you get short now, the difference is
now if you're going to get short here,
you must cover some into this because
you don't know that this washes, right?
You don't know. So if it offers a short
up here, you must respect these levels,
mustn't you? You don't know that we make
a lower low. So you always pay yourself
now because now you've got structure
where you must pay yourself some and
then your runners for lower. Hopefully
that makes sense. I'm trying my best to
teach it as we go here.
All right. So, if we go back to Bootmap,
we're rejecting that same box. We've
just created more buyers trapped up
there again. They're currently stuck in
that same box we just talked about.
Starting to see aggressive sellers
stepping in here. And if you are now
short, you want to be covering into that
pivot that I just talked about. All
right? So you want to be watching down
into 360s. You must cover some in 360s.
I'm currently short in this now. And I
will take some off into 360s and hold
runners for a flush below. So there's
the See how we instantly hit 360 and
found an an initial bid. Now if we flush
below this, it would be really nice. And
the next level here is 350. That's point
of control on the session now is 350. We
need to get beneath 350. If we can't get
beneath 350, it's a problem. I don't
know why Trading View has PC up here,
but it's actually at 350 now. So, I'm
watching 350.
Nice continuation. And if we can get
under here, there's potential to go
lower.
So, already paid myself a bit into 60s
now. Just waiting to see. Here we go.
Come on, baby. You got to get through 50
or I'm out. You got to get through 50 or
I am out.
Because a big seller just jumped in
here. 361 lot. You can see them on bookm
right here. 380. Here we go. 50 50 50 50
50 50 50 50. They're reloading. We need
a snap now. Otherwise, Alex is out of
this because they're trying to
aggressively sell without the ability to
move low, which means there is a passive
buyer sitting here trying to absorb the
tape. So, I'm out. There we go. And I
can always get back in. And this is how
I trade. Like, if I'm playing
continuation, I can always get back in.
Uh well it it actually is based on tick
volume and delta volume. It is down here
now. It's moved down here
right right here.
Watching this level. You see see how
we're respecting this level. Big
sellers. Big sellers. Big sellers. We
have to get below this. This is volume
point control currently based on delta.
And if we flush this we're going to come
all the way down to here. So here we go.
If they hold this, squeeze back up.
I'm just saying what I'm seeing. If it
doesn't line up with what you're seeing,
uh, I don't know. This is just what I'm
seeing.
You know, you can see they're absorbing
50 50. But it's based on delta, I guess.
So,
it's big level.
Big level. Lose this low day. Hold this
then second leg higher. All right. So
lose this.
Oh, lose this. Come on Trading View.
Come on. Come on. Trading View. Lose
this low of day. Absorb this. Second
leg. One. Two. Possible. Both are
possible. It's why I'm very proactive
when we come into these ranges.
is my Ninja Trader chart. It's a five
minute on a Ninja Trader chart.
The reason I don't have that up all the
time is I can't do things like draw on
here and move it around and show you
what to do. You can see like the
difference between me and other
streamers is I try and teach you as I go
rather than just you can watch the
biggest streamer in the world yesterday
lose $45,000 in the space of 15 minutes
by going against momentum without giving
you a reason why. So, I try and show you
what I'm looking at and why I'm looking
at.
Okay. So, big delta there came flying in
again. We're starting to lose 50s. We
should now really start breaking down
and come and test these 23s.
So, 50s is you're under over now. And if
they reclaim it, then it will be a
problem.
M if you have to choose between Ninja
Trader and Trader of Eate which platform
uh they're well they're owned by the
same so you don't you don't need to
choose you don't need to choose like you
get your accounts on trade of eight for
me Ninja trade is more professional
platform I don't want to be on something
web- based
so get your accounts on trade of eight
trade on your desktop on Ninja Trader
and if you go on holiday or you want to
trade on a laptop then you just open up
Trader 8 and you can trade on there you
So, all right. So, everything playing
out how I just showed you, that's not me
being an arrogant prick. That's me
trying to explain to you how the market
works in certain ways. All right. So, we
rejected low volume node. We came back
underneath previous day low. We lost
this shelf. All right. We trapped the
buyers up here and we're now using their
pain. And your cover points were 50s.
Unfortunately, I got knocked out of
this. I was probably a bit impatient.
And we should now take out low of day.
And your next target would be down here
to 190. You should if you took the short
here, you should have already paid
yourself. Your stop can go at break even
or it can actually go at 50, right? So
your stop now in the money. You protect
versus this shelf. You don't want to
reclaim with that. So if you took any
short here, stop now at 50. You look for
low of dayb breakak and ideally you get
196 and 900. All right? So I don't want
to hear anyone say I don't I don't tell
you what I'm looking at or stuff like
that. I I try and make this as clear as
possible. You show me someone else who
teaches you like this live. This is not
hindsight.
Uh, I'm not going to I'm not going to
say names. You can work it out. Whoever
has the 20,000 people following them
every day. Um,
Gangster Garber 53,21
on TPT. That's a pass, right? That's a
pass, my friend.
Good work. High five.
How do you link other accounts that will
trade the same? Um I Well, you can use a
tra trade copier. Um I use um affordable
indicators trade copier. That's my
preferred one nowadays.
Yeah, I'm live here every day, Monday to
Friday, right? 9:15 Eastern time. We go
through pre-market. I tell you what I'm
looking at, why I give you a review. ES,
Spy, QQQ, NQ, VIX, uh, Mag 7, and then
we talk about any news, any big macro
events. And, uh, that's it. And if you
haven't already, click the link in chat,
uh, that, uh, Nightbot sends for the
newsletter, right? Newsletter goes out
every Saturday morning. It's totally
free. I tell you what happened the last
week, what news, what earnings are
coming up, and the levels I'm looking
at, the big levels that buyers and
sellers need to defend. If you just mark
those on your charts and you trade
around those levels, you'll probably
find that you start having better
performing trades. Because for me, a big
part of trading is trading in the right
levels. Understanding the market is one
thing, but trading in the right levels.
Having the discipline to not trade in
poor levels is important.
You're trading in poor levels, you will
get chopped up. If you traded in those
range rotations all week, I mean, unless
you love that stuff, you will get
chopped up. And big sellers coming in
here. We should break down here, folks.
You should see a new low day. They're
trying very hard to get underneath
initial balance. Technically speaking,
if we get under IB, we can have an
expansion model of an IB, which would be
amazing.
Why did you not sure if you knew it was
happening? I I
Jack, I did.
Go back on stream. I did. There's the
breakdown. I did. I just got knocked out
against 50s.
I don't know if you're purposely here to
be a dick like normal or you're actually
like genuine, but I did. Here's the
breakdown. So, here's the expansion
model. Previous week low now is the
level to come to. Big expansion.
Okay, so previous week low here, 190s.
And if you fail that, the naked point of
control. So, those of you holding for
naked point of control might get it.
Oh, I'm annoyed. I got knocked out of 50
now.
150 point trade. Missed there. Why
getting knocked out of 50 [\h__\h]
So value area low moving lower now.
Chasing the market down. Not me chasing
the market down. The value is chasing
the market down. This is your cover
point. All right. This is your cover
point. All right. There's the bare flag
we talked about. There's the breakdown.
There's the fail of 50s. There's the
move. Next point is here. So TP1 here,
TP2 down here. You do not want to do
anything beyond this. The market, if the
market gravitates to this, fantastic.
You don't need to do anything beyond
that. That is probably maximum move for
the day. Okay.
Oh, I'm sorry to hear that, Willer.
That's Yeah, I mean, you will know I had
CO what, two, three weeks ago. It's
horrible.
So maybe a reprice here, a rebalance
because that was a very thin move.
Buyers have come in here versus 55s. If
they get through 55s, they can maybe get
back up to 310s. If they get stuck at
55s, you might might see continuation
back down to that previous week value
area low.
Okay, so watch these 55s because this is
where these buyers keep coming in. If
they get through this, they can very
well squeeze all the way back to 310.
Remember, this was a very sharp snap.
So, we we need to fill in some of the
participants here who are waiting to get
filled. I would say now any reclaim of
this, do not touch it. But all the time
we reject this, we're still looking for
lower prices. All right, we're in a
trend. We're in a trend continuation.
But if we start reclaiming this, I'd be
done with it for the day. I think the
best moves probably happen now. You
should just be holding your positions
that that you got in hopefully with what
I was calling out. Hopefully you didn't
get knocked out at 55 like I did like an
absolute wally. We have imbalances here
all the way up to 307s, right? all the
way up to 307s.
Thanks, Alex. You're the best. You're
welcome. Thanks, Alex. I'm 1,300 up on
my funded account. I also passed another
email and lovely Jonathan. Great work,
everyone.
Nice. Some of you catching that.
I just talked you through your biggest
NQ win ever. That's awesome. Apex still
on sale? Yeah, Apex is still on sale
till Tuesday, I believe.
Okay. So, what happened at that low?
Right at that low of day, we have 99
sellers caught offside there. All right.
So, 24s, that's where the sellers are
caught offside at 24s.
We have a balance to fill here. Some at
80, some at 92, some at 95, some at 300,
some above that. All right.
So sellers are stuck at 94s and there's
repric higher available. Um but you know
I'd stay short bias unless we reclaim
everything. But right now it's getting a
little bit thin. So you just want to be
a little bit careful.
But I think we can still move down to
that previous week low and then beyond
that to that uh naked point of control I
keep banging on about.
Right. So this green line is ideally
your next TP. Ideally all this is a
build out. There's your TP and then in
here. All right. And that's your
ultimate TP. This is your ultimate TP.
It's where I've said the market has
wanted to come for a long time. It needs
to retest that area. It's left it alone
far too long.
This previous week low. Once we snap
this, I tell you what, I'll put a little
bit of volume in here so we can just see
a level. Right? This is a level. Once we
snap this, this is the cue that we go
here. this gray box
just based this is just looking at the
volume
um really from Wednesday the 26th
I think we're going to move low. I think
you're going to get it. Just be careful
though. This is where these sellers keep
trying to come in here at these 24s I
keep talking about. But they look like
they want it. Uh spy now under 82. That
is a problem for the market. Like I
said, anything under 82, this market can
uh get quite nasty. And SPY is now half
a point under it. And I think you're
going to get the previous week low here.
It's probably a matter of time at this
point. You've got every single bull for
two weeks now trapped above.
I think you're going to get it. What's
that? Level 90s. I think you're going to
get it, folks. Lots of sellers coming in
here. So, just be careful. They need to
get their way because they're piling in
here. I think you're going to get it.
Here we go. Here
we go. Here we go. Here we [\h__\h] go.
Here we go. Right. Hold. Now I'm in this
short, by the way. Now, cover some here.
Runners only now. And if we lose this
gray box, we're coming down into here.
And I don't want to hear any [\h__\h]
idiots on this chat talking [\h__\h] about
me ever again because I'm sick of it.
Gifted. Absolutely gifted.
I said that you don't have to choose
between platforms. Does that mean I have
a 50k futures account purchase on funded
next? Yes, you can switch between trade
of eight and ninja. Yeah, absolutely. As
long as you purchase
any platform on trade of eight, right,
you will always be able to use trade of
eight or ninja trader. They're the same
company. All right. Ninja trader own
trade of eight. They're the same
company. All right. covers into here,
runners. Now, if we get expansion,
fantastic. But, you know, anything
beyond this is an absolute gift. Uh,
spying to 680s. All right. If we lose
680 and spy, when I checked last night,
there were no put walls. They were so
thin. The put walls, I don't think they
expected this move. If they lose 680s on
SPY, it is game over. Game over market.
So, massive, massive levels. You see the
gray box, edge of the gray box. Just
like we talked about the blue box. How
did I do this? How did I do it? So that
you guys can learn. How did I find this
gray box? Why is it edge? Look at this
volume here. All right. Can you see this
volume here? This is a weekly volume
level. All right. It was created here.
Here's the edge of volume. Here's the
lower volume. This is the rotation.
Remember, when you see big volume, we
rotate in here. We might well rotate. We
lose that shelf. We're coming to here,
right? Because we're thin in there. We
lose that shelf. we come to there.
I'm about to get fully out of this on
the runner here, unfortunately. Second
time today, it's about to stop out. As
long as it doesn't stop me out, it would
be nice. I just got caught then again
into 15s. All right, I tell you what.
I'm going to lean against this guy at
24s. We take out 24s, I'm out. That's
where seller is stuck right now.
Seller's not stuck. Sorry. Sell's in
control
about to knock me out. Oh,
there out. Okay. Out on runner. Still
fantastic trade. Still a fantastic
trade.
Okay. So, if you guys are in from 50s,
you can or or above, you can hold this,
right? We talked about if you guys are
in from here, you should have gone TP1,
TP2, you can afford to hold your runner
for down here. Any reclaim of this
though, you're gone. You're done for the
day. Hour left. You might still get it.
What a day. Killer day, folks.
Slux Deluxe, I want to say I am your
fan. I'm glad I found you. Hey, thanks
for joining, man. Appreciate it.
Appreciate the good energy. Previous
week high and previous week low taken
this week. Been a tough work getting
there for me this week. I can't lie.
Yeah, it's that is a market in rotation,
isn't it? That is the definition of a
market in rotation, right? Think about
what that looks like on a chart. But my
feeling now is we're probably in
breakout.
We're probably unless we open up next
week. All right, give you a clue what
the newsletter is going to look like.
Bears are in control. As long as we
close down here, bears are in control,
right? Bulls need to reclaim 470. The
big level of of contested area is going
to be the 900s. Yeah, we start getting
under 900s, bulls are absolutely [\h__\h]
Um, but we can still see a higher time
frame pull back into that. So, let's
just think about
daily,
right? Think about what we're seeing on
the daily. What have we lost on the
daily? The low volume node. Where are
we? 20-day, 50-day. Okay, this is mean
reversion. We're at mean reversion. All
right, two standard deviation, two
standard deviation, mean reversion. Very
well might find a bid here. But the
bigger level for me is the 900s
here.
Right? These kind of guys here, maybe
even eights. This is that old weekly
point of control. We can think about
this even in an RBS, right? Think about
structure,
right? Pullback, right? We expect the
market to pull back into this, don't we?
On a daily. I expect bulls to try and
defend this. If they successfully defend
this and we reclaim, I'll tell you what
I then I'm very confident about alltime
highs and that's probably going to be
next year. But I'll also tell you this,
this was done on no volume and if we
lose this level here, then I'm very
confident that it is night night time
and we're going for a 200 day revisit
at least into here, right? And I think
this will be the 2026 move and this will
be the decision point. So, I don't want
to be too biased because this is
possible and this is possible both on
the daily. And what matters is this
because do they set a daily higher low
and set this up or are we going to see
the divergence? Same divergence we saw
in the 90s, same divergence we saw in 07
where RTY makes an all-time high. Q's
don't and then you get the start of a
rollover and we get that JPY carry trade
starting to happen. I think it's
December 18th that comes into effect.
Anyway, these are all things we went
over earlier in the day on the start of
the show and everything else. Let's just
want to have a quick look at the bonds
and treasuries here. And look at this.
Surprise [\h__\h] surprise. Who's
pushing?
I'm telling you, I keep telling you this
is the problem for this market. All
right, this is a big big problem for the
market. That and the jobs number is
going to cause a major issue.
You know, what do I know? I'm just a uh
small time streamer.
Oh, the last trade. Where did I enter? I
entered once they got stuck. I entered
get up here.
43s
I added at 19s
and I got most that cover off into 93
and then stopped out on the rest might
still break lower. Like I said, I you
lose this gray box. It is a big problem.
Big big big big problem or the market
and same level 80s on spy right
I've got a price alert set 80. So this
will tell me have a look at the VIX. O
again go back to the pre-market show
this morning.
Willow, do I believe the market will
have a continuation down next week? Um,
uh, it all depends where we close and
what levels we've taken out. That's what
I'd say. It's too early yet to say. Does
it have the ability to now do it?
Absolutely. We've left volume, right?
But it really depends where we close.
Do I trade GC? I do not.
Excellent market analysis. Top-notch.
Thank you very much. You, legend, helped
me pass so many emails. Oh, that's
awesome. Honestly, I'd love to cancel
the Santa rally. You might need not need
to. It might be that that everyone else
cancels it. Okay, new breakdown here.
This gray box is key. You can see
they're trying to absorb in the low
volume node on a daily underneath this.
They lose this. If they lose this, your
target is down here. Okay, if they lose
this, your target is down here. I'm
going to put a red line on for that
exact target so we can see it. That or a
white line. That is your point of
control, okay, that we're looking for if
they do lose it.
Which level on spy did you say to watch
out for? Again, the levels were 88, 85,
82, 80s. All right. So, if you look at
this morning, and that's not just today,
it's been the levels all week. Look at
this morning. Once we lost 88, we got a
cascade to 85. We trade under 85, we
back test 85. If we stay heavy 85, we're
now trading, we trade down to 82. We
lose 82, we back test 82, we're now
trading down to 80. If they lose 80,
we're going to go 20 day. We're going to
go 75 and stuff. But I'd imagine they'd
really want to pin this and hold 80. If
they lose that, it's such a big problem
for the market because when I had a look
at the put walls, it was so low on
volume. Everything was cool wall.
Everything was 90 and 700. The volume
below for the put walls was not great.
Do you have a video created on contract
sizes? I do not. I don't think. Uh maybe
on the apex videos. There might be some
stuff. Quick question. Are you looking
for closure below the gray box or a
retest? Yeah, it would need for for to
get a new position in. You mean? Yeah,
it would need to get underneath if I was
going to put any more trade on today and
I'm to be honest, I'm thinking probably
just going to be risk off. I'd need
something like this, right? I'd need
volume built out here. We want to see
like this kind of thing here, right? We
want to see volume built out, a trade
under, rejected it, and go lower. Just
remember, we've taken out a weekly
level. Th this is like an absolute bonus
if you get there. Remember that. That
means we're a 3% down day. If we get
there or if we go from New York open
2.4% down, we measured it earlier,
right? So, I think this is the draw on
liquidity,
but uh you know, maybe they save it for
next week. I wouldn't mind if they did.
If they if they could save it for next
week, it'd be really nice, right?
Because what we could see, let's imagine
market closes like it does now. That
means what I'd be looking for next week
is a trade into here, short side from
here, and a slam back down to there. And
then from here, I'd be considering a bid
up
higher time frame.
Is there a reason I don't trade GC? Um,
no, not really. Like, it's moved really
well, but um I took a short on GC
earlier this year, swing short. So, I
was long
GLL, which is the two times or three
times ETF on it. Um, short side. So, I
was long GL
CGL. I can't remember what it is. I'd
have to have a look at it. Um, but I
just trade NASDAQ. I'm I'm used to
NASDAQ's personality. The whole reason I
left small caps and large caps is I
don't like looking at scanners. Um I
don't want to see
even though I think there's more edge in
in there's way more edge in stocks than
there are in futures uh because they're
way more inefficient. All right. You
don't you like
if if if the cues and spire down on the
day and like you can find a market which
is weak like Nvidia, you know, Nvidia,
AVGO, Oracle today. You just want to be
short those, don't you? Relative
weakness. It's a way easier trade than
than this, but it require requires way
more brain waves. Maybe I should go back
to it. I think I've improved as a trader
so much the last three, four years that
I could probably absolutely smash stocks
to bits. Um,
but for GC, I don't know its
personality. Um, I know that hedges are
just going to keep printing it up. I
know that all the time this market has
under the hood a engine which is rotting
where they haven't put any oil in and
it's about to blow up. Then they're
going to keep bidding up GC.
So,
I don't know. What can I say? I've only
got so many brain waves, I guess, is a
way of putting it. So much I've only got
so much energy.
Yeah, you're right, Zar. You're right.
OPEX next week. You are right. We talked
about that in Discord.
What indicator are you using for volume
on the right side of the screen? I'm
using VR. Oh, uh, anchored. Anchored.
So,
this one here, anchored volume profile.
And then I just anchor it from 9:30. And
you just have to in the settings.
Uh you have to tell it placement, right?
Thank you. The best. Yeah. I mean, it
can be when when she's playing kind,
she's great.
when she's being a little [\h__\h] it's
[\h__\h] pissed me off. There's days like
that when I'm like, why don't I just
trade stocks? It's so much easier. Um,
new here and I love your analysis, mate.
Do I have any content for swing trading?
Um, no, but every everything that I
teach you, um, it works the same for
swing trading. It's just the difference
in in swing trading. You you really
don't need to pay attention to any of
this. All right. So, if we were going to
look for swings now,
um let's have a think about what's
moving today. Uh AVGO. All right, let's
go to AVGO. Right, I'd start everything
works the same way. So, I'd start on a
daily and I'd be like, okay, who's
trapped on ABGO? Okay, very clearly all
I all I need to see is here. All right,
pain point for a ABGO is all the buyers
trapped above here right now. Right, big
gap down. Buyers are trapped. Where's
the big puke? Well, the big puke will
happen under here for a gap fill. All
right. So, we've got higher highs,
technically higher lows, but any return
back in here offers a possible swing
short down to here. Any break of that
fills the gap. All right. And that's
just how I would trade it. And
it would be the same for absolutely
anything. I can show you big swings that
I took this year. Um, so AMD,
all right, my big swing
was
58s, I believe. So, I bought this um
right here. So the same thing we look at
lower time frame inverse head and
shoulders right flag consolidation.
Um, if we move this into like an hourly,
I have to get back to that same level
right into an hourly. You can see here
that we were starting
to liquidate guys under here.
All right, Woff theory. Bulls were
buying this. So, short side came flying
in. Absorption on the tape here. I got
long at 58 right in here and I'm still
long and I sold 80% of it into this move
because it's a ridiculous move. So, if
we just think about this, same thing we
would do. What's the measurement of the
move or what's the expansion of that?
All right, 3x 261. I actually got
filled. So, I'm above that, which was
amazing. And I'm down to tiny size. So,
80% of me is filled here. And I'm just
going to hold this now from here
because, you know, I I don't care. Maybe
we come back and I stop out break even
on it. But, uh, maybe they want to do a
resqueeze next year. I don't know. It's
all the same things. It's exactly the
same things. And the best areas to buy
on are the same levels I always talk
about. It's really you you want
consolidation on a 200 day. Um so if I
go get you on a daily so it makes more
sense. Market's calmed down now. So we
can do this. All right. So if we go to
here like AMD
so you can see where I got long. Look my
stuff's still on it.
My charts are still on it. All right. So
we got back above the 200 day. We were
holding in this Ballinger band. We
created a squeeze. Here's the Ballinger
band squeeze. You see how tight it got
here? Once we do a squeeze on Ballinger
band, we're going to expect expansion.
And because of the type of market
condition we were in, right, we're
looking to abuse these stops. And
there's the swing. There's the trigger
higher. And we can do the same thing. I
did the same on Apple. On Apple. I'm
still long Apple
from 202s,
right? And it's exactly the same from
202. Same kind of thing. Is it 202 or
220? I have to have a look. Maybe it was
220.
August. No, it's 202s. I think it's the
same kind of thing, right? Squeeze on
the Ballinger bands.
Oh, no. It would have been 220 cuz I
always wait to get back above the 200.
So, there's the 200, right? There's the
higher low and long trigger here. Abuse
these stops. And I'm still longing this
because I've got no reason to sell right
now.
Um, yeah. Other ones I took this year
open, I took for the squeeze from 198.
All right. So, this is about as easy
pattern as you can get. Shorts will pile
into this. Remember, my bias is always
short side in small caps. There's a
higher low. There's a hold of 198. And
uh we got long for this squeeze and we
sold up into here.
Really simple. Use these stops. We're
still hold like open's still valid. I
mean that it's a [\h__\h] company, don't get
me wrong, but it's still valid. It's
still holding a higher low here. Like
they can resqueeze this. If they get
enough shorts caught in here, they can
resqueeze it long term. Doesn't mean the
outlook longterm is good. But yeah,
that's that's literally everything's in
the course. It's the same the same way I
treat anything, right? Same way I treat
anything. So I I would love this market
to come back down to here longterm at
the moment. I think a buying opportunity
becomes from Oh my god, going to let me
do it from here. If this keeps drifting
higher, right, that might be a buying
opportunity. If we lose that, then all
hell breaks loose in the market. It's
the same thing. No matter what you're
looking at, market's moving the same
way,
right? Aren't we starting to see a
breakdown here,
starting to potentially lose that gray
box. They are trying to reclaim it over
and over. They know that they're into
low volume node and they know if they
lose this they are in mega mega problem.
How do I join the discord? Oh, you just
got the course yesterday, didn't you? Uh
Indie. Um I will send it to you. I'll
send it to you.
Um but yeah, it's in the course at the
end, but I'll uh let me shoot you an
email now. Hang on. Give me a second.
There you go my friend and just emailed
to you Indie.
Um
I would love it if you would switch to
stocks especially with trade the pool
would be awesome. If I did it I'd just
trade my own account. Um it's just so
like to follow futures and teach and tra
like you see how much
this requires so much of my attention to
do this. Um
that's why I stopped trading stocks
really is because I'd have scanner up
momentum scanner gap down scanner gap up
scanner lowflow scanner new scanner.
Like it's just
can't do that. And futures it's one or
the other. All right. It's going to
break down here, folks. All these buyers
keep trying to step in and they're
losing that gray box. All right, so they
might well come down into here. It will
get really nasty. If any of you are
still holding this, uh, you look really
good. I'm not going to take another
trade now. It's, uh, it's done what it
needs to do for me.
Thank you, brother. Just pass Lucid on
that trade. Nice, man.
Which one do you use on the daily chart?
Uh, so that volume profile is the 2025
volume profile. So it starts Jan, first
day of trading. So it's just extending
out.
It's just extending out.
Hey brother, first time viewer. Love it
so far. Awesome. Thanks for joining,
man. Appreciate you being here. Seems
like we're going to go for 24900. It
would be nice. It would be nice. I'm
just a bit devastated that uh I mean I
got a little bit here and I got a little
bit here, but I'm a bit pissed off with
myself if I'm honest. I got knocked out
of the 50s here. I didn't want to get
recaught on it, but uh you know, so I
had to grab a bit later, but
annoying. Annoying because I if I if I
still had that entry from up here, I'd
still be sat in this trying to let it
work.
There we go. Is what it is.
Can you join the Discord without the
course? No, unfortunately not. There's a
reason for that. It's not to make you
you don't have to do the course, but
it's because I have been in many many
Discords, as I I'm sure lots of other
people have on the in the past. If
you're in like a free discord or a
monthly fee Discord or anything like
that where there's no education, you
will all trade different ways and you
will all just piss each other off and
you'll start calling stuff which the
other person in in the chat's looking at
the other direction and it just causes
confusion. So the way we've set it up is
just for members only who have done the
course and it means that they're all
looking at the same thing in the same
way and can support each other and for
me that cultivates a very good community
who are there to support each other and
I feel like that's what we've got. It
might be a smaller community as a couple
hundred of us, but it's an active
community who support each other trading
the same way.
Yeah, quite exactly, Rosco. Exactly. But
like this week's kind of a good example
like so many of you would have seen me
here all week and last week being like
please caning leave this range. Can we
leave this range? We've got to leave
this range. I don't want to trade in
this range. And eventually we leave the
range and it's a beautiful, beautiful
day. It's so much easier to trade where
momentum is obvious, where liquidity
hunting for one side is obvious. So much
easier than just playing that chop.
Where would the re-entry be? Uh, okay.
I'll have to focus in on this to have a
look you.
Well,
what I'd say, they've already regained
87. I wouldn't like that.
If they start taking out 23s
and 30s, I don't think there's a
re-entry. I'm going to be honest. Uh,
not anywhere down here. So maybe an IB,
they might well squeeze this all the way
back up to IB. You're starting to see
compression down here, right? You're
starting to see compression down here.
They they've had this chance to move.
Remember, this is a level here, but it's
also a level off the uh yearly chart.
Their chance to do this has has happened
and they haven't taken it. It's very
very possible if too many shorts pile in
here and they haven't done this. If too
many shorts pile in and they reclaim, I
mean, they're rejecting the edge of this
right now. If you think about tightening
this up a little bit, if we put one of
these in here, right, they're rejecting
the edge. They've still got the chance
to protect 210s, but I'd say if they
start getting above 210, I would
potentially uh leave it alone. All
right, if they start getting above this
and holding above it, we're thin in
here. I would imagine we come and fill
this into this level. And then how we at
here becomes important. Maybe there's a
re-short there, but we did just take out
a weekly low. Remember, they don't have
to do this today. they can leave it for
next week.
That's why I'm like trying to tell
myself, do I really want to think about
a new money short down here? Think about
where our first shorts were this
morning. 500s outside of range, 460s
joining here, 370s. We're now at 200s.
It's 300 point lower than our first play
this morning.
What are the benefits of Discord? Um,
analysis if I'm trading in the
afternoon, afternoon trades, support of
other traders. I mean, there's no
monthly fee for it. It's just the people
have done the course, so it doesn't cost
anything. Community
Giveaway. Yeah, we'll do a giveaway in
half an hour if we can get up to 200
likes. How many likes have we got
currently on stream? Haven't looked.
We need another 50 odd likes. We get to
200 likes, we'll do a giveaway.
Yeah, we're already 2%.
3 3% is the uh
3% is here or 2.44 depends where you're
measuring it from. I think from New York
it was 2.44%. If it was from previous
day close 3%. So already at 2%
absolutely and you're starting to see
look we're clearing the shelf now. So I
wouldn't be short biased now. It doesn't
mean I'll be long because you're counter
trend but they can start to do one of
these if they really want to be naughty.
All right. They can come back up for
here.
drawn liquidity remains here. It just
depends like if they haven't built
enough remember to get down, how can I
put this? To get down here, they need
bulls. They need bulls involved. All
right, so if they get this squeeze and
bulls get involved, all right, and if
people join here and then they fail up
here, then they use these bulls who are
trapped to move lower.
But right now, if they've got too many
sellers caught here, you might get this
squeeze out and then they will want
bulls to chase and then they will want
the collapse. And it doesn't happen have
to happen today. I keep saying that uh
the easy money's definitely gone into
previous week low.
How do I get the newsletter? Uh just
look at the stuff underneath um the
links underneath in the chat or even
there should be a post from Nightbot
somewhere. Look, if you just scroll up
Nightbot free weekly newsletter, it's
right there. Just click on that. Doesn't
cost you anything. All you got to do is
stick in your email and you'll get it
tomorrow morning.
Do I trade other sessions? I will trade
uh afternoon sessions if there's a
setup. Very occasionally, I'll trade
Gloveex if there's a setup.
Try not to trade GloveX. So, if it's A+,
I will take it.
I bought the course within an hour of
joining the Discord. I made back the
cost of the course because someone
called something out in chat. There you
go. Like, there you go. Beautiful. free
a free education. Chris logging out for
the day. Gonna walk off this dopamine
hit. I can't thank you enough, Alex.
Have a great weekend. Hey, thanks for
joining, Chris. Congrats on your payout.
Happy for you.
Totally. Well, I mean, it it's
absolutely possible. Keeping safe.
Absolutely possible to do that. Alex,
how did I get into trading? Uh
well, one of my best friends was um
at Morgan Stanley that I used to live
with in London and then he left there
and was at Standard Bank. So that was
one of the first ways. My father as well
was at CIBC.
Um so I first started interviewing to
trade when I was 21 22. Got offered some
jobs out in Dubai and in Cairo. I
interviewed at uh Credit Swiss in
London. I interviewed uh with Marwan in
uh emerging markets at Morgan Stanley.
Um and then yeah got offered some jobs
and then my life just went in a
different direction. I ended up you can
listen to the interview with um Austin
Silva. ended up getting into music and
having very successful music career for
about 15 plus years and then came back
to trading as I got older and didn't
want to be in the clubs anymore taking
stupid amounts of drugs and partying all
the time which is just the truth as
well. It's a much healthier life now.
Shorting was smooth today. It was indeed
smooth. It was indeed smooth and
hopefully I kept you lot out of it. Some
of you were looking for longs down here
and I kept saying, you know, momentum's
heavy. I wouldn't be long unless you
reclaim that level. And you will see at
no point today did we do what I said
we'd need to do if you were going to be
long. So hopefully, even if you didn't
get the short, if you were looking for
longs, hopefully I stopped you being
long.
Can I please explain what the course
covers? I'm an absolute newbie to
trading. One month bin. Do you recommend
the course for me?
If not, would I recommend it? Um, yes, I
would recommend the course for you. I
It's probably unfair for me to ask me
because I'll be extremely biased. Um,
but if you go on my YouTube and go to
the course, there is like an advert
there that talks about it all. Um, maybe
ask some of the other guys in chat first
because I don't want to sell it to you.
And if you're I don't know how many
times you've joined me in stream, but
make sure you like how I teach because
there's different pedigogy. Different
people teach in different ways.
Different people learn in different
ways. Make sure you enjoy how I teach
and you understand how I teach or or
you're grasping it. Best way to do that,
go through the free education on my
channel first before you do anything
else. There's a free course on my
channel. Go and do all the free
education first. Make sure you enjoy how
I talk and how I teach. Do not spend
money trying to learn with me if you're
like, I [\h__\h] hate this guy. I don't
understand what he's talking about. I
don't like his attitude. And that's
okay. Like, that's not me saying that.
Like, that's okay. I remember being at
school in university and being like,
"This lecture, this teacher is [\h__\h] I'm
not learning anything because they the
pedigogy, the way that they taught
didn't work for me." So, make sure that
you you you enjoy how I teach first
before you spend a penny, right? Um, and
everyone else in chat who's done the
course can tell you whether they like
it. And maybe maybe there's some people
that don't, and that's also okay. That's
human nature. But it's 20 hours long,
the course. It's not like a
flimsy
course. It's quite in-depth, and I
always advise watching it a couple
times.
All right, I'm going to use the
bathroom. Um, I still think this wants
to break down. They just They had the
This is unfortunately what we're going
to see now. In this gray box, we're
seeing the Oh, don't do that. We're
seeing the rotation. Remember, this is a
yearly profile here. This is a
rotational range. If they lose this,
this is where they want to come. Bull
bears had the ability to break under.
Didn't take it. Bulls just had the
ability to go for a squeeze. Didn't take
it. My bias higher time frame is lower.
I just don't know if we need to do this
first. It's why I'm not going to enter
here. But, um, if you're still holding
from this position up here, you look so
good.
So good. All right. But I'm going to use
a bathroom and I'll be right back.
Oh, you're going to get it. You're going
to get it. Oh, it's night night market.
Where's spy? Under 80s. Oh, it's night
night. Good night, market. [\h__\h] Can't
believe I got knocked out in those
[\h__\h] 50s up there.
Just happens sometimes, doesn't it?
Tesla are about to take out previous
days low. Oh my god. Congrats all you
guys who are still in this uh from up
here. It's fantastic. Fantastic trade.
Uh I think it's worth rewinding the tape
today and talking about what and and
looking back at what we talked about
here. Anyone that likes continuation
trades, I know I fl I fluffed this up
here. I was short and I didn't like the
buying coming at 50s and I should have
just given it more room and just let it
work. Um, so I had to join again later
for a remove down. Um, but yeah. Is
anyone still in from up here? Hopefully
some of you are.
Let me see. Sorry guys. Trying to catch
up since leaving the desk.
Welcome to the team. Super V.
Mr. Osa 315. Wish I found your channel
years ago. You help clarify so much
about the market. Thanks, Alex. You're
welcome, dude. Thanks for the insight in
the market. Appreciate it. You're all
welcome. You're all welcome. Don't go
anywhere. Remember, we're going to do a
giveaway at 9:00. We will do some Apex
giveaways.
Made my loss bat. Nice. Nice. Good work.
You learn a lot and reinforce reinforced
by general trading concepts.
and his course adds more depth and daily
discussions. Lots of people here have
done the course clearly. Richard, yes,
get the course. Recommend the course.
Answer for you, Alex. Course is
definitely laid out for someone starting
for sure. Yeah, it's literally that's
one thing I probably should have said
for whoever asked. Like it is laid out
for someone that knows nothing. Like I
will build you up. That's why it's
called beginner to advance. I will
literally build you up, teach you very
basic principles about the market. It's
it's I think it's over 20 modules so
that by the end of it you've got you
know we put the foundation in so you
understand how and why the market moves
and we build blocks on top of that so
you've got a nice broad understanding
because I think there's too much out
there where people come to the market
and that and this isn't against one one
teaching method or anything else but
they learn like oh this is my setup you
never understand why it does or doesn't
work so you'll never understand then
like the nuances of like when not to
take that setup cuz there's no
foundation.
Thanks guys. Lots of kind messages here.
Random guy. My first time joining your
stream. I love the vibe. 5 minutes in. I
also love the comment section. Took one
trade with you. up 400. My first funded
account which was in $800 draw down.
Hey, nice man. That's awesome.
Techno producer here. I was better with
Ableton than Topep X.
Ableton was never my jam, man. I was a
Logic Logic X guy. I mean, I used to do
my mixes in Ableton, but um
I never used it the right way. So, if I
was using Ableton, I was you always
using it in like the horizontal axis.
I'd never did all the like clips and
stuff. It used to drive me [\h__\h] mad.
But I think it's super powerful. People
People love it. If I was going to start
all over again, I'd probably probably do
that.
No re-entry. Um, oh, it's tough, man, to
think I mean, look, you can think about
this same level here. It's just tough.
Like, you're entering low of day to try
and go lower. Like, it's not it's not
you still got compression.
This guy here is still like you're under
over. Uh let me check on the delta. Um
88s are still 88 and 94 are still big
levels. So buyers are trapped over that.
So I guess 88. Yeah, it's the same
level. This shelf here all the time that
this is being protected potentially
lower. The pro the problem is is how for
me if we zoom out. All right. The
entries today have been here, here, and
here. We're now trying to like we're
trying to get that. What if it doesn't
come? That's all that goes through my
head. Like if in terms of RR, we're
losing RR, right? We're losing RR. And
you want to be careful of this little
nugget down here. Let me just check.
Yeah, there is excess at the low. So I'd
say be very careful of this right here.
Now,
if they hold this, so I'd say your
rotations are between here, right? Now,
this is the buildout liquidity.
That's the buildout, right? You can just
see that on the volume profile. You
don't even need the footprint for that.
If we go to the footprint and have a
look what's been going on the last few
minutes,
you would see just in this there sellers
just caught there. I just saw it. There
you go. All right. So, this is the
problem. When you're trying to play low
of day, you've got everyone trying to
force the breakdown of the lows. You're
seeing absorption here. If you remember,
these are all market orders, right? If
you're seeing all these market orders
flying in and we're not moving lower,
right? we're not moving lower. It means
there's a passive buyer here and the
squeezes can potentially happen. And if
we look to the upside, we want to see
where the buyers are caught to the
upside. So there's a little bit in here.
Yeah, a little bit at 50s
and big selling came in above 50. So I'd
say if it can start printing above this
can probably be repriced. You can see
how thick that was there. If we look
left, yeah, same area. So, this is the
thing now, right? Definitely some
sellers caught down there at the lows
and they can very easily give a squeeze
relief. And we can see this is a proper
imbalance, not a fair value gap, a legit
imbalances right here. It is a fair
value gap, but you can actually see the
imbalance. This is washed out because
stocks got run out here. We're going to
do a lesson on liquidity later in
Discord. We talked about that. Once we
get off stream, let's do it like uh
maybe maybe we can do it straight after
stream. Maybe we do it straight after
stream. Then I get my the rest of my day
free. All right. So, you can see you see
this delta flip. You see this sell sell.
No more selling or lots of selling but
no more available lower and we shift up.
All right, because these sellers are
caught. So we've got an imbalance here
and if we trade through 90s then I'd say
we can come and test 220s.
You can see this imbalance here being
filled in. This is where buyers were
caught. So this is why we're doing a
rotation between these right now and you
need to wait for acceptance outside of
that in my opinion which will probably
line up with there. There you go. So
exactly the same levels. If you think
about what we just looked at the same
levels are the same levels here. So
confluence here. This is what sellers
are trying to protect. This is what
buyers are trying to protect. This is
the rotation within this tiny range.
Acceptance above, squeeze, acceptance
below, probably down here. All right.
Uh,
is my caption wrong? Is it really?
Oh my gosh. Thank you.
Let's change that now before I forget
that people will watch this back and get
confused. Let's change that 12. There we
go.
Got knocked out where I did. Yeah. [\h__\h]
Sorry, man. Sorry about that. It's
annoying.
23 RR trade coming. Oh, nice. So, you're
still in it. Up 225%
on my SOX calls today. So happy to see
the market finally break down.
Yeah,
Jeremiah, your live is one of the best
I've seen in a while. Great education.
Thanks, man. Thanks, everyone.
Appreciate it.
Where do I anchor volume profile? Um, so
if if you're doing it intraday, you want
it how I would do it. Uh, 9:30. All
right. So, I'm interested in 9:30. You
can of course measure out GlobeEx if
you're interested how we trade in
GlobeEx. Then you go from the open of
the new day into 9:30. But I only really
care about where volume's traded. 9:30
onwards. And if you're doing a weekly,
then obviously the whole week. If you're
doing a monthly, the whole month. If
you're doing the yearly, the whole year.
Yeah, I I would agree with you, Rosco.
Like to go lower is lower probability,
but there's still a draw there. The only
thing I'd say is look, look at SPY at
these 280s. It can't break down 280 680.
That's the level, right? So, it might
need to retest 82 and uh see if they
actually want to sell 82 and get follow
through. Remember, the levels on spy
were clear. 88 or 90, 88, 85, 82, 80.
Those have been the options levels all
week, probably for two weeks. So, here
we go. So, starting to reclaim. We're
going to go and test the top of this or
the the red box above. We're going to go
and test this red box above, which is
previous week low there as well. The
green line is previous week low. If they
get through that red box, they can
potentially come and run these stops.
Remember, this is like compression like
we've talked about. All right? So, if we
start doing this and this, all right,
then we're going to get a squeeze relief
to here because all the shorts will get
caught. If they reject this and we keep
rotating in here, and if we do that long
enough and then they get the breakdown,
then maybe there's enough bulls caught.
But there's a lot of if buts and may
right now.
How does volume profile fit into that?
Uh, fit into watch bit which bit deluxe.
Sorry, you might have written that a few
minutes ago and I've missed it.
Vicks wants previous week high so bad.
Uh, where's that high?
Wednesday's high already. Where is that
previous week high?
Uh 44s 1844s around there maybe.
Am I live on YouTube Monday to Friday?
Yes, I am.
So they're fading this top edge again,
getting thicker and thicker and thicker
and thicker and thicker in here.
Remember the the main trade is downside
today. This is the final target it can
hit. The main trade is downside. So, if
you're going to play the long today, if
you're like, I'm going to play it long.
I've missed everything. I'm going to
play long and I'm going to play it on
this. Just remember your counter trend.
Traps can live in here, right? All traps
can live in here. I wouldn't expect it
to get above any of this really today.
Right? If you get that, you get lucky.
But traps can live in there. This is the
main trend today. This is why I'm not I
never play counter trend. I do not play
counter trend in trending markets. We
are actually in a trending market today.
It's the first time. We had the chance
to go into trend a few times this week,
but this is the first day we've seen a
sustained auction outside. So, we're
definitely in trend.
Back to this blue box. Now, do they let
go of this blue box? Now, this is where
buyers are trying to defend like we
talked about. So you can see the
rotation between these two areas over
and over and over and over and over
again. Eventually someone will win.
Won't stay here forever.
Should we do a giveaway team? How many
likes have we got? We're almost at 9:00,
so maybe we can do a giveaway.
How many likes are we up to?
Uh we need another 11 likes.
Let's get up to uh 200 likes and we will
do a giveaway here.
323 of you currently watching. We can
get this up.
Just got an email saying merch store.
Look at that.
They're trying to sell this. They're
trying to be aggressive here. All right.
Have we got enough likes yet?
Yay. All right. Let's do a giveaway.
They're trying to sell this so hard down
here.
They are really attempting to come in
here. And these sellers,
man, if they get their way, I think it
will be it would be so nasty.
If they get their way, it might be so
nasty
flying in their [\h__\h]
Steel absorption
hanging on by a thread this market, I
would say, right now. Right, let's set
this up. Where's my mouse? There it is.
Okay, I'll do two things today. I will
give away a flow zone uh beginner
course, not beginner to advance, like
the introduction course. Um, so it's up
to you guys. If you win it, you can keep
it, you can give it to a friend, or you
can roll on it. So, let's uh
do that one first. So, just type
only type it once, folks. If you type it
more than once, okay, then Nightbot will
just disqualify you. So just try type
course in chat in chat. Type course in
chat.
Just type it once. We'll do that one
first.
So buyers trying to absorb this blue box
again.
And what I'd say now, I'd watch this
little ledge here into 66s because we've
developed tiny little spike here now.
All right. So sellers are going to try
and sell this edge here and force the
downplay. And if they don't successfully
defend 66s, then we're going to come up
back up to 200.
Guys, a few minutes to do that.
So it's just a a small course. It's like
a two-hour course. introduction to
trading. But if you do do the course,
you do get a discount. Um
value of that course is like 99 bucks.
You get that off the
beginner to advance course if you do it.
So there is some benefit.
Couple more minutes.
But map looks intense on NQ. Yeah, it
can be.
There's a lot of orders. It can get thin
and nasty very very quickly. It's why I
like playing just like the bigger
levels.
Don't worry, like if anyone's spamming
like Nightbot just pulls them out. So
like if anyone's typed it more than
once, they don't get to win it. I I did
make that clear.
Okay, going to pull the winner in 10
seconds here.
All right, here we go.
Taylor,
I don't know how to say that.
Breastnahan. Breastnan. Hopefully I've
said that right and haven't butchered
it. Taylor Brnahan, are you here?
Taylor,
Breast Nahan, was it bad?
Breast Nahan, I'm trying. I'm trying,
mate.
All right, Taylor, just shoot me an
email. Uh, the email is
info@flowzontetrader.com.
screenshot your YouTube page uh with you
logged in. I'm going to make a note of
it that you are the winner.
Um send me a screenshot of you logged in
and I will sort you out of course.
Congratulations
and
no worries, man. appreciate you joining.
Let's give away an Apex account.
Don't worry, I I can I I saw him. It's
okay. The bot's just being silly. I saw
him. I got him. Okay.
Free Apex account code FCT. All right.
That will always get you the best price
at Apex. Currently 90% off. Type FT in
just once.
and we give away an Apex account. That
is your code for most of the prop burns.
Anything other than um
take profit, we use code flow zone if
you want to support the stream.
Still holding this blue box, man.
Holding on by a thread. Now coming up to
this little red one. If we get through
this, they're going to squeeze back up
to 200. You can see this is getting
tighter and tighter and tighter. This is
not the one thing I'd say. This is not a
nice uh look for a continuation lower.
This is the opposite of what I would
like to see for a continuation lower,
but we're getting tight. Something's
going to give holding on by a thread.
These buyers
you guys another minute
All right, let's reclaim that little red
node. It's going to try and now come up
490s to 200. If it breaks out of there,
potential squeeze into this low volume
node all the way back to IV is
potential. Has potential. I personally
wouldn't be trading counter trend today.
All right, let's pull this winner.
Erin.
Erin Egan. Is it? Is that right? Eron.
Erin Egan.
Are you here? Erin,
let me know you're here, Eron.
Otherwise, we reroll.
I'm going to give you another
20 odd seconds to say something in chat.
Never had a bot in chat. You guys saying
I'm probably a bot. I've never had a bot
in chat. All right. Well, you were given
a minute there.
We'll reroll this. Sorry, Erin. You had
your chance.
We like people who are active here.
R-rolling. Here we go. Cold strike.
Cold strike. Are you here? You don't
need to type it again, guys. We just
reroll it.
There we go. I see called strike.
Congratulations. There you go. You are
here. So, just shoot shoot me an email.
Same thing as before, right? Shoot me an
email info@flowzonerader.com.
Just send me a screenshot of you logged
into your YouTube and uh I will send you
a free Apex account. You can have any
size you want. You've got until February
to use it. So, if you don't want to use
it straight away, you don't have to, but
you've got until February.
Awesome.
All right, guys. We are at lunch and
you're seeing that relief now starting
to play out. Okay, so finally buyers did
not let them come underneath this blue
box. So when we call these sellers were
stuck here, they had one more attempt to
move lower. They didn't. Buyers
absorbed. They took this little red
block out. We come up to this red block
now. And any relief over here is likely
to come back up into this. Right. we can
repric some of this low volume up into
here. So, I would say shorts now are off
the table. My expectation would be
potential squeeze out here. It wouldn't
necessarily be high and then maybe
there's a short back up here. Maybe you
can think about a short uh as we get
into some of these nodes here, but I'd
say most of the damage has been done for
the day.
So, the long here once they held this
and I said if they take this red line
out, they're going to come back to this
one. And if they hold above this now,
then they can repric into here. I'd
expect bears to defend this level here.
All right, especially we've got both
VWAPs. By the time you get there, you're
going to have everything in one place,
right? We can move this to red. And um
I would say once we get up there, I
would expect bears to defend that level.
If they fail to defend that level, well,
then they're opening themselves up to
get caught in a squeeze, aren't they? is
through previous daily low. If bears
can't defend
this under here, all right, bears need
to defend this. They want to do this,
cover some runners. If they don't do
that and they get caught here and it's a
fail, look below previous day low and we
will trade back inside range. I will
absolutely pray to the ENQ gods that
that is not how today finishes. All
right. I would love us to say close any
any close under here is good. It doesn't
need to close down here. I'd actually
wouldn't mind them leaving that for next
week. But if we can just close around
here for the day, fine. And like build
out a range here, fine. Because then we
have a range to play come Monday for a
breakdown underneath, which would be
fantastic.
Uh I think that's probably it from me,
folks. Um sorry, catch up on chat. Quick
question. when we've broken down below
previous week's value, do you just go
back to the last week that was in range
that we are trading into? Yeah. So, it
really depends where that week is. It's
a good question, but yes, effectively.
So, you look for the last area of
support and resistance, right? So, if we
look at what we've built here,
just think about value since October.
So, we're looking basically three months
worth of value. Make sure you can see me
in screen. All right. So, why was there
supply up here? Because we had we spent
a week up here, right? And we failed
under it, right? So, we know buyers are
trapped up there. They become our supply
level into 900. We spend a week moving
away from it. The next week we spend
inside. So, we now have consolidation.
All right. So, we move point of control
down, down, down. Value is moving lower,
but we create an inside. Once we break
outside of this, we're going to see a
liquidation event. There's the
liquidation event. We move value lower.
The next week we hold the old point of
control. We move value higher higher but
we get stuck in this same box. Right?
This same box is the problem. Market
does not want to let out these buyers.
That's the big problem right now. So now
that we failed
two weeks worth of value,
right, we failed previous week and on a
Friday we're failing current week.
All we're ever going to do is look left,
right? We can never look right. It'd be
amazing if we could look right. Magic
eightball. We're only ever going to look
left. So, if we look left, if we think
about this red box was at one point
blue, wasn't it? Right? Because we're
thinking, well, the market might pause
here. It might come down to the old
value area high and find a bid. But it
didn't. So, if we come back up and we
reject this red box, what are we saying?
We're not willing to move back outside
of this value. So, if we're going to
rotate value from Monday the 24th, that
whole week from Monday the 24th, where
are we going to go? Well, if we lose
gray box, remember there's a little node
here, which is why it's singled out
right here. If we lose gray box, so if
we come to red and we lose that and we
lose gray, we're going to go naked point
of control, which is also the week
before that value area high. All right,
so this is why I want to watch this
because this is a confluence level. It's
two levels. It's a value error high and
a point of control. Both of which are
untested. I think we're coming down
here. It is a matter of time. Today,
next week, I don't know when. It's a
matter of time. So, in answer to your
question, yes, you always look at the
previous week's value or not necessarily
the previous week's value. The last the
last closest bit of value because I'll
give you an example why I say that.
Imagine we had this and then for some
reason we had this down here and then we
had a gap up week here, right? And then
we had a void in here, we'd we'd respect
this level, right? It's not necessarily
the week before. It's the next week to
retest. And the fresher it is, the
better. All right? So, the fact that we
haven't retested this is important,
right? Because once we left value here,
this is our first retest of this value
area high. Never retested this. It's a
fresh level. Fresh level. Which is why
on the lower time frame,
I would want to see bears defend this
level here. At the very least, defend
this. But really, we'd love to defend
this.
This area here must be defended by bears
for that rotation next week. Please,
next week market because I want to get
off the off the stream.
Look at you guys. You guys are in Alaska
and Australia. 4:00 a.m. for you guys.
Oof. Oof.
Yeah, no worries. All right, guys. I'm
going to get off the stream. Um those in
Discord, I want to go over that quick
lesson on liquidity because I think now
is uh today's actually a really good day
to go over it so that you understand.
All right, team. And um
yeah, I'll see the rest of you Monday.
Make sure you're signed up for that um
free weekly newsletter, okay? Doesn't
cost you anything, but I will give you
my ideas and thought process of what the
market might do that next week. And um
yeah, I'm really looking forward to
Monday. I like now that we're leaving
this range, I think we have some uh
really really good trade setups for the
rest of the year, whereas all the time
we're in that range. Hopefully, we don't
go back into that range. Please,
everyone say the same prayer. We don't
want to go back into that range. Please,
please, please, please, please, Mark, we
don't want to go back into that old
balance. All right, peace and love
everyone. Use hard stops. Those in
Discord, um I will set up that lesson
now. Let's get straight into it if that
works for you all. And um then I'm going
to get off for the day. All right, take
care. Have a great weekend.