Okay, there we go. Sorry team. Yeah, my
uh like I was saying when volume wasn't
on, my PC overnight has done a full
restart without telling me. So, I've
lost all my settings. So, there we go.
That's why this has happened. So, let's
get through this because we're running
out of time here. Right, failed
breakout. There's your range. We're back
inside it. Failed breakout of the highs
yesterday. Couldn't get up to 900.
Couldn't start digging into this old
supply zone. Failed causing rotation
lower. Gloex sold off into low volume
node. This acted as a support system. I
would have liked to seen this dig a
little bit deeper, but we didn't. Right
here, 50-day and 20 and yes, and 20-day
mean reversion. Still no sound.
No, you've got sound, Chad. Uh, everyone
can hear me now. Um,
all right. So, 50 day and 20 day, and
we're founding a bid on this low
here. All right. So, if we find a bid
here, then potentially this can be a
daily higher low to move higher. We
can't rule it out. Is it ideal? No. We'd
like to see that happen in New York, but
we get what we've uh been dealt with
right now. We've traded right back
inside range. Uh, this is possibly the
one of the worst charts I've seen. I'm
just being really honest with you. Uh,
failed breakouts both sides back into a
multi-week channel. Um, and range is not
what you want to see. All right, so
right here,
multiple attempts to get back above this
900 to find acceptance into this old
value. All right. So, value, if you
think about this, value moved down,
value moved down, value moved sideways,
value moved down, value moved up, value
moved up, and now we're just inside this
same level. We can't find acceptance
above. We can't find acceptance below in
this exact zone. We've spent 3 weeks,
right? So, no migration either way. It's
trying to figure it out at the moment.
So, we want to be very, very careful. Uh
if we put on a developing profile of
this week,
you can see
we're right back inside and we're inside
this week's point. Well, we're right at
this week's point of control. So, I'll
be watching that rotation up to previous
day value area high. All right, 723s. If
they fail 723s, we're probably going to
come back down to value. These are the
opportunities today. It's just a
rotation till it proves otherwise into
here may well be a fade back down to
there. You can see we could not get
under previous week's value area low.
There was a wick down but we reclaimed
it. We're straight back up. I was
attempting to short that back down there
last night but took the stop. Um so
reclaim a value rotations in here
outside of here. Well, we can argue that
we can come all the way back up to these
highs again. All right. So if we start
printing above value on current week and
previous week and previous day, if we
start basing and holding these sort of
700 750s, 720 750s, then we can think
about that move higher. But if they look
above into here and fail again, we're
coming right back down to the other side
of value and this will just continue to
wash and rotate until they're ready with
it. So super super careful today, folks,
while we're trading back inside that
range. If we look at GlobeEx, you can
see what I'm talking about. Right,
there's the look above and fail on FOMC.
Those who traded FOMC with me will know
I said no more longs up here. We were
long from here for the drive. I was
expecting a two-le pull back here to
hold. We came into Globex and they puked
the whole thing. Now we've reclaimed
value. Get out the way. So you can see
here that's your look below and fail.
Here's the box trigger box and back
inside. So messy, messy, messy, folks.
That's uh this is just what we've got.
Can only can only play what's in front
of us, right? We can only play what is
in front of us. But you know, this is
very, very thin. Gap fill will be all
the way back up to 800. Basically, I
wouldn't rule that out right now with
how we're moving. Let's have a quick
look.
Going to leave the ES. We can have a
very quick look, but you see, same kind
of thing. All right, it's trying to
reclaim and get up to gap fill. If we
think about this as a fib, it's the
other thing we need to be careful of
right now. All right, from the high to
the low, we're into golden zone. Full
retracement is there 891. going gaffful.
Uh, what I want to be very careful of is
this right here. I've talked about this
numerous times. 82 85 88 90. All right.
down here gamma 85
gamma 90 and then 700s. All right. So,
cool wall here. Put wall here. Rotation.
Rotation, rotation, rotation under here.
Definitely under 80. There's actually
not much in terms of put walls down
here. So, if we start losing 82s, it's
actually going to get pretty bad. But,
uh, we've got cool walls, 88, 90, and
definitely 700. There's huge lots up
here on 700. So, we we will just see.
We'll just see how we go. Uh, let's have
a quick look at the VIX and then the
mag, and then we've got to jump into it.
I don't think I've even got Ninja open
yet. Let me just get that booting up
while we're doing this.
Uh
so VIX,
same story here. You can see we've
peaked out trading in between levels. Um
fill in this gap. If we start losing uh
16s and rolling over into low 15s, then
market can just go on a slow low
volatility grind back up. Sorry guys,
give me one second. Just trying to get
in up while we're doing this.
No, doesn't want to play ball. Of
course, it doesn't
Okay, sorry. Mag
[\h__\h] PCs, mate. Windows is the worst
worst operating system, honestly. All
right, Mag. Apple gapping up.
Incredible. Apple gapping up around
previous day high again. Still boxed in.
If we start to break, though. All right.
If we start to break, you can see
Apple's trying to curl. If we start to
break, we might be going back to the top
side here on Apple. Uh Amazon, that's a
gap down back into range. Nothing to see
here. Okay, fail breakout above, failed
breakout below. This is your base. This
is the rotation. That's an ugly looking
chart.
Goo flat. You can see it's trying to
curl with built liquidity here. question
is can it break out previous day high,
previous week high for a continuation
opening up flat but that's looking a bit
more bullish meta uh this won't look
good right this got hammered uh with
Oracle so
I'm still long from where was I long
from 580s
yeah I'm still long from 580s didn't
take any profit I'm just sort of very
small position waiting to see how this
sort of works out but back into this low
range if we start losing this then we're
going straight back down to those 580s
Microsoft
gapping down. That doesn't look good
either. Nvidia. Okay, this got smashed
on Oracle. You can see there's your gap
down. Oracle had earnings yesterday. The
earnings are actually good, but
everyone's adamant on selling at the
moment. I'm actually watching to see if
Oracle starts holding a bit of a bid
after it will be SSR this morning when
it opens up. And Tesla, all right,
gapping down as well. So, MAD doesn't
look too good. I'll show you Oracle.
There's Oracle. All right. So, there's
the push yesterday on earnings. There's
the sell. Um, but we know we have a gap
fill into 87s.
What have I got here? We've got a gap
fill.
Is it 8778? God, gone the wrong way
around. So, I'm watching this to see if
once we fill the gap, we find a bid on
Oracle or not. Uh, it's one thing I'm
aware of right now. Remember, we've this
move is ridiculous.
Um, but if they want to keep selling it,
they will. We're now down 40 45%. If we
fill that gap, we'll be down 50%. So, if
we get into there, I will consider it.
It's got to It's got to start I mean, I
was looking for it to put a higher low
here and it didn't. So, if we get down
to here and we start basing, I'll
consider it, but I'm not going to buy
the knife in case we uh start rolling
over the market. The one thing that I
would say is watching the 10year and 30
years. All right, they had the chance to
do this breakout. We've been talking
about it for months on here. All right.
Yesterday we broke out. We're already
trading back inside. That's what's
allowing this market to cool off a bit
as in to like regain some control. If we
did this, all right, and that held, this
market would be puking right now. So,
worth having one eye on that today, I
would say.
All right. So, Magnog looking too good.
Bit of a mixed bag. Apple relative
strength because why it hasn't got much
exposure to uh to the chips like we
always talk about no exposure to chip
names right let's pull this down
hopefully I haven't lost everything else
let's share this stream quickly how long
we've got one minute left.
Sorry folks, it's a pain. I don't know
if any of you have this when
your PC just restarts
and closes everything down without
saving. It's uh it's got to be the most
annoying thing about PCs.
Okay, so let's have a look. Not yet at
previous day value high. We want to be
careful around here. Remember, we found
a bid all week around these 600s. We've
reclaimed point of control.
So, we want to be somewhat cautious. I
don't want to have too much bias in this
market. I actually want to let this
market just uh make a bit of a decision
and then I'm happy to join in
afterwards.
We can go from there.
All right, 30 seconds to the open,
folks. Sorry, not going to get chance to
get through the hellos.
Check these levels. Are these levels
I've got on here correct? Yes. All
right, good. Sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry,
team. Bit unorganized today. Like I
said, can't uh can't do anything about
it.
Um, let's see if my copy is open.
All right, let this shake out for a
minute, folks. Let's see
see what this market's intentions are.
the spy opening up right at that 85.
Want to be careful right at 85. Spies
opening up. Most of the mag opening up
down other than uh Apple and Goo. And it
won't take a lot for them to go green to
red. So just be careful here. Let me
just go down and check bonds. They're
all open at 1% down.
Big selling here.
Here's the previous week point of
control. So, they're puking this open.
This level here was where we found a bid
all week long. Uh we did it the same
yesterday as well, but if they don't
find a bid here now, um it might be
night night time, but we will see. We're
still inside value, so I want to be
careful. Here's 24hour VW up. Previous
week point of control, previous day
value area low. We're still just inside
value. There's no move outside of value
yet.
Give this a chance to settle down.
Right. All of magn now red other than
goo which is holding on for dear life.
This thing looks heavy but uh who knows?
We are at that key level but wouldn't
surprise me if they puke this under be
right down to previous week value area
low. So small snapshot is possible here.
It would just be a continuation if you
take it. It's beyond my uh parameters.
But if we do lose this, I wouldn't be
surprised for them to retest this level
here. They do lose this. The problem is
this is all in one candle and they can
squeeze straight back up here. And this
is what they've been doing all week
long. I'm just going to personally I'm
going to let this settle down for 5 to
15 minutes because we've had huge moves
overnight
and I want to see where the liquidity
comes in in the New York session.
So holding previous week point control
the same level that they held all week
but we have lost current week's point of
control. We're finding a bid of current
weeks value area low right now which is
also previous week point control. So
it's very very tight around here. buyers
did just got get caught there trying to
bid above 600 or 609 again. I want to
let this settle down. I don't think
people will be too sure what to do with
this. I think the market's in fear. Um
the jobs report again was poor and more
people unemployed again.
And uh we are in stagflation.
You know
this whole narrative that pal was given
yesterday. Uh he looks very upset. Um, I
don't know if anyone watched it. I felt
like he looked very upset and very
uncomfortable. The fact of the matter
is, uh, the jobs market is bad and
that's going to cause a major problem
for him. So, you've got no one in jobs.
People in jobs are trying to stay in
their jobs. No one's moving jobs.
There's no job creation. He blamed that
a lot of that on AI. And then for the
first time, he started talking about the
tariffs calling causing inflation, which
is everyone said that doesn't happen.
Well, it does. And um, inflation's been
steady. Right back to VWAP. Back under
current value area low. Back under
current week value area low. The next
level underneath you is previous day
value area low. Under that we found a
bid. Oh, we found a bid in GlobeEx from
five. You want to watch 550 to 470.
That's where they found a bid. If
they're going to do a higher low,
they're going to need to hold that. If
they don't hold that, we're going right
the way back down to the lows. And we've
got an old naked point of control much,
much lower that I've been talking about
for a while.
How much long we got left? Need a five
minute bar. Where are you?
Another one minute left for this five
minute.
Spy trying to reclaim the 85. I'm
watching that very, very carefully
as an overunder.
It's under it right now, but it's a huge
level. Let me mark this on. It's lost
that as well. Jeez Louise, what a pain.
I need to put an auto save on. Okay,
back down to previous day value area
low. If we start losing this, then we've
got previous day lows we can come for.
this. We're still in a range. Every time
we've done this in New York session
before, we've drifted straight back
upside. This is why I'm being very, very
cautious cuz I don't think this market
is really too sure what to do. We've got
a fail break at the high, fail break at
the low. If we're going to put in a
higher low on like an hourly, now is the
time to do it. All right, if we think
about this, if this market is adamant
and pushing up, all right, then this is
the area where shorts got stuck. This is
the area that they would need to
protect. This is your value from
yesterday. So look below here, fail
reclaim can allow this move. Uh if we go
into here, I would say that's very very
bearish because we're building liquidity
outside of old range to move lower at
that point. So this is why I'm like just
want to let them make the decision. I'm
not a big trader. I can't make this
decision. I've got to let the big
players make the decision on what they
want to do.
If they're adamant that we're going for
all-time highs, if they're adamant that
this market wants more squeeze out, if
they're adamant that the Fed's really
going to print and they actually think
it's quantitive easing, then you know
this is the time where they need to save
the market. If they're saying that's a
load of [\h__\h] we need to go deeper,
then they will do it.
And it's just knowing like I I I
just know
I'm not a uh got a big enough ego to say
this is what we're going to do. When we
failed both sides of the range, it's
ugly.
I would say we didn't leave too much
excess at the highs yesterday. We
trapped and we talked about it and we
can talk about this in uh here while
we're waiting. Right. If we have a look
what we were looking at yesterday in
Discord,
where are we?
We talked about no more longs at the
highs right here.
All right. And when Very dangerous,
they're tank it when he's done. All
right. So, this was all before it
happening. We were long all the way up
to that point up to previous week value
area high. Right. We just play momentum
longs all the way up. And then my call
for overnight was one of two things to
happen. All right, here we go. And we
did it. All right. So, either of those
things. I would have preferred they were
bullish, but we've we've done the wash
and now we've reclaimed that level. So,
we need to be careful. Now, this is why
it's important to just wait. Sometimes
you just got to know when it's a waiting
game. At the moment, unfortunately,
it's now a waiting game.
So, sellers keep coming in under 590.
Buyers keep coming in over 590. And we
are not moving.
Just lost my cumulative delta as well.
Gosh, back on.
Let me save this before it loses
everything.
There we go.
Okay. All right. So, holding previous
days value, reclaiming previous week's
value, holding current week's value. Uh,
next move will be up to previous day and
current week's uh point of control,
which would be 634. That's the most
traded level so far. In that last drive
up, we did just trap a load of bulls up
there into 6:30. 634. You can see this
level here, right? So this is current
New York open, previous day point of
control and current week point of
control. Everything's here. This is the
area that bairs would defend. This is
the area that bulls would defend. Is
your rotation right now?
Nice Chad. Good work. Good work. I
haven't even looked at gold today. It's
up, isn't it?
What's happened to silver? Is it still
going
or have they called that off? Um
JP Morgan caught short side in that
getting destroyed off that. That is
another push on Delta where they haven't
reclaimed point control. Lots of buyers
are coming in here and they're not
moving higher. Not not enough.
This is starting to look more and more
like a short setup here.
That's twice they've tried to buy above
609 and failed.
still playing. We're still inside that
opening five minute. Everything red.
I'll give you a readout on the market.
Tesla 1.43% down. Nvidia 2.72% down.
Microsoft flat. Meta 0.72% down. Google
0.59% down. Amazon a third of a percent
down. Apple half a% down. Oracle 14%
down.
14% down. I'd say you can put a price
alert on Oracle for that gap for what do
we say it is 78 or something. Put a
price alert there. That's probably where
it's trying to go. All right. Sellers
are starting to take over this market
now. They are trying to take over this
market. Those last two pushes above uh
609s
have got them caught. The buyers caught
back to point of control. We've just
gone here.
What are we doing market? Can you make
your mind up?
Is there any follow-through downside?
They've got the opportunity because
they've got buyers caught above and
definitely above point of control. So
sellers are attempting to take control
of this market here for a breakdown. I
can see it in the tape starting. So I
want to just see if we get underneath
that value.
How do we act?
Do we get underneath this value? Is this
a snap? So in here on the tape, buyers
have come in numerous times, aggressive
buyers, market buyers, and we've not
gone higher. There's passive selling
happening here. We're not breaking
outside of value. I'm trying to be
patient because I don't want to get
caught. If we break outside of value,
I'll consider this here for a move to
previous day low and previous week value
low. I want to be careful of that move
there.
the end of this auction, we did get a
seller slightly offside at 65. So, we're
going to have to trade under him.
Microsoft trying to find a bid. The rest
of the market's still selling. And bid
now 3% down.
It's a battle here, folks, for sure.
Trapped bar at 620. Yeah, I'd say
actually everyone over 606 is trapped.
Everyone over 606 is trapped. So, if you
look at uh
where can I put it?
[\h__\h] off. Why is it lost literally
everything?
Um,
okay. If you look at this, uh, bring
this over here.
Right. Look at all this buying.
If we go to a one minute, you'll see it
really clear. All these guys over here
trapped. Here comes a sell. All right.
So, here's previous day value area low.
Important. What happens now?
So, they saved it again. So, shorts have
come flying in there trying to get the
breakdown. So, why I'm waiting for
confirmation. I want to see us go under
it and hold under it. So, there's a
passive buyer sat a previous day value
low. There's a passive seller sat at 610
and above. That's your range right now.
So 560 to 610. Look at that. Say this is
why we wait. Exactly why we wait.
Range actually not too big. Still only
94 points. just going back and forth.
Microsoft has caught a bid.
Jesus Christ.
What are we doing?
Oh, it's Groundhog Day. It's Groundhog
Day. Can you sit still?
Can we get underneath value?
It's like a battle of H1 right now. This
is like I can just show you this is the
battle.
Bulls know like we talked about they
want to defend this leave short stop for
a higher low to go higher. Bears know
that if this is a driver up and we get
back into here they go lower. This is a
very very contested level, especially
the top side of it. So, we don't know
what we're doing because there's value,
there's a failure, there's a failure,
there's back inside.
It's just it is what it is, folks. It is
what it is.
Waiting for that guy to tell me it's a
trending market again.
VWOP chop. Yeah, VWOP chop as well.
Stuck between the VWOPS. Absolutely.
One thing we could do which I haven't
done. Let's actually do
an anchor.
There you go.
So, we're right at the anchor off the
low. Let's do one of the high. I bet you
it's exactly the same spot.
All right. There's There's your problem
right there. Right. This is average
buying price off the low. That's average
selling price off the high. That is your
problem right there.
Right. Average buyer, average seller,
condens. Um,
we're getting tighter and tight in
between it.
They're trying. They are now trying to
break out outside of it. So, if they
hold this, then you're looking for
washes to previous day low, previous
day, previous week open, previous week
value area low. If bulls come in and
they soak this up, then they're going to
try for that hourly high hour hourly
higher low that I've been talking about
in this area down here, right where we
tried to bid off overnight. This level
right here, right? This level right in
here.
No acceptance lower yet.
Spy still holding 85s, folks.
Still holding 85s.
They're They're not trapped though, are
they? Your trap sellers between five
under 571. We're under 571. So, they're
not actually trapped.
If we're at that price, they're not
trapped, are they? Cuz we can still
break down here and make a new low. If
we move over it, then yes. But
understand that these participants are
not trapped right now. They're in
control. There you go. There's a new
low. So, there's a big difference, mate.
You when you're calling levels, you
better understand if we're above it or
below it. You're saying correct, but
you're saying that they're trapped.
They're not trapped.
All right. If if we'd done this, moved
back over, all right, and left excess.
Yes, but we hadn't. So, don't don't
confuse yourself and say that these guys
are trapped when we're they're in
control of this market right now.
There's a big difference, right? So, I'm
going to leave value. So, this short
sign of payout now into previous day
low.
You want to be careful here. There's a
passive buyer down here. But if we snap
this, there's possibly a move into 480s
to 470s.
Strong selling coming in.
SPY underneath that uh 85 level into its
lower day here on SPY.
Big big level. Higher time frame algo
here as well. Big big level. Sellers
still in control here. You're still
seeing potential expansion lower, but we
have just swept. Be very very careful.
We've just swept. So your TP is like
already been hit or at least one of
them. Big sellers coming in at the low
and they're not getting their way yet.
They need to see a further breakdown
here.
Big big sellers coming in at these lows
at 23. So 23 down to 19. Lots and lots
of selling activity on the market taking
place. They need expansion lower
otherwise they're going to get
themselves caught for the first time
today.
There's a reclaim or attempt to reclaim
previous day low. So I'd say how we act
here into 27 all the way up to 57
becomes important.
VWAP here for ES. 24-hour VWAP coming
up.
High time from Algo Spy still in play.
Watching to see if we get one more
little snap down or if they're going to
turn this inside. Nice. Okay, beautiful.
So, can we now get down into 82s
and then under that into what's previous
week? 69s. Looking good. Looking good
here. Finally rejecting. Lovely.
Going to sell a little bit. Sorry. Cover
a little bit into this.
See this guy on the bid here at 500.
Snapped him. Now he's out the way.
Previous week open here into 82s.
And then previous week value here. And
then if we fail that all the way down we
go.
can afford a drift back up to 26 here
for a retest.
So happy to risk up there at the moment.
Nice further breakdown coming here.
We're going to get that previous week
value area low now. There we go. Tagged
it.
Okay, so I'm down to tiny tiny tiny tiny
size. I want to still risk 27s here.
Sellers come in at around 25. So he's
looking at the same level of me. Sort of
27ish.
He's moved down. He's Oh, he's jostling
down now. Okay, let's see.
Down to tiny size here. If we get
expansion lower, great. But uh this has
been a big move. expecting some little
push back and then a roll over for a
retest and then if we're going to come
into GlobeEx all the way down here.
Market's really really rolling now.
Starting to get aggressive, but I don't
don't want to add any size down here.
I'm down to tiny tiny micros here. So, I
need a push back up for me to get
involved with any more size. But we've
hit most of the targets. Previous week
value low now being taken. If we're
going to expand underneath previous week
value low, I can think about that naked
point of control that I've been banging
on about. So 25200s I think it was and
24900s. 25200s 24 900s. Globeex is 2580s
down here. Okay, here's the move back
upside. So I'm watching here to see how
we act at 25, not just cuz it's previous
day low because this is where some
buyers came in and got themselves
caught.
So we're holding previous week's value
at the moment.
Big buyers coming in here getting
themselves caught again. Can they get
one more lift higher? Don't really want
to add here. Market's losing every level
though.
You really got to get higher for me to
be interested
and then add
So back to yeah. So there you go.
Holding previous week's value. So I'd
say all the way up to 26 is possible for
relief and then how they at there will
become key.
So they hold value again. Here is the
question. If not, we're going to snap.
Here's previous week value area low
being tested again. The weekly buyers
are trying to hold this here.
Please come a bit higher first.
Push was a bit weak into that whole
number.
Love to get a bit more size on. Don't
think you're going to let me. Are you?
These bids stacking up here at 50s. I
just think they're just going to snap
and wipe them.
There's the flush.
Careful here now. There's a bit of a
battle here, but we are outside of
previous week's value. I think we still
move lower now again back to GlobeEx low
by the looks of it. Here we go. There's
an imbalance here, by the way, 440 to
420. to be aware of that if you're still
in
really starting to sell. Really nice
sell now outside of value. It's
important that first five 10 minutes,
whatever it was, to let those players
make their minds up, not join in until
we got outside of the value area.
I'm just a bit annoyed that we didn't
get a bit further up for a retest up
here. It's what I would have really
liked to have seen to resize into it,
but uh it is what it is. It's going to
be a a smaller win. Would have liked to
have been um huge win. I never really
sized in.
Don't chase. By the way, folks, if if
you didn't take the uh breakdown of
value here, which we kept talking about,
we need to see
the move outside. I drew it for you
enough times here. Anywhere here, you
can join TP1, TP2. I'm now looking for
this. And really this and really
this. And where's the other green level?
Or maybe that's it. Nine. Where's that
naked point of control? Yeah, that level
here. 950 I think is doable. It's a
naked point of control on a weekly,
which we've never gone back to if we
really sell. Doesn't have to be today,
but I think 950 is possible.
Doesn't have to be today. Can be
tomorrow, next week.
But yeah, no reason to fully cover yet.
Still, still we drop. Right, this is the
imbalance from last night down into 20
that I talked about. There's a a buy
side imbalance here where we found a bid
last night. So, we're repricing some of
this. Might see a reaction here.
Where did I enter? I entered once I saw
this break. I was a little bit late,
right? I was watching this. I actually
entered about here.
Let's have a look. Entry was Yeah. 4550
is where I got in.
I really wanted to retest 26s. So, here
26es here. We had lots of buyers come
in, fail, and I was hoping this would
come back in and I would just slam these
guys back down. But, we never got back
to that level. So all I got was this
original position in
and would really have liked that to come
a little bit higher and then I could
have used their pain to go lower. But it
is what it is. Still a really nice
trade. The key was if you like it didn't
tell you it didn't tell I told you
numerous times wait for us to move
outside of value and if we stay heavy on
a retest right we need confirmation.
This candle here was it. That was it.
We're moving away now. Right. Really
simple. Range created. moving away from
range.
What were the flow zones doing? Sell.
We're in a cell. We just had to leave
this range. Once we left that range,
this guy right here, everything started
to play out.
Still coming low. We're going to we're
going to come and take GlobeEx now,
[\h__\h] I mean, it's really good.
Like, I shouldn't be complaining. I just
never got the size on I wanted.
Green otter. A friend of mine joined
today. They asked if it's always this
easy. I mean,
when we're out of like some of you would
have been here for weeks, months, some
of you for years. How many times do you
hear me say I'm not interested in
trading inside range, but when we leave
range, that's when I'm interested in
trading. Right? So you would have seen
it all week just like can't be bothered.
Can't be bothered. Can't be bothered.
We've got to leave leave range. I traded
long bias yesterday on FOMC because we
got above this range. So everyone who
was in Discord with me once there's a
range. Once we got above this, we were
long biased to previous week high up
here. We were probably short biased for
a pull back to here. But I did not want
to take that. Wanted to take a long from
here which never turned out because they
sold it. Right? So market's always
either in doing one or two things. range
rotation or consolidation or whatever
you want to call it, accumulation
distribution depending on the way we're
going or range expansion. Right, we're
now in range expansion
target right here is here 380s and then
under there 195 and then this is the
real target for me, right? And it's been
the real target for me for a long long
long time. And if you're like
not heard you talk about it, um yeah,
I've talked about it numerous times.
There you go. old point of control on a
weekly, untested, naked, virgin, however
you want to call it, that's what it is.
All right. Did ES sweep there? No. All
right. It's trying to base above. ES is
trying to find a bid at 40 is where it
broke out from. So, just be aware of
that. This market can afford a drift up
before it resells. It doesn't mean it's
going to do it, but it can afford it.
They did just trap a ton of buyers on
that last little one minute shove up.
This right here just trapped a [\h__\h] ton
of buyers there. 244 lot, 156 lot, 98
lot. So, as long as they are out the
money, um 25 434 is their big pain
point. All right. So, if you break I
just call it 35. If you break 35, these
buys are going to be okay and you might
get a drift. But all the time we're
under 34s, they are in big big trouble
because they came in with size.
Mhm. I'm going to grab a coffee. Okay,
then be right back.
>> Do not be bullish. Please don't be
silly.
Yeah, those buyers are still stuck.
Lower you don't.
Orange line is your target, right?
Orange line is your target. Let me just
check this uh blue box one and make sure
I've got it in the right spot.
Okay, there's like a little
I'll do this so you can see how I do it.
I'm watching this here. There's this uh
node above value here. We're thin here
and then we repriced it and we broke out
from. So, I'm interested in that. But
once we get under that, right, except
the the bottom of this blue box will be
the old value area high. Once we lose
that, then what are we going to do? All
right. If we can't hold above value,
we're going to search for fair value.
Where's fair value? There it is. It's
standing out, right? So, if we lose
this, this is possible. It doesn't have
to do it today. I want to really make
that clear. This might take a few days
or weeks to happen. But this here is a
highly probable area for us to trade
into because we've never come back to
it. All right? So, that's previous or
many many weeks ago value area high
became a point of control. We've never
retested it. It's been one, two, three.
This would be the third week of not ret.
Well, actually, technically, it's two.
This would be the second week of not
retesting it. All right. So, I think
there's a highly probable chance that we
come down to that. The only other thing
I want to be considerate of is these
daily levels that I keep talking about.
We do have a bit of a shelf developing
here. This works. This is the same area,
290s. This is your 50-day, 20-day. So,
in here, I think there will be a lot of
bulls waiting. All right. If they're
going to set a higher low, like I've
talked about for weeks and weeks and
weeks, this is where they need to do it
on a daily. If they fail to set a higher
low here on a daily, it is night night
time. All right? Because this is a
straight move up. They need to set the
higher low here on a daily to have a
chance to go back up, which will be
beautiful inverse head and shoulders.
Fail that. Okay. Good night. Good night
market. So, I'm willing to play both
ways when we get into that. But that's
what I'm watching for is what I've been
watching for for I don't know 2 3 weeks
now.
Lots of buyers coming in down here by
the way folks. Lots and lots and lots of
buyers coming in here. They are trying
over and over again. Hu like if you look
at bit maps huge buy. We're not really
moving higher. I would not be short down
here, right? I still short bias, but you
don't want to be a new money short down
here. The next new money short really
comes if we expand underneath Gloveex,
right? So, if we start coming underneath
here and if we build liquidity here and
we expand underneath and use that
liquidity to move lower, then you can
think about this move. But just think
about how violent this move's been down
without a repric. We can afford a repric
maybe into previous week value area low.
Maybe they come back. Are you sure we
don't want to move back into value? No,
we don't want to move back into value.
Right? That kind of move there can
easily happen if we get through previous
week value area low then you know if
they start lifting the offer right if
there's no sellers hanging out here we
know where was I waiting 26s
26s
it was 26s right double check this was
26s I'd say 26s where are those big
buyers 63 there's a massive lot got
stuck at 82 so delta big delta up to 82
so I'd be watching Yeah. Well, it's the
same kind of level in and around here.
Do sellers hold this market back down?
Is this a pump which gets resold into in
and around 82ish? If they start
reclaiming value, they can come all the
way back up to VWOP, can't they? They
failed to take out that. Just want to
make sure.
Did we take it on the ES? We didn't take
it on ES either. So, I'd be watching for
a reshort around here if you see
failure. All right. If they reclaim
this, you don't want to be short because
they're going to lift it then and they
can attack VWAP and previous day low and
even previous day value. But I'd be
thinking if we're going to sell, we
should sell around here. Big ifs, but if
we're going to sell, this is where we
should set sell around into sort of the
80s.
Am I ever looking into session high and
lows? Yes, what this orange line is.
That's your GlobeEx low.
Absolutely.
Okay. So, here we go. They're going to
lift this into these sort of sort of
80s, 70s and 80s, but I would say the
big delta is stuck at 82. If they get
above 82, the buyers start to feel
comfortable. That's where they're going
to try and lift it up to. Meta and
Microsoft both gone green. By the way,
I'm watching ES as well. It's not too
far away from both of its V VW what? So,
it's almost there. You see the current
high on that push was 63s. I'll be
watching 82s. be watching around 82. So,
I'm not like I'm not going to slam this
short as we come into it. We don't know
if they just lift this whole thing, but
if we start to fail and we create a
lower high and we build out some
liquidity, maybe I'll be interested in
another trade.
Yeah. Well, I can see that the delta's
gone positive on the last five, one,
two, three, five minute candles, but it
doesn't mean anything until we reclaim a
level. Of course, we're going to go
positive. There's lots of buying coming
in here, but what really matters is this
level here that I keep telling you
about. The delta is stuck 82. Let me
show you on bit map. See if you can see
this. It should stand out here. If I
come up to 82, where are you
70?
It's moving so quick. It's going to keep
pulling it away. All right. You see this
here into
here. See 81, 127 lot, and a 50 lot.
These guys up here are offside. You're
looking at the level two on the right,
the tape. That would be what I'd be
watching into those 82s. Those are the
guys that are currently offside. If you
if they take that out, then we can
squeeze right back up. Like I said, I
wouldn't just be slamming short in this.
You want to wait to see if there's a
reaction because if there's no reaction
at 82s, right, then they're going to
come straight up into here and we're
leaving that alone, which is a bit
dirty. And you also watching ES into
this same level. ES is almost here. So
that's what I'd be watching personally.
That's what I'd be watching. I wouldn't
be bullish bias until we start taking
out levels and put like and putting in
higher lows. This is just a rebalance
and a reprice. And you can see we just
tapped into 82s and just got slammed.
Right? So that little first reaction
straight into just above 82s. Actually
went 84s. And you can see it's the first
sort of attempt from sellers and buyers
just got caught there again.
That is the level based on delta. That's
the level. That's the overunder right
now. And they're trying to now absorb
previous week value area low. So this
becomes the battle. Do they fade this
all the way back down or buyers get a
squeeze out into view up here? I don't
know. This is why we don't attack it. We
let them do whatever it is they need to
do. And if they start to roll over, we
play. And if they start to, you know,
put put higher lows and reclaim, we can
bid up.
I'm not into um
playing counter trend longs when we've
just left balance, but uh we do need to
be aware of that previous week value
error low. Absolutely need to be aware
of it. Okay, so drift into VWAP now
looks probable.
ES is at VWOUP. Spy has got a tiny bit
left to go. Guess what the bottom was
today on Spy? 82s. All right, so all
those guys have been here the last few
days. Everyone in Discord, 85 to 82
rotation on Spy. All right, look at this
morning. Once we lost 85, we went
straight down to 82. Gamma exposure is
at 82. They bid back off at 82. I'm
telling you now, there is not much of a
put wall underneath. If they lose 82s on
spy, it is a little bit night night
because everything was heavy topside.
And again, I gave you that in Discord
last night. We talked about it. I'm
pretty sure
sure I mention it.
Did I not mention it? There we go. Spy
levels for tomorrow 69700. Not much
below most of call walls topside. So 85
and 82 still key lose that weakness
possible. that was given at 625 last
night, right? Those are still the
levels. We're still just playing gamma
to gamma at the moment by the looks of
it. Options dealers still playing this
market.
So, straight squeeze up, repricing.
How much more juice has got it got in it
is the question.
Bid bid bid bid bid
through to 82. So bulls now completely
comfortable because they've repriced and
they're holding and bears have a chance
to come in previous day value area low.
But the fact that they didn't hold the
previous week is a bit dirty. I don't
like that they left that. That's a bit
naughty. But you know it's the ENQ. She
loves doing that especially this year.
And then we do have some imbalances here
43 to 54. And then there's some more all
the way up 70s. If we claim the opening
range though, that's going to be uh it's
going to be a bit like last night really
like one move down and then um all the
way back up. It's not very nice.
So Meta and Microsoft half% up. Rest
rest of the market still in a bleed.
Rest of the market still in a bleed
here.
They're trying to get to VWAP by the
looks of it.
Does the spy 185 again back inside its
initial balance on the spy? This is
silly market at this point.
This is a silly market at this point,
right? There's no higher low yet. This
is just a straight squeeze.
So watching if there's acceptance, but
you'd imagine there'll be some rejection
at some point.
There you go. It's the start of a
rejection there.
So probably going to come down fairly
decently here and then try and set a
higher low. So either VWAP or down into
here. So this is the battle now. Can
they get this move here? And they need
to use this cluster to go higher if they
are. Otherwise, bears will lean against
this and look for a rotation to here,
right? And this would be their cover
point. And if they got acceptance below,
great.
But I'm not going to trade this here
because they should have rejected here
versus 82. They didn't. I want to be
careful of a lift up into this.
Where's What was that high we just
traded? 8480s. So, it got very close to
85s. So, we know that's the rotation.
85s and 82s on the spy. I do I do
personally think that is controlling
most of the There you go. Here's a
flush. So, this is their chance to set a
higher low. Maybe wick to wick 500s. If
not,
might drift all the way down into here.
Spy will or ES and spy will look to hold
VW up here. If they can set a higher low
here, then they can have that move back
inside the range.
So, good higher low or good attempt at a
higher low here. I'm not convinced yet.
We did just repric a buy side imbalance
at 12s.
Sellers definitely caught offside there
underneath 24s now in this current
candle. I say sellers came in
aggressively underneath 24s.
This is all bid bid bid bid bid coming
in here.
Man, if this daily
closes inside the old weekly range
again,
how many days will that be? One, two,
three, four, five, six, seven. This
isn't day number eight. Please, please,
please. I'd said so many prayers for us
to just get out this range. I've
constantly said, I don't care which side
we go. Just please.
Yeah, totally. Well, the it makes sense.
Look, when you see stuff like this,
right, we're not balancing it out. The
thing is bears needed to defend this 82.
It's why I said there in here that in
this wick here, there was a lot of
buying. All right,
so bears really wanted to defend that.
If they could have defended that, they
could have caused this move down here.
This is why I was like, I'm not going to
just come in and hammer short. If you if
you just rewind the tape, you'll hear me
say, I'm not just going to come in and
hammer short because we don't know if it
wants to come up to here or here. And
right now, we're going right the way
back to value. All right, so bears, this
is last chance that they really have
here is to defend this. They've now
lost. All right, here are the VWAPs.
This is off the high pivot. This is off
the low pivot. They've now lost that. If
bears don't defend this, then guess
what? Well, that's going to be used to
go up here, right? That will become
liquidity to go up here. It's very ugly
now to play this bull side with this
micro pullback. It's like this bare
side. That was a micro pullback. It's
all you got. The better bullish move
would be like this. But I've got a
feeling it's not going to give that to
us. It just feels very this
82 spy. Okay.
This now here
spy. All right.
I can show you.
This is how quickly it's happening. It's
literally just options dealers, guys.
Here you go. 82,
85 through 85. There's a little bit at
88 and uh and then 90 and then 700.
Under 82, there was no put wall. So, if
they didn't save 82, this market was
gone. It was completely gone. That was
their only chance really.
Sorry. Do I need to catch up on some
stuff here? Sorry, folks. Uh, what are
you all saying?
Have I missed something? Someone pass
something? Thanks. That was a 70 point
reversal to almost V up. Re-entered
three times. Thanks, man. Oh, lovely.
Really nice. Good work. You just played
the delta flip
and there was never a reason to get out
if you played that. Yeah. Never give you
a reason to get out. Once it got above
82, that was it.
All right, let me have a look.
Well, I'm kind of put off doing much
now. I'm going to be honest.
Bears need to defend this and they've
done a terrible job as
they've done a terrible job since April.
Uh, so we want to be careful. We're back
inside previous days value.
Let's put some volume on here now as
well. Sorry, I forgot to do that because
it's on my other chart. You got to
remind me if I ever forget to do it.
Just uh shout at me.
Aren't you gone? Let's get rid of these
anchors because we've traded over it.
Let's put this guy back on.
Right, there we go.
So, high profile point control on the
day all up at this kind of level here.
This is your I would normally call this
an underover over. I'm reluctant to call
it today an under over, but I guess it
is where we built out this shelf. Uh
bears must defend this. Failing to
defend this will cause an inverse head
and shoulder, and we will go for a
resqueeze higher.
So look at spy. It's just rejected 85.
It can't get a close over 85. It's
trying to get a close over 85. If it
does successfully get a close over 85, I
would expect it to attack 88.
Alex, what are the bands on your chart
that show the rotations?
Um, I'm not sure what you mean. The
bands, do you mean these the clouds?
These are my flow zones. Yeah, these are
the flow zones. So, these are rolling
fibs.
See how wide this got here? All right.
Maybe we can see we're rejecting
previous days value.
Where would bulls want to defend? I
would imagine they'll want to defend
this right here now. Right? If they're
going to set a higher low, I mean, if
they can't hold V up, if they're going
to set a higher low, bulls will want to
defend this. This can still be sold,
right? This is structure at the moment.
If bears sell this, they will attempt to
sell it down to here. Bulls will attempt
to defend this area here or that move.
If we get acceptance in here, you do not
want to be short bias. I'm telling you
now, if this thing starts to find
acceptance inside of value and chopping
in here, remember this is fair value on
the day. Chop chop chop. If we go chop
chop chop chop expansion, everyone down
here gets cooked and we'll come straight
up for well maybe not for gap fill but
if we can get through previous day point
of control. If we get acceptance inside
value, it's hard to see there. Then
we're going to go other side. All right,
so this is yesterday.
All right,
let me clean this up and make this make
sense for you. Right.
This is yesterday.
Yeah, there we go. That's yesterday.
Where's previous week?
Where's previous week value very low?
Where is it? Where's it gone?
Is it just there and I can't see it?
It's here. Hang
on. Disappeared off my chart. Let me get
this previous week.
Okay, so this is yesterday's rotation.
This is last week's rotation.
overnight.
If we think about what we did overnight,
we failed to get over previous week and
previous day and we came all the way
down underneath previous week and set a
low here.
So overnight and then we came back
inside. So we failed. So we failed
upside failed downside overnight. New
York session we've failed to reclaim top
side of this come back down found accept
well trying to find acceptance inside
previous week possibly inside previous
days. So this really for me is the no
trade zone. Definitely this is a no no
trade zone. I don't want to play in
there. But if you get acceptance in here
and if you like playing rotation, there
is a difference. It's a no trade zone
for me. It doesn't mean it needs to be
for you. If we start finding acceptance
inside here or inside here, if you're
playing the weekly level, you're playing
that. If you're playing the daily level,
you're playing that. And if we're not
getting acceptance underneath the weekly
level, we should come and test the other
weekly other side of the range. If we're
not getting acceptance underneath
previous daily value, then we should
come and test the other side of the
range. Technically speaking, but uh like
you will hear me to say all the time, I
flipping hate playing rotation, so I
will avoid it like the plague. I've just
lost that level again. You bugger.
Hopefully that makes sense. Different
between a rotating market and a trending
market. We've had the ability or we've
had the option to trend um yesterday in
FOMC and this morning. We've had the
opportunity to trend twice uh but we're
not seeing the continuation yet yet.
moment we've just seen back into range.
Oh, well, if you just think about
Fibonacci numbers, yeah, 13, 21, 45s.
There's a reason, like, if you didn't
know, there's a reason people use like a
21 EMA. Yeah, it it's a fib.
Same with these. These are fibs fib
numbers. 788 82s.
All right.
Yes. About to take out higher day. Uh no
acceptance underneath back inside value.
This is looking more and more like an
inverse head and shoulder. It's very
dangerous to play this because this
pullback is weak. But this is looking
more and more probable right now.
There's your point of control on the
session. I would say uh bulls have the
ability to
really take over this market.
I can't see me doing much else with this
right now.
Yeah, I know, Peter. It's It's silly.
It's silly. But that's uh like we said,
that's been ENQ a lot recently, isn't
it? I mean, leaving this is gross. What
would have been better for the whole
trigger would have been this, this,
this, this, this, this. Okay, then we
have a base built out. We've taken the
liquidity. We've got a higher low. We've
got acceptance in range. That becomes an
easy long. This V-shaped recoveries are
are so gross.
But whatever. This is the market. So,
back into this anchor off the high. I'm
going to get rid of that now. I think
we're just going to scream upside.
Shorts are absolutely cooked because
we're back inside value. Shorts are
absolutely cooked now.
big seller at 582. Yeah, I'd say yeah, I
agree with you. 582 to 578.
That's where they tried to sell it.
So again, if we come here, we will see
them.
Let me come down.
Let's look at the VPD on the left. 582
to 5678. There's one here 589.
Here you go. So these guys here 583. You
see all this sellside stacked and then
this guy here 580 187 lot offside. So
all the time we're over this guy here at
580. Bulls have the chance to stay in
control of this market.
Yeah. I guess one of the things when
you're waiting when you're one of the a
trader like me that waits for a
confirmation on a hold
I mean this is
without taking liquidity
it doesn't even pull back to 30s all
about here this for me that's just a no
go it's a nogo I I can't shoot myself
for not taking longs here
but yeah we're going to get that
inverted head and shoulders look so back
inside previous week point control. Next
stop is 637.
Then you've got that New York open 644
and through that previous day value area
high because we're going to we've had no
acceptance under previous day value high
and under previous week high. So we
should come and test the top side of the
range. So if you are long in this, I
don't see a really a great entry model.
But if you are longing this, it's a
fantastic trade and these are your
targets. And once you get through that
gap fill to 800. And if you get through
800, you might as well go to 926,000
to be quite honest with you, which is
flipping insane when we just zoom out.
What the bloody hell is this? But there
we go. No. Sweet. Technically, higher
low. If we reclaim this, we're coming up
because we've got three lots of stops up
here now. We did take it yesterday, but
you know, by what, like a tick or
something? This red line here, 870.
get through 870. You're you're
screaming. You're screaming. That's
going to be the big short pain point is
870.
Went for rotation in at previous day
value low got 617.
Spy might go for gap. Yeah, spy is
definitely looks like it's going for
gapful at 8750. Just remember 88 is a
quite a big level.
TP at the gap. Yeah, I mean
all the way up here. It's possible. It's
possible.
This level is fair value currently from
previous day. So you need to find
acceptance over 637. my TP. If if I was
long, I'd be taking a partial here and
I'd be looking for this previous day
value area high. This level here would
be my TP, right? A little bit into here.
That's your New York open and your
previous day point of control and here.
And I'd want to this pullback would need
to hold value. They have to hold value
here if I'm bullish. Right? If they
don't hold value here, it can hold in
front of value, but it's definitely got
I do not want it back outside of this.
It's done all this work to get back
inside of value. if they lose value. No,
it's just it just means I don't know
what it means. It just means it's [\h__\h]
I I don't know how else to describe it.
They have to hold value. Yeah, they have
to hold value here on a pullback. If if
if I'm bullish all the way up to the top
side of the range.
Hopefully that makes sense.
We don't want a market that goes fail
breakout outside of value yesterday,
wash all the way down underneath daily
and weekly value, fail breakdown
underneath value, back inside value, up
to midpoint of value, back down, loses
it again. You can't, we don't want to
lose this box, right? If you think about
previous week, previous day value in
here, all right, we've had no acceptance
above, no acceptance below, right? But
we're moving from under and reclaiming.
Once we reclaim, we should go top side
of the box. If we lose bottom side of
the box, it's not a good look. Hopefully
that makes sense. So, basically just
this is your box
like we just talked about. Just we can
just do the whole thing. This is your
box. All right. This is your box and
this is your box, right? We've reclaimed
this. We don't really want to lose this.
All right. If you're bullish, you want
them to hold here. You do not want them
to lose that. And you want to complete
the rotation up here.
Yeah, ADHD market. Yeah.
Vick's getting absolutely crushed at
that um just above 1650. So, was that
the level from last night? It was.
It's wild how quick these moves are
happening. But you know when we we've
had consolidation in tight ranges for
eight days and then we get an expansion
outside. What's this range been from
yesterday's high to the low and we've
done it multiple times now.
And that's not a joke. Just shy of 500
points.
And even this morning from that New York
open
260 points down and then what almost all
of it back up. Crazy.
Crazy.
Watch your ATR on your sizing.
Big old V shape.
Yeah, ES very strong. I agree. ES very
strong. But it's because you got spy
back over 85s.
So they're going for gap fill.
They are going for gap fill.
So you're at globex high now really on
ES and spy.
It will want gap fill and it will want
to test 88. If we get through 88, next
level is 90. If we get through 90, next
level is 700. All right. 8. And I would
say the same thing. You do not want to
lose a pullback into 85s on the spy.
Right? It's done all the hard work to
get back above it. It held 82. It got
back above 85. You do not want to see it
lose 85 on the spy.
We haven't had a good pullback on this
market since I would I know these are
pullbacks, but I would say this is a
very very steep trend. Just be very very
aware. It would not surprise me to come
and see them retest this level down
here, right? And then they need to hold
this kind of level. This is what they
must hold to complete this rotation.
Failing to hold this, they're opening
themselves up for this move back down.
It's flipping gross. You don't want to
lose this level. Really, I don't know
where you guys got uh your bids in from,
whether you took the weekly or daily
reclaims,
or maybe you took the 82s once we got
above the 82s.
becomes a rotation.
Remember, you want to find a bid a
previous day value area low or above.
You do not want to lose that. That will
create the liquidity that you need to go
higher. All right? This will create the
liquidity you need to go high because
then you'll have all the stops in and
then you should then use these stops for
a big drive. That's what you're looking
for if you're looking to either buy back
in or uh or hold your position that
you're already in. Um, initial balance
now set. So your IB highs is up here as
well. Technically speaking, we're in a
initial balance rotational day with 250
odd points for the IB. Let me just check
that. I think that's about right. 250
260 points on the IB. Right. So here
comes the pullback. You will want them
to hold this value area.
I haven't had a good pullback on the
market since COVID. I mean, I think I
don't think that's fair. I think the
tariff pullback was pretty good. That
was a pretty good pullback. The tariff,
I'll give you a readout on the mag while
we're letting this uh sort of cool off
and come in. Uh Tesla 1.78% down, Nvidia
3% down, Google 1.34% down, Amazon 0.44%
down, Apple 1.14% down, Microsoft has
found a little bit of a bid today. 0.19%
up. So relative strength, Meta relative
strength quarter of a percent up.
Oracle,
did we gap fill on Oracle?
Did we get there?
What did I say it was? Was it 87s or
78s? I can't remember.
78. Okay, I'm going to set price alert
here
or I forget
You can see this level here. It's where
you want it to bend. There or
thereabouts.
Don't want to lose previous days value.
If you lose previous days value, you
will come and test previous week and
current day's value. You don't want to
lose previous days value.
Spy. You do not want to lose 85.
Ideally, you want ES to find a bid
initial balance high New York open.
Ideally,
what do I use to see other stock
percentages? Trading View. My watch
list. I have a watch list. See this
here? Top right? Watch list. Here's my
MAX 7 plus oracle plus equally equally
weighted and then stuff I'm following
down here. And then I have my bonds and
then FX.
Really useful to have a watch list at
the side of your one of your monitors so
you can see what's moving and you can
see where the relative strength is
coming from or relative weakness. What's
dragging the market up or dragging the
market down. Remember like the last few
days for example, I can't remember what
was bidding up. Was it Meta? Meta been
bidding up, holding the market up.
Oracle with that big sell overnight,
dragging the market down.
Still waiting here to see uh
if I want to consider a range trade.
Not really, but might not give me a
choice. Uh buyers keep getting caught
here at 90s. buyers everything is buy
side above 90s. I want to see this come
a little bit lower first ideally
trading right at previous week point of
control and current day point of
control. I do not want to be entering
around here. This is basically telling
you fair value for the last
week and this week. So it's chop zone
would love this just come down test
previous day value area low VWAP kind of
area we can see what's what
previous day's value right here 563
value area low 563 any bid in front of
that they can actually if they do a
twole they can look below and reclaim
right so you don't rule out this that's
equally good right so if they sort of
come into this area of liquidity find a
bid reclaim it that's also good But uh I
want to play this side of it. I don't
want to try and bid here hoping.
I want to see sellers come in and delta
not allow us to move down. I want to see
passive buyer sort of around here
absorbing because if we don't see that
the reason I don't want to bid against
it is what happens if they're not here
and they go, "Oh yeah, [\h__\h] you." They
can do it. You can see they did it this
way. They did it this way. They can do
it again if they want. Croak wrote
again. All right. So here we go. Here's
the drift in. Sellers are trying to sell
these lows.
Uh let's see.
Spy probably got like another point.
It's into IB high here. It's got another
move down if it wants to come down into
value.
And uh 85 test.
We will see folks. We will see.
We will see.
Are we going to test value is the
question.
They absorbing in front of value. Sell
is now caught.
Errors on my screen. There we go. Can't
put limits out again. Are you really
going to do this?
Sellers just got caught there into 70s.
All right. They came flying in at 70s.
They got caught offside there. If we
protect 70s, we're probably going to go
higher now.
I can't get a limit out. [\h__\h] ninja.
Pardon my French.
It's got to be AI trader or whatever
it's called. Here's the test 70s. They
need to hold this. If they hold 70s, we
go higher. If they don't hold 70s, it's
a problem. We'll snap down to previous
day. Okay, not holding it.
Still not in this. I was trying to get a
limit out into it. I'm kind of glad I
didn't now. So, here's a retest of value
area low previous day. Now, if they lose
this, you're going to go either full
rotation or a trap underneath. Do we
have What do we have underneath? Is
there an imbalance? No. No. Big five
minute imbalance. One minute imbalance
down to 33s. That would be disgusting.
So, you can see this is the area I think
bulls need to hold, right? If they're
going to go for the rotation back up,
they need to hold this area. If they
lose this, there's either a trap play.
All right. What you need to be careful
of is this. There's either a trap play
here or they hold this or if they lose
it, we're coming right back down to this
because we're kind of thin in here.
And that would be my worry.
All right. So, they're losing value. So,
now it's either a trap play or they're
going to lose all the way down. It's
going to go straight up, straight down.
If we're going to do that, we can think
about a fib. Remember, we didn't sweep
the low. It's the one thing we have to
bear in mind. We didn't sweep the low.
Bull flag area is into this 30 50% back
pullback will be into that imbalance.
That imbalance is at 33s.
And balance is actually up here at 33s.
So
still viable for bulls.
Alex, stop moving that you wally. Stop
it.
Sellers do keep sending the lows, but
Delta's still heavy here. Not flipping
Delta. They're trying to absorb around
previous days value. Are we at 85s yet?
Not quite. They're trying to reclaim
initial balance though on the ES.
Big battle here. They know it's a
sensitive level. Something's going to
happen here either way. We can't sit
here for too long. Someone's going to
get hurt.
Nice reclaim. Where are those sellers?
70s.
Delta's at 80s. So, it's starting to
look a little bit better for the bulls
here. They're holding that previous day
value area, but uh sellers came in at
80s. So, they came in at 70s and 80s.
So, if we get over 70s, we're going to
test 80. We get over 80 a squeeze as
possible. Just be careful because buyers
got caught at 90 and above. That's your
rotation. You just want to see a bit of
a delta flip here. Starting to see it
try and creep in.
Yeah, there's definitely a little bit of
absorption here on the tape. Looking at
the cumulative delta
price not dragging down, delta dragging
down. We've got an absorber on the tape
here, which is what we wanted to see.
So, can he just step up now and uh drive
us straight back over the 80s because
that's where the sellers came in. You
got 189 sellside delta at 80. Can we get
over that for a squeeze? Point of
control just above that as well. So,
buyers having a good go here. Here we go
over him. We should be able to squeeze
out now. Should be the start of the
squeeze. Here's point of control on the
day. Don't want to lose these 80s. You
want to see a shove over 80s. Otherwise,
we're just going to go 70 80 70 80 60 70
60 70 and no good. Okay, no good. Then
failed. Failed to hold over 80. Fail
point of control on the day. That's what
we just talked about. This area here
sensitive.
This is your fair value on the day. They
had the opportunity to do that. They
just failed. I'd be very careful now
about well, one of these moves here.
This is the hard thing right now is
timing it when they've left such a big
move.
Do they want to come all the way back
down? Very hard timing this
seller stuck under 50 right now.
Retesting that seller at 50. If they let
him out, we snap. They're aggressively
selling this. Really aggressively
selling this. They're flying into this
book. Here's the new low. So, they're
going to keep breaking down here.
Still no bulls here.
They had the opportunity to step up for
like about 30 seconds and failed
previous day low here into 28s. Uh got
an imbalance here at uh 33 to 31 by side
imbalance.
We're starting to see that pull back.
Did we ever take this high? No. I
if we' taken this out, I'd feel so much
more bullish. If we' taken this out, it
would be much easier for me to really
think about trying to attack this high
side. The fact that we haven't taken
this is a little bit concerning, but
there's your ledge.
If they lose it, they're going to come
back to here. Previous week's value and
a ledge. We're very, very thin in here.
I'm still bullish in it in based on what
I'm seeing because we've reclaimed but
uh we've losing this. I still think
bulls are not done yet.
Go all the way to the bottom. I don't
think we're going to go all the way to
the bottom. Spy holding 85. I think it's
a pullback which is likely to be
absorbed unless something changes. The
question the only question is when are
bulls willing to step in? If everyone's
like me been not playing the V-shaped
recovery, you're waiting for a pullback.
You're waiting for an area to hold. They
had the opportunity.
This is the bull flag area. If this is a
two-leg, this is the bull flag area.
Otherwise, 61 fib. Think about 61 fib is
also lining up with the previous week
value area low and the current shelf.
All right. So, maybe they're going to
hang out here.
Maybe if they can't get involved in a
bull flag higher.
But uh we're now developing potentially
a micro head and shoulder for that wash.
What will that measured move be? Will
that be if we call this the neckline?
Where's the 100%.
Oh mate, there's so many factors here
going against each other. This is not a
high confluence setup.
Spy still above 85. Still in its initial
balance. All right, let me use the
bathroom while this does whatever it's
going to do and we'll come back.
still selling. They just aggressively
sold 27s there. Are there any bids
stacking up on the book?
It's the first time seen a little bit of
a reaction here, but there's still sell
sign and balance at 550. We've started
to lose previous days value area low.
This is
basically, how can I best say this?
Weekly and daily traders are trading uh
against each other right now.
I don't think they really know what they
want to do with it. I just think it's
gamma exposure. SPY still holding IB. ES
still holding IB. Both of those still
above the New York open. Uh ENQ relative
weakness here. Unsurprising when we look
across the mag and we see what's
happening. Look at Oracle. Look at
Tesla. Look at Nvidia all in big sales.
But here we go. Here's the attempt to
reclaim value. Okay, so those sellers
underneath 30 did get stuck. This is the
attempt to reclaim value. They must
reclaim these levels. And the problem
now is if you're going to be bullish,
okay? You have to respect this level up
here. You have to unfortunately. All
right? So, if they're going to be
bullish, you need this. And really, you
want a bid over this. You want to use
pain here to move higher. Like I said, I
think they have the ability to do it,
but timing it's going to be hard. This
is the first time we've seen some
sellers trapped. We can see it. Bring
this up. Hope you can see this right
under here. You can see these sellers.
This is all sellside under sort of 40,
but definitely under 29s.
So, you wouldn't want this really to
come under 40. Now, you want to reclaim
value. You really, really, really want
to reclaim value. If you've got a shot
here of really driving back out, you
want to reclaim value.
Yeah, exactly. It it is it's the level
that we broke down from from 5:00 a.m.
this morning,
but there's
542 could potentially find a bid.
600 could potentially sell, but we poked
through it. So, it's like I just think
you've got a battle of time frames right
now.
You have a battle of time frames.
They're trying to sell this again. Heavy
delta coming in here again. Now, if they
don't get a breakdown, this will be a
clue.
Is there a passive buyer here? We're not
breaking down now. We're starting to
break down. Are they going to take out
this guy? Where did I say it was? 29s.
Aggressive selling into 29s. And they
haven't got their way yet. Doesn't mean
they don't.
There's the 29 test. Buyers need to come
get us back above 35 here to leave these
sellers stuck. Otherwise, we can still
wash. 29 test. So, still washing. Still
no alignment.
I just think SPY is going to come all
the way back down to 85 and then make a
decision. I just feel like that is all
we're going to do. I have maintained
this uh thought process for a while now.
I think option dealers are in absolute
control of the market. probably because
they don't know how to hedge this right
now because they're not sure what we're
going to do. Definitely in stagflation.
So, they're like, "Well, let's let's
just pin this market." Okay, here's a
move down to 85s, 8513s,
8514s, 8512s.
They're trying to pin this down to 85s,
and then they can make a decision maybe
once they get to 85s.
notice my IPs are wrong. My other chart
there we go is better. Right. So 85 test
spy
and we might come all the way down to
this box that we talked about
and that would be the kind of 61 and
previous week value and the edge this
current edge giving back this whole move
straight up straight down last night
straight up again this well straight
down this morning again then straight
back up and then straight back down.
We're just not finding uh or not
building anything out yet but it will
come. We're losing 85s now on the spy.
VWAP's the next spot. This is looking
very ugly for this market. How have we
gone back into range and lost range
again? Why not reject it this morning on
the retest? Why do these silly things at
the point of controls are the only thing
being traded at at the moment? So,
previous week value low, next stop
likely then I would assume and if we
lose that then probably the Globeex low
because we didn't take it this morning.
I don't think it's choppiness. I think
it's actually the the opposite. It's
it's a lack of liquidity.
It's a lack of liquidity. So, bulls want
to defend this blue box. If they don't
defend the blue box, then we're going to
we're going to go all the way for the
globe slow. They can't defend this,
we're going for globeex low. Simple as
that.
I've watched this 85 test on spy. Going
to back test it now. If they lose that
wash is available.
Failed the back test. So far
back to be what spy. If it loses if it
loses that we're going back down and
it's starting to lose it. So previous
week value area low this level key now.
If they lose this we're going back to
the GlobeEx lows in my opinion. This is
the last chance to loom for for buyers.
They need to come in here and here now.
If they don't we're coming back down
here. So they ended up doing a deep
pull. If they don't hold this then I
think there is a sell all the way back
down. Look at the lack of structure both
sides. It's ugly. So here's previous
week value area low. Are we going to
continue to sell through this now and go
for low of day?
I'd say it feels like yes. It definitely
feels like yes at the moment.
ESF VWAP. See how Spy back tested that
85 once it came under it and lost it.
Very, very thin both sides here. You're
going to have to be careful if you're
going to play this. This is crazy thin.
I think we're going to come to Globeex
low at this point though. We've lost the
key levels.
Problem is we lack liquidity. It doesn't
need to drive up to 8530s
again.
Here we go. So 84 is now on SPY. So once
it lost at 85, that was very, very
quick.
Losing previous week area low here. I
think we're probably going to trade down
to the lows. It's just a question if
they pop it up first.
VIX finding a bid after filling its gap.
This is tricky here. Previous week value
area low. So bulls trying to defend
this. I would say at this point bears
will want to sell this, sell this, sell
this. This is what they want to do to
complete it. Bulls will want to do this,
this, this, this. I think bulls are on
in a bit of danger here.
Big level here for sure.
Asia logo looks good. Yeah, it does
potentially look good. I'm not going to
deny that. I think potentially looks
good if you lose value.
But I think uh
bears need to defend 520s basically. I
think that's the level. 520s. 500 maybe.
There's some buy side delta there at
500, but 520 is somewhere up here. So,
there's the hold of this blue level. I
still think bears have got a chance
here, but you know, this market's done
weird things this morning. It's been
V-shaped recovery and then uh V-shaped
recovery and I don't know what you call
this. What's that move? Reverse V-shaped
down. Maybe we go V-shaped recovery back
to the 20s and 30s. Now,
we lack liquidity or or we lack
structure is probably a better way of
putting it. So, the moves happen sharp
and fast.
just up my phone.
It's my wife. Probably shouldn't
get a slap.
Okay, 500 test 520s above that. That's
the level. Bears need to defend. Uh they
need a breakdown underneath value.
So 500 or I'd say 98. There's some delta
there at 98. Buyers do look a little bit
trapped right now in and around there,
but uh last time we said that we just
went straight upside. So,
previous week value still holding this
blue box. We had the chance to sort of
break and use it as resistance. We're
not. We're going to bid back up towards
here now by the looks of it. Anywhere
from here, bears will need to defend and
look for that. If we get this move here,
I'm interested. Uh, I want to be very
careful because if we don't and we get
this move, we can go straight back
upside. Why am I going like, "Oh, it can
do this or it can do this." Well,
there's your weekly level. There's your
daily level. Failed. Daily level holding
weekly level. This is the problem. We're
not in alignment right now. Once we find
alignment like we had this morning was
really nice smooth trend, but we've lost
alignment. We've gone back into
rotational markets.
85 retest on the spy. Does it reclaim it
now? Jesus Christ. Can we stop trading
gamma levels, please? Dealers, just get
us out the [\h__\h] range. Please, I
don't care which way you go. Please get
us out the range. Option dealers, I
really don't care which way you want to
go with this, but it would be lovely if
we could leave this range.
Be really lovely.
20 and 30 is retest. That's what they're
trying to do.
85 retest spy again. It's right there
right now. They squeeze through this.
They're going to try and drive right
back to the highs.
There you go. Vshape again. [\h__\h]
hell. Come on.
You think the market's been in range
most of the time this year? Are you mad?
Are you mad? You think this year we've
been in range?
Seriously, you think this is a range?
You think that's a range? I'm being
deadly serious. You think that's a
range? This is a range. Uh, that is not
a range. Uh, that is not a range.
Yeah.
Don't know what to say to that.
I don't I don't know what you're looking
at. If you think the chart's been uh in
a range most of the time this year,
get back to these 30s.
Let's buy back over 85s.
Can go 88s if it really wants. Now, I've
become completely uninterested in this
market now. We're just going to do
silliness. And Friday tomorrow they're
going to do more silliness. What is the
Hang on?
When's expiration?
19th. So they've got another week of
doing this silliness.
One more week of silliness.
Anky might still dump. Yeah, it might
might still pump though. I I would not
bet on anything right now. Look,
blue box. Weekly players said no, we're
not going lower. Daily players will try
and say no, we're not going higher. So,
daily players want this down under here.
Weekly players want this up over here.
There's the battle. This is the first
time we've actually built out liquidity.
This is your rotation. Acceptance above,
we're going to go. Acceptance below,
we're going to go. This becomes the
rotation. This that's just all it is.
It's I'm going to stop talking about
rotations cuz I feel like I talk about
it on here a lot and
people join the channel and just can't
see it and don't understand it.
Has anyone got um some GEX levels up on
Spy? Can you just tell me if if you've
got them up?
Has the uh put wall moved up from 82?
And is there anything below? And is the
call wall still 88, 90, and 700?
If anyone's got that up, it' be useful.
I would imagine so, but it would just be
good to know
initial balance. Yes, I've lost interest
here, folks. I'm just going to be
honest. I've lost interest because we're
uh in a rotation.
I want to be interested in selling this,
but I'm not. I want to be interested in
selling this, but I'm not. I have to
respect this right now.
680 put.
Yeah. So far away. So that's the biggest
level. 7690. Yeah, I know. 7690.
Um, okay.
Thanks, Julian. Thanks, Myon.
And most of that will be for next week
I'm assuming
680 put. Yeah. So we haven't even tested
it then. Here we go. Spy is going to go,
man. SPY wants to go. This thing's going
to squeeze again. So weekly players
trying to take control. Can they get
back inside previous days range? Um
probably at this point. And this is the
level right here. This guy right here.
That's your rotation here to here. Here
to here. I don't know what happens until
we get outside of this box right now.
This is your box.
Right. They've confirmed that as the
box. That's where we're pinned.
That is where we're pinned. No doubt
about it.
There you go. Rejection insider value.
[\h__\h] hell, mate.
What a [\h__\h] market. Every time I think
we might get a really good market.
We get back into this.
Look at that last candle.
It's like a 50 point I don't know what
to do candle. Look at that.
505 to 555s and no edge in it.
We did. We got an awesome Look, I'm not
complaining, right? Look, I'm not I'm
not complaining. It's It's been a decent
day. I'm not complaining, but it's just
like,
come on. Let's Let's de Let's develop
something. You've had FOMC.
You've had your ability to go upside.
You failed. We know the market's [\h__\h]
Every idiot under the sun wants to talk
about quantitive easing. Stick it up
your ass. The market's [\h__\h] No one's
working. You've got a liquidity crisis.
I guess we're just waiting for Japan to
absolutely tank this market next week.
And then my question is, everyone knows
that's coming. Is it already sort of
priced in? But maybe that's what we've
got to wait for. We've just probably got
to wait for this carry trade to see if
it actually does anything. I would like
it to do something, but the more I think
about it, the more I think if everyone's
looking for the same thing, it will not
happen. But I'll talk about it in the in
the newsletter on Saturday.
It feels like a small cap market. I
can't like I cannot say it enough. NQ
literally feels like a small cap market
now.
And if everyone's waiting for the trade
or the carry trade,
it just makes me feel like a small cap.
If everyone's waiting for a fade and
everyone's stacked shorts side in it,
then the chances of it happening are not
very high and it's probably going to go
the other way and catch everyone. So
that's where my head's at
and it's probably where dealers heads at
as well.
What date is that trade? Is it the 18th?
Is it be
options and 19th? Hang on. JPY carry
trade. I put this up yesterday. Why
can't I remember anything?
19th. Okay. Carry trade 19th.
OPEX 18th. It's all heading towards that
date then. That's that's what we're
heading towards.
18th 19th. Look. Market doesn't know
what to do now.
What date that JD
have a look
anytime? Didn't they already vote on it?
And um he said he just pushed back. I
don't understand. Right. Explain to me
this one thing. If they come out and say
it's illegal, he can't do it. What are
they doing with all the money which has
already been gained? What hap? How do
you give that money back? Who's tracking
that? If they can't even track the jobs
numbers, how they tracking the uh
billions or trillions, if you listen to
Trump, of dollars that they've made out
of the tariffs, they're back into this.
You can see this blue line. This is the
the level. This is your overunder right
now. This is daily daily traders, daily
short sellers trying to force the market
down. Weekly
buyers trying to force the market up.
And we're trading against each of them
right now.
Market down 1% and VIX even. Um, it just
I would say the VIX is actually up
0.44%.
And the ES is down 0.25%. So,
correlation still there.
Correlation's still there.
Long 25473.
You got long on the level down here, was
it? Nice. It's good. It's a good long.
Just make sure you're paying yourself
some here because you don't this might
come right back down. This is your
rotation like we talked about. This is
your box. This is why I've come
uninterested.
We did talk about potentially getting
long here, but uh I didn't like that we
lost that level really. That would have
been much easier play. I just don't want
to play a rotation now where we're
fighting. Um because this can be a lower
high, this can be a higher low. This can
be the rotation. They will build out
here until they're ready to make a
decision.
You can see that blue line and this blue
line. That's where we're in stuck in
between right now.
Uh, I don't think so. Dim.
I think that just I think it will always
say reset account if you want to do it.
I don't think so. But you won't know
until you get to end of day. Unless
you're looking at your screen and you
can you I mean you know if you've blown
it. It will tell you in front of you.
Um,
I think both sides are though, uh,
Sigma. I think you'll find you've got
both sides.
So, if you look up here, if we just get
you on map, this is why I don't trust it
right now. All right. If we just look at
this.
Yeah, buyers came in here.
These guys down here are still caught.
So
yeah, I don't know, man. I just think
it's a rotation now.
Made my money anyway. And how long we
got left? A [\h__\h] hour left. God, this
is going slow.
Yeah, I don't have a bias right now.
I don't have a bias.
If we go to 5 minute,
you can see we're holding
here.
Here. No acceptance. No acceptance.
If we lose this, maybe
it's just really like for me now it's
becoming harder and harder and harder to
pull the trigger. Just it just looks
like the market doesn't know what it's
what it wants to do. Oh, I had you on
the wrong thing. I'm sorry. Yeah.
No acceptance.
No acceptance. If we look at that same
level overnight, this is where we found
a bid.
If we look at this same level here,
this is where they lost control.
And that's just your rotation. Now
until we get confirmation and one side
really comes in more aggressive and
starts to win
on the daily. Um,
yeah, but to to where JD, that's the
thing, right? We keep holding this low
volume node.
I want to see us trade into 900. I I
think there's a really good trade down
into here,
24,900.
And then the other one is 24,200. This
guy here, right? 20-day, 50-day. Lots of
reasons to come down here, but uh all
depends. Are we going to reject this
range?
I guess this here is key. 650s, 630s.
I guess you're right. All the time we're
rejecting 630s and 650s,
there's potential, right? There's
potential to move lower. I think you're
actually right. All the time we're
rejecting up there, there's potential to
move lower.
Oh, sorry folks. Do that again. You got
this weekly kind of level here which we
keep coming into
and we cannot find acceptance beneath
previous week value area low and that's
all I know right now in the current day.
Here's value area low of the current
day. Here's our profile on the current
day 620 to 500 and we're not finding
acceptance either side of that.
What trade copier do I use? Um, I
currently use uh affordable indicators
trade copier.
Spy 685 again. Same level
685 again.
Mag still does not look pretty out
there. All of it down other than
Microsoft, but uh
is 500 probably the key level.
psychological.
Yeah. Well, quite right, JD. We'll see.
Right. Maybe a revisit of previous week
value here and maybe then they make a
decision. Maybe they come back up to
those 20s and 30s again. Maybe then they
make a decision.
What are you saying, Rosco? On the 10 on
five days, you have triples at 870s.
870s.
Okay. What I'd say up there is yesterday
that was the target, right, was to take
that liquidity and once we took it,
we've rolled away from it. I'm not
convinced there was enough excess up
there, Rosa, if I'm honest. Like, we
took it by like a point
uh 868 and we traded to 872. We took it
by like a point. Um,
should we move away from it? Yeah. Would
I have preferred a bit more of a push
through and then a rejection? Yeah,
that's been the story of ENQ for a while
recently. But yeah, potentially.
And it and it applies to every time
frame for sure, but like every time
every time frame with fractal.
We got hate in the chat, have we?
[\h__\h] hilarious.
Uh, indie power. It does it. Everything
I teach works for everything. Market
will work the same way. No matter what
you're looking at
sellers tried to step in there at value
and couldn't get a force down. They got
caught again. This market still does not
know what it wants to do. We're just
doing a rotation. They just stepped
stepped in there at 95s and no follow
through and spy at 85. Market's gone to
sleep.
Market's gone to sleep at this level.
Bears need a breakdown underneath
previous week value. Simple as that.
Bulls need to reclaim previous days
value. Simple as that. Nothing else we
can do.
Uh, Billy, just quit for the day, mate.
If you if you got that back, quit for
the day. Walk away
because you like, you know, you should
have stopped out. You didn't stop out.
You made it back by the sounds of it.
Um, definitely don't take another trade.
Chances of you taking another trade and
winning is very, very small. If you ever
go like max loss and get back to break
even, the chance of you actually going
positive is very small. Yeah, good for
you, mate. I mean, well done for logging
out, but slap on the wrist for not
stopping out.
Spy holding 85s. Doesn't want to let go
of 85s.
Does not want to let go of 85s.
telling you this is just [\h__\h] option
dealers, man.
There's nothing to do here. There's no
trade to put on. There's literally
nothing to do. There's nothing to do.
We're just going to chop in this range.
You just got to let it do whatever it is
it needs to do.
It is a shame.
It is a shame that we've had a fail
break at both sides.
Trying to think of the last time I saw
that
of like a multi-week range where we had
a fail break out both sides on this
chart.
October. Not really.
It's been a while.
Been
a while since I've seen this.
Yeah, I bet. Julian,
I bet. How do you like So, I'm
interested. How if you if you trade
pretty much exclusively off Gamma, what
do you do? Do you just bid 82? Like when
we hold 82, you bid 82, you take some
off 85s. If we hold 85s, you bid 85s,
you try and take some off at 80. You
lose 85s, you sell 85s, you bid 82 back.
I'm interested if you're just
exclusively playing that how how you
position yourself.
Options are way beyond me, man. They're
just scary. And are you are you playing
zero DTE in those or are you going
further out?
still stuck at value area low for the
session.
In the last one, two, three, four, five,
six candles, buyers are stuck over 20s
and uh over 20s, over 02s and sellers
are stuck under 96. That's how tight
it's gone. Feels like flush is coming,
but I wouldn't guarantee it if we're
holding 85s. If we lose 85 and it's
probably a bigger move.
I want to wait to see if we get outside
value. Can we get outside value? Are we
going to start washing
spy 85 again?
Um what is coming up rest of the day
starting to lose 85s potentially here.
Do they rebid it though? We're
underneath current value. Do we trade to
value area low? Feels like it wants to
wash, but what it feels like and what it
does have been two different things
recently. There's the retest of value
reclaim of 85 holding VWAP. Yeah, buyers
did just get caught on this candle here.
So all the time we protect 500 I think
maybe maybe a move back down to 470s
but SPY is going to make it very hard
for you I would say if you're adamant on
trying to get this rotation once that
thing loses it you can just set a price
alert I set it underneath as well
because it keeps ducking underneath and
finding a bid on VWAP. 85 is basically
VWOP right now on the spiders and that's
that is the soak level. If they lose
that, 82 is the level I would say. Well,
what was that pin? 84 we traded at
earlier. Don't remember seeing anything
there. Maybe Julian can tell me
otherwise, but 82 was the level
downside.
Yeah, totally.
So, how much like if you're trading off
it, how much room do you give it? Like
for example, today
we
trade if you were bidding 85 on that
pullback, we traded right down to 84.
How much room do you give it? Do you
give it level to level and you're
trading like small size or are you going
far enough out that you don't really
care?
Still, these buyers keep getting stuck.
If they're trying to trade through 500
and they're not getting their way,
that's the one, two, three attempts now
to get through 500, not getting their
way, which is value on the day.
Delta's trying to move higher, price is
moving lower. There's a seller on the
tape.
[\h__\h] delta is trying to move higher.
Price is moving lower. There's
definitely a seller on the tape
versus 500, I'd say, at the moment. So,
we might get a snap here. Here's your
previous week open. I think there's a
snap potentially coming here just based
on what I've seen on the delta there.
And your cover level will be 470. If we
let go of that, it would be lower of
day. Remember, we didn't take out
Gloveex. 500 is key. Uh 5685
is key. Here you go. Here's a snap. So
70s previous week value area low
possible here and if they get under that
then you're looking for Gloveex and that
delta did just shift pretty nasty there.
So the buyers over 500 did just get
caught.
Spy will not let go of it.
Julian, is is it you? You're just buying
you're just constantly buying calls.
So that was your cover point into
previous week value and the weekly
players have just come in there again.
Uh I would still maintain buyers
currently are caught at five over 500.
what's that last four candles? One two
three four 500 to 507s.
There is a sellside imbalance to 50875.
So 500 to 507s is where those buyers got
caught. If they reclaim that then um
potential squeeze but until that point
they are out the money but again spy
will not let go of 85.
I'm trading them like futures taking
partials on ES MEES and SPX.
Good for you mate.
If you bought um out of interest, if you
bought a zero I don't know, you might
might not be able to tell me, but if you
bought the 82s this morning on a zero
DTE and you sold 85s,
what would you have uh what would the
percentage gains have been on this
morning? I reckon they would have been
pretty good because that drop was pretty
nasty. Probably everyone was a bit
worried just out of interest. Is it like
a 100% gain or something in what's that
5 10 15 20 minute 15 minutes you could
have got it in 15 minutes
out of interest.
So if you bought that c that 10 a.m.
move into 82s and you sold
1010 so 10 minute candle you sold 1010
into 85 and you bought the zero
um expireies.
Come on. Do something.
Those
buyers got caught again, but there
sellers caught on that last uh dip down
and sellers got caught under 77s.
It's just it's just back and forth here,
folks. Testing each side of it.
Oh, you're trading SPX as well. So,
there's a few of you trading options
here.
Yeah. Uh, yeah, I was good friends with
Am. Um, I was on cuff. I had a track
called Fun Train to Reno. Um, which I
released on Cuff. A mean was like an
early supporter of me. I used to I used
to do all the cuff shows, sank keys and
stuff.
It was good good fun. Don't know why
that just got removed, but
yeah. A mean's he's gone solo now. Dance
is just doing um producing for hip-hop
artists in Marseilles.
Those are good those are good times,
man. Very fond memories.
Are you a fan of that G House?
Good fun.
He's a really nice guy. I mean, really
did good dude. You love it. Are you from
France? From like where you from? You
English?
Italian. Italian. And you love your G
house
living in London. I would have thought
like you'd be fans of the Italian guys
in London then
like Cim.
Maybe a bit more housey for you.
I'm from I'm from London, but I live in
Los Angeles. Man, this market doesn't
know what to do.
Back to 85 on the spy we go.
Big kill candle there.
My stomach's rumbling. I need to eat.
back down to previous weekly open.
Are they going to just pop this straight
back up to 500?
Yep.
They just soaked 85 again. I think
there's a snap coming soon. They can't
keep soaking and soaking and soaking and
soaking without a break. One way or
another,
I'd be watching these 500s here. There's
a sellside imbalance to 506. But again,
we're still just trading between
previous day value, previous week value.
Did we take any trades today? Yeah, I
was short this morning.
From Mexico, living in Chicago.
I used to enjoy uh playing in Mexico
prior to uh them arresting Chapo when
BPM was still going. It was so much fun
that festival before they went and
murdered everyone on the beach.
I used to go there every year. Where
else did I play? I used to play uh Merid
Merida. Did I say it right? Merida.
Meridia.
And I'm friends with quite a few guys
from Chicago. Um
John Summit. John Shust is from Chicago.
Um
who else? I think
feels like they want to break down, but
these shorts can't get continuation.
Every time they try and sell underneath
82, they're getting stuck.
Um, who else? Who used to do the vocals
for me?
Can't think of his name. I'm going to
have to look it up now.
find it. Why I can't think of his name?
That's embarrassing, man. It's been so
long since I've played
Trying to find a picture of me at ADA
and then I remember everyone.
Oh, it's breaking down. [\h__\h] The moment
I look away.
Oh, you bastard.
Okay. Previous week value area low. Do
they sell under this now for expansion
is the question I would have. The answer
is yes. Oh my god. The m This is why you
can't get distracted like I just did.
The moment I look away, we start doing
it. All right. So, ES starting to let go
of those 85s.
If we start rejecting previous week
value and current week value. So, if we
dri reject 77 to 90, there's a drift
lower here in this market available.
And I've missed an entry by [\h__\h]
around on my phone like an idiot. It's
my fault.
My absolute fault there.
Okay, back to value. This is where big
buyers came in. Where was their ledge up
here? tens.
So tens, no it was tens. Five tens where
they got stuck. Okay. So willing for it
to go there, but I'd rather we didn't go
that high. If I'm going to resell this,
I'd rather watch this guy 82 and 90. So
let's see how we act up here. Do they
resell this on this push? Or is that yet
another fail breakdown under me previous
week? I'm watching SPY back into 85,
which is retesting now. So do they
resell this for the move to 82 or do
they reclaim it for move to 88?
And that's on spy that I'm talking about
when I say 82 and 88.
Very very thin on that kill candle above
500 to 506.
I'd say sellers are in control here
versus sort of 506. 500 506 sellers are
in control for a potential leg down.
This depends if they're going to give
any follow through today.
OTM puts were 24x.
That's awesome. You're doing on props
right now. What as in uh there's
options? There's Sorry, how do I say
that? There's props for options.
I didn't know that.
Okay, here's the ledge into this area.
If they reclaim this, we go straight up.
If they reject this, they're going to
retest this low and they're going to try
and get acceptance under value. So, this
is the area here. Bears must defend this
if they really, really want to get that
GlobeEx. If they don't, then this just
comes straight back up to here. Again,
you can see we're very, very thin in
here like I just talked about. So,
here's the attempt to defend it.
They just trapped a ton of buyers in
that last move up there.
This buy still holding 85. It's still
not getting a confirmation of a big kill
candle yet. It feels like it's coming,
but we're not getting confirmation yet.
It's a good rejection of that ledge,
though. They need to close outside of
previous week value here. And then we
can go pukey puke
main flush in the afternoon. You might
well be right, Peter. Uh, I won't be
here for it today, unfortunately.
Just like last night when I was so
pissed off last night,
I went out for food. I was watching a
film. I thought, oh, just quickly check
the charts. And I saw where we were and
I was like, you have got to be [\h__\h]
me.
Yeah. Nvidia 3.65%. 65% down. It's just
Oracle, mate. Anything anything chip
related is going to get dragged.
Yeah, I know a few of you would have
been insane. What was tough is I was
waiting for two moves last night,
yesterday. I was looking for Here they
are. All right, so this was posted uh
3:22 in the afternoon. Right. So, this
is what I was looking for. either a
retest after taking out the high and a
squeeze back higher or a break under and
stay heavy for the rotation. If we look
at what we actually got, it was even if
we look at that level that I'm talking
about rejection into sort of 230 240s.
We look at what actually happened.
230s was it 730s? I think it was I just
said 230s.
7:30s or is it 6
uh yesterday?
Yeah.
Right. Right here.
If we look at what we got,
break down.
There's the rejection and there's the
roll. And if you look at what I said I
was looking for, right? Breakdown,
rejection, roll back down to previous
day value, previous week value. is
literally perfect. This is everything I
was looking for. Previous week value,
previous day value. It's just [\h__\h]
annoying when they do it. I got to stop
swearing. It's really upsetting when
they do it when you've been waiting for
it and they do it when you're not at
your desk.
Did any of you actually get it? I'm I'm
interested.
Did any of you get it? Were any of you
at your desk for GlobeEx for the Asia
Move or did any of you bid it back up? I
think that was a really brave move to
bid it back up. I didn't want to bid it
back up after the leaving value.
Nice. Yeah, I mean I caught a tiny bit
and then I had one more go and I left it
on and I was like we either dump or we
don't and got knocked out just just in
front of break even on it. Good for you
though, Chris.
in sim. Yeah, but sim's still good,
mate. It's just practice, isn't it? All
right, so reclaiming current value area.
No acceptance underneath previous week.
I am feel like I'm repeating myself.
I feel like I'm repeating myself. I tell
you what, though. If these guys don't
get this breakdown soon, they're going
to get caught. All right, because they
cannot sell under here. They've had
numerous attempts. If they don't get it
soon, this is going to happen. They're
going to get caught. All right, they
need this. And if they don't get it,
they are going to get this slammed.
Wouldn't be slammed pumped in their
face. So they running out of time here
versus this ledge here. They must
protect this ledge. Failure to protect
this ledge.
There's lots of room upside for them to
come and squeeze. Because at the moment,
if we think about this,
there's the pullback for bulls to buy,
right? There's the push. Here's the
attempt from shorts to fail. they
haven't completed it. This here is a
failed break. All right? So, if they
cannot get under this level here, this
is where shorts will get caught and they
will allow a squeeze back up to here,
here, here, and who knows what happens
once we start running. Okay, so shorts
right now are definitely caught versus
this level. They've had numerous
attempts. One attempt here, another
attempt here, another attempt here, and
they're starting to get themselves
caught offside. It can change very very
quickly like we've seen very very quick
moves today when they when they've got
enough c offside.
This is why I'm
skeptical in this area.
Time frames not aligning. Look at this
even here. Lower time frame in a buy.
Higher time frame in a cell.
Lack of alignment.
squeezes
on here.
Squeezes on. Nobody looks. But
shifting so quick this uh tape once
they've got one side caught and it's
just like we go the other way for 5
minutes and then stuck and then we go
back down for five minutes.
Yeah, let's have a look at these H1s.
This um valid point there. One of the
raises.
It's uh it's messy.
All right.
Current week point control up here.
Unable to reclaim it since the New York
open. All right. staying heavy but
unable to break down under this low.
Does this look bearish? It does look
bearish. But why are we not breaking
down under this low?
That's my question right now. We should
we should be breaking down under that
low based on what they've done here.
Failed breakout, taken liquidity,
failed, pull back in, sell, didn't take
the low. Okay. Build more liquidity.
Haven't taken the low. They need to
break down here. All right. The shorts
need to take control of this market and
break down. The one thing I'd say is
these shorts, as we know, since April
have uh not been very good at doing
their job. But if they get the breakdown
here, then this level here can be traded
into. And this level here for me, this
is your magnet. All right, this right
here, this guy right here is a magnet.
Doesn't have to happen today. Can take
days and weeks to happen, but this trade
here feels like it needs to happen in
this market, but they're just not
willing to do it right now.
too much conflicting uh thoughts on
what's happening in the market macro
wise. I would say
20 minutes left. Oh, and then it's gym
time.
Leg day.
starting to find balance today.
This looks like a fairly typical Dshape.
Not good for those of you looking for
trend.
any giveaways yet? We're going to do an
a Apex giveaway. I'm going to do a
Christmas giveaway as well. Um it's
going to have to be either on the
community or on Twitter. Um, we're going
to give away
three different winners. We'll do it uh
a funded next account,
an Apex account, and
what else we do? Maybe we do one of the
new courses or a coupon for the course.
Um, so there'll be three different
winners. I'm going to probably set it up
next week. It will have to be on like
some stupid thing which I don't want to
do like a Twitter question or on the
community tab on YouTube because Funded
Next won't won't give me codes just to
give to you guys.
So, I don't know why, but for whatever
reason, um, they want me to set up like
a Q&A or, uh, something where you guys
respond and then I pick the winner and
you have to give me your email and I
have to send it to them. Such a lengthy
process for a giveaway, but I can't
control what they do, guys. I'm really
sorry.
Alex, I have a question for you, bud. I
bought my first Apex yesterday. I made
290 over the profit target. the eval.
When will I know that I pass it? At the
end of day today. Give them like an hour
or two after close the day. It's done.
Aha. Oh, got you, Jillian. I understand.
Awesome work, mate. Nice work.
All right. So, uh 85 held spy and uh
we're probably going to go 88.90 now. So
the squee like I said about I don't know
three minutes ago squeezes on here
failed to break down all the way back
down to pre or all the way back up to
previous day value area and you'd say
shorts have failed this rotation and
we're going to come back up to this
point of control and if we find
acceptance over it well a ginormous
squeeze is potentially on here now
mad mad mad mad market can't make its
mind up but it's starting to potentially
make its mind up once we get over here
remember this is liquidity they need to
get over here if they are able to base
around here. Build liquidity. This is
available. If they chop it, then they
just chop it back down and that becomes
your range. Look at the range on the
day. That's your range on the day. Six
to 470 130 pointsish.
So this PC and stuff here becomes key.
And this is currently trading into value
area low on the current week, developing
week.
We can pass in one day on Apex. I took
one with your code yesterday, mate. Is
this you? Just say I'm not sure. I don't
know what you mean. Can you pass in one
day? Yeah, you can pass in one day, one
trade, whatever you want to do.
Yeah. Um, you can just uh rotate a
micro. Just press buy sell the next two
days. You don't need to make profit. You
just need to trade them.
Will any trade copers group different
prop firms at the same time? Yeah,
most of them will.
Most of them will.
Okay. It's a current we're trading back
up to uh
point of control on this session. This
is where sellers came in last time. 880
all the way up to sort of 890. Am I
saying it wrong? 580 to 590. Jesus
Christ, Alex, you're an absolute
imbecile today. Can't talk. 580 to 590.
All right, we can zoom in on this. 580
to 590. Here's current point of control
and previous week point of control. All
right, this is fair value for the last
week and current week. And this is also
the edge of current developing value.
All right, and if they fail this, they
will need to hold this. If they don't
hold this, well, guess what? We just
come back down and test another ledge.
This is just all this market can do
right now is rotate. We It has the
chance to go super bull here, honestly,
if it can catch enough. But, uh, you're
a braver person than me if you want to
trade back inside this old range.
For me, when I'm looking at the hourly,
we're just trading right into the edge
of it. We can This is why I have
conflicting ideas right now. We see
this. This is developing profile for the
week, right? This is current week. We've
traded outside of it. We traded inside,
rejected. We're coming back to hit
question mark. Do we reject
for this roll down? Why haven't we taken
it? Why haven't we taken the lows? If we
get back inside, yeah, maybe more
upside, but it's ugly, man. You just got
so much conflicting
things here. If we done this,
I'd be way more bullish.
But we didn't do that.
And the squeezes happen so quick.
They're just like, "Okay, we're going
right once we trap down here. Okay,
we're going. 100 points."
It's still inside initial balance as
well.
What trading interview? Uh platform just
purchased it. What? What? Which one did
you purchase? Indie power.
Because if you purchased it, there's if
you actually bought an indicator, it
tell you exactly what to do. You log in.
Which Trading View one? The Flow Zone
Pro.
Yeah. So, if you if you log in now to
that platform,
um
it will tell you what to do. It'll tell
you the email to email me at and I'll
sort you out.
Point of control here. All right. So, if
they squeeze through this, you got
previous week point of control, current
value area high 604.
That's kind of the level that it can
trade up to. And if they're going to
start really turning this on, they're
going to have to start setting a big old
squeeze out. Uh ES starting to go,
spy starting to go. Previous uh day
close possible on the spy here. It's
really not very far away. Same with ES
should go and fill that gap now on those
markets. I would say big old squeeze out
here is possible on those markets. 600 a
big level.
So ES is getting very close to this
level up here. It's very close to this
close up here. So relative strength in
those markets. So possible squeeze up
here. I'd say we're now above value um
point control on the day. Lots of buying
coming in here. It's just whether they
can continue a squeeze. You've been
straight up. This is just a huge squeeze
out. It's nothing else.
So reflipped value, so held value. So
now you're starting to see alignment
where weekly players want it up, daily
players want it up, and where they're
trying to go. Weekly, weekly, daily, and
then these levels up here. Completion of
rotation will be all the way up here. So
if we're not going to auction under
these then we should auction back to
this
should
didn't do it earlier has failed numerous
times and this is your key level.
So, here's a retest of previous day
again.
Are they just really going to leave this
pinned in between the two?
VIX finding a bit of previous day low. I
can't imagine this auctions finished
higher after just work. They've just
worked so hard to do this move. Are they
literally going to give this right back
to 24s? I cannot imagine them doing
that. But they've done some weird things
today in leaving liquidity.
So ES just poked through initial balance
high. Look above IB high and fail. It
had a gap filled to 91. We got up to 86.
It's now rotating back inside. It might
try and test 78 to 75 on ES. Uh spy just
ripped up to 87. might well come back
here to what's this 86es. You wouldn't
want to see it back at 85. If it comes
all the way back at 85, it's major
problem again.
Gold alltime high. Is it really? O
node here. They need to hold this. So,
they just got stuck at point control
again. So, current and previous week
point control hit all here and current
value area high, value area low for the
week. So, there's your resistance point
and this might be the new rotation. Oh
my god. So, all they had to do is get
over that for the squeeze. They failed.
So, this might be the new rotation, you
know.
Pathetic. They're pathetic. Both sides
pathetic.
No Santa rally for NASDAQ. Um
probably not. But uh I mean things can
change very quickly like we know.
This got news hitting the tape bit. What
is going on here?
So, back down into the shelf and view
up.
So, straight squeeze up. We uh lacked a
pullback. Here comes the pullback. Do
they find a bid here now? Or are they
just going to collapse this whole thing
from one side to the other?
Dogs just w. All right, Luna.
So, if we lose this shelf, we're going
to go into that low volume node and
trade right the way back down to the
500s.
I expect they would try and hold this
shelf here,
Indie P. Just shoot I tell you what,
just shoot me an email
info@flowzonerader.com.
Shoot me an email and um I'll look it
up. But you should just be able to log
in to the course and it should tell you
what to do unless there's an issue with
it
and I'll sort it as soon as I get off
stream. I'll sort that for you.
Big sellers trying to force it down here
into this low volume node. Oh my god,
this market is terrible. It's just
squeeze one way, squeeze the other.
Squeeze one way, squeeze the other. It's
uh we lack we lack any structure here.
We lack any confirmation. They they had
the ability here to try and confirm
weekly and daily buys tried to confirm
to go higher. They failed. They're going
to come straight back down. Here's your
node. They can look for that rotation.
If they fail that, they look for this
rotation. This just becomes a no trade
zone for me. I've maintained that
numerous times. If we can get outside of
value, I'm interested in trading. Once
we're inside of value, when it's, you
know, unwilling to move properly, I'm
very uninterested.
This is just uh become more and more and
more sloppy. They had the ability to do
this move, they failed. They now have
the ability to do this move, but they
failed every time they've come down
here. It's
not a momentum trader's dream. This,
let's say that
[\h__\h] me.
We come back to 85s. Yeah, spy is coming
back to 85s. What is this market?
Let me just let me just get this right.
They checked 85 5 10 15 20 25 30 35 40
4550 for for an hour. They checked 85.
They break out of 85 and they think,
"Oh, [\h__\h] We better check it one more
time." Are you for real, guys? Are you
for real right now?
Yeah. Let me just make sure 85 is okay
one more time. Oh, [\h__\h] It's not okay.
So much selling here. It's insane. Like
straight up, straight down. This is the
market today. Insane.
Insane. in the membrane.
Back to 450, you think? Where's 450? Oh,
back to this. Yeah, I mean you if you
called it. I didn't see you call it, but
if you did, yeah, then you you are
indeed correct.
Back to value.
Are they going to bid off here though
and just go back upside again with no
follow through? Like, what are they
going to do? Here's 85s coming on the
spiders.
Quick, let's bid value. Let's buy value
again. Let's just trade back to the
other side of the range because we've
got no follow through.
There you go. Bid value. Quick, quick
bid value. Bid, bid, bid, bid, bid, bid,
bid, bid, bid, bid, bid. Do they get
stuck though finally today? Do we
actually get a follow through in this
market? Is there ever going to be a
follow through in this market for more
than like a minute?
They're trying to bid it and they're
getting caught. They're trying again.
Passive buyer here. He's trying to step
in here. I think he's going to get
caught here.
Here comes Spy into VW up and the all
important level 85.
If we do a Vshape off 85, I'm going to
[\h__\h] I don't know what I'm going to
do.
I'm going to do a naked dance on stream.
Okay, back to previous week. Valer low.
Can we please see some acceptance? I'm
happy to play lower. If we're going to
if we can see some acceptance under
here, it' be really actually really
nice.
might actually do something today.
Running out of time into lunch though,
right under 85 now. Are we now going to
see acceptance lower? Please don't
Vshape off this same level. Let's see
some acceptance lower so we can actually
do something.
Here come the bid bid bid bid bid. Here
they come. Bid bid bid bid bid bid bid
bid. Previous we value low 85id bid.
They come flying in. Right. If we if we
can now break below them, it would be
fun. If they bid this up to 520, I will
not come back this afternoon. Bid bid
bid bid bid. Here they come flying.ID
bid bid. If they get stuck, we can have
some fun here and we might actually
break down. If they go bid bid bid bid
bid bid bid. I'm uninterested. I want
them to go bid bid bid bid bid bid and
get smacked in the face.
Get smacked in the face. Come on.
They're trying. They're trying to bid
it. They're getting stuck here. Come on.
Get undervalue for [\h__\h] sake. We can
have some fun if we get undervalue. Come
on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on.
Come on. Come on.
85 85 85 85 85 85 Come on, auction
dealers, just pull it. Pull your 85. Let
it go 82. It would be so much fun if you
actually do that. Finally, we've got
GlobeEx to go for. There's a low hanging
fruit down there we can go for. Come on,
market. You've got to get under these
70s.
I tell you what, there was last time we
down here, there was a seller stuck at
58. So, just be aware of that from when
we were down here at 11:30.
There's a chance to I I do think there's
a chance to snap this. It's just whether
they need to pop it up first
because it's a third visit. Now,
once this goes, we've got a low hanging
fruit down here. This is just rotation,
rotation, rotation. I want to play
outside of rotation. I don't want to
play in here. I want to see this if
we're going to play that or I want to
see this if we're going to play that. I
don't want to play in that. It's just
garbage.
Okay, here comes Mr. Bid bid.
Mr. 85 absorbing again.
Bid bid bid bid bid bid bid. Come on.
Seller stepping down into 512s here.
So, they're trying to get filled into
twelves here. Oh, he's just pulled it up
higher.
He's moved up to 37s here now. Let's see
if they pop this up and then smack it.
Answer is so far, yes. Okay, this is
good. They need follow through now. Now
or never for these spares. They need
follow through now. Now or never because
they just came flying in. Doesn't look
good for them.
And you got a spoofer on the tape who
keeps lifting his offer. That's not
good. Look. And he's just lifted again.
That's not a look a good look at all for
these bears. If you've got a spoofer
lifting his offer, probably means he's a
buyer and he's not actually interested
in getting filled to the sell. So,
you're going to have to wait for a
momentum shift here to come. And it's
gone buy side delta and they're starting
to try and squeeze this all the way back
out. I'd say 500 is going to be the key
level over 500 low volume node straight
up to 520. So, if they get over 500,
they're going 520 and you're right back
into this low volume node here. So bears
failing miserably to get this breakdown.
This is their level to defend. If they
don't, they come right back here and
this becomes yet again a no trade zone
because we never broke underneath value
for me to want to get involved. Just
repeats the same thing. Terrible. Look
at that. Straight up to 520s. There we
go. What an awful market. Absolutely
awful market. You cannot Well, you can
do what you want. I cannot trade inside
value like this. is far too dangerous.
They have every opportunity to take
control and they are not. That's all I
know about this market. Every
opportunity buyers have to have to take
control, they are failing. Every
opportunity sellers have to take
control, they are failing. So, all we're
doing is a very [\h__\h] dance right now.
Here's your dance.
That's your dance.
Sellers can't take control. Buyers can't
take control. [\h__\h] dance. All right,
that's that's your market. That's what
you've got.
Is it lunch now? Oh, yes. Okay. So,
small day. I mean, relatively speaking,
considering what was in front of me, I
don't think that was really the best ex
execution
today. Where did we trade? We traded the
breakdown under underneath previous
week, right? We caught that there. That
was it. That's all we caught. It's the
only time all day that we've left value
once we reclaimed it. There was probably
a trade upside, but like we say, Alex
doesn't like trading inside value. So,
ever since 10:05, there's basically not
been a trade opportunity.
This is your box for me. For you, if you
like trading rotations and and value,
there's plenty of trade opportunities
for what I look for. Look at the flow
zones.
Gross. I want outside of here or back
above here. Either side. I don't care
which side. I'm not going to play inside
here. Okie dokie.
Yo, what's up, Tony?
How's it going, man?
My Mexicali brother. I hope you're good,
dude.
You got a rinse on Netflix. What? You
were long Netflix?
I mean, what you were long postlit?
It's into an interesting area to bid
back up to be honest.
Possible buy here versus 82s.
I like I like this zone here.
This last pullback zone. That's probably
a buy zone.
That's probably a buy zone. If you swing
long, that's your buy zone. uh you're
going to have to hold it for one to five
years,
right?
Because they've done a split now. So,
lots more liquidity injected in here
now. So, it's going to take a longer
time.
That' be what I'd be looking at.
Nice. All right, let's do a giveaway
before I forget. Before I forget,
please. Some of you spam chat. Let me
explain something to you. If you type in
the answer more than once, you don't get
picked. Nightbot instantly deletes you.
So, please don't spam chat. You're not
going to help yourself. All right?
You're not going to help yourself win.
You're going to guarantee you don't win.
Let's do
All right. Just tuck FCT once in chat.
Once. Once to make sure you get entered.
All right. Just once.
Right. Just type it once. I'll be right
back. Another refill here.
All right,
let's pull this winner up.
I don't know how to say your name, so if
I get this wrong, I'm sorry. Batuta Y7P.
Bata Y7P,
are you here?
There you go. All right. Nice one. There
you go. So, all you got to do is shoot
me an email info@flowzontrader.com.
Send me a screenshot of you logged into
your YouTube and I will send you a uh
free Apex account any side that size
that you want.
Point control now rejecting here on this
market. I cannot believe what I'm
watching on this market. The rotations
are just mental.
All right, team. And that's it. That's
us done. Uh Freaky Friday tomorrow.
We'll see how we go tomorrow. Hopefully
uh
hopefully we can move outside of this
range. I am not going to hold my breath.
Could I repeat the email? Yeah,
info@flowzonerader.com.
info@flowzonerader.com
and that's it. You've got until I remind
myself all these
How long has Apex got left? I don't
think is it till Tuesday, Monday,
Tuesday?
Five days, right? You've got five days
left for the 90% sale on Apex. Okay, so
every account right now will cost you
$1960. It doesn't matter what account
size you go for. It's $1960 to do the
evals.
Uh for the activation fees, 25K, 50K,
100K are $65 activation fee. So if you
pass first time, it's $84 all in. And
for the 150K, 250K, 300K, it's $144 all
in.
Which one is best?
It really depends what size you like
trading, what your ambitions are. Um 25k
50k are in terms of RR are the best. All
right, they're the easiest to pass. Um
but they obviously give you less draw
down. The bigger the accounts, uh the
more draw down you get, but the less
efficient they are because you're going
to need to make three, four, five R in
terms of your uh trading draw down. So
my advice is always 50ks.
50ks nice and small. Let them build.
That's the way to do it in my opinion.
I've got plenty of videos on that. But
again, look, if you don't like trading
draw down, I don't advise trading with
them. Like, you want to use other
accounts, plenty of other people you can
trade with as well.
Um, all right, back tomorrow. What news
do we have tomorrow? Let me just quickly
have a look.
Tomorrow 13th
12th. What we got tomorrow?
Bugger all some Fed talk and wholesale
inventory. So if we don't move out the
Oh, is it AVGO tonight?
It is right. Uh,
I think AVGO's tonight
broadcast. Yeah, it is. AVGO tonight.
That would be the big mover, especially
after what everyone watching uh
uh Oracle yesterday. So, if AVGLO
misses earnings tonight, I wouldn't be
surprised to see this market yank a
little bit um like it did previously.
But who knows? I would love it if we
leave this range. It would be really
nice. The best the best move that we
could get in this market, the best thing
that we could ask for in this market,
whether it's today or next week, right?
It's really simple. Best move that we
could ask for is to leave this range
with a gap. All right? If we had woken
up
this morning and we were trading down
here. It would have been really obvious,
wouldn't it? Back test, failure. Really
simple. Leave buyers trapped, fail. I
don't want us trading back inside here.
All right? Because then we're not
leaving the buyers trapped. Remember
here,
really simple. Back test, fail, trade
away. That's what we want. Or it's if
AVGO has blowout earnings and we open up
here, that's also fine. back test buy
upside. That's going to be the easiest
thing. If we're going to continue to
trade in here, I'm going to continue to
be in scout mode and very uninterested
and just see money take money.
Does that make sense? Sorry, I didn't
realize you couldn't see all of it.
There you go. All right, folks. Uh back
tomorrow we go again
and uh we see what we get. Fingers
crossed. Everyone say your uh market
prayers for a move outside of uh value.
Maybe we get lucky and get it. Um be
sensible, use hard stops, all that usual
good stuff. Those in Discord, I'm going
to set some price alerts. Uh I probably
won't actively trade, but I will try and
uh jump in and support you for some
levels later that I'd be looking at. All
right, peace and love everyone, and uh
see you tomorrow morning.