All right, morning team. Morning.
Morning. Morning. Hope you're doing
good. FOMC day. It's going to be a
shorter stream today. I've got stuff I
need to deal with personally off the
chart. So, we'll be here until
um about uh 11:00. All right,
let's go over it all. [sighs and gasps]
What are we looking at? Daily chart, no
change. All right, another day pretty
much opening inside the current weekly
range and the previous weekly range,
right? So, we can see yesterday, even
though
many of you may disagree. Yesterday, we
had another inside bar. So, here's
Friday, Monday inside of Friday, Tuesday
inside of Monday. Currently we have
Wednesday and so Tuesday. This is
compression. This is not trend. It is
nothing else other than compression. Uh
the market will make a decision soon
enough when it's ready probably after
FORMC on what it wants to do. Okay? But
right now we are trapped. Here's the
edge. That's what we're trapped in. This
is rotation. It is not trend. If you buy
the top of this, you will get hurt. If
you short the bottom of this, you will
get hurt. Unless you get very lucky and
you end up timing the breakout or the
breakdown, you will get hurt. So, the
best thing to do is follow the rules of
rotation. You want to play the edges and
nothing else. All right, you can see
we've been developing quite a big node
here, which is starting to stick out
like a bit of a sore thumb here. Sort of
650 to 600 worth paying attention to.
Um, once we start to break below the
fives, and we're going to go over this
in the hourly, there is room for us to
come and repric some of this, right? And
we have some support down here. And we
also have the 50-day and 20-day. the
mean reversion to there would be the
healthiest thing for this market. It may
very be that it doesn't want to do it.
But in terms of bullish progress, you
know, if we actually did this and set a
firm higher low here on a daily and then
reclaimed this, then guess what? That
move there becomes much much easier than
trying to just have a pause for a moment
and continue that. That's a much harder
move for the market to do, which is why
it's struggling. We have exhaustion and
we still have the buyers trapped up
here. But we're going to have a look at
these levels.
uh on the hourly now to make it all make
sense. Let's go over to this.
Uh let's make sure you can see this down
a bit. Okay. Hourly here.
This is your previous week's balance.
All right. Previous week's balance. Nice
clear L shape. All right.
Clean distribution. All right. Just in
rotation. You can see Friday we failed
to get outside of balance. Monday we
failed to get outside of balance. So
what are we doing? Right? If we can't
get out of balance, we're going to
search for balance. Right? If we can't
search for fair value. What is the
biggest fair value from the week before?
Point of control. Right? That's your
fair value from the week before. We
cannot get a close underneath previous
week's point of control. So what are we
going to do? We're going to create more
rotation. All right. Where's the
rotation inside previous week's balance?
We are creating current weak rotation.
That is all there is to say on this. You
you don't need to make it any harder.
Right? These these are the conditions
we've got. This is your support system.
This is fair value right now uh from the
previous week. We cannot get above fair
value of the current week. You can see
every time we're driving up to current,
this is developing. This is a developing
profile. Current week's value area high.
Current week's point of control. We
can't get through it. every time we come
down to previous week's point of
control. All right, it was naked on
Monday. It's not naked anymore. We've
revisited a few times. Every time we get
down to there, we're not seeing the move
back down to previous week's value area
low. So, what are the range rotations?
Well, it's just within this. All we have
right now is fading this back down to
here, buying this back up to here. Once
that breaks, if we get a breakout of
previous week point of control and we
stay heavy, then we can think about that
move to previous week value area high.
If we get a breakout of current value
area high and previous week value area
high maybe you can think about the longs
but then you have to be aware of what
you're coming into right you're coming
into this level here uh sort of 8 885900
massive level massive massive massive
level so that's where we're at and
that's what you need to be aware of this
is why yesterday I was very adamant and
animated you cannot be long up here it
is not a trend I don't care what you
think this is telling you All you have
to do is follow right what is in front
of you range and new range. Do not get
caught. This morning is likely to be low
volatility. It's likely to set traps for
later. It doesn't have to. There have
been times on the past where the morning
before FOMC has been absolutely
beautiful to trade. The range on FOMC
has been getting smaller and smaller and
smaller because we're not actually as
interested in the rate cuts. You can see
we know it's going to be a 0.25 cut,
right? There's a 95% chance that it's
0.25. What does that mean? Well, it's
probably already in the price. Then it's
already baked in. So maybe we get an
algo move off it as in a news algo move.
What everyone's going to be interested
in is what Pal says afterwards. All
right. It's all because last time it was
a 50/50 split and whe whether we did
more cuts in the future. People will be
listening to are we going to do more
cuts in the future? Do they even care
about inflationary pressure? My guess
would be no. what they're going to care
about is the jobs market because the
jobs market is in a bad bad way. All
right? Worse and worse and worse and
worse and worse. People are not actually
quitting their jobs now because they're
scared. They're staying in their jobs,
but jobs are scarce. That is what I
think he's going to talk about is the
labor market. And that's what will shake
the market. I would imagine people will
ask him some questions about liquidity,
the JPY carry trade and our current uh
treasuries and bonds and the fact that
the 10 and 20 and 30 year look like they
might break out. That is what the tone
is going to be. I would imagine when we
get to the Q&As's that is what the news
algos are going to move off. If you like
being risky, by all means trade it. For
me, I like putting size on tomorrow
because I think we get, you know, a move
on liquidity today. Maybe we wash both
sides today. All right. It wouldn't
surprise me at all to see either
something like uh [clears throat]
a dip and rip or a fail and back down.
All right. The big move for me is going
to come once we get out of here. Once we
can get if if we're going to get out of
here to the downside, once we get
outside of previous week value area
high, right, we have an old naked PC
which lines up perfectly down here. This
for me is the buying opportunity. That's
the big buying opportunity down there.
Right. If we come down here, do a double
bottom. Yes, please. Thanks very much.
I'll be looking for that probably next
week. If if if today is a sell the news
event or even if they push higher today
and they use it tomorrow as liquidity
for a sell news event, this is where I'm
interested in really getting potential
buys from. Right? So that's what I'm
watching. Uh we can look at what
happened overnight. Not a lot is the
answer. All right. So yesterday, believe
it or not, even though [clears throat]
many of you decided you wanted to buy up
here, it was not a trend day. It was a
rotation back inside. All right, it took
a long time to do that. Why? I'm going
to go over the spiders shortly, but we
had recessionary
uh pressure. J uh JP Morgan stuck in
silver. Uh we'll deny it, but they're
stuck in silver. They've got a big short
position in silver. And on top of that,
there came out Jamie Diamond saying, you
know, he's he's worried uh about the
state of the market. Okay. Well, SPY
came all the way down here. Uh ENQ
relative strength mainly because we're
still finding a bid on Oracle, which has
earnings tonight. Okay. So, drift down
overnight. What do we do? Not a lot.
London peaks out over yesterday's highs.
Fails. Surprise, surprise. Because we're
in range rotation. We fail the high. We
come back down to the low. We're now at
previous day value area low. There's not
a lot to do here, folks. like the range
is going to get tighter and tighter and
tighter. Current range if we look at
previous day value area high is set
around 25730s
and previous day value area low 25 653.
So it's not even 100 points of range for
rotation right now. We can easily set
traps each side of it. So just be aware
of that as you're coming to the charts
today. Understand what the uh
environment is right now. Must
understand what that environment is. So
here you can see again overnight all
we've done
failed above
come down back to value bounce back to
point control back to value back to
point of control back to value that's it
that's all we're doing boxed in all
right so like I said the range is going
to get tighter and tighter and tighter
you don't want to be risk in this
environment just let it figure itself
out um what I do want to talk about
though is the divergences in this market
so let's go to ES move to five Yeah. All
right. ES yesterday, like I talked
about, much much heavier,
right? And exactly the same fails the
top of its range. Look above and fail.
Traps liquidity. And there's the full
roll. Right. That's what I was hoping
ENQ would do, but we just did it on this
single market. And that's all from the
banking sector. All right. Finance is in
trouble. And now we've gone back into
test this level, fail back to the low,
found a bid, back up here, you can see
the rotation. All right. So on ES your
big level is 35s. Now what I'd be
watching is the gamma levels on SPY
because they are what keep coming up
over and over and over again. So you can
see my price alerts. They're still here.
85. All right, is your call wall right
now. Um they have got room above it if
they get through on FOMC. Um 82 was a
cool wall uh a put wall yesterday, but I
would imagine they've probably moved
some down into 80. I know beneath 80
we've got about a 10point room right
now.
right beneath 80. If they start letting
go of this, I think the next one was
like 75 and even 70. Right the way down
here, right, a long, long way. So, this
is the range. Once we get outside of
that range, if there's gamma exposure,
it's going to move. Is worth watching
the spy. It's trading between 85 and 82.
If it lets go of 82, it will trade
between 82 and 80. If it lets go of
that, there is a deeper move. I think
there was some exposure at 78 and then
there's potential flush on this market.
So, just be aware of what broader
markets are doing. Uh we can have a
quick look at Dixie
just trying to find a bid recently is
trying to get back up to this top side
for this 100 break and VIX is now
trapped between some key levels. So VIX
on the daily you can see we have started
to base out starting to find a bid here
at 15s. All right, but we're coming into
a couple of key resistance points. So it
really depends, you know, is VIX
actually going to have a push and fail
here. Remember, as we get down into
here, this is low vol and that's in this
kind of area here is where we expect N E
N E N E N E N E N E N E N E N E N E NQ
and SPY to do like those slow grind
steady steady steady grind days. Okay,
so down here very bullish for the
market. Up here we're going to increase
volatility. I would imagine during FOMC
it will come up here. All right, it
probably comes up here because we're
going to get volatility coming into the
market.
Uh let's have a look at the mag. How we
doing for time? 5 minutes. All right.
All right. Apple doing actually not too
bad. All right. We did start to roll
over yesterday. Um but like we talked
about, it's not letting go of the key
levels. Same thing that we talked about
yesterday. There's your neckline.
There's your pin. All right. If it can
reclaim 80, it's got a chance to go back
to highs. We can build liquidity on
here. 80 is the chance to go back to
highs. 75 failures is that neckline
fail. If we did a neckline fail, you'd
be expecting a measured move probably
the size of this, right? And we'd be
looking for a move back to 65s, which is
where that liquidity is sat. All right,
so all to play for on Apple. It's got to
make a decision much like the uh Q's
right now, just stuck in between.
Amazon gap up there.
Uh kind of similar, not quite as weak,
but kind of similar. There's your
breakout. All right, there's the low.
There's the start of the higher low.
That's your pullback. If Amazon wants to
hold, then it's got a chance to get
going here. So, it just needs to hold a
bid at 26es. You can call it 25s if you
want. Break out over 38 will be uh you
can see this clear level on the chart
right here. Right. Over 38, oh, uh we
get motoring. So, if you want to set
price alerts, I'll be setting price
alerts. Under 15, it's risk off. Over 38
is potential risk on other than fail
breakouts. Goo. Uh not a lot happening
there. That's not something I'd be very
interested in right now.
Lower highs and lower lows, but uh this
can easily easily easily be absorbed for
this move. Right. So again, just in that
range. You can see there's the rotation.
No confirmation of down, no confirmation
of up. Just building liquidity.
Meta. What the hell is going on there?
Must have had news this morning. Either
that or that's a dark pool print. Maybe
someone can tell me in chat. That looks
awful. What is that? Well, that doesn't
look good. Whatever that is, if that's
legit. Same kind of story as Apple. It's
coming down into this range, right? Peak
high. Coming back into this range. Can
it hold this to have another go to break
up? If we lose this, remember, it's got
lots of room downside. I've got a small
starter in this. Haven't taken any
profits. Just waiting to see how we act
in the uh overall market.
Microsoft gapping down. It's left trap
volume at the highs. I'd be concerned
about that if I was a trader. left trap
volume at the highs there from the last
few days. Starting to break away from
it. That is not a good look. Yes, we're
coming back down to potential support,
but you can see every time it gets up
here, it's failing. It's got to hold
this uh 82s now for a chance. I've got a
price alert in case it breaks out, but
yeah, that doesn't look great. Uh
Nvidia, this is the big one. Remember,
we got Oracle tonight. That will
probably affect Nvidia. They have their
chips approved to be sent to China. And
then I read news this morning saying
that um Deepseek have got some of their
uh chips which they shouldn't be allowed
to have. So, you know, all sorts of sort
of political events going on with this
company. Um we will just have to see. Uh
it's trying to base and curl. It is
trying to base and curl. It's not up to
those highs yet. Let's move this out a
sec. Uh
let's see where volume is trapped here.
If we just do one of these from here,
where we at? Yeah, you can see. So, it's
just in a rotation.
All right, there's your rotation.
No acceptance above, let's call it 90
and no acceptance below 74. That's your
rotation. Nothing else. Tesla, uh, looks
good. This looks really, really, really
strong, isn't it, for a while now. Um,
big moves last week and early this week.
Still holding on. So as long as Tesla
holds dips into 440, it can continue
higher. Lose 440 and lose previous day
low and uh well the next support system
is back here. It's built out good
liquidity here. 15s to 8 to 380s. Big
liquidity built been built out there. I
don't expect it to drop beneath this
unless uh we have a shift in the macro
environment as a whole on the mag.
Equally weighted. Where are we opening
up? Slightly down. Not really much here.
One thing you need to be aware of today
after hours oracle. All right. Oracle
earlings after hours. Um, everyone is
talking some absolute garbage on Oracle.
I have no position in it, so this is not
loaded. But everyone's saying, "Oh,
they're like overexposure and they're
going to have liquidity issues and
they're going to roll over and they're
going to dunk and they're going to this
and they're going to that and blah blah
blah blah blah." Look, the last earnings
we moved from 224 to 3449
off good earnings. Uh, this move off
absolutely no reason other than fear
being created uh to me seems a little
ridiculous. 46% down, right? So,
ideally, I just wanted before earnings
to set a higher low in here and look for
that rotation back up for a trade, but
can't really position myself into
earnings, but I wouldn't be short. So, I
definitely are not new money short. Lots
of people talking about puts into this,
so just be careful for you doing that.
Market has just opened.
Let's get into it. I'm not in a rush
today, as you can imagine.
Let's see what we get.
Probably a whole lot of nothing would be
my guess is what we get today.
And good morning everyone. Sorry I
didn't get to go through all the uh
hellos and stuff in chat. Let's just see
what we get here. What did we have
premarket? We've got some buyers trapped
over uh 680 right now. And uh
were there any sellers that trapped down
here? A couple on that morning push into
34s just got trapped but pretty low
volume. Let this shake out. See what it
wants to do.
What did you guys say in the poll?
You're all expecting chop as well. Yeah,
76% of you expecting chop this morning.
Not surprised.
Not surprised. Right. Testing current
value area low on the week here. Seeing
some uh big selling coming in here.
What's the market doing? Split names.
Big seller down there. Just came in.
Split names. Uh Apple up, Amazon up,
Tesla just about up. Nvidia pretty much
flat. Just gone red to green. Microsoft
the big loser today over 2% down. Uh
Meta just under 1% down. Google just
under half a percent down. So mixed bag
in the mag as expected.
SPY coming back into those 82s that
we've talked about.
I don't expect the market to do a lot
here. It might. Like I said, there have
been days where prefc we've had amazing
trends develop, but uh I find it
somewhat unlikely that we're going to do
that when the market's in such big
balance. Why let the air out? And if
they do, I'm going to make the
assumption that it's going to be a trap
for later. All right, let's see.
Testing current weekly value area low
right now. Developing profile.
[snorts]
Previous week point of control that we
keep absorbing off has been 600.
Remember has been 600.
It's the level it seems to like
gravitating to and trying to find a bid
around there recently.
This can potentially become red now 650.
If they lose it previous day value area
low, that would be an indication that
we're staying heavy on the day for a
rotation lower to pick up
by side lower. [sighs]
Nice, Otus. That's awesome. Glad I'm
glad it's helping, my friend. That's
That's awesome news. Good stuff. Good
stuff.
Okay, so we had strong selling coming in
here at 35. If they reclaim this, I
expect we go to previous day value area
low, which would be 650. Then we have to
see if sellers defend that. If not, then
we've come right to the top side. We've
got old VWAP sitting at 71s, 24-hour
VWAP up here.
Really not expecting much today. So,
unless I see an opportunity which stands
out, I'm going to just sort of let the
market do what it needs to do.
Vick's trying to break out. It's
actually having a go. It's trying to
break out. What's that? Yesterday's
highs. Pre-market highs. Pre-market
highs. Trying to break out through
pre-market highs. Not successful yet,
but it's trying. We did just catch a few
buys here into 34s. They're trying again
here for a delta flip. So, we did just
catch a few buys there into 34s on that
last move.
They're trying again here. So, I'd say
34 to 36. There were some buyers caught
through there. That's where the strong
sellers came in last time. So, there's
probably a passive seller there. If we
get through that, then buyers will want
to rotate to uh 650s.
Amazon finding a bid. Tesla finding a
bid. Both about 1% up.
Rest or flat.
What's going on here? Big flush here
come previous week point of control.
Like I said, those buyers were stuck up
here. Could see them stuck. It's a nice
rejection of VW up there. There are some
aggressive buying into there who got
themselves caught. Here's your cover
point.1. Now, if we do flush this, you
can look for previous day low here, but
just be careful. I'm expecting sort of
whipsaw action.
There we go.
Sorry folks, just having to sort
something out. There we go. So through
previous week point control, next
targets previous day low. So those
buyers getting themselves caught there
this morning. Previous day low probably
coming up here. Uh you must be covering
into this. These are the 600s. This is
where we keep finding a bid over and
over and over. This is like been the
edge of the range all week. Maybe they
dip through it, but this is definitely
the edge.
Spy coming down into Oh, it's lost 82s.
There you go. So, it's lost 82s on the
spy. That's key.
You can see there's some bids here into
60s. You need a drift back up to sell
back into if you want to resize into
this. Otherwise, we're going to take
previous day low and there's going to be
nothing left to do.
Remember, this is where they keep
bidding from this kind of area.
This kind of area they've enjoyed
bidding from
value on the day now back at 600. So,
maybe a retest of there.
and see if they just drive back through
it again.
Previous week point of control.
Remember, this is fair value for the
last week or so. There you go. So,
there's the drift back to it. What they
do now is important. If they don't sell
this, we go straight back to the upside.
This is the same thing that they've done
all week long. So, how we act here
becomes important. Are they going to
just bid straight off this like they
have all week?
Time will tell.
And the place where the buyers were
stuck is 30. So if we let them out,
that's where we let them out. Up at 30s.
You can see just reclaimed 60 straight
away. 60 600. God, get your words out,
mate. This is the same move we've done
every day this week. Come to this low
kind of area previous week. Point of
control, find a bid. We went over it
premarket.
the big scoop of those lows. Look at the
drive. Like, it's mad, man.
Just range rotation. We're never going
to move out of this range rotation. It
feels like it's been months now of
sitting in rotation. Look at that drive.
[laughter]
What a [\h__\h] stupid market. [laughter]
And bid up. And here you go. are right
to the upside now
and probably if we break previous day
value area low we start screaming higher
and coming and testing previous day
value area high. So look below this was
the level we talked about. Remember
pre-market we kept talking about
previous week point of control. Every
time we come into this level all it does
is find a bid. Never even sweeps. It's
the same thing again. Here's the edge of
your range. Everyone wants to call this
a trend. We are not in a trend. There's
your rotation. All right. There's your
rotation back inside. Same rotation.
Rinse, repeat, rinse, repeat.
Nothing to do here, folks. You've got
nothing to do here. Unless you Unless
you love rotation, which obviously we
all know I absolutely hate.
Absolutely hate these type of markets.
These are not not not things that I
personally enjoy trading.
>> [sighs]
>> All right. So, back to value, back to
that New York open.
Bulls can't reclaim it. Remember, this
was the area where I said bulls got
stuck into the sort of these 30s.
So, [sighs] the rotation now will be to
retry and retest 600 and hold it. Um,
bears will want a drift down underneath
that.
Just a 100 point move there.
Don't know why that went to that. Sorry
folks. That should be like this.
So here's the bulls trying to hold 600.
All right. They're trying to hold it.
There isn't that much excess underneath
it really if I'm honest. So
just for me it's a it's a leave alone a
leave alone day for me personally at the
moment.
I just want to wait for this market to
get outside of its uh
of the range. I don't like I don't like
trading rotation. I think it's just the
the
the antithesis of what I like to do. So,
just let it develop. For me, all I have
to do is wait one more day. Once we get
to tomorrow, I've probably got some
really nice uh breakouts or fail
breakouts.
So, it's just a question. Can Can I just
get through to tomorrow?
All right. Testing between 600. Like I
talked about bulls want to defend same
level I gave you 600. Bulls will want to
defend this. I there is not that much
excess here. So one thing I would say
not a lot of excess here but bulls can
defend this they try and get back to
previous day value area low. If we get
acceptance through previous day value
area low they'll want to come and test
point of control and previous day value
area high. So bulls are trying to look
for this. Bears are trying to look for
this and acceptance lower. That's that's
what we have right now.
I know, Julian, but calling them and
enjoying them is two different things,
right? Like maybe I just need to be more
willing to trade them, but they're just
it's I try and trade where my personal
edges, my personal edge is in breakout
and fail breakout moves. And um it's
just what I I just enjoy. If I went
through all my data for forever and ever
and ever, I know my edge will be
uh when we're trading outside and when
we're trading inside, I know I don't
trade it as well. So, by knowing that, I
just try and stick to where my edges.
Like, for me, you make more money as a
trader by, how do I put this? By not
doing what you're bad at. Does that make
sense? I'll make more money. my P&L at
the end of the year is is bigger if I
cut out the trades which I'm not as good
at. So rather than adding more trades,
what I want to do is just cut out the
ones that I'm not very good at. And the
impact of that's massive.
Yeah. Like I talked about, I always use
that golf analogy, going around the golf
course with an eight iron. If you're
good with an eight iron, if you get a
driver out,
maybe for a couple holes, you perform
really well. Maybe you get you get to
those holes in less shots and you know,
you make a birdie or whatever. But every
now and again, because you're not that
controlled with the driver, you're going
to [\h__\h] up.
Okay, so here you go. Here's the test
previous day value area low. So there's
the rotation failed under previous week
point of control. Never got to previous
day low. Scooped it. rotation to
previous day value. Now, this is last
chance for bears because if they don't
defend value area low, then what do we
have? We have a move. We have a fail
break outside of value. Think about
yesterday's profile. Yesterday's volume
is all here. All right. So, bears must
defend this if they want this. If they
don't defend that, then we're going to
go where? Back to these points like we
just talked about pre-market. [snorts]
Look below and recover. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Totally.
just stuck up here now. Market might go
to sleep. Now this is the thing. It's
very possible that market just calms
down now and doesn't do anything for the
day. Like very very possible. What we
doing with the mag? Tesla 0.25% up.
Nvidia's gone red to green but it's
0.05% up. Google quarter% up. Amazon's
doing well. 1.1 a half% up. Apple
quarter of a percent up and then you got
Microsoft the big loser 2.40% 40% down.
Meta 1.12%
down.
All the sort of BNC list names I would
talk about OSCR, PayPal, Bull, um,
Nen, OQ, MBTS, RGTI, those sort of high
beta, high gamma exposure names, they're
all red on the day. If I look across the
index, everything's red currently.
Dixie down, gold down, crude down, Q's
down, spiders down, RTY down, YM is
flat,
Bitcoin down. Yeah, it's just it's what
we expect.
It's what we expect, folks. It is what
>> [snorts]
>> There we go. So probably now it will
attempt to come up to previous day point
of control if they can find acceptance
inside yesterday's value. That is what
they will attempt to do. Whether they
can do it or not is different, but that
is what they would attempt to do.
as a a trader I know always says do more
of what works and less of what does.
Yeah, that's it. That is literally the
biggest rule. Like if you want to
increase your profit factor, that's for
me that's the number one rule.
The number one rule.
That's it right there. Exactly what you
just said. That is it.
Morning,
Nico.
So, here we go. Still driving. Still
trying to get up to previous day point
of control and then probably up to um
previous day value area low if it can.
I've got like another hour with you here
and then I'm going to have to get off
early today. I'm afraid got some stuff
I' got to deal with.
So, uh, spy like
that first 5m minutee candle came
straight under 82s down to 8130s.
Literally closed back above 82s and is
now driving higher and the next place it
will want to go is probably 85s if it
can go there. I don't expect like my
anticipation with this market is we do
not move outside of range. I can't see
why we would move outside of range right
now. Um
prior to uh
I can't talk prior to uh FOMC. I I don't
see why we would do that. There's no
reason for it to do that in my opinion.
Unless unless something spooks the
market, uh, all this would be about
doing is building liquidity into the
market, I would imagine. Anyway, that's
that's my anticipation.
That is my anticipation.
Okay, back down towards VW up. So,
failing previous day value area low.
Let's put some current profile on there
as well.
So, there's your rotation.
Current rotation anyway.
I don't Sigma I don't understand. A
couple times you've said that big seller
at 635. You mean you must mean already
like I don't understand. You must mean
already filled
cuz that's below current price. So do
you mean someone's stuck when you're
saying that?
I noticed you did that yesterday as
well. You you quote you quote pri big
seller when they're below current price
which means they've already got filled
otherwise you don't know they're a big
seller.
Big stuck seller. Okay, good. Cool. Just
wanted to check like we're on the same
page there.
Just wanted to check
Is there any levels above here on book?
Someone offering 700 a few bids at 25
just looks
there's just nothing here like pulling
me in. I can show I'm just like flat.
I'm not even pulled in at all. In fact,
why is that not connecting on that one?
This happened last week as well.
did next keeps disconnecting.
Back to Vup we go.
Man, this uh trade copy, I really like
it, but it definitely keeps
disconnecting me from stuff. I think
it's that I've never had an issue before
using it.
Maybe I'm wrong.
Maybe it's my computer.
Okay, back to VW up. So, we're trapped
between 24hour VWOP and uh New York VWOP
here.
Just in range. No, no, no. Uh big moves
here like we talked about. We're just in
range. The only thing I'd say is we
didn't complete, we didn't take out the
previous day lows, but now just drifting
back down to current value area low on
the day. Some stronger selling coming in
here, but I'd imagine they just bid off
it like they've uh wanted to do numerous
times, but we will see. Maybe we come
down to that previous day low. I don't
know.
Okay, that's developing profile, is it?
Yes. Okay, that's uh current weekly
profile though. So, I was just trying to
work out what that was. [snorts]
Okay, so back up to New York, back up to
point of control on the day. Stuck in
this rotation.
Uh did we have a lot of selling at those
lows? I'd say yeah, under 600. There was
a fair bit of selling that's probably
stuck.
And where's the buyers came in? Buys
over 50s right now. So, buyers over 50s
are stuck. Sellers under 600 stuck. 50
points there to play either side. That's
about it.
VIX want to pick up 1850 to FOMC. I
mean, no, Peter, definitely not. Look,
it's just failed to break out this
morning. It looked above 1766. I don't
see why it would come up to 1850 before
[clears throat] FOMC that you'd be
asking for a lot of volatility to come
on the market. Like I find it unlikely,
but we'll no I could easily be wrong,
but at the moment all we're doing is B
is bouncing between basically 1750 and
1720. Yeah. So like the previous high
from Tuesday, December 9th, acting as a
support system. If we fade that, we
probably come all the way down to 17s,
close the gap in VIX to 1693s.
uh it will need to sustain a bid over
1750 or 1760 really to get anywhere near
those 18s and I'll be looking at 1820s
first stop. So yeah, for me for me it's
just a
it's just going to go chill. It's just
going to go it's just going to go into
what we're seeing here. All right,
here's your profile. Now
we are rejecting previous days value
area lows. The one thing I'd say at the
moment we have not got back into
previous days value. All right. So
really they need to do this to get us
inside value. All the time we're outside
of value. This is open. Um but this is
key. That previous week point of
control. If we start letting go of
previous week point control and we start
getting like a fade underneath these
previous day lows, then previous week
value area high becomes more probable.
But it's a big if right now. Sellers
trying to be aggressive here. We might
get a breakdown here if they really let
this out underneath the 600.
Watching this 600. They're trying to
sell very aggressively. If they sell
this, it is potential that they want to
wash it. But uh remember this previous
week point control is what we bid off
nonstop, right? Nonstop. Big selling
coming in here back to this same level.
This is where they got stuck this
morning, but they are trying. Mag is all
going red other than Amazon and Apple.
Worth noting MAG is going red other than
Amazon and Apple. But I'd say this
previous week point of control and now
I'd even say 612 becomes important. That
big sell candle.
This is where we sold from. So yeah,
sort of 612 to 625. Bears will want to
protect this. Remember all we're doing
is trading into this low where they
caught those bears this morning. They
caught the bears at 78. They caught the
bears at 78.
Where's that volume sticking out? 600's
a big big traded level this morning. Big
big traded level. [cough]
[clears throat]
I'll be watching that uh 82s on SPY
again. 682s on spy again. We've just
traded back down to it in front of it.
Found a bid again.
Like I said, I think we will just
rotate, rotate, rotate, rotate all
morning until we get to uh FRMC, but you
never know. Some days it's not what
happens. But that's what it feels like
at the moment. There's that 610 test.
They've got definitely got bears, a
little bears trapped under 600 again for
the second time today. So bears will
need to get closed well under 600
otherwise they're going to be in
trouble.
this edge. Yeah, we are rejecting value.
Potential that they move lower here, but
they're going to have to get under 600.
I don't like it for me personally, but
just saying what I'm seeing.
Yes, back above New York open. Back
above both the VWAPs. Divergence there.
Vicks at previous day high
was traded downside. Might make a new
low here if it does spike and squeeze
and then NQ might want to follow. We
don't know. So no close below 600. These
bears are struggling right now. Back
inside current value for the day.
There's liquidity up at 40. I don't know
why they're dangling it up there, but
they are.
Yeah, I watch the Q's as well.
I don't have to pay as much uh attention
to the Q's because I'm trading NQ. But
yeah, I I'm watching the Q's as well. Q
spy VIX. That's what I'm watching.
This doesn't look good for the bears.
Think there's potential squeeze out
here. They might get themselves caught.
They need to get under 600. These bears,
they're having another go here.
They've got to get a clo definitely
under 607s. It's point of control from
that last candle and it's being
absorbed. Delta in this candle is
negative and we've gone higher. So
there's a passive buyer on the tape.
There's passive buyer on the tape down
here. Surprise, surprise. At that
previous week point of control, there's
a passive buyer. Same thing for
well five days last week and where are
we today? three days this week. So,
[snorts] same thing as we talked about
this morning. And there we go. So, there
there's the squeeze we just talked
about. This is why I just don't I have
no interest in trading this. None.
Yes. Right back to PDC. This is where it
has two wicks up here high this morning.
If it gets through this, it will just
scream higher because all those bears
just came flying in 620 down to 600 or
to 590 and got stuck again. And look at
this. Mags flipped.
This is the game, folks. This is why I
keep saying to you, uh I know it's like
a stuck record for the last
I don't know, week and a half, but uh
this is the market condition we have. I
cannot do anything with it. If if
they're going to do this, we have to
respect what they're going to do. We
can't fight them the way I respect what
they're going to do is by staying away
from it.
Until we get under previous week point
control, bears have no control in this
market. If we get under that and we stay
heavy, there is a chance a chance that
they can get a rotation down to here.
I'm not saying it's going to be
absolute, but that there is a chance if
they get under that.
is a retest of current value area low on
the day. It's being absorbed and they're
trying to sell through it again. So, I'd
say sort of 608s now is going to become
key. If they can't get under 608, bulls
take control and we probably go straight
back through to 650s
spy relative strength.
It is kind of weird. I'm going to be
honest, like looking across like those
I'll call them sealless names and seeing
some of them down 5% in tech and NQ not
letting go kind of makes you wonder like
woof is this market okay with itself
back to these 600s
Yes, back to view up. So, failed those
top wicks again. Closed. It's closed gap
and it can't get over gap at the moment.
Where's the spider? It's probably coming
back down to the 82s again on the spy.
It's just gamma. It's just gamma
exposure. It's all this market is
if we get under point of control, I'll
consider something. And like not just if
we get under it, if there's like
uh if we if I feel like a sentiment
shifts coming, if SPY starts to get
weak, if I'm seeing like some of the
rollover happen, if I'm seeing heavy
pressure and us actually moving lower
rather than delta divergence, I'll
consider a trade. But until then, I'm
not not considering it.
Right now, we're holding current. Uh
that blue line is your current profile
of the week. We're pinned and holding
the current value area low on the week.
We are just going to trade from one side
to the other. You can see it. All you
got to do is put a profile on this week
and last week and look at an hourly
chart and that is just telling you the
whole story that you need to know.
There's nothing you need to know beyond
that. Look at that. What one,
two, three drives we've had off this
kind of level we're at now and three
failures from seven just over 700 back
to this level. We're just pinned 100
point pin. That's basically what we're
in. 100 point pin
six to seven basically.
Yeah. Agreed. Agreed. Sigma agreed.
So here we go. Cellis failed.
It was they had three candles there of
heavy delta and we didn't move lower.
That's telling the story. We're coming
back into where these sellers are at 35s
again. And if we squeeze through this,
we probably go straight back to previous
day value area low, which is value area
high on the day, which is 50s. And if we
get through that, we're going to go high
of day probably.
This is the game right now.
This is point of control on the day now.
Almost traded level.
See, look how tight this ranges.
This is why I keep saying like we're
just getting tighter and tighter and
tighter and tighter and tighter.
Eventually, this thing is going to
either implode or explode. Right? So,
we've gone from that. Now, we've gone to
this. Right? We're either going to get
one of these or one of these probably
after 2 o'clock or maybe even tomorrow
to be honest. They might do some
nastiness today and then real move comes
tomorrow.
[snorts]
Apple looks like it's holding on here.
It might go red soon.
May very well go red soon on Apple.
pacifier on a taper again.
Trying to absorb 20s at the moment. See
if he gets himself caught. He's trying
by VWAP. It's trying to absorb you up.
This buy looks like it wants to break
out to me.
It's had enough chances. It looks like
it wants to break out to me.
YM's gone green. RTY has gone green.
Come on.
I got another hour left, folks, and then
I'm out of it.
Can't believe I've got up for this.
Waste of time. Waste of time.
There we go. Spy is going to break out.
Like I said, it's having another attempt
at 850. See once it gets through 850
should probably just rip some faces to
be honest. Probably so many caught in
this now.
There we go. They just caught everyone
with shorts down here. So go straight
back up to previous day value low. Same
thing applies. Like I'm [\h__\h] bored of
saying it, but we get through value low
and try and test up here. If we can't
get through value low, it's going to
come back down to here. And you're
playing in 50 points range. That's
that's literally all you are playing in.
The spy trying to break out. It is
attempting to break out of those 850s.
It's trying to drag the market up with
it. Um,
Tesla has just gone red to green just
about. Nvidia's red, Microsoft's red,
Meta's red, Apple's flat, Google's half%
up, Amazon's one and a half% up. It's
just a mixed bag. Again, I cannot
remember a day where I've looked at the
Mag 7 and they're all doing the same
thing for a long time, a long, long
time. And you might say, why does that
matter? Well, they're worth 60% of the
cues, so it matters. So, if you've got
half red, half green,
probably not a lot you can do with it in
terms of confluence.
Am I trading later? Um, if price
action's good, I will trade with my team
in Discord.
Generally speaking, I normally don't
trade FOMC. I normally let the move
happen, but if we come to an extreme and
I think there's something to do, then
yes. But we will see.
I'll be here for it, that's for sure.
Nice. Keeping safe. Good work.
Spy trying to break out of 850. Failing
850 again.
Feels like it wants to go though.
Seeing a rotation now. Tesla's gone
green. Apple very close to going red.
It's just like rotation between the
names.
[sighs and gasps]
What's this
level that we're at? Oh, it's the
playback's low. Asia low. Okay. I was
thinking, what the hell is that?
[snorts]
Spy really looks like it wants to break
out. It's just struggling at that 850.
There must be some exposure there.
Control now down at 30. So that's you
can use that as sentiment.
There's 30s. There's the tap. They just
tapped it in hell. There you go. So
literally just called it and they just
absorbed it there.
So buyers are sat at 30s right now.
Right here.
Came straight in and said, "No, we'll
gobble that up. We want to go higher."
So buy still trying to break out of 850.
Don't understand really why hasn't just
gone for it. Why isn't just absolutely
ripped faces at this point?
Got them caught. Just rip the faces. You
have them caught spy. What are you
doing?
Q's stuck at VW up. Back to point of
control maybe here to these 30s again.
We do have big buy side delta there. So
everyone there has been a buyer at 30s.
If you flip under that then maybe you
get exposure lower again. So this is
just the range rotation. So back to 30s
we go again like we just talked about.
This is key. Now if we start flushing
this we can get really really heavy
because they've come in very very heavy
by side here. So 30s is your level. They
will need to absorb around these 30s
these buyers otherwise they're going to
get themselves caught by failing to
break out again.
Problem is the the rotation. This is why
I don't like it when some of you have
asked why don't you trade it when you
can see it because you're fighting over
10 or 20 points. Like sellers are
currently stuck under 20. Buyers are
currently stuck over 30 definitely over
40.
Does not do you know what I mean? Like
you see the days when we're in expansion
when I'll sit here and we'll trade 200
point winners together. I'm trying to
fight over 10 20 points like it's just
not what
it doesn't get me going is the best way
of me putting it. Doesn't get me going.
Spy still trying to hold on and break
out.
Vicks trading around lower date. I tell
you what, if SPY doesn't break out soon,
they're going to get caught. They're at
They've been at 850 all morning. 5 10 15
20 30 minutes they've been up here.
Strong delta coming in by side again.
They're still not moving higher here.
This is going to get dangerous for these
buyers on NQ soon.
they don't get a breakout here, they're
going to get themselves caught
in this current 5m minutee candle.
They've sold under 30s without getting a
breakdown and they've bought above point
of control. So, it's very very tight.
Here come the sellers. They are trying.
They are trying desperately to get a
breakdown back down to this low, back
down to 600 value area low. They are not
getting their way though and it's just a
massive battle here. Look at Spy trying
again. Come on, Spy. What are you doing?
Why are you struggling so much?
PC again here.
Spy going again for high of day. I
cannot believe it's taking this long for
it to try and do it.
Q's are stuck under VWAP. Spy relative
strength. SPY is trying to break out. ES
is trying to break out. Q's of relative
weakness here.
The market does not look good in tech
right now. The only thing dragging it up
is Amazon.
It's amazing to me that we're even
holding on. This is what I mean by it's
a bit weird. I don't know if you can see
this. These are like what I would call B
and C list names in tech. They're all
getting absolutely clobbered. Then we
come to here. Can you guys see this?
Yeah. It doesn't look It's not like
we're having big drive out, but we're
just holding on. Which is why I've been
so focused on the spiders and the gamma
exposure because I just think it's
option traders controlling this whole
market right now. It's the dealers.
It's just the option traders. I don't
think it's anything else genuinely.
Right. There's the breakout on SPY.
Still can't hold its gains. Traded
straight back down to 50. If they don't
get a confirmed breakout soon, they are
going to get absolutely whacked. Back to
point of control again. This is where
the biggest level traded again and it's
all buy side into 30s.
So buyers will need to protect this. If
they sell under this is a big problem.
VIX looks like it wants to close its
gap. Gap fill on the VIX will be 1694.
So, I can't remember which one of you
said you were looking for 18s. And I was
like, why? Why? It doesn't need to go
there before FMC does it. 18s is very
high.
All right. If we're having a low
volatility day, we'll go low teens.
We're not going to go high teens.
Yeah. Just bouncing between gamma walls.
Yeah, exactly. That's all we're doing.
Okay, back to these 30s again.
They lose this. We might test that value
area low at 600 609s.
Try and absorb again. Passive buy still
here. Big selling absorbing again. Man,
if you lot trading this, you you got
balls of steel. I don't know what to
say. I don't know how you trade this
chop. I don't know how you're even
attracted to trade it either.
failed breakout on spy again over 650.
That's starting to fail now.
There's still absorption on this tape
here this morning. But uh if he gets out
the way because we've had a failed
breakout on the spy and we start to
roll, we're going to come back down to
fiero low which sort of 6, we just call
it 610.
And then if they get close below that,
then they can look for low day and
previous day lows. But uh that's kind of
where we're at at the moment.
I will just remind you that uh at these
levels sellers have had no success for
two weeks. I'm just going to remind you
that while we're looking at this two
weeks, no success at these levels.
Anticipation of a Fed rate cut today.
Yeah, they check. It's so annoying and
contorted. I don't like we were talking
about it yesterday. I don't know why
they've done it. It's so dumb because
now I don't know who any of you are.
And it's not like they've given me an
option either. I've I've looked it up to
see if there's a setting I can change.
There isn't. So stupid. So so stupid.
Back to sleep we go then.
Look at this. [sighs and gasps] This is
what you're dealing with right now.
Seriously.
Cannot close above. Slow grind. Can't
close below. Where's the 82s? Here. So,
look below 82s. This is the gamma. Come
back up. The next level is up here at
85. So, I don't know what they're going
to do. Do they want to revisit here or
revisit here? So, 50/50 right now. No
idea.
It's [\h__\h] stupid. This is This is
what we've been served for
as long as I can remember now.
Basically, it's getting that long.
Yeah, totally. I agree, contorted. I
totally agree with you. It's I don't get
why they did it. They did a trial
earlier in the year and then clearly no
one liked the trial because they put it
back after two days and now it's back
again. It's like what? Like what are you
doing? No one liked it. That's why you
got rid of it and now you've brought it
back again.
Hey spy going to try again at these 50s.
It's failed here one, two, three, four,
five, six times. Six fiveminute candles
have all failed here on the spy.
Can we get back inside previous day's
value? That's current value. Area high
is basically previous day's value. We
cannot get acceptance higher. We cannot
get acceptance lower. Which means we're
just going to do a whole lot of nothing.
at this point. They've done so much
work. They should just go back inside
value, but they just can't.
They can't They can't get They can't get
over 50 and they can't get get below 620
or 600. Like we've talked about numerous
times. You got 50 points to play with.
Do I not use real orderflow instead of
trading view? Yes, I do.
Spy trying again. failing again. Sellers
just caught got caught again at 30s.
Buyers again can't get through 50s. Once
they break 50s, there's probably a run
straight up to these levels up here.
Once they break 50s, oh, sorry, I've got
you on this still. My bad.
Once they break 50s here, then there's
probably a run up potentially close the
gap at 700s if they can get going.
I don't know cap. Yeah, I'm not I'm not
sure. There's value area low, right?
Let's see if they get acceptance now. If
they do, then you're looking for a drive
up into 700. So, you got 50 points
expansion here. If they can get
acceptance over this level, they have to
find acceptance over it. If they don't,
then you're going to go straight back
down. You're testing that same with spy.
Looks awful. They're testing the same
level. You can go straight back down.
Buyers just got trapped up there again
trying to trade through it. This looks
terrible like a failed breakout to me.
But, you know, who knows? This is moving
very, very quickly one side to the
other.
This looks terrible. This looks like a
fail breakout.
So, back down to point of control on the
day, which is 30s again. If they absorb
here, they try and go back up. You get
my point? Like your range, there's no
range here to play. There's nothing to
play with. That's a failed breakout
through value. So, they tried to get
above here. They did all this work,
didn't get confirmation. They come
straight down to here. If they lose
this, they come down to here. So,
there's a rotation between here, there's
a rotation between here, and there's a
potential rotation between here. Those
are the levels on the charts right now.
Right? If you like rotation, you like
playing for 10 20 points, then this is
your market. This is your market where
you can clean up.
That is my idea of hell. I'll be honest.
Oh, and up we might go again then.
[laughter]
You guys are brave if you like this.
Yeah, exactly. Everything's flat. Like
this is a no trade. Look guys, this is
this is why we use profile, right?
That's your range. This is what you're
trading. That's your maximum range right
now. That,
right? Be able to look at the charts and
be like, am I interested in trading from
50s to 15s? Cuz that's all it's telling
me at the moment that is available. That
can change, but at this moment,
remember, you can only trade what's in
front of you now, not what you hope.
acceptance, a drive above with volume
and a hold, right? Not that that is not
acceptance. That is a clear rejection.
If we come into it and we have trapped
buyers in here and we fail this blue
level and we come straight back down to
point of control, that's not acceptance.
So, this is the like I just talked
about. There's the rotation. Failed,
failed, failed, failed, failed, failed.
You need to see this or you need to see
this. this. If you're playing edge to
edge, that's your edge.
Like a tap into something doesn't mean
we're going higher, does it?
If we get above it and we pull back and
we hold it, that's a good sign, but not
if we can't do that. Again, they've just
trapped buyers up there again. They've
just run up to 55. It's all buy side and
we haven't moved higher, which means
there's a passive seller up here. They
need to now hold. If they don't hold,
they're going to get themselves caught
like I've talked about numerous times
today.
They need to drive higher now because
they've come heavy in by side again.
They came in heavy and buy side up there
into 55s
failed again.
You get the point here folks. Are you
seeing acceptance over that blue line,
this horizontal line on your chart? No.
Are you seeing acceptance over current
value? Remember this is previous day,
previous day. Oh my god. Come on,
Trading View. This is previous day. This
is current day. Is price above current
day? No. Is price above previous day?
No. So, what are we likely to do? We're
likely to just keep doing this. And at
the moment, there's your point control.
So, this. And if we fail this, probably
maybe this. And if we fail this, maybe
this. If we're going to base above, they
need to squeeze out. They need to hold a
print here. And you got to remember you
got trap buyers here. And if they get
lucky and they use their stops, we can
come up here. That is the maximum move
I'd be looking for at the moment would
be 700. But it would have to get above
this and find acceptance.
Thanks, Contorted.
Like I said, those buyers came in 652
and above and they failed uh again. I
should just say again. They failed
again.
Spy at 650. It's barely moving the spy.
It is barely moving.
Totally. I totally agree. And it's not
just today. Remember we talked about it
pre-market like zoom out on the daily.
How many inside days are there? This is
why I got so animated yesterday when
someone's like, "It's a clear trend."
Do you understand the definition of a
trend?
I [snorts] get annoyed because
saying things like that when we're at
700 encourages people to size in at 700
expecting like we're going to get a big
move and it had another 30 points before
it failed. And that's why I get
frustrated. It's like if you're going to
call something, you better be have some
good thesis or or know that you're
right. Otherwise, there are new people
here. I remember being a new person
many, many years ago, following
people into trades that didn't know what
they were talking about and getting
stuck. And that's the last thing I want
you guys to do. I want you guys to
understand the conditions. Right?
Sellers are trying again here.
Currently, sellers are stuck at 45s
again. So, they just came piling in
there. We're not moving lower. There's a
passive buyer here at the moment. Let's
see if they come right back down to 30s
point control.
Yeah, I use IB levels. And we've got
another five minutes left until initial
balance is set.
Absolutely. If you want to look for
auction, failed auction, IB levels, you
can use
point control here. If we fail point of
control, we probably come to 14s. If we
hold in front of point control, we're
going to retest this. And that's all
we're going to do. Back and forth, back
and forth, back and forth.
I agree, Mo. That's why I'm not trading
it.
If we come outside of RA, if for any
reason they want to go risk on or risk
off before FOMC, I'm all ears for it.
Like I'm here for it. But if we're going
to just keep doing what we're doing, uh
I'm not really interested.
How do I use initial balance? I use it
well, there's confluence to to dictate
what is a trend day and what is not a
trend day. what is a potential auction
and what is a failed auction. Right? So,
it's no different to what we've just
seen here. If you imagine initial
balance high is here and let's just say
initial balance low is here. Right?
Let's just say that's what we had this
morning. Forget I know we don't because
that's not the times. That is a look
below and fail. Right? So, we're going
to go to the other side of the auction.
That is a look above and fail to the
other side of the auction. To the other
side of the auction. This is the key
level. Now, like we just talked about,
if we fail point of control, we're
probably going to test 15. And if we
fail 15, we're going to come to previous
week's point of control. It's just
auction theory. It works the same way.
It doesn't matter what you're looking
at, whether it's an orb or initial
balance or profile. It's all about the
auction. Who's stuck? Where are they
stuck?
I don't use premarket P sigma. Um, that
doesn't mean you shouldn't use it. I
just don't use it. I I don't pay any
attention to the volume created
pre-market unless there's been a decent
move and I think there's an edge to
play, but that doesn't mean you
shouldn't use it. It's just my personal
thing. I don't really use it.
This is volume. This is delta.
So rather than cumulative delta, this is
delta each candle. All right. So you can
see at the low, we had strong delta and
we flipped, went straight by, had
straight back up.
Okay, so we're at these sort of 30s
again. This point of control on the
current day. If we wash here, we're
going to test value on the day, which is
14. If we wash 14, we're going to test
previous week point of control, which is
600. SPY has definitely done a failed
breakout, but it's back to VWAP again.
ES back to VWOP as well. Q's relative
weakness on the day.
VIX has found a bid in front of those
17s we talked about. So, in that demand
block we drew out this morning, VIX has
found a bid. It's going to come up and
test 1720 now on the VIX, which is
previous day high. If we fail that,
market can get relief and move um back
up. If we rip through 1720 on the VIX,
you might see some weakness coming to
the market. Right now, we're just in
balance.
Am I leaning towards a rate cut? Yeah.
Like 100 million% is priced in. 95%
chance we're getting a quarter rate
quarter base point cut is priced in. In
my opinion, we already know that there's
a reason,
right? Let's let's just make sure we all
understand this.
when we were here, right? When we were
at these levels, this was the last FOMC.
Remember that. This was the last FOMC.
Don't forget that. The old highs is the
last FOMC. When we were here, we were
expecting the rate cut. We was we were
saying, "Oh, we're going to get a cut in
December and then maybe we're going to
get one in January." And then Pal went,
"Um, well, I wouldn't be so sure you're
actually going to get one in December."
Right down here. And then they were
like, "Oh, [\h__\h] Well, we've hurt the
market here." And then what what's said
by Fed members here? Oh, we're
definitely getting at least a quarter
point cut here. Like 100%. Oh, we price
it in. We go straight back to where we
thought that before. All right.
Remember, we price in ahead of time.
That's not to say that on a rate cut
decision, we don't go higher. That would
be a raid of liquidity. But for me, it's
priced in. This was pricing it out. This
was pricing it back in. If you go and
look at the timings when pal said we're
no longer we don't guarantee a December
cut that's what caused this move the
moment then he said well I don't think
it was him it's Besset and some others
yeah yeah we're going to have to do a
cut we came to here like I said this
morning in a pre-market show I'm not
worried about the cut I'm more
interested in what they say about the
labor market I think that's what all the
questions are going to be on the labor
market and the bonds that's what people
are going to care about today in my
opinion in my opinion they already know
the cut's
What we don't know is the January cut.
January cut is much less likely. I think
like 30% chance at the moment or
something is what's priced in.
Correct. I don't know whoever said that.
Suptoid.
Sorry if I've said that wrong. Yeah, I
agree with you. It comes into what's
said afterwards.
What date am I changing the course? Uh,
new prices next year. Um, but the new
course, it's almost ready, folks. It's
it's been uploaded. My web developer is
just doing some finishing touches. Um,
the only thing I haven't been able to do
is I want to record a trend day using
orderflow and um, we haven't had one.
So,
it's kind of what I'm waiting for. So
hopefully [laughter] hopefully we can go
into a pro trend this week or something
at some point and then I can record that
because at the moment all I've been able
to record using old flow is rotational
markets but I can't force it.
the new course uh $3.99. It's going to
be considerably cheaper if you're
already a member though and I'll do a
sale price for non-members, but it it
will be much much cheaper for
non-members. If you've already done the
beginner to advance course, you're going
to get a uh fat discount as I always
promise like you if you're already
grandfathered in, I look after you.
All right, spy starting to fail here
and Q's are holding a bid. This is
hilarious.
What's holding the cues up? Amazon.
Let's have a look at Amazon here.
Look at that. Just bid, bid, bid, bid,
bid. It's [\h__\h] stupid, mate. Bid off
bid VWAP. Where are we in? Let me have a
look higher time frame. Yeah, we're in
breakout. That's why we're now in
breakout and coming up to this level on
Amazon. So, that's holding the market
up.
at P again.
View and PC again. Same thing. If we
fail this, probably going to go 615s. We
reclaim this. This is your range. I've
talked about it all morning. So, last
time I'm going to say it cuz it's
probably getting boring.
This edge to here, this edge to here,
this edge to here, this edge to here,
this edge to here, fail this here, fail
this here, and fail that here. Right?
until that it's like level to level.
Just think of it as I don't know lifts
or however you want to think of it as
like this will be respected. This then
will be respected. This then will be
respected. This then will be respected.
This is a level and this is a level.
Okay. So we will keep testing each side.
Can we get above? No. Can we get below?
No. Can we get above? No. Can we get
below? No. Okay. Can we get below now?
Maybe. Okay. Can we get below that?
Maybe no. Can we get above that? No. Can
we get Do you see what I'm saying? And
then it would go, okay, let's try this
one. Okay, let's try this one. Okay, no
acceptance. Straight back up, for
example.
It's just a rotation, right? Very
different to a trend. A trend would just
be absorbing and absorbing and absorbing
to move higher or move in one direction.
We're creating liquidity right now.
Yeah, ping pong. That's a really good
way of putting it actually. Ping pong.
Here we go. So, value low about to be
tested. 7:15 we just talked about 7:15
615. This edge of this blue right here,
this is what we're testing now. If we
fail that, probably back down to this
600. Okay. So, here we go. This is also
the New York open becomes important. But
also down to 600 is now possible. So, if
they fail this New York open, then
previously point of control. So, if you
are short here or short up here, here is
a cover point one. This would be a cover
point two. If you fail this previous day
low, current day's low. And if you fail
that uh previous
weak value area low, if you get value
area high, if you get really lucky, we
come down to here if you get very very
lucky. I would doubt it, but uh you get
very very lucky.
So there's the 600 test like we talked
about. Okay, so now the ping pong can be
between 615 and 600 this level. And if
we fail that low day.
Yeah, exactly. Adam, Americans won't get
that. To me, to you. To me, to you.
[laughter]
Reminds me of being a kid.
Okay. So, now what's going to matter is
these value area lows on the day. Right.
So, we've gone to point control again.
We might come up here and revisit this
sort of level again. And how we at there
will become important.
And these 600s, remember we've talked
about over and over again.
Heavy selling here, but will they get
their way? Will they get low of day,
which is probably what they're trying to
get, but uh I'm not convinced in this
market they're going to get their way.
Bids here at 80, bids here at 70.
They're they're walking down. I still
think this needs to pop back up to 15s
to test that value area low at the
moment.
No, it's from uh it's from Chuckle
Brothers. Skippy the Bush Kangaroo. That
was that Australian thing. I I haven't
heard anyone talk about that since I was
like 5 years old. All right, there's the
600 test again. All right, so if we
flush here, then initial balance low,
previous day low, and if we get an
auction lower today, then you can watch
these levels down here into 500s.
So, we are starting to see some heavy
action. Spy failing that that uh 850
numerous times. Um spy. ES uh spy back
to 82s. Remember this is gamma level
into 82s. Be aware of that. We're into a
gamma level of 82s. If they hold this,
you want to be careful. But if they drop
this then move to 80 is possible based
on gamma. Here we go. Previous day low
and initial balance low. Now clear
targets down here. Right. This is where
we absorbed earlier. But I kind of
expect this to get taken now. I've been
here so many times and if we crack
violently then these are your next
levels if we're going to see expansion
550 on the book. There's an old
imbalance down there at 550.
Are we going to trade into him?
IB low coming up. Previous day low just
beneath that. Under that we've got room
Watch this spy at 82s. We've traded
under it. Now, if they trade back to it
and reject it, there's a move to lower
day and then possibly to 680. I wouldn't
bank on it because we're technically
still in a rotational market, but we
have a chance to expand lower if sellers
take control. It's a big old if, but
that's the if.
So, IBL your target. If you've already
been short in this, then you want to be
covering some here for sure.
You send me indicator Gmail, but
nothing's working. Then you probably
either sent me your wrong name
or you need to hit refresh on your
cookies.
Won't be my end. Be you putting in your
wrong Trading View name or something.
I still think we probably sweep, but we
might might need a push up to test
first. We will see. They're offering f
they're like bidding at 550. So, I
expect the market to flush through 70
6560 5550 to fill these players. But
it's just whether it needs a retest of
610 615s first.
Doesn't look that way though at the
moment.
And I would watch those 82s on spy.
We're coming back up for a back test of
82s now.
Here it comes. Here's the 82s on spy.
They reclaim this. We're going straight
back upside. It just means a dip into
gamma and then straight back upside.
They're starting to try and reclaim this
fiveminute candles dropped under it
again. So, two 5-minute candles have
come under 82 and reclaimed. How are we
going to close here? 10 seconds left in
this 5 minute. I want to see if we close
heavy.
Closed right at 82.
[laughter]
Like on the money spy. Uh I'm going to
get just a quick refill of my coffee
here. Look below here.
look for lower here. Here we go. So,
there's your IB low. That's your TP1.
Next level is that previous day low.
[clears throat and cough]
Sellers got caught down there underneath
initial balance low. They definitely
triggered some sellers under 66. All
right. So, just be aware at the bottom
of this candle. There are some sellers
caught
back testing 82s again. It's definitely
that is the level on spy. That's your
over under.
Yeah, totally agree Sigma. There's a
seller down there underneath 66. He sold
this guy here as well. 135 lot and then
a 200 lot right at the low of day. So if
this is the end of the auction then the
last seller sold. But we will see won't
we'll see.
82's test here on spy. They're through
it. It's just depends how we close on a
fivem minutee bar I'd say. and we can
still afford remember a retest of 608
610 somewhere up there into this value
into previous week point of control. We
haven't retested anything. So if they're
going to build out liquidity, they're
going to build it out here. If they want
to build that out for this move, they're
going to build it out into here and use
these stops to do it. If it's a failed
break, then they'll do this, this, this,
and this. And if they reclaim this, then
guess what? You know where we're going.
Remember, level to level, level to
level, level to level. It's all we're
doing. come and back test this level now
and see if the sellers are up there.
See them stacking on the book here. 600
625.
Okay, back through. Here we go. Here's
the previous week point of control test.
Now, this and value will become key. I'd
say from here to sort of 610
sellers will need to sell against,
right? To to force the market lower. If
they don't, we can come straight back up
to 20 because we're thin all the way up
into here, aren't we? So, sellers need
to come here. Otherwise, we're going to
go back up to 20. If sellers confirm
here, they will look for a breakdown and
a new low. If they get a new low,
there's a chance we see previous day low
and get like a bit of a cascade.
Otherwise, back into range, fail
breakdown.
Hopefully, I've made this clear. This is
everything we talked about pre-market as
well. So, nice rejection there so far.
Previous week point control. Watching
this very carefully here. Do we get
follow through now? They're trying to
bid here.
Think we're going to sell through it. I
think we're going to get follow through
here.
There is tempting. It's a big level into
85 where we just broke out from.
Spies reclaimed 82. Very aware of that.
Very aware of that on the spiders.
might well squeeze up here if they're
going to reclaim and just set it go back
upside then spy previous day low 8260
and then 83 is possible on spy so that
will pull this market up if we do
no spy is not it be up
is at 8266 is at 8240 right
Okay, back into previous weekly point
control. So, here's the test here to
value area low is key. Like I said, up
to sort of I would say even 610 would be
uh appropriate with this little node
here. If they get acceptance through
this buyers, then they're going to go
all the way up here to 626. So, sellers
need to defend this level here. They're
failing to defend this level here will
allow relief all the way back up to
here. And this would be the same thing.
A look below and a failure and back into
range. Look below into range. Look
below. Well, that didn't look below, but
back into range. So, sellers must sell
here. And if they don't, then they've
failed to complete the rotation lower.
So, this needs to be a buildout of
liquidity for sellers. Otherwise, a hold
of this and you're right back into this
level.
It's good drive there. Buyers got stuck
at that high. Sellers taking control of
this current candle. Buyers now stuck
over 600.
Great from sellers. Okay, let's play,
baby. Let's play. Let's play. Let's
play.
So, in this from 96es once I saw that
transition. I'm not going to hold back
above 600 though. I'll give it four
points of risk here. I haven't taken
profit yet. Just want to see if we can
get a breakdown because I think they've
got the chance to do it. The only thing
that's putting me off is what SPY is
doing right now. Maybe I need to take
one off here. Where did that strong
selling coming in? 94s.
Think we can get it. SPY's got to
reject. Get back under 82. I'm not
seeing what I want to see on spy. That's
the only thing I'm concerned about. And
selling on this candle's starting to get
caught around 80.
Need to break down here otherwise I'm
out. Not going to give this all the way.
Okay, I'm going to cover one just in
case. I want to be greedy.
There's a nice buy side stuck right now
over 99. I can show you here on this
like they're stuck over here. Looking to
see if we can trade this down. I'm just
concerned about this setting here, but I
want to see these guys get stuck and a
rotation.
[snorts]
Come on.
Sellers can't get a break here. Let's
buy back through 82 84 8240s. Don't like
this. The more I'm looking at it, the
less the less I like it right now.
sellers just had the opportunity to do
it and they haven't. Still holding one.
I'm going to move my stop break even
though.
Maybe I'll give it give it a little bit
of room. Stop at 96es cuz actually
where's that point control? Stop at 98.
[snorts]
See if we can let this work. I don't
like what I'm seeing on spy and that
might ruin this trade.
Either way, locking in money.
Come on, [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] off, spy. Go back down.
[snorts]
It's just Amazon holding this market up.
Everything else doesn't look good.
We've got stuck here.
Yeah, spy is going to be a pain.
Close to stopping out here. Break even.
They need to protect 98 98. Yeah, 9600s,
I guess.
So, here's my break even point. I'm
giving it a tiniest bit of room here,
but I'm at break even now on this
runner.
Buyers have tried again here and are not
getting their move higher. So, we're
stuck again in small rotation, but spy
is now at VW. If spy doesn't reject
here, I'm going to get stopped out into
600. Very close to tapping me out here.
O
tick away from taking me pretty much.
I'm out. So stopped out on that. Gave it
a chance, but again, this was all
because of spite. This might still work.
But again, like I said, it's option
dealers are controlling this market.
It's [\h__\h] annoying, but that's what
we've got. No breakdown under 82.
Reclaim 82 now to 83s. reclaim that 85
is possible. That's why I've got price
alert here and here. I think this is the
pin at the moment is 80 to 85. So that's
what I'm watching is the extremes. But
they had the chance here. Failed to
break down. We took we had a go at it.
Got one off in profit and one just a
just uh I gave it a bit more room than
break even to be honest, but made money
on that trade either way. Okay. So now
if they're going to find acceptance,
we're going to come back up to this
shelf like we talked about. So, this
becomes the area that they're going to
attack where we got thick. All right.
And we've had another look below and
fail. And they're going to come right
back into this area here. And at this
point, I wouldn't be interested really
in reshorting this. I'd have to see a
lot of weakness because they just had an
attempt down here and failed.
Hopefully that makes sense.
Look at spy now at 83s. It's just so
predictable with the uh options, guys.
kind of wild. I don't remember a market
that was uh this much pinned
uh by options by levels. Yeah, but it
just feel it feels like it's all options
because if you actually like just zoom
out, we're often not taking liquidity at
the moment. We're just coming back into
a level and finding a reaction.
VIX still looks like might want to close
that gap. If VIX fails 17s, we're going
to close that gap. So, back to point of
control on the day. Back to these 30s.
Remember there are buyers stuck above
30s today. All right. So buy side is
stuck above 30s. But uh you know this is
a strong move after a fail breakdown.
Big buyers coming in here. Big big big
buyers coming in here trying to get that
move back through point of control. And
all the delta is buy side basically over
31. So big retest up here. SPY looks
like it might go all the way back to
higher day at the moment.
And sellers are trying to get a close
under 18 at the moment. Just failed.
They just came piling in and failed
again. This feels like it's going to go
higher at this point. To me, sellers
need a reaction in front of point of
control. They keep getting absorbed. So,
we'll see see how this like next minute
or so closes out.
What's that imbalance? 09. So, tens.
So reaction in front of 30
sellers came flying in right where we
are now. This is their price that they
came flying in and they are being
absorbed.
Like I said, I don't want to play up
here. I'll wait to see what we do next.
It's too risky now. I had my shot.
That's my one shot at it.
Oh, the roll over of the new contract.
You think they'll do it then? I think we
do. I mean, we'd better do it before
then. I hope we do it before then, mate.
Okay, sellers trying again here. We
caught We just caught some buyers above
20.
Okay, on those last couple of candles,
some buyers have been caught up there
above 20s.
This is looking a bit more promising,
but value area value area low now is
605. Previous week point of control 600.
That's still like your sort of
sentiment.
It's possible that they did needed to do
a big squeeze out into this level that I
just gave you up here. Remember this
shelf here. I said if they get through
where was it? If they get through this,
we will revisit up here. They are
selling that at the moment. So this is
your twoleg. It's possible that they set
one of these, but again, we're in a
range rotation. I don't want to have too
many goes at it, but we will see.
Back to point of control from previous
week. If we sell through this, it's got
a chance
again. Uh, SPY is still above VWAP right
now. It's just coming to back test it.
They're trying to sell under this.
Interesting.
Yes. Inspire V. Really? We've done
nothing. When you zoom out, we've done
nothing.
Venom. It's probably because you it
means you prefer trading trend and uh
you've got to be see money take money
and play the extreme. So like even I
didn't take the short up here. Even
though I said it could fail, I don't
like how we got there. I need to see a
lower high form here. This is a two leg,
but at the moment it looks like they
might just dunk it.
does look like they might dunk at this
point. If they reject uh 600s now,
maybe.
Maybe. But we're into this little node
here. We sell through this. We can wash.
But I'd like to see them reject come up
here and reject this. If if it's going
to be really kind, I'd want to see this
this this
reject this. Fail this. Wash this.
Reclaim this.
Nothing's on
if it's going to be kind.
Staying heavy here. Let's buy back 82s.
Oh man. Can you give me something to get
involved in.
If shorts fail to break down here
though, they will get caught.
Come on then, baby.
They're trying.
Think we're going to do it. I think
they've got enough core. Come on.
Here we come.
And we see some expansion now.
Think we're going to get it, folks.
Big sellers coming in at 77. Buyers just
got trapped in this single candle here
again. I think we're going to flush
lower. This breaks this current low 71s,
we should flush. Here we go. There we
go. Boom.
There's your order flow. Oh my god. What
did I just say? [laughter]
[\h__\h] nailed that. You best believe I
absolutely hammered the [\h__\h] out of that
once they were caught.
What a beauty.
Literally saw them get caught right in
front of my eyes.
All right, let's see if we can get any
more here. So, there's previous day low
now taken. Now, if they're going to
rotate this range, 500 469 is possible.
If they're going to rotate this range,
okay, this is why we're here today. Just
in case they do it, there's no guarantee
they do it, but just in case they want
to play ball, that's what we're looking
at.
So, IB retest here. Remember, if sellers
fail to move lower um and we get
acceptance back into initial balance, it
would be look below and fail and we're
going to go right back to 600s if they
want. All right, just be aware of that
of like what we're looking at here.
Here's the sweep of previous day low. If
they get no acceptance under here, they
might need to come and check like these
82s where we just broke down from this
here.
Sorry folks, I'm trying. I'm trying
here. They [snorts] might need to come
and test this. If we stay heavy versus
this and break down here, then I expect
a revisit into these areas. Okay? If
they reclaim this and hold a higher low,
I would just be risk off for the shorts
at that point. But buyers are attempting
here. You're seeing strong buying coming
in and at the moment, we're not moving
higher.
So, these buyers are going to get stuck
here again. If they can't get above,
they've just come flying in. 62 to 67s,
they've come flying in. If we can't move
above that and we break down a new low,
everyone in this candle will get stuck
again.
That IB low is a key sentiment now.
Yeah, I do TJ and especially in the
orderflow course which should be live in
like the next week or two. It's like
literally what I focus on, but it's in
the beginner to advance course as well.
If you've not traded me with me before,
I would advise you do the beginner to
advance course first just so that you
can understand the setups, what I'm
looking at, why I'm looking at it, and
then um afterwards do the order flow one
because you're going to need some bigger
understanding. All right, so we might be
coming up to these 80s here like I
talked about. And if we get through
that, then there's no acceptance lower.
All right, if we get through that, then
there's no acceptance lower.
Guess what? Spy caught a bid at.
Guess what? Spy caught a bid at. Right,
here's the test towards these 80s that
we just talked about. It's so funny.
That's like it's literally to the tick
there. What was that low on spy? 68203.
Are you [\h__\h] kidding me?
[laughter]
All right, so this is the test of 80s.
That little volume shelf. Let's see if
they break below initial balance now and
create a new low. Here we go. Really
nice
[\h__\h] market, man. It's hilarious. All
right. Really nice. Really nice
rejection off the 80s. Like we talked
about, they might need to revisit these
80s. Really nice. Can we see follow
through now? Can we see follow through
now?
[snorts]
[laughter]
Spy, you're horrible, Spy. You're
horrible. Really good. I think we're
going to get breakdown here. Oh, be
careful. Actually big big seller just
came in there and he got caught. 226 lot
at those lows there. Literally as I said
that at 556 you got a 226 lot sellside
and he is caught. So we need to trade
under him. If we trade under him he's
going to be fine but we need to trade
under him
and he's at about 5.56.
See it on map right here.
This guy here 227 lot. What's his
average price? 559 is his average price.
He's stuck. There you go. He's stuck.
So, be careful.
Be careful.
Back to IB. Those 80s is your guide. If
you get acceptance back through 80s,
then you probably get a drift higher.
All right. If we get back through, you
should call it 90s. Really, the test is
80s, but if they get back through 90s,
then it'll be a look below. If they hold
above here, then we squeeze. If they
reject this and build up more liquidity,
then this is the target, right? Just be
careful because low hanging fruit was
previous day low. We've taken it. This
is all about the weekly profile. Now,
are we going to expand the current week
to come and test previous week's edge?
All I'd say is there is uh not from the
previous week, but from the week before
that, there is a naked point of control
down at two I think it's 200s. Where is
it?
24950s.
That's where I want the market to trade
to.
Yeah, let's go then.
Give us the puke then.
So, can we get now into this and this?
That's my question for the market at the
moment. Can we get all the way down
there?
Just trying to zoom out and see what
levels we have in between these. Just
make sure I'm not missing anything.
There is a bit of a node
540. I want to be aware of 540. There is
a little bit of a low volume node at 540
and then a spike out to 530. So 540 530
is going to be key. And if we get below
that then I think there is a chance
to trade down to 500 or 491 and 470. So
540 530 is a key level coming up here
just based on previous week volume. If
we trade under that I think we get a
snap.
Guess where spy is.
Can it let go of this?
Sellers are coming in here. We're not
moving lower. Just be aware of that. 540
530. Once we're out of this trade, I can
show you why I'm looking at this level.
If we can close below this, there's a
low, if you look at a weekly profile,
there's a little low volume node of sort
of 540 and then we spike out to 5 530.
So, this is like a little rice on
previous week. If we close below this,
we can wash. They're trying. They're
trying. They're trying. They're trying.
Have they got any juice? At the moment,
they haven't got any juice, but I think
it's coming. Here's the 40 test. All
right. 1430 coming up. If we trade
through this, this blue box is target
500s. If we trade through that this
previous week value area like you don't
want to be risk on as in you don't want
to be short under here that's the edge
of value
and you don't really want to trade this
back above 50 here because all the
sellers came in at 50. It can trade
above 50. I'm just saying you don't
really want it to trade above 50.
Really nice. This is looking really
good.
Yeah, 50 is key. It's where all volume
was traded up to 50. We don't want it.
If you're sell side, you don't want it
back above 50. All right. If you're sell
side, you don't want this back above 50.
Am I looking at 488? Uh for targets.
Yeah, I see that level. That That's what
I'm just above that. Yeah, that four.
Yeah, 4904 this box basically it's the
same area. It's there or thereabouts.
This area here. So that low from
December 4th. And if you look at the
profile previous week, we're go Yeah.
Come on. Get under 30. Now sellers are
trying to come in here aggressively. Be
careful here. Be careful here. They're
trying to come in aggressively. If we
snap this, we move lower. If we don't
snap this, they are going to get
themselves caught. Cannot trade back
above 50. In fact, I don't even want to
get that high now. Lots of selling
coming in here, folks. If we don't move
lower, it means there's a passive buyer
in this little node. Remember, I said 40
to 30 is a key level if we're going to
find acceptance lower.
They're struggling here. They came
flying in sellside here. They're caught.
If you get back above 50s, you want to
take this trade off in my opinion. If
this gets back above 50s and you're
holding that runner, you want to take
this trade off. Here's a retest of it.
Sellers are now caught. For me, sellers
are caught under 30 right now in here.
Sellers are caught in this wick.
Sellers are caught here. They're trying
to defend here. All right. If they don't
get their way, a squeeze will come
available back up to these levels for a
test. Just trying to make you guys
aware. Those who took this short up here
or joined down here, right? You don't
really want it to reclaim this.
[snorts]
There's the tap of 50. Big reaction.
There is a fight here coming.
Spy retesting 82. Staying heavy so far.
Buyers trying this candle. They're
attempting to get back acceptance back
through.
There's a you you keep saying that.
Okay. And like I said, it will mean
you've either sent me the wrong username
for the indicator
or that you need to refresh the cookies
on your chart. So, if you tell me your
name, your Trading View name now, I'll
be able to check it. Just type your
Trading View name into into chat and
I'll be able to check if you've been
approved or not.
Buyers just caught got caught there
above 55s. So, that 50 level is still
big.
Delta's starting to flip from sell side
to buy side. They're trying to expand
now. So, they're going to come and test
60s now. That previous day low and
initial balance. Remember, if we go back
inside initial balance, it's to look
below and fail.
Schlomza 11. Right, let's have a look.
Slow-mo
11,
right? It means you put it in wrong to
prove now. It means you put it in wrong.
So, it should work now.
Uh, easy buy. Uh, I don't think so.
I don't I don't There's no confirmation
here that we're going back upside right
now.
The only thing I'd say is you got
sellers trapped under 33s. Momentum is
downside. You're outside of initial
balance. You're breaking out away from
previous week point of control. I'd say
for me, we've left value. This is the
first time
Here's
previous day's value. We've left it. We
rejected it a few times today. We're
searching lower now. We're probably
likely to search to previous week's
value area high. All right. Maybe here
if they absorb or do a look below and
fail, there's a buying opportunity.
But I wouldn't say now now that we're
breaking away from value. Look at the
volume we've left trap. We're breaking
away from value. I wouldn't say it's an
easy buy. I'd say that's uh it might be
what you consider a cheap buy, but I
wouldn't say momentum's on your side
yet, other than knowing that the sellers
are trapped under 33s. And it also
depends what your ambitions are. If we
start pivoting here, then yes, I think
that's a safer action, but you've still
got to get through this. I'd just be
slightly concerned about this right here
right on the edge of value. But if you
get acceptance in, then I would have to
agree with you. I would definitely say
that shorts are trap like I said once we
get over 50.
You think my previous week value area
high and value area low flipped?
Oh yeah, I see what you mean.
Okay, let's just
I see what you mean.
There we go.
Thank you for pointing that out.
Appreciate it.
There we go. All right. So, for me now,
no more shorts because for the first
time we've had shorts caught at the lows
and we're now
back inside and this. So, for me now,
now I'd consider if we want to trade
back inside, it's there. I'd still be
somewhat hesitant.
I'm gonna use the bathroom while this uh
figures itself out. And I've got to get
off uh I've got to get off when I come
back to be quite honest. Didn't realize
All
right, let's do an Apex giveaway and
then I got to go, folks. Sorry, I didn't
realize the time. I did say today was
going to be a shorter stream. So, let's
get this set up. Um, don't type anything
yet, otherwise it won't be included.
Uh, I should say Apex, I just got an
email from them. 90% sale just started,
folks. And insane Christmas sale. So,
they're going to do a 90% sale.
So, all evaluations currently are priced
at $1960. No matter the size that you're
looking at, $1960 for all evaluations.
Um,
activation fee on 25, 50K, and 100K is
now
$65.
Super cheap. That's really good. And for
the 150K, 250K, 300K, $125. So, great
time to grab these. Uh, sale ends
December 16th, so you haven't got long.
Actually, that's a very short sale. 4
day sale. Apex, that's for Apex. Okay.
So, let's uh So, code FCT will get you
90% sale. So, if you want to load up for
20 accounts, now is the time to do it. I
think they only do two to three 90%
sales a year. So, if you want to get 20
accounts, now is the time to do it. All
right, let's give a giveaway. Here we
go. You know the score, folks. Type FT
in chat.
So, whoever said that easy buy, you're
actually looking really good. I would
say it's an easier buy back. Well, safer
buy, cheap buy down here, safer buy here
once we reclaim initial balance. So,
whoever asked me earlier about the how
you use initial balance. This is your
prime example. Holds initial balance,
fails initial balance, reclaims initial
balance, back inside. That's your
target. VWOPS are always your target off
the IB trade back inside. So, if Tyson's
here, I'm sure Tyson just took this
trade back up to here. That's his trade.
Bread and butter trade every day. Can't
remember who asked me, but there we go.
Okay, give you guys one more minute. Um,
I'm really sorry it's a shorter stream
today. Um,
some of you in chat will know I'm
dealing with a lot of pretty big family
stuff um, offline and I have to deal
with that this morning. I'm sorry I'm
already running late. So, I'll uh if you
find me snappy on chat or
short-tempered, just know I'm only human
and um I have some pretty major stuff
going on off the charts. There's only so
much capacity I have to be calm.
Sometimes,
you know, things like mourning and grief
can cause a lot of pain and I will snap.
So, I'm apologies for the days when I do
that, but try and give me a bit of grace
if you can. I'm a human being. I'm going
through lots of things at the moment.
All right, let's pull this winner. I'll
give you guys 10 more seconds.
Okay, let's pull this winner.
Ron Ron 1847, are you here? Run, run,
run, run, run, run.
Are you here, my friend? Are you here,
my friend? Let me know you're here. In
chat, just shoot me a message.
Otherwise, there you are. Yes, sir.
Okay, I can see you. Ron Ron, what I'd
like you to do, shoot me an email,
info@flowzonetrader.com.
Just send me a screenshot of your uh
YouTube with you logged in. That's all I
need to see. So I can see the back end
of your YouTube. I can see you logged in
under your username and I will sort you
out a free Apex account. You can have
any size Apex account you want.
And that's it from me folks. Uh those in
Discord, uh I should be all done in time
and I want to be there to uh help you
guys with FOMC. Um just be cautious now
what I've been looking at now uh for the
remainder of the day. Let's just zoom
you out. Where's this? And just get you
prepared for the remainder of the day,
those that aren't with me. Okay,
so we have just
we are now coming back to test previous
week's value. You can see how important
this is. All right, the rotation. And
this is what I was talking about every
day this week. This is your previous
week's value. We're looking below
failing. We're looking above failing.
Looking below failing. Looking above
failing. Looking above failing. Looking
below currently potentially failing. I
would say you've got a bit longer. How
we close is important. If we stay heavy
here, then we're going to look, this is
current week's value. Then we're going
to look to trade underneath this to
here.
All right. That is a potential long
trigger there. All right. If we get down
into that and they hold, that's the
potential long trigger. If they also get
back inside current week's value and
previous and current days value and they
can't find acceptance, then what we're
going to do back up to the other side of
range. Be careful. Those of you trading
FOMC, if you see a rate cut, quarter
point cut, and you see the market doing
this, do not be tempted, okay? Do not be
tempted to just slam long as you see it
breaking out because we've had a rate
cut. We have trapped buyers up here.
Every time we've come up there, we
failed and we haven't actually tested
that volume. Beyond that, if we look
left,
look at the confluence.
Value area high, value area high, value
area high, value area low. I would say
from 900 to sort of 700, that is a big
supply zone. Now, we get through 900 and
you base above and hold, you find
acceptance, there's a trade up to 26,50.
Be very careful being risk on above
that. That's your point of control.
These buyers here from the week of which
started October 27th had never been let
out. Just understand that these guys
haven't been let out. All right? So just
be careful because I'm sure the algo
will probably want to print higher.
Remember it often will do it one move
one way fake and then go the other. It
might be that it does this. All right?
It might be that this this morning is
it? I don't know. But all I'm trying to
say is don't go full send. All right?
Just chill, chill, chill, chill, chill.
Um, see you guys Thursday, tomorrow.
Yeah, see you guys tomorrow morning.
Please trade safe in the afternoon.
Peace and love. Be kind to each other.
Use hard stops and uh, thanks for your
patience. I appreciate it.