Oh,
where's the camera?
There we go. Give that a second. Let's
move this. It's got jammed up.
All right, folks. Welcome back. Welcome
back. Hope you're doing good. See if we
can move this chair down a bit.
Okay.
How's everyone doing?
Oh, we're having tech nightmare already
to start the day. Funning games.
There we go.
There we go. All right. Welcome back.
Hope you had a good day yesterday. Nice
easy short yesterday. super super clear.
If you had the newsletter, you would
have been ready. All bears had to do was
defend 900, which they did, right? So,
on a daily chart, here we are. Here's
the defending level. There's the old
gap. There's the old swing high. Bears
are trying to defend this. Bulls will
want to catch a bid either here or here
to go back to alltime highs. That's the
game right now. We're not in multi-time
frame confluence. All right, you can see
on the daily, it's probably very likely
that we need to set a higher low
somewhere. We don't know where that's
going to be. All right. If they fail to
set high low, obviously we come all the
way back down to this volume node down
here. But uh that's what uh the market's
looking for at the moment, which means
all the time there's sellside pressure
down here. Bears have the chance have
the chance, not necessarily confirmed,
have the chance to try and have a little
break down here and a wash back to the
mean. Remember, you've got 50-day, 20
days sitting right there. So top bowl,
bottom bowl, mean. All right. two
standard deviation two standard
deviation. So it's very possible we see
this rotation at some point. All right,
bulls very clearly. They just got to get
back over well really the first stop
would be to get over 760 U because they
failed to hold there 760 740 750 that
kind of level that I talked about in the
newsletter. They have failed to get a
close above and hold. That's not very
good. This high here from Thursday last
week. All they needed to do was hold
that to force the squeeze. They haven't
um but they have built in supply up
here. So bulls need to get over 760 over
that. They're looking for 926,000 break.
Very, very simple. Into this old balance
range where we don't really get thick
until we get to uh 26. All right. So,
that's the story right now. So, what are
we watching? Well, if we get a
breakdown, we're watching for a break
underneath previous day low. If they
stay heavy for that rotation, right? If
they do a little sweep or a hold, then
you're just expecting more range to be
built out until there's a close above
25750.
And we can look at that more on the
hourly to make it make sense for you.
All right. So just focus on this chart
here. This is going to become really
key. All right. All we've got so far,
this is your previous week value. All
right. And we have had a look above on
Friday, fail. A look above Sunday and
Monday, fail. We're back inside previous
week's value. There you go. Right. We're
back inside balance. So we're rejecting
uh old supply. If we look left, we're
rejecting this. We can't even get up
into it. All right. So, this little node
here, right? Wait, from uh Monday the
3rd. All right, we can't get through
that. We're rejecting that, which means
we can't get back into these trapped
buyers up here. And we're back into an
old balance range. Look how much time
we've spent here this year, right? One
week, two week, 3 week, we're now into
week four. You can tell this is a huge
level, folks. All right, so that sort of
25, 900 down to 25, let's just call it
400. 20 25 450 massive level of rotation
because we've done it for uh this is
week four of doing it. So that's what
we're watching. So we have to pay close
attention to that previous week value. I
think all the time we keep failing where
I've put this now red box on. If we fail
previous days value area high, there's
probably a rotation back down to
previous day value area low. If we look
below reclaim that, that's probably a
rotation back up. We might well build a
Dshape in here because we've got FOMC
coming tomorrow. If big big big if, but
if we get weakness underneath previous
day value area low and previous day,
previous weak point of control. All
right, so we've got a double confluence
here. We know this is a massive area.
We've soaked off it. We couldn't close
below. We bounced off it. We couldn't
close below. We bounced off it. We
bounced off it. We bounced off it. If
this actually starts to let go and we
turn this into resistance, then I'd be
looking for this rotation down into at
least take out 500 and maybe down into
this 470. And we've got these double
wicks down here into 400. So that's what
I'm looking for. All right, it's very
clear. Very, very clear. Either we break
down, stay heavy rotation, or we come
in, find a wick just like we have sort
of here. All right, reclaim and come up
here. It might have to go deeper like it
did here. But we will see. At these top
ranges, I don't want to be bullish. All
right. So, we want to be bullish if we
do a fake out and a reclaim up to here.
And we want to be taking profit off the
table up here. And then if we get a
runner, great. Alternatively, if we
break down, stay heavy. I want to get
short side here for that snap rotation
down. Hold a runner just in case it lets
go. That's the plan today, folks. And in
here, if you are a rotational trader, if
you love this stuff, which I hate, you
can potentially trade here, right? Edge
to edge, edge to edge. But we can see
we've set a lower high here on the
hourlys. What we haven't done yet is
confirm it with a lower low. All right.
So, if we think about what we've done
ever since this pivot,
I'm not going to go too far back, but
we're going to higher low, higher, low,
higher, low, higher, low, internal
range, internal range, higher low,
higher low, higher low, lower high. All
right, this is potentially rolling over
the backside. Thank you. But it's a tiny
bit too early yet to say, but
potentially this lower high here can set
in for that roll over. So, that's what
I'm looking at. All right, that's what
I'm looking at. You can see overnight if
we look above Asia went sideways uh
London liquidated Asia rejected top of
Asia and then we've moved lower. So
not actually that nice when we see that
because we might want to run back up the
stops but we will see. Let's move
up. I've got to get through these pretty
quickly now. Um we have slight
divergence here to the ES right which
has relative strength. Um, so if you
didn't see some of the news coming out
last night was that we are going to be
allowed to ship uh chips to Nvidia chips
to uh China at a 25%
tariff price. Um, so that got the market
moving yesterday and then this morning
they announced I think there was some
tariff to Mexico an extra 5%. There is
actually a lower high here. I could
convince myself that wasn't the case.
Let me have a look at spy.
All right, SPY is still the gamma
levels. All right, we're going to make
this really easy. 88 85 82 80. Those are
your gamma levels. So here's your 85. We
lost it. All right, so once we lost
failed 88,
lost 85, traded down to 82, traded back
towards 85. There's your range. 85 to
82. If you get weakness under 82, we're
going to come to 80. That's the last
line in the sand. If they lose 80, well,
good night. as we would say in England,
good night, sweetheart. And we're coming
way, way, way down. Right. So, a similar
kind of setup in spy. Um, but slightly
more strength we've had there. Let's
just have a quick look at the mag then
the VIX,
gapping up on the VIX.
Nice drive out. So, uh, that thing got
buried for too long. We're just coming
to the top side of the range, though, as
you can see. Here's your range. Want to
be aware of this. Caught a bid down
here. Failed to break down. Reclaimed
top side of the range. I want to be
careful if they get stuck here. So, this
would be red, obviously.
Okay, moving into the mag. Let's have a
look. Looks a bit backsidy for Apple,
but again, into an area of interest into
here. Failed to hold back to this level
where we've traded at for quite a long
time. If we zoom out, right, this is the
old base highs. Highs, right? If it
can't hold this, we're going to go back
into this range and the dance would be
back down to here. If we hold this, it's
got a chance of making another base to
go again. So, we will see in time. But,
uh,
not looking too good. But, we're opening
up flat on it. It's the most important
thing. Opening up flat. So, no edge on
Apple. Uh, that looks like a gap down.
Yes. No, actually opening up flat on
Amazon as well. Google, that also looks
flat. Slight gap down. Meta, that is an
ugly looking chart right now.
Microsoft slight gap down. [sighs]
That's actually looking a bit more
bullish if it can break out. So that's
the first one I'd look at. It can set
some price alerts. I'd say up here
really 95 96.
Nvidia. All right. That caught a bid
yesterday in after hours like we talked
about off that news off the chip news.
There's the bid. It's already closed the
gap.
So, they didn't like it that much. They
liked it enough for a push and then that
was it. Tesla,
that's not looking too good, is it? All
right. A little bit like Apple leaving a
high, rolling over back into its old
base. Have to see how Tesla acts. Does
it find a bid here or is it going to
come into here and go sideways for a bit
and then offer one of these trades?
That's it folks. Um, remember market is
probably waiting for FOMC. And we also
have uh after close tomorrow this guy
Oracle.
So got one eye on this. It's trying to
find a bid. Remember Oracle last
earnings were blowout earnings
which got us all the way up here.
Right. We're starting to come back to
reality more recently
[clears throat] of this base after this
April low. But uh if we sell this and
set a lower high, you know what's going
to happen. That's a daily shift at that
point. It's already shifted to be
honest. It just if they can't reclaim
that on earnings, it's night night. And
uh the other one to look out for this
week, I think it's Thursday
is Broadcom, AVGO, this thing on a tear
again,
right? Alltime highs. You can see just
since these pivots, just massive,
massive runs. I mean, that is insane.
Absolute insanity. Um, but yeah,
earnings coming. I think it's Thursday.
Look at that. 190% gain this year. Wild.
So, that's us. That's what we're looking
for. Gets you set
in range till we prove otherwise,
basically. And, uh, we'll wait to see if
the edges become fadable or if we get a
trend.
Can have a quick look.
this in a bit.
Any outliers?
612. There's lots of buying gone on
around here. 618 620.
Okay.
about two minutes away from the open.
We're just trading around that big core
level that we talked about that previous
week point of control, previous day
value low, previous day low. So don't
really want to short the low of this
range because we bid off this quite a
few times. So ideally this morning
offers a pop which is shortable or
drifts underneath and then collapses. Um
if we go underneath obviously and
reclaim um we're long for the trade back
upside.
Sipping my coffee here. I won't get
through the good mornings folks. Going
to run out of time here. There's only
about 90 seconds. But thank you for
joining. Hope you're all doing okay.
Sorry I missed you all yesterday. Um
hopefully you had some good days.
Very clean action yesterday. I'd say
that um failed break of Friday's level
and uh that previous balance and we had
a lot of buyers trapped up there on uh
on the footprint or bookmap or however
you want to use it. It was very clear
there was lots of buying activity that
got themselves caught.
Right. Starting to wake up a little bit
here as we get into the open. About just
over 30 seconds, folks. Let's see what
we get.
Starting to find a bid off that previous
week of control.
[snorts]
Mic is low. Yeah, you guys can turn it
up your side because I'm not shouting
because it's 6:30 a.m. and I don't need
to boost it anymore over here.
Oh, really, Adam? Yeah, that doesn't
surprise me. All right, here's the open,
folks.
Most of the mag gapping down other than
Apple.
Most of the man gapping down other than
Apple. It wouldn't take a lot for it to
uh go red to green. And most of them
between a quarter and meta is the
weakest one right now. 42% down. All
right, here's the test into previous day
point of control up here.
And there were buyers caught there
straight away.
Straight away buyers caught at previous
day point of control.
Those buyers got caught up at 37s.
Let's just see folks that shove trap
buyers up there. Can see it on the
delta. They got caught uh buying the
market at 37 and above.
Pre-market, we haven't been able to
break down under these se 600. So, it's
having an attempt now. Let's see if
there's some follow through or not.
Doesn't feel like it really knows what
it wants to do. Here comes the breakdown
of the 600s.
Nice. Here we go. So, little bit of a
cover here.
Oh, that's a shame.
Why is it not filled all of me on my
accounts anyway? Here we go. Break down.
So, letting go of 600. I'm short here
for that breakdown of 600 at that
previously point of control.
covering some here into previous day
low. Now we need to wait to see if we
get acceptance below this because we can
get a trap here folks. So just being
very very cautious here. Still very
early in the day. But that first move we
trapped delta at the highs like I talked
about. First time we're getting a
breakdown of 600s. Don't want to short
these lows cuz everyone else is trying
to short these lows and getting caught
right now. All right. Can tell you sell
side is currently stuck under 73s. They
keep trying to force their way in at
these lows. So a retest of 600. How we
at there would be key. If they reclaim
it be a failed breakdown. We'll go
straight back upside.
>> [snorts]
>> So, just one little trade there. And
it's really unfortunate. I only got
filled on one, two, three of my
accounts. What?
That's the problem with limit orders
sometimes.
So, this was the target. How we act here
becomes important. Yesterday's
[clears throat] low.
Are we going to see follow through?
[snorts]
Lots of volume being built out between
uh 88 and 70 this morning as in since
the open. That's where we've traded the
most. So those are kind of your edges of
range which previous week point of
control down to previous day low
just above.
Want to see if they retest higher and
resell it again. I don't want to get
short down here.
I've already had that snapshot. That is
such a shame they didn't fill them all.
VIX trying to do that breakout over
1720. It's trying to do it. Is having an
attempt.
Q's nice breakdown underneath previous
day low.
SPY not there yet. All right. SPY still
holding well in front of 82s. Remember
82s is the level. If it fails 82s, we go
80 or we possibly go 80, I should say.
You just want to be careful because
point of control the last five minutes
is down at 74 and we've caught sellers
under there. So that's what I was saying
earlier. I don't want to get short down
here. We need to break under it, retest,
stay heavy if I'm going to add uh
anything with conviction. Otherwise,
it's just a little snap trade for that
rotation. We might well go sideways
until we get FOMC. The other thing I
want you guys to be aware of is I'm
pretty sure it's today. There's a bond
auction just after 1. Let me check
because that is going to matter right
now with what uh
has been going on with the yields.
Where is it? I'm sure it's today.
Yeah, 10 year 1:00. You want to be aware
of that today, folks. You might get a
really whippy move around that time. So,
I won't be here for it. Just so you guys
are aware.
All right. So, here's the retest of
those 600s.
They need to sell this really if they're
going to stay heavy and they need to get
a close underneath all these levels. If
they can't sell 600s and get close
underneath, they're going to get
themselves caught. So, back to this old
point of control again into these sort
of 72s. They're not not able to get
heavy underneath this right now. They've
tried. There's definitely some
absorption going on going on under 72s
right now.
And we're just trading in a very tight
range. Sort of 90 to 70 is your value
area currently on this day. Apple's
holding up pretty well. Rest of the
market's gone into a bit of a sell. Some
buyers just attempted here. Let's have a
look.
They need to get back above 600. The
buyers, I would say, to take any control
of this morning session if they're going
to look for a rotation to that New York
open. So far, I'd say sellers are in
control, but we've tightened up in
range.
Tightened up in range. VIX also failing
that break. So, came into that top side
of supply, looked above, and failed. Be
aware of that. Be aware of that.
There's the 600.
So, their next target will be New York
open if they're going to hold this
range. So, if this is a look below and
fail, remember we talked about this
pre-market. We don't want to get short
down here. And the short is on a pop and
fail.
Pop and fail 600 break rotation. You
don't want to get short here because if
they want to hold this for a failed
break and come back up, they will.
That's what they've done every time so
far. Doesn't mean they do it today, but
currently we're just in
the edge of a range until we prove
otherwise. Let's get this anchor on.
and they can see your value for the
session so far.
Bears have got a shot here. It's just
whether they want to do it, if they've
got any juice.
Whether they want to do it or they've
got any juice. ES back to its VWAP and
previous day close.
Spider's the same.
Q's got a long way to go to get back up
there. Vick's still failing to break out
here. So, trading back inside. I'd just
be very careful in this range. Can go
both ways very, very quickly.
[snorts]
I think we've got news today. Uh, I know
they said a lot of the data they've
decided is not going to come out, which
to me just says the data is terrible,
which is what I've been saying the whole
time. At 10:00, we've got a delayed
report of job of jolts. I think I think
it keeps saying, "Yeah, we're getting
this, but we're not getting this, and
we're getting this one, and we're not
getting this." yesterday like you're not
going to get November, but you can have
October or something like that.
All right, ES back to VWAP.
Tesla's caught a bid. Apple's caught a
bid. Rest of the market lagging behind.
Bonds seeing a bit of relief today
so far anyway after that breakout on the
10-year that we've been talking about
here for months.
Okay, back to that New York open. So,
down here, bears got trapped yet again.
All right, we went over this pre-market
like why I don't want to get short in
the hole. There's a snap short down to
there, but I'm not sizing in unless we
break down and stay heavy. We haven't
broken down, stay heavy, and you're
starting to see the squeeze back upside
now. So, probably going to come up here
to test sort of 640 650, which is
previous day's point of control, and
your uh 24hour VWAP. If they get through
there, then all we're looking at is a
failed look below yesterday's balance
low. There's yesterday's balance high.
So here will be important if they
squeeze through here back up to the top
side of that. If they fail here, they
have a reattempt to this previous day
value area low. If we build out enough
liquidity there and break down under, we
can use that to move lower back into
here. But the moment flat on this and
just waiting.
Let them mess around with it before FC.
I do not want to get caught at the low
side of a balance range.
[snorts]
>> [cough]
>> I'm all right. Thanks, John. Thanks for
asking. Yeah, as some of you know, I've
got um a lot going on outside of trading
right now. So, I'm just trying to keep a
a steady head, let's say. Not always
easy when you've got uh
family stuff going on outside of
trading. The last thing I want to do is
sit here when I'm feeling emotional or
I'm being delivered uh tough news and
stuff like that. So, that's why I wasn't
here yesterday. Had to deal with some
stuff. I won't go into it. Don't really
want to uh share all that stuff, but
yes, it's uh it's why I wasn't here
yesterday. I had some stuff I had to
deal with. All right, there's the drive
into the VWAP and the previous day point
of control, the 50s like we talked
about.
And how we act is going to be important.
If we start breaking above here, they
might look for that rotation up to 700s.
I think they might struggle to get above
700s today unless they really turn it
on. So that would be the probably the
top side for uh bulls if you're bullish
will be up here. But I'd be if you took
that rotation, that failed breakdown,
I'd be taking some profit here and
holding some for another 50 points in
case you go, but not expecting it
because we're just in range. I wouldn't
expect anything. [snorts]
Delta going positive as well.
So on a 5m minute strong delta flip at
those lows. Positive delta coming into
the market which means we're seeing more
aggressive buying.
[cough and clears throat]
TP on long. Your TP on long should be
one here. Or maybe that's what you're
saying. And then I'd hold runners for
this 700 mate. So if if you get if you
took the long if you took the fail
breakdown under here or the reclaim of
this or New York reclaiming New York TP1
is here, TP2 is up here, right? This
might well just rotate straight back
down. We don't know what they're going
to do with it. It's a choppy market.
Remember, we're inside. This is week
four in this balance. I know we've moved
above and below it, but we've spent four
weeks in this balance um since when we
were here since the beginning of
November.
Whoa. Hello. Someone got stuck.
Someone got stuck.
They didn't like that VWAP then. What
the [\h__\h] was that?
[laughter]
Like I said, it might have to come back
back down. I didn't think it would do it
in one candle that way. I'll be honest.
A big seller just tried to come in
there. Let's have a look.
Was that something shaking the market or
is someone stuck in this at the moment?
This is the problem when we're at the
edge of balance.
Oh, it's Hasset talking. Is it?
What's he said that spooked the market?
I was right to question those saying we
need to cut. Well, it won't like that.
It won't like that, will it?
asset saying I was right to question
those saying we need to cut. Market's
looking for a cut. So if he's saying
he's questioning it, remember he's
[snorts]
he's supposed to be uh extremely dovish.
People won't like that. Clearly spooked
them.
I'm sure we would have left imbalance
there. Yeah, we've left an imbalance
between uh 30 and 40 right now. Back to
that New York open. Apple still holding
up well. Tesla still holding up well.
Oracle flat. Nvidia half a percent down
on the day. Uh Microsoft a third of a
percent down. Metas of the weak one
1.63% down. Google 0.14% down. Amazon
trying to go red to green. Messy messy
sloppy sloppy market as we expected.
You think it's the opposite? Really?
I was right to question those saying oh
saying no need to cut. You're right. It
is the opposite. Well, why have we
flushed on that though?
We all know we're going to cut, so that
doesn't make sense. Maybe everyone read
it how I read it.
Okay, reholding New York open.
There's your New York view up.
Target for bulls was here. They took
some profit. Next target for them is up
here at 700. We're at the edge of a
balance right now. I'm not really
interested. This is, as we've talked
about for weeks and weeks and months and
months when we're in range rotation,
Alex doesn't really become interested
unless we trade an edge. Algo is dumb.
That means I'm dumb as well, cuz I got
it wrong. I read it wrong.
I did think it was weird. I was like,
isn't he supposed to be doubbish? Isn't
he Trump's right-hand man who's going to
start doing uh QE for him? Vicks back to
17. Big overunder here. Worth watching.
[snorts]
Big over under here for VIX
follow through here. O, back down to
these 600s.
They're trying to aggressively sell
this. They are definitely trying to
aggressively sell this into this little
pocket.
still have that imbalance up at 30 from
that flush. So 30 to 40 or 30 to Yeah,
30 to 40 is an imbalance. We're trading.
We're trading right at the New York open
right now. No, like nothing's changed.
Some buyers caught above 45.
They're not getting a close underneath
600 right now. They're not letting them
have it.
So that's your sort of small dance that
40 point dance at the moment.
Yeah, thanks Gigi. Thank thank goodness
you made me uh read it again because I
was thinking that's really weird. How's
he changed his tone? You're not going to
be put in his uh
head of Fed
if you do that. So yeah, you you were
right. Okay, now they come do they come
up to these uh imbalances up here? This
market doesn't know what it wants to do
obviously.
Of course it doesn't. It's the day
before FMC. It's not going to know what
it wants.
I would say low hanging fruit has been
taken for the day downside underneath
that previous day low. That is one thing
to be aware of. I've got a feeling we
might want to edge lower today, but I
wouldn't be banking on it. I wouldn't be
like confirming that. Nothing in the
chart is telling me that right now. I
just wondered, did they wash them out
today? Use everyone's stops to go lower
to bid it back up tomorrow
or are we just going to go sideways? All
right, Vick's trying to find a bid here
at 17 like we talked about.
[snorts]
These imbalances are still up here. 30
to 40. We left in in this sort of pocket
here.
We left an imbalance. Buyers are trapped
right now over 44. Over 44. So they all
came in. All of this is buy side. So
there's been a passive seller up here
this morning and we're now starting to
fill this imbalance. Well, we're trying
to. It needs to get through here. So
there's the imbalance. 30 to 40 is the
imbalance into that previous day point
of control. Sellers need to hold that.
That's the edge of their range on the
current day. Just on the current day,
not previous on the current day.
Sellers will need to stay heavy there.
If they can't stay heavy there, then we
probably let those buyers out who are
stuck at 640 and we probably do that
rotation to 700. So sellers need to
protect this area right now. That's
their job at the moment is to protect
this area. Buyers want to reclaim it and
go for 700s. That's your battle. When I
look at the higher time frame right now,
the reason I'm become less interested
on the high time frame like we talked
about. We've set a lower high.
All right, think about this. If you're a
seller, we've set a lower high here.
What do sellers need for confirmation?
Break down under here. What have they
not done this morning? They have not
done it. All right, they've had a fail
break and then move back inside. This is
where sellers get caught. So, this is
why I don't want to sell the lows today
because if we're not going to do this
move and if we're going to do the one we
talked about pre-market, which would be
a look below and a fail, then this up
here becomes possible. This becomes our
range. This becomes the rotation.
So, selling down here, psychopath move,
you need to wait for that.
Or you sell the top of the range looking
for the rotation.
Right now, no man's land. If we think
about
fib from this to this, we've just poked
into 50%. We're just we're just nowhere.
We got nothing. I I gut says we're going
to trade lower today, but I don't trade
off my gut.
Rejecting [clears throat] after that
imbalance. Then 30 to 40 was the level.
The sellers did a good job there. They
just protected that imbalance. That's a
decent job by then. We're trading right
back to the previous week point of
control. This is where the most traded
level was in the previous week. All
right. So, still just chop chop chop
chop in here.
Shorts will want moves under 600 for a
wash of low of day. Bears will want to
reclaim 640 for a drive to to 700.
That's where we're at right now.
Rotation, rotation, rotation. There was
some big selling came in there at 613
though, I tell you that. Big selling
came in at 613.
They're trying to find acceptance under
600s. They're not finding it yet. Big
selling. It's come in there at 600 again
and got themselves caught. But 613
kind of the level where they just sold
aggressively on that last pop. So if
they get caught there, bears, they're
going to be in trouble.
They get caught there bears, they're
Tesla finding a bit of a bid right now.
That might help the market. We will see.
It looks so messy.
What's the range right now? Only 93
points. How long we got?
New 4 hour coming in 10 minutes. So we
can see what's what after that. Maybe
stuck between New York view up and
24-hour view up as well. Never a good
sign.
This is their level, that 613. That's
where you've got sellside um delta
stuck. They if shorts can't get under
613, they might get caught. They need to
get back underneath that 613. It's
standing out like a sore thumb.
Can't get under it. They keep trying.
They've tried a few times here.
They're in trouble. They're in trouble.
If we start going above this, there's
going to be a squeeze. They're in
trouble down there. They've tried
numerous times. They are stuck under 613
right now. And Tesla continuing to find
a bid. Oh, it's a messy, messy market.
It's so unfortunate. This
be nice if this market would move out of
this range tomorrow. Please, FOMC, get
us out of this range. Please, please,
please, please, please, FOMC, get us out
of this range. All right, here's what we
talked about. Those guys are stuck.
They're possibly going to open up a
squeeze here back to the 630s to 640s,
which is where we had that imbalance
through that. And it's uh well, it's big
big trouble for uh for sells.
We have to see if they can get back
through that 30 to 40.
ES pushing as well, helping drift this
or lift this market higher. Q's not
pushing yet.
VIX trading downside that that didn't
reclaim 17. So that looks terrible for
the market to move lower. So you've got
complete divergence. ES trying to break
out of high day. ENQ nowhere near it. ES
above previous day close. NQ nowhere
near it. Divergence across the market.
Tesla found a bid. Apple found a bid.
Rest of the market's red. VIX trading
downside. Oh god, this is like as many
red flags as possible on a session right
now.
Lots of red flags I would say. And the
market's not in alignment. ES is trying
to squeeze.
And that break of ES will be the 83s and
that can get up to 86s potentially,
whereas NQ doesn't look very pretty.
We're stuck at current point of control.
Stuck between the VWOPS. Stuck at point
control. Stuck between the VWOPS. Stuck
at point of control.
What was that level? 613s. That was the
level. 613s is where sellside delta is
stuck. That's where aggressive sellers
cannot get a close under. They need to
move under 613s and really underneath
600 to take control of the market, the
sellers. Otherwise, they can get
themselves caught like we've talked
about.
Again, we're trading back to the 613s
and they see this level here. They
cannot get under it. They've they've
sold this very aggressively this morning
and they're not getting that move. And
if they don't get that move, they will
get themselves caught on a break above
here for a squeeze. So, that's their
level. 613 to 610. That's their level
that they need to get under the bears.
Yes. Still going.
Sloppy market.
Sloppy sloppy market right now.
Going to test that level again.
Here we go. Testing the 13s again. Do
they get a close underneath and start to
rotate? If they can close heavy here and
get under 600, they've got a shot of low
day.
It's a big if, but that that is what the
if is.
Here we go. So, there's underneath. Do
they see continuation? They cannot let
this bid back above 613 now because
they're trying to take control.
This is your moment, bears. You've got
to get under 600. You've failed 613.
You've got to get under 600, bears. If
you can't do that, you're going to get
yourself caught again. So, here's the
retest of 13 where they just came in
heavy.
They got to get under previous week
point control.
Back to the 13s again. Oh god, they
might get themselves caught.
[laughter]
They're doing the dance. It's standing
out like a sore thumb here at 13s.
Honestly, it's like such big delta
compared to the rest of the market.
ES still looks strong up to its five
day. Cleared out those stops and it's
holding a bid. [clears throat] Massive
divergence.
Here goes ES trying for another squeeze
on ES.
VIX trading down into a possible support
system here.
You see our previous week point control
absorb absorb absorb this level here key
this is your this is your key level
where we're trading at right now
got a chance here they have got a chance
here to do it especially if goes into
failure for a look above and fail
Can't get under it though.
Yes, possible RBS here as well. If it
soaks off this, I'll be watching ES
versus uh 860. If they soak off that,
they can go for GloEx and that will lift
this market higher. There you go. Just
soaked off it. There you go.
[laughter]
>> [snorts]
>> So quick
getting crushed here.
Well, I don't know. I feel like I've
come back to the market and we're not
moving. Is this all we're going to get
for the day?
Is this literally all we're going to get
for the day? What's that like? 20
points. 20 point range for the last I
don't know 20 30 minutes. Maybe that's
all we get for the day. Feels like it.
Right. While while we dance around, I'm
going to get a little refill on my
coffee.
Has
it made its mind up? Yeah. No, no
change.
Back to New York open. So, literally
nothing's changed since the opening
print. We've got a big buyer. 812
lot at 90s right now. Let's see if we
come down to him and if he pulls. Just
interested if he's a magnet that pulls
here because he feels like he might be
with that kind of size.
same level again.
New York view up. [sighs]
Definitely a passive seller now. Present
at 20s and above. They haven't been able
to close above and definitely passive
buyer at 600. So you got a 20 point
range here and that's it. That's all
you've got right now.
Bit of a joke really, isn't it? We all
know this is likely before FOMC. We said
it's very likely we can go sideways
here.
What you saying? GG December without
news. Well, it's not actually without
news today. There's plenty of news
today.
We had news pre-market. Uh we've got uh
jobs report coming, delayed data. We had
uh Mexican tariffs. We had chips being
allowed to China. So, I wouldn't say
it's a no news day. And we've got a big
bond auction at 1:00.
Uh probably just a liquidity provider
then, Adam. Let's have a look.
He'll be real, but he's just a liquidity
provider. It's just whether they
actually fill him or not.
Yeah, still holding that uh 860 we
talked about.
Microsoft's just gone green. Amazon's
just gone green. Tesla's driving this
market at the moment. That's the big
gain. Now, the rest of the market's not
actually really doing very much. As per
usual, we've got divergence between the
MAG 7. It's been like that for as long
as I can remember now. I cannot remember
a day where they all sell or all buy for
so long on the cues. I can't remember
it. Right. It we have to go back months
now which is not a good look.
So back into this top side into previous
day point of control now.
What the [\h__\h] was that?
>> [laughter]
>> What the [\h__\h] was that?
How much? That was literally in a
nanocond.
In less than a second we did that drop
and scoop.
Oh, that is hilarious. Yeah, Jolts.
Exactly. Who was it that said no news?
And I was like, yeah, we have got news.
[snorts] It's delayed Jolts, though.
It's not this month, just so you're all
aware. It's delayed. It's like two
months old
from September. Job openings.
I mean, they printed that wrong.
[snorts]
I guarantee you they've cooked that
books. Oh, yeah. Job openings 7.67
million versus 7.117. That's funny.
Completely uh beat. Yes, I guarantee you
they've cooked those books. They love
doing it. No way do we have more job
openings right now. Absolute horseshit.
Yeah, exactly. It's nonsense. Yeah, we
we you can't have any of the data that
shows it's bad, but we will cook the
books and find a way of showing you some
data which is good.
Exactly, Ronald. Exactly. I agree with
you. I agree with you, my friend. It's
absolute bollocks and they know it.
Still just in a range. Nothing happening
here. Buyers just got caught again over
34s,
but we have no close underneath the 600.
So, we're in like 30 point range.
What are they going to do with this
market?
Are they just going to shove it higher
now? Looks like it.
Q's trying to play catch up. Still not
closed their gap on Q's. Remember,
that's what ES has done. It's closed its
gap and it's well over its gap as well.
on this market looks like it wants to go
buy side right now and just go up up up
on uh probably a fake jobs report. So
PDC is probably the target here. Here
you go. There's your PDC. So finally
they've closed the gap. Previous day
value area high above. Like I said if
bulls get up to 700 that's probably
where you see a little bit of take
profit up uh here. That's yesterday's
range top of yesterday's range.
market is trying to find a bid here as
in like on when I say the market the mag
has started to find a bid here across
the across the names. Tesla's doing the
work though. Tesla's the one doing the
work right now.
So back into the opening range. Do they
hold a bid here at this opening range?
Yes is the answer so far. That's your
opening range. This white line. They've
found a bid there so far. That's your
overunder for sentiment at the moment.
700 is completion of rotation. It's
actually 94s but we call it 700.
completion of rotation.
So, here's your opening range. Do they
hold a bid here or do we go back into
the opening range and go right back down
the other side of it? ES now taking out
GlobeEx.
What a mess this market is right now.
Doing that orb dance at the moment.
still holding there or thereabouts, but
if they can't hold it too much longer,
you might see a bit of a flush here.
We've seen like top of the range has
been rotated numerous times today.
Remember,
back down they go into it into the VWAP.
And if they lose this, we can go right
back to the other side of the range all
the way down. So, this is current value
area high on the day. If they lose this,
we probably trade back down to uh 620s
again.
>> [clears throat]
>> What mess?
So, I'd say uh yeah, 620 is possible
now. And if they lose 620s, low they
gone from one side to the other. So,
here comes the dance. Can they reclaim
orb or do they fail 620? like 20
to 44 will be the rotation and if they
lose 20s then I'd be watching uh 600s
and if we lose 600's low day
that's what you're looking at at the
moment
Wait.
They've got a chance to come in here
bears again to try and force a rotation.
They're not doing a very good job again.
It's the story of their life. ES holding
up really well. So ES just soaked that
860 again that we talked about. Uh
notice the top side on SPY is 85. We
talked about it pre-market. 85 to 82 is
the rotation on SPY. Low of day is 8259.
High of day 8493. Those are your gamma
levels. Here comes the rotation back
down to 20. And if they lose 20, then we
probably come right the way back down
here cuz it' be a failed look above. So,
we'll have to see.
They're trying to force that move under
20 right now. If they get under 20, then
the move is to 600. But so far today,
bears haven't been able to get rotation
under these levels.
I still got croak in my throat.
We just go sideways. Vix is finding a
bid here on the old demand level.
So, do they sell the next pop-up or is
this just going to go straight back?
[sighs] So, you'd be watching
44s to 55s. The bears will want to sell
and bulls obviously want to reclaim that
for a move back to high day.
Unconvinced right now of anything.
50% of opening range. Yeah. Well, a
trade back into it. Yeah, a lot of
people like that trade, but it's not a
trade I've ever taken. I don't
understand why
me people love that trade so much
because it's not based on even volume
traders take it. I'm like, but it's not
even based on structural volume. It's
just a percent of a range. There we go.
If it works, it works. Okay.
So that 860 is key on SPY.
This is the potential lower high if they
want to do the rotation back down. The
bears need a close under here. Now we've
come to that 620 we talked about. If
they get under 620 now, they've got a
chance to move to 600 and low lower low
day under that. But it's uh
they've got to get under 620 first. So
this is potential for a lower high. It
can also be trapped here.
This is where bears got stuck last time
where we are right now. This is where
they keep kind of trying to keep trying
to come in and sell and not get in their
way. So so far they're being soaked.
They can't get that close under 20 that
they need. So far,
there's the 20s again. They're trying
they're desperately trying here to get
underneath this volume point of control
and the New York open. If we lose that
600s and then lower day is possible like
we talked about
still soaking there. Can they get a
close underneath it?
Oh, it's so boring, man. We're in like
20 point rotations again.
the grab it again there. No close under
the 20s. Back to the top side we go
again to test that over. Rinse, repeat,
rinse, repeat, rinse, repeat. So you can
see ES doing the same thing. Holding the
60s. did get just slightly under 60s but
holding it for now. Market will need to
make a decision. We cannot just keep
staying here forever.
But that decision doesn't need to come
today. So yeah, we don't need to stay
here forever.
Back to where these bears tried again.
So bears came in aggressive from 30 to
17 and did not get their way. They got
soaked from 30 to 17. From 30 to 17
they've been soaked. So there's a
passive buyer now. soaking from 30 to
17. Top side of it, where do we have
balls trapped? Well, we have some
trapped into 50. Most of them are
trapped up at 67 and above.
Mad doesn't look very good. You take
Tesla out the equation and it doesn't
look very good. Right now,
no, with rotation, I do not mean
consolidation. I mean to take to test
one side to the other. Yes,
consolidation is that range, but the
rotation is the move from one side to
the other, from one side to the other.
Big selling coming in here. Is there
still a bid down here? Who's soaking?
This is what I'm interested now. We're
seeing very aggressive market selling
here and we're not moving lower. It just
came flying in there and we're not
moving lower. So, we've got a passive
buyer on the tape again. This level here
at 30 has become key. They've trapped
all the shorts under there for the last
10 minutes. So 30's become key without a
doubt because they just tried to
aggressively sell it here. There was
over a 100 lot came flying in and we
didn't move lower. So we've got a
passive buyer right now trying to absorb
everything in here. He is sat right
here. He's just saying I'm going to eat
anything you give me. If he becomes a
seller, we get a rotation down. Until
then, they're trying to force back up to
here.
is definitely 30 is your level. 30 to 20
this 10 points they keep trying to
aggressively sell and we're not moving
lower that if that changes you'll see
bigger moves but until that point buyers
have control of the market for me or at
least a buyer is having control of the
market. Yeah, exactly. Absolute garbage
range. I I agree with you. Uh full
forward and divergence, right? Garbage
range and divergence. Like you look at
um ES versus Q's like we've closed the
gap and failed. ES ES man is way up
here, right? So massive divergence in
the market. So breth probably I'll have
a look but I'm guessing energy or banks
are doing something. [snorts]
Let's have a look at the sectors. Yes.
So again this is why so banks are up. So
finance up, healthcare up, real estate
up, energy up,
households up, and semis down. So
massive divergence. So you've got the
broader market looking good.
[\h__\h] is that one about?
All right, they're trying to sell this
again here aggressively,
Alex. After a passing 80% discount, Evo,
how much PA fee? Thank you. I don't know
what account you're talking about or I
have no idea. Need a bit more detail
than that, my friend. If you're talking
about Apex, uh, it's $6 right now,
but it's not 80% off. I think it's 60%
off. That might have even finished
today. I have to check.
Oh, it's like banging ahead on a brick
wall with this market. It's exhausting.
I just want the year to be over. This is
absolute shite. I've never seen anything
like it the last few months.
I just smell a rat in this market. This
is why I smell a rat. Bonds, big
problem. JPY carry trade, big problem.
Data, big problem. They're lying to you.
The data is terrible. More people miss
mortgage rate payments again. Three
months in a row. More people close their
businesses again. The most since 2020
and since then since 2008. More business
closures since then. people not being
able to pay their uh finance on their
cars up three months in a row. People
not paying their student loans up three
months in a row. Sales on Black Friday,
regardless of what Trump said, were
actually down when you consider
inflation. Right? Prices were 7% more
expensive, 11% less sales. 95% of sales
were done on credit. The market is
[\h__\h] All right? Everything going on
right now is [\h__\h] and it's in big,
big trouble. The question is how much
higher do they want to sell it to trap
retail before they sell it.
So yeah, I don't trust this market one
bit. And the fact that they've hidden
numbers, if I was an American, I'd be
asking why I pay tax for them to hide
important data.
That's the thing. How are they legally
allowed to do that? It's uh How can you
pick and ch? Oh, we'll give you October,
but you're not going to have that. Well,
we'll give you September. You can't have
October or November. No, no, no, no, no.
You don't. You can't have the ones that
are bad.
It's just insane that they're allowed to
do it. Like, it's lit. It's It's
complete fraud right in front of you.
Absolute fraud.
[snorts]
Still dancing, same range. Nothing's
changed, folks.
Previous day point of control acting as
resistance right now.
ES come has come back down into VWAP and
is trying to find a bid there. VIX has
found a bid in those uh sort of 1680s.
We're just flat.
And if they don't get their way, if
bulls don't force the rotation soon,
you're going to have a huge liquidity
build out. And uh well it's opening
itself up to problems.
Still must be a buyer on this book. He's
absorbed everyone who's tried to sell.
So he's still not letting them out. So
sell sellers are stuck. Like I said 30
to 18 that 30 is your level. That's your
level where he's just soaking soaking
soaking soaking the tape. Once that goes
and they get follow through, if he's not
there anymore, you got to wonder who's
going to absorb that tape any longer
because he's been there for the last
20 minutes gobbling it up.
He's still trying to gobble it up for
higher. They're just not seeing any
follow through though.
I think once 30 goes, he's in trouble.
But if he can force that to 50 and
above, he can get a squeeze. ES trying
to go again.
Tesla holding this whole market up. This
is a all from Tesla right now. Rest of
the market's red. It's just Tesla
holding this market up. It's impressive.
Right back down to test this guy at 30s.
Is he still on the book or does he get
out the way?
This is where he's been just gobbling
from here to 18.
And if he gets out the way,
I'd be very concerned that this doesn't
snap all the way down cuz I feel like
it's a one guy just saying, "Feed me,
feed me, feed me, feed me."
There you go. And again, trying to
gobble it. If he gets out the way
though, I wouldn't be surprised to see a
snap. He's now bidding 25, 30, 25, and
20. And he keeps rebidding, rebidding,
rebidding. Number
30 is the level where he starts bidding
at.
I think once he's out the way, this
could be impro a problem if he gets out
the way.
You got buyers caught offside now.
34 to35. Huge delta caught offside
there. 34 to 35.
>> [clears throat and cough]
>> So that's probably that guy that keeps
bidding. There you go. Soaked again.
And we're already back through 34 and
35. And that's got a bit must be his
average price because we've got huge
delta there. Now
he keeps bidding around there. I'm just
looking at the book map. I'm looking at
the uh volume profile delta here. And
this stands out here. This where we're
trading right now. You can see it's all
buy side where we are right now. That's
kind of giving me sentiment for where we
are in this range. This sort of 34,
let's just call it 35.
Well, eventually there'll be a move
outside of this one way or another. We
can't stay this tight rather.
Yes. Finding a bid on VW up.
We're still trading the same level. Oh
my god. How many How long have we been
here? All day, basically.
All day.
Sorry folks. Can't do anything with with
this. We had one trade today
here. Low hanging fruit gone and now
we're stuck.
All right. My bias is actually that
they're going to do this because they
failed to get above here. But we've got
a buyer in here gobbling everything up.
So it doesn't matter what my bias is
until I see this. I don't see
acceptance. And we are just going to
trade in this range forever until
they're done with it by the looks of it
at the moment.
And if they want to come and test up
here, they can remember 700s is the
target for bulls. Um, but this doesn't
look very bullish at the moment. Yes,
like we are drifting, but this feel Oh,
don't do that. This feels like a just a
guy's in here,
right? Just eating this market. And my
concern is if he keeps getting size and
we've got a passive seller here saying
no, this happens and eventually either
this or this happens probably pretty
quickly once one side wins because this
is getting going to get very tight in
here.
So back to these 34s and 35s again. This
is where I think the buyers been
starting to move away from him now and
he keeps absorbing into 30. So if he
gets out the way, I would not be
surprised to see a bigger flush in this
market. It just depends if he gets out
the way and use the New York openers
sentiment shift really.
Yeah, the PA is is dreadful. Guys, I've
got a question for you. Lots of you,
your names, I don't know what changed on
YouTube, but your names are like your
aren't your names. It's the handles. How
do do you know if there's a way I can
get you back to your name so I know
who's talking? Is there a way I can do a
setting my side or is it just YouTube
and that's how it is now? Or is there a
setting you guys can do? Vick's still
pushing back up towards the 17 so have
to see how Vicks when he gets up here.
Gosh.
I mean, this is just awful, man.
Probably my side. Yeah, I never changed
anything. So, do do you know how to do
that? I can't see it. I've looked on the
internet. I cannot see a way of doing
it.
Back to VWAP. Everything flat. Look,
everything's tightening up. This is one
way or another, someone's going to get
hurt. Otherwise, we're either we're
squeezing out of here and ripping out
all the shorts or we're going to dump
here and rip out all the bulls.
Yeah, it's changed everywhere, has it?
Yeah, I asked AI. It didn't have the end
of the answers.
Just wondered if any of you knew.
It's annoying that they've done it,
though. I think it's a bad change.
Big bar coming in here.
Big bar coming in here. Maybe they're
going to force this breakout now.
It's really stupid that YouTube have
done that though. Like what a
what [\h__\h] idiot has sat there and
gone, "Oh, I know what we'll do. We'll
uh do it so we can't see their names
anymore and we see their hand." I don't
know who half of you are now. Whereas
like some of you have been here for a
year plus with me and I I don't know who
you are. It just seems like the most
stupid decision from YouTube.
There you go. So, Hercules, I'm Stefan.
So, I would never know that. [laughter]
I would never know that.
There you go. Steven cat. Okay, good.
I'll try and remember all these.
But you don't have to have your full
name on display. You can have like it's
it's your choice what your username is.
Do you know what I mean? It's your
choice.
You're probably right, Rosco. Yeah,
you're probably right.
[laughter]
Yeah, Tyson, I know. I know who you are.
All right, they're juggling this book
around now. They're just being silly
with it. Still nothing to do while they
act like complete Pratts this morning.
So, Vicks failed to get back above 17.
that's failing in front of it. So, you
got to watch out here. VIX sets a lower
high and rolls back over. Market will
squeeze. ES is holding its VW up. Much
more strength on ES. It's holding above
PDC. We are not doing that on the Q's.
Relative weakness in the Q's, but I mean
there's just no trade available here.
You've you've started to get a Pratt uh
start to offer on off on off on off on
off on off for the last two minutes. He
started acting like a bit of a silly
Billy. He was here last week. So doing
the same stupidness again with a 100
lot. Someone's being an complete
imbecile. There you go. Pushing,
pulling, pushing, pulling, pushing,
pulling. Probably a buyer who wants to
lift the tape.
All right. While this market does
absolute stupidity, I'm going to use a
bathroom. So, you know what that means?
Probably doesn't move.
All
right, back to the games. So, flush
down. Is there still a soaker there?
Yeah, 30 is still the level. And we've
said it's been the level the whole time.
They need to trade under 30s, otherwise
you've still got someone just soaking
the tape. If 30s lets go, there'll be a
move. But there has someone there has
been someone trying to soak it over and
over and over and over and over again.
And the delta is really 35 to yeah,
let's just call it 35 to 34. That's
where we've had big buy side delta and
sellside delta's been under 30. That's
why you need to get a close under 30 for
shorts to have an available legitimate
trade downside. But you're not seeing
it. And SPY is holding this market up.
SPY and ES are holding above PDC. They
are holding their fee up. You've got
complete divergence. VIX just failed in
front of 17 to do a lower high like we
talked about as well. This is just
trash. Like absolute trash that you're
watching this morning. There's nothing
to do here. I feel like I'm on repeat
from last week when I last traded with
you guys and I just said it's a [\h__\h]
market being controlled by options. Just
look at SPY 85 82 808 888.
It's just options dealers. Like there's
there's no momentum in this market.
There's nothing to do. Like I see money,
take money, and
get the [\h__\h] away from it, honestly.
Like, just avoid avoid it like the
plague. Try and just get to January
without doing something stupid. I'd see
is I'd say is probably your best bet
because I can't see why anyone would be
risk going into December 13th with the
carry trade and with what bonds are
doing. In fact, let me just have a look
what we seeing here this morning.
Yeah, it's uh if that turns around
the 10 year,
mate.
That's what I've been calling for.
I don't see how anyone can be risk on in
this market right now. It is a
psychopath move, but
we all know like if they're going to
build it out, it takes a while. I've
talked about it numerous times. You
can't be early.
So, we're just slap bang in the middle
of yesterday's range.
Oh, don't want to do that. How do I get
out of that?
There we go.
All right, finding value. [sighs]
So, fail breakout beneath yesterday's
value. There's the trap play back
through to a previous day's point of
control. Buyers want to get up here.
Sellers want to get back down here. Here
is a level of the most traded area. This
is fair value. You don't want to trade
at fair value because this is what
happens. You don't really want to trade
there. Market needs to move away. This
is market imbalance. You don't want to
trade in balance. Not in these ranges.
You want to trade out of balance. Out of
balance.
Oh my god. Market. [\h__\h] me. What are you
doing?
I'm going to give this a couple more
minutes and then I'm getting off. I'm
definitely not going to sit here any
longer and watch this slop.
It's just a snoozefest. You can't trade
this guys. We can't trade around these
areas. These are where we can't trade.
Must not trade around here. too
dangerous. It needs to come up here or
down here or at least fail away from
this. Don't want to get caught in all of
this. This is just slow grind. You don't
want to fade a slow grind.
What do you mean it's struggling to get
over V up? It's over V up. It's over V
up. ES is over V up.
Don't convince yourself you're seeing
something that's not there. It's over V
up. There's 24-hour VW up. There's New
York VW up. Anyone who bought the open
is in the money. Anyone who's bought
VWOP is in the money. Until it proves
otherwise, they're in the money. Don't
convince yourself of something which
literally is not there. What you've just
said is literally not happening. So,
make sure you're not convincing yourself
of a play cuz it's not whatever you just
said is not what I'm seeing. It we are
over VWAPS. Spy over VWAPS.
All I'd say is buyers are stuck above
57s.
Sellers are stuck under 30.
They're absorbing 30.
That's all that's happening right now.
There's no like there's literally
nothing else happening. We're in a tiny
tiny tiny tiny range. What's the range
on the day? Still like 90 points. Sorry,
110 points range on the day. The initial
balance now set
I don't what I don't understand what
you're talking about. Um
I really don't know. It looks like it's
resisting crossing new VWOP. You just
said it looks like it struggled to get
over VWOP. VWOP's here. The other VWOP's
here. We're over both. How's it
struggling?
It would struggle if it was doing this,
right? Or this. It's just chopping. I've
given you the levels all day. 30s is
where they keep buying.
They're stuck at 60s. You got 30 points.
That's all you've got right now to play
with. 30 points until it proves
otherwise. Right. 30 points
with a slow drift higher. It's all
you're seeing. Slow drift higher.
Well, you've got to you've got to well,
two things. Firstly, don't say something
then in chat if you don't know what
you're talking about in all honesty
because you can get other people caught.
Secondly, it's pretty clear, isn't it?
If you've got VW up on your chart, if
you're over it, if you're over it, then
you're using it as support. If you're
under it, then you're using it as
resistance. So if you're over it, then
the average participant in the market
based on volume is a buyer and they're
comfortable. When we're under it means
the average participant based in the
market based on volume, sellers would be
in control because remember VWAP doesn't
identify anything based on anything else
other than volume, right? It doesn't
know who's a buyer and seller. So if
you're going to use it sentiment all the
time, we're over New York VWAP. Then
anyone off the open who's a buyer is
comfortable. And anyone who's a seller
is not comfortable. Same with this
24-hour VW up. We're over it. We used it
as resistance. We got over it. We use it
resistance. Resistance. Resistance.
We're over it. Buyers at the moment are
in control of this market in the New
York session. In this session here
overall, we're just in balance. Right?
There's yesterday's session. We're
inside that. What do we expect inside?
If this was yesterday and we're now
doing this, what do we expect?
Crap is what we expect.
Absolute crap. Market's nice when we
leave balance. All right. If we did
this, really nice. If we do this, really
nice inside here. This is for Alex. This
is where he says, "Hey, I don't play
rotations. I'm not interested." You hear
me saying that all the time. Not
interested in playing inside balance
ranges. It's too dangerous in this
market. I can't play a balance range in
this market. It's far too dangerous. If
it was like the first day here, sure,
this is week four in this same place.
We leave balance, I'll be aggressive
with it. We've got to leave balance.
Remember 30s is the level.
Are they still there at 30? Just zooming
down. And it is still offside delta 35s.
That's the level. 35 and 30s is the
level. Sellers need to take control
beneath that. Beneath that.
Yeah, Richard. Absolutely. Which is
stupid because we all know what's
happening tomorrow.
We priced it in quart
um cut.
Jack, you keep calling for this big
short, but you were big short here
before. You've taken draw down all the
way to 55s and we're just back to the
same level. Nothing's changed, my
friend. I'm afraid until it changes.
What do I use for the heat map bookm?
Can they get under 35s? That's the key.
Back to point of control for the day.
Back to VW up for the day.
We need to start trading underneath 35s.
Any big sellers? Yeah, all the guys that
are stuck I keep telling you about at
35s to 30s and then you got to get under
18. So why I'm saying like you're just
in a rotation. There's no big move here.
So, I ignored your thing earlier like
short hair. You you you you ate a [\h__\h]
ton of draw down. I just didn't want to
even talk about it because you do the
same thing every day.
So, like we talked, buyers keep getting
stuck over 60, sellers are stuck under
30s. That's That's it. 30 point range.
Nothing's changed. Nothing has changed.
You're still holding V up. You're still
holding point of control
till they let go of that.
You're trying to fade a slow grind,
which is dangerous. Or just let volume
come in.
At least that's what I would do. I just
wait and let someone come in and take
control of the market.
say ES into PDC becomes key.
If they do a gamma rotation to 82 on
spy, it would be it would be fun. It
would drag the market, but it just
depends what their intentions are.
still between these 60s and 30s. No
change. Buyers try going to try and take
control here above 60s now. So they want
to push for high day. That will let all
the buyers out. And then again, you're
seeing VWAP hold on the spiders. Soak,
soak, soak, soak, soak. But buyers have
been stuck over 60 today. But again,
slow grind higher. No change. Like I
said, don't try and short a drift
higher.
There's absolutely no control here for
sellers. They would have to get closures
under 30s and really under 600 and
you've not seen it
back towards PDC,
back towards initial balance high again.
Tesla's the one doing the damage.
Amazon's found a bit of a bit, but Tesla
is dragging this market. It's it's a
one-stop market right now. Can give you
a readout. Tesla 1.42% up on the day.
Amazon half a percent up on the day.
Everything else is red. Nvidia half%
down. Microsoft 0.13% down. Meta 1.37%
down. Google 0.12% down. Apple 0.10%
down. As an equally weighted index 0.16%
down.
[cough]
VIX failing like I talked about. Cannot
get back above 17. It's put in a lower
high. If they start selling VIX and they
go back to PDC, this market will
squeeze.
Nothing to do. There's literally nothing
to do here. If you're clicking buttons,
I don't understand what you're looking
at. If you're saying things like, "Oh,
we're struggling at VWAP." We're not. If
you're saying things like, "Big short
here." There's nothing indicating it.
You are convincing yourself of something
which is not there. It means you don't
have an actual strategy. You are just
hoping rather than playing what's in
front of you. It's the big difference
between trading and gambling. You have
to play the cards in front of you at the
moment. Do you have pocket aces? No. I
would say you haven't even got a hand at
the moment. You're sat at the table. You
should be just having a drink at the
table sat still. I don't think even
think you've got a hand.
Do you account for time to build
positions before a big move? In my
honest opinion, bears are building a
position based on what? Based on what?
Bears are building a position based on
what? On what time frame? Why? Based on
what?
I'd love to know why you think bears are
building a position right now.
Like what is it that's telling you bears
are building a position
and and on what time frame? You think
swing swing bears are building a
position right now going into FOMC
breakout coming.
Feel like a fight with the same person
every single day here.
So, at what point are you wrong? Hi Day
break.
Hi Day break.
Get bored of saying it honestly.
Yeah, you've done one. Well, uh, Black
Widow, if you've done that, that's
that's I think that's all that's been
available. Unless the only trade the
other side, I'd say, is, you know, along
here, you'd have to risk that,
unfortunately, due to structure, and it
would be what do we talk about? TP1 in
here, TP2 up here. Unless you were long
here. So, I think the only trades are
like that fail and break down and that
grind higher. And I think since then
there's been nothing to do.
They're probably going to look for
value, aren't they? Right? Because
that's yesterday's value. Look below and
fail. They're probably going to try and
trade up to yesterday's value. And if
they can try and get GlobeEx out the
way, they will. Like if they get
acceptance over value,
then I'd say London at 713. Basically
that red block and the top side 730.
[clears throat]
>> [snorts]
>> So, you can see how key those seven
those uh 630s I kept talking about were.
I kept telling you there's someone
absorbing. Go back and rewind this when
I'm done. When we were here, I kept
telling you they keep trying to sell 630
to 600 and we're not moving lower. All
right, we had negative delta here. They
were trying to shove us down and I kept
saying there's someone absorbing and
then they moved up to 630 and they
started absorbing here and you're all
shorting into him. Well, not all of you,
but some of you keep shorting into him.
He's a bigger player than you. Right? If
he's got his exit here, where will the
short be? Right under here. That's going
to be the safest entry once he is out
the way. But there is a big boy who's
just absorbing. Like I said, he kept
flashing 100 lot, 100 lot, 100 lot, 100
lot, 100 lot, 100 lot, 100 lot up here.
I said to you, go back and rewind it.
He's probably a buyer trying to attract
the market to go higher. If you see
someone flashing and removing, flashing
and removing, flashing and removing,
they want it to come up there, which
means what? Are they likely to be a
short seller? No. They're likely to be a
buyer attracting price higher, removing
their offer so it skips up. That's what
they try and do. It's naughty, naughty,
naughty games, but that is the game that
they play.
Right, we just had a big lot come in.
500 lot just came in and sold here at
63s.
And if he gets absorbed again cuz he
just sold at the market, then again,
we're going to have short sellers stuck
higher. So, we need to start moving
under 63s now to see follow through. And
then it's the same levels, folks. It's
30s and 600s.
Nice. Full forward. Yeah, good. Good
work. I forgot that you took that off
the bottoms. Nice.
So, sellers are starting to come in here
at 60. So, they're starting to take
control. 30s is still the level. In my
opinion, 30s is the big big level. They
start closing on the 30s, we can think
about 600 and then lower a day. Those
are the big levels in my opinion. My
personal humble opinion is VWAP. So, can
we trade under point of control here?
This is where the big delta is now at
40. It's standing out and 30. So, you
can see back down to that level 30 and
40 is this huge huge level that I keep
talking about where they keep absorbing
the tape point of control. This red
line, right? This is where they keep
absorbing. If he gets out the way and we
get closures or we can trade. If he gets
out the way, we trade to 600. If they
get out of the way, we'll probably trade
back down to low of day. If they keep
absorbing here, we're going straight
back up.
Big selling coming in here.
They're trying to force it down. They
want to get back under 30. They're
desperate. ES back into PDC here. So,
this is sentiment now for the day. We're
at close price from uh from Monday for
the ES. It just failed again. SPY
couldn't get back up to the 85. So, if
they fail PDC, there's a move back down
to 82s in the SPY. just based on gamma.
Big selling now starting to come in.
30 is still the level.
35s really 35s is where the big buyer
has been. That's his average price where
he keeps absorbing. You're going to need
to see a lower high here if you're
adamant on shorting it. and uh
you've got an imbalance [clears throat]
from sort of 55 to 60. So you wouldn't
want them if but bulls reclaim that
you're in trouble. You wouldn't really
want that to happen.
You're adamant on selling this back down
again. I would maintain 30s is big big
big big level is big. [snorts]
are starting to see backside. But you
need this to set a lower high here. And
really, you need to get under this and
this to see that otherwise
this is their level which they keep
absorbing all day.
Back to the imbalance 55 to 60s.
If they get back through 65, that's
where you have that 524 lot come in. If
they get back above 65, you might be
forced to cover and you'll see a
squeeze. So, just to give you an idea of
what's going on.
Here's the 65. This is where the big
seller came in. If he doesn't resell
this, you are open to a squeeze here.
This is where he came in with size and
he's now out of the money.
And guess what? Did we get a close under
30? No,
we did not.
rotations all the way back to 700. They
haven't finished testing previous day
value area high by the looks of it. So,
they're going to come back for it.
Yes. Again, held PDC.
Held PDC.
You can buy 635. I'm not stopping you
buying 635, am I? You buy 635 all you
want, but I'm not trading inside
yesterday's value. I've made that
crystal clear.
And I'm definitely not trading the
midpoint.
Here's yesterday's value. You want to
trade this, you go ahead. You want to
trade that midpoint, go ahead. I'm not
trading it. I've made it absolutely
clear what I'm looking for today.
I will stick to my thesis. You guys
learn to trade your setups. I've given
you the levels. You can use them how you
see fit.
Who's this guy? Where's his stuff again?
664 665
trading back down towards lower days.
I I just don't understand. I don't I
don't look at this and think, "Oh, I
can't wait to trade it." So, it's just
amazing that people want to put a risk
on or or do something in this market.
Like,
I don't look at this and think, "Well,
this is a great market to trade."
I don't understand. Like why would you
want to trade
inside this?
Inside this
inside this
just should I keep going? Do you get the
point? Inside this.
You get the point? Until we move outside
of this, you're going to see [\h__\h]
action. It's tell it's already told you.
It's told you for four weeks, but some
of you just can't help but clicking by
the looks of it. Like, you have to be in
a trade. It's
the best traders out there make money
from when everything's lined up on their
side. You don't have that right now. So,
I don't know. Unless you're like trading
a little bit of range rotation for a
scalp, I don't see what you're looking
at here, which is saying, "Trade me,
trade me, trade me, trade me, trade me."
There's nothing saying it. It's quite
the opposite. This should be screaming
at you. Don't trade me. Don't trade me.
Don't trade me. Don't trade me.
Jack, why don't you be more patient when
you're front siding it? And do you think
I don't trade when I'm not with you? You
think I don't trade with my community?
Why don't you be more patient instead of
guessing and saying the big shorts
coming and then sitting in draw down?
I'm not whining, Donnie.
This is going to get really easy. Got
[\h__\h] idiots on stream again.
There's a difference between knowing
when to trade, knowing not winning a
trade, and teaching you. And uh
and you are gone. See you.
Yeah, they've already gone. They're
gone.
All right, drift higher because they
protected 30s
and they want to come for previous day
value area high. That's where they want
to come. And if they get through that,
they want to come for GlobeEx. All
right, which is up here.
Yeah, it's funny. I try and teach, but
amount of people who won't, you just
don't listen. So
God help you. God help you. Honestly,
all right. They're adding liquidity
above because they want this market to
drive into 700s.
They want to come and test previous day
value.
VIX lower day. It wants to close its gap
to PDC by the looks of it on the VIX.
And we can consider what happens after
we get some of these moves.
They're now above initial balance as
well. So always been protecting 30s.
You're starting to see some bullish
action take place above 80s. They are
starting to get stuck up here again
above 80s. So aggressive participants
keep buying. The guy that's in the money
is the guy that's soaking. These guys
who keep buying the highs who just got
stuck above 80s again, they will get
themselves in trouble unless they this
Mr. bid at 30 steps up and starts
soaking for them. Just seeing buying
delta come in offside above 30 in this
current 5m minutee bar. You still got
another two and a half minutes for this
to close. But definitely they keep
getting caught trying to aggressively
buy above 680 at the moment. The
rotation is up to 700. That's where
they're trying to get to or to 94
previous day value area high.
Yeah, Tesla pushing. Like I said, Tesla
is the one doing the damage. It is
dragging this market up with it at the
moment. We can have a look at it.
Right, just straight upside. This is
what's dragging the cues up. It probably
just wants to get to previous day high
and then it's probably game over from
there.
Have a look at how they sell it
yesterday. Yeah. Or maybe a little bit
above. So you got an old range here.
It's coming up to back test. All right.
So double bottom drive up. They probably
sell it in here unless there's some huge
gamma squeeze. But you see like 50 is a
big level as well. But you know there's
going to be probably going to be a cool
wall here.
So this is what's doing the damage. If
we look at the rest of the mag, are you
seeing that kind of participation? No,
definitely not. Apple, no. Amazon tried
has caught a bid. Google trying as well
to be fair. Coming up to uh pre-market
high. Nothing from Meta, nothing from
Microsoft, nothing from Nvidia. Just
Tesla and Amazon then really
you're trading em ES then you're trading
even worse because that's been even more
upside all day. And you do this every
day. You say one thing and then you try
and change it later. Um you just
I can't help you, man.
You do the same thing every day. I can't
I can't help you. You call for a big
short you set and then you wait for it
to squeeze you out. Then you say, "Yeah,
now now it's now it's doing." It doesn't
do it. And then afterwards when we still
squeeze up, you go, "Oh yeah, I'm in
MEES, which is still squeezing up near
day." So
I can't help. At some point, I'm just
going to delete chat because it's just
become becoming pointless.
It's not like I'm always right or
anything like that. It's not an arrogant
thing, but
there are clear patterns with people who
fight markets in that chat.
value area high is where it wants to go.
700s or 94s technically, but 700s. They
keep adding liquidity up there.
Definitely buyers keep trying up here
and they're not getting their move, but
I would expect we'll probably complete
that rotation up there. It makes sense
that it wants to get up there at the
moment.
ES has just got it fiveday just like
overhead just like holding it at the
moment. VIX's about to complete its move
to fill the gap. It's pretty much done
it.
What was the sale setup yesterday? Uh,
it's super clean. Yesterday was the some
of the easiest action I've seen in ages.
Where's yesterday? Monday.
Right. Where did we get stuck? Friday.
Where was the short we talked about
Friday? It was up there when we left
that volume shelf.
Right. Friday we left this volume shelf
up here. Buyers were stuck up there.
Right. So this is the return inside up
here. Buyers were stuck. If you look at
we got it here somewhere. Hang on.
We bring this over.
You look at all the buying in that
opening five minute bar yesterday. Where
did they get stuck?
Why is that dism?
No.
They got stuck here. Look at that buying
volume up there. That's aggressive
market buying. Did we move higher? No.
So, they bought in supply. We close.
Next candle. Start seeing sell pressure.
Opening range. You can also use they bid
back up. they fail against these point
of control and sellers and then we
rotate away. So your selling opportunity
is that high and that breakdown and then
that's a trend all the way back down,
right? And all we do is fail and it
gives you another opportunity if you
missed all of this
and that squeeze out here
was into an old value area low and it
was on current value area high and again
buyers got stuck. There's your bare
flag. There's a breakdown and retest of
previous day low. It was cleanest action
you've seen for a long time in my
opinion.
Yesterday was very clean. Okay, so there
you go into the 700s and uh previous day
value area high.
You know what the [\h__\h] do I know,
right? There's a retest of that key
level. There's been someone absorbing
the book all morning like we talked
about at 30s. He's now completed his
rotation. Only thing left for them to do
is to come up here into GlobeEx if they
really really really are desperate to
get up to that uh 729 sort of spot. But
they've uh they've done the damage.
Tesla into that 85. So remember that was
a big level. If Tesla starts failing
here might help the market do something,
but we'll see.
But you're through previous day value
area high now. So if they fail here, you
probably get a rotation back into 84s.
So I'd be interested here if you start
to see failures. If we've peaked out, if
we're just going to trade from one side
of value today. All right. From one side
of value
to the other side of value. Max move
probably up into here. Very possible we
come straight back down into here at
this point.
They've gone from value to value.
Let me have a look at this five minute
bar. Did they catch anyone? Yes, they
did above 95s.
All right. So, I'll be watching that
this trade here for a move back down to
value area high of 66s. If if they fail,
if they're going to sell value, if they
fail, we might see a rotation back into
66s. But right now, they're holding 84s,
which is the old shelf right here,
right? But if they fail, there's
probably a trade back in 66s and then
40s. So, I want to see if we can pop up
here, trap some buys, and fail.
I want to be careful. Where's Tesla?
It's not at that 450. I thought it was
just there. I missed that.
And I want to watch 85s on SPY. All
right. So, watching this carefully now.
If we track buyers up here, which we've
just done on this one minute chart up to
30. So I am interested if we start to
see a rotation away. Just want to give
this some time. How much longer we got
left on the 5m minute?
One more minute. Let this close out.
Are they adding above? Yeah, they're
adding into 30s,
which would be GlobeEx. So I want to be
careful.
considering a fade here, but I want to
be careful because if they squeeze out,
they're going 30s and they're adding up
there as well. So, just wait to see if
we get buyers caught here or not before
I think about doing anything else. They
just caught some more again.
Watching that previous day valing 700s.
If they reclaim it all, then I think we
go uh 30s. Not that much excess on the
high at the moment.
This is a 700 test. If they hold this,
we probably go 30. Spy not quite and ES
not quite high day. So might have one
more push in this yet.
Big still breaking down underneath
pre-market lows. This might go 30s at
this point. Not too much excess up here.
Waiting for ES to see if it can break
out. Watching that 85s inspire. That's
going to be key for me.
85s in the spy.
In the spy. On the spy. On the spy.
It's failing.
Want to see more delta court of side.
Not seeing it yet. Interested, but not
seeing it yet.
Now there was two pushes which have
failed up there but 8685
still holding a little imbalance here of
this RBS right here but fail under here
we can see a wash
not convinced high days in yet
trying to sell this aggressively right
now 90s
close under 85 Maybe there's a bigger
wash.
It's support 75. They're trying to sell
this aggressively here. Let's see if
they get their way or not.
They're trying again to sell
aggressively at these lows. They don't
get a snap, they're going to get caught.
And I'll join if we start to break down.
Here we go. Okay. See if we can get down
to 60s then. Lovely.
Being patient, scalping a bit out here
because we are picking a high of day
here for a rotation. Looking for a move
into 6817 if we close under that.
Looking for a move back to 43s.
Already in the money. Want to protect
this edge here at sort of 80s and 90s.
Now don't really want it to come back
above that level
because this can be a fail breakdown and
then a rip back higher. They can still
move to 30s if they want. 730s that is.
want to be careful if they reclaim this
range. I'll just cut and leave it. It
would just be like a 10 20 point scalp.
Holding P up here now on this last few
candles. They just tried to aggressively
sell that. Haven't got their way. Want
to be careful of this edge at 80 which
they're bidding off so far.
So any rehold of 80, I will just cut the
rest. They've got to sell through it.
You can see it aggressively close under
80 at this point and just wash everyone
out.
Stop already in the money. Want to
protect 90 now.
There's a retest of 80 again. This is
their chance. They got to sell through
this otherwise I'm not interested.
Starting to see a bit soaking here at
80.
Yeah, they've soaked again at 80. Want
to be very cautious now.
Going to move my stop just above this
delta at 87. So my stop's at 87 now for
the runner up. Try and let this work.
See if we can get down to value area
high on the session and initial balance.
So I'm just looking for this trade is
counter trend. But I'm looking for this
to here. And if they fade this, great.
But I'm not really expecting the market
to come below here. But this is the
rotation. The reason I'm short up here
is because I know we're in a rotation.
I'm trying to play the edge back to the
mean at the moment. They need to get
under 80 though. these sellers and they
keep trying and the more that they try
and don't get it, the more it means
there's a passive buyer. They might get
stopped out here on the runner, which is
fine if we do.
One thing I'm concerned about is 7:30 is
still available and ES is still trying
to break out. All right, stopped out
here on my runner. ES is still trying to
break out uh through initial balance
high. So, it might have more juice.
So, just a tiny scalp there. Market not
ready. can always rejoin him. But
selling came in aggressively at sort of
82 down to 77 and didn't get their way,
which is why I wanted to be cautious. So
in this candle here, they sold
aggressively down here, which means
there's a passive buyer here. Probably
the same guy that was here is trying to
soak this, trying to get this rotation.
So I'm very, very aware of him right
now.
So flat on this. Give it a moment to
shake out.
VIX really needs to reclaim PDC
otherwise uh this market can keep
drifting higher.
[snorts]
It's interesting here. It's a battle as
they build out.
Just want to see if Spy can do one more
push into 85, clear out the high of day
and then see if they sell it or not.
That would really help if we can see
something like that. Here
goes SPY. It's going to try it.
It's trading 8480s. I want to see it
trade into 85 there or thereabouts and
then see how we are. Flat on this at the
moment. Like I said, it was a small
scalp, didn't break down, so I cut it. I
don't hold on to stuff. If I see
participants getting stuck and I'm the
wrong side of it, I cut it. I cut it in
the money, but I still cut it.
More buyers just got trapped there
again.
that last push into 90.
So 90 and above. On this last one
minute, we had buyers just come in and
get themselves a little bit caught. SPY
is still not into 85 yet. I'm waiting to
see if SPY can get into 85 with a high
of day and a failure to see if there's
confluence here.
Needs another 20 cent spy. Here we go.
Another 10 cents now. Here we go. Spy is
going to test this 85. So, we might well
go for 730s here if they do.
Blow zones are bullish. I know we're
above initial balance, but I'm trying to
respect previous days value at the
moment, which is why I was looking for
the short on the failure of this level.
Give it to you all morning. I was
looking for this in case they rolled.
They haven't rolled. But if they want to
do this and come up here, they can. They
absolutely can. If they base above
previous day value, you want to be
careful because it means there's no
acceptance lower.
Come on, Spy. Just hurry up and get to
85 and we can see what's what.
All right, Richard. I'll have a look
later, mate, once I'm done.
We're into a key level at the moment, so
I just want to focus in in case there's
another trade opportunity here.
I'm not going to fight it. If it wants
to break it, just let it break. I'm not
going to fight it.
Trust trap buyers again there into
proves day value area high. I can't.
This has got to go higher at this point.
Surely spy wants to chest 85 at this
point. Surely
it's 10 cents away or so.
>> [snorts]
>> Where's my mouse?
ES and Inspire banging their head
[sighs] on the initial balance high high
of day and it's basically that uh 85
level. So, I know that's probably a
massive, massive, massive call wall. It
was last week. Um, if they break through
it, we can go to 88s on spy whether they
do it today or not. This [snorts] might
very well be the edge of the rotation,
which is why we were trying to time it,
but need to wait. Let it develop a bit
more now.
Definitely buyers caught at high day.
Just wonder
just wonder do they need one more shove
and see it's a sensitive area. Markets
like slowed down while they wait and see
are they going they're think everyone's
thinking the same. Are we going through
here to 7:30 or are we about to collapse
and come right down to this volume down
here?
Volume's down here.
There's a bit of excess on this, but not
that much. So, if SPY goes 85 and
through, we're probably coming here.
Otherwise, if they look above and fail,
this trade is available.
What's Tesla doing?
Did it actually get up to
Okay, failed in front of this five day.
Tesla rolling a little bit, but still
above initial balance and still not a
previous day high. It might still have
more in it Tesla as well.
Okay, here's 85s. Here we go. 685s now
on spy. How do we act here? Do we get
base above this or are we going to fail
into this?
If we base above this, we can go
previous day high. If we fail into it,
we're going to go rotation.
Asia high swipe. Yeah, I mean very
possible it comes up to to here the 30s
like we talked about and like you can't
ignore if it wants to base above and
they want to start printing this higher
they can. Remember we've had a failed
breakdown this morning. Um if we think
about in Discord,
those in Discord will know what what did
I say this morning? Uh
from
these are the trades.
All right, that's what we're doing.
Look, looking below right now. Uh, if
you really want to short, just wait for
the bat side to come in. It would be
obvious on M30 on an M30. Just know
every attempt for it since November 21st
has failed so far. All right, every
attempt has failed so far. Today's
another attempt of a breakdown which has
failed from bears. You have to be aware
of what the sentiment is. Bears are not
seeing follow through underneath key
pivots. They're just getting stuck. And
it's the same thing today. Okay, so 30s
looks possible. SPY now well through the
85 peaking above. If it wants to go
previous day high, 8663 on the spiders,
it can. So if it pulls back and holds 85
now, it's probably a bid. If it pulls
back and fails and slices through, it's
probably of high day. We just had a big
buyer join in at hive day. And if he
gets stuck, that might signal the hive
day. We're finally seeing some excess,
but I'd say 30s is not out the question,
but there's definite excess here for the
first time today. I think 30s is what
they're looking for at the moment.
They're trying to get back up to
Globeex.
Who's at my door?
Yeah. Okay, hang on. Someone at the
door.
Amazon package delivery would be my
wife. Okay.
Okay. Definitely excess. Where did that
buyer come in? 707s. So definite excess
707s, but you're still front side at the
moment. This is a squeeze out. This is
possible target. If you see a roll and
they start letting go of here, then this
is available down to here. And that is
the first time today I've seen excess at
high
spy coming back to test 85. So we can
still bid up from here if they really
want to. [snorts]
We've been buy delta by delta by delta
cell delta by delta by delta. And we're
going to test this cell delta point of
control which is 704.
Can't rule out 30s. Still look at ES
going and spy going. Okay, so they held
85s. They're trying to squeeze previous
day high as possible.
Very possible. Let me check the breadth.
still
starting to see some of the uh MAG sort
of cool off a bit or try and go red to
green when I say cool off. Uh finance
still good, asset management good,
energy good, utilities good, consumer
cynical good, defense pretty much flat.
So it's really financial sector and
energy driving the ES right now. What's
doing well? XOM. So oil.
What else? L nem
and the banks having a good day. Asset
management and banks having a really
good day. Probably pricing in the rate
cut for tomorrow because obviously they
can lend cheaper then. So probably more
clients. Okay. We never got through that
point of control I just talked about 704
buyer stuck over 704 705 right now. We
just retested that level. I'm getting
interested now in how we act. I'm
getting interested here.
When I say interested, I'm getting
interested to see if they let it go.
Only thing I'm aware of is we haven't
taken out 730. We're back under 700.
We're back to previous day value area
high. If they start failing this, we're
going to start washing.
And really, they need to get back
beneath 80s. Okay,
feeler on here. Let's see. They've got
to get back beneath 80s before I do
anything drastic.
Can I get filled on this feeler? Am I
going to have to chase beer? Can you
feel me?
Come come up and then fail. Oh, don't
miss me by that much.
Watch 685 on spy under over for
sentiment.
Still holding. I was very very tempted
to take a short here in front of 700.
And I'm
don't like what I just saw here. They
just sold aggressively here.
It's moving very very uh not fast in
terms of range but between who's stuck.
So sellers are now stuck under 92s.
Buyers are stuck over 704s. Sellers are
stuck at 92. So 12 points 12 points
range. Yeah, interested in downside if
enough buyers get stuck only because
we're playing the range but very
concerned that we can move to 730. So
and uh spy is holding 685 on dips. All
right. So
yes, I know we're inside GlobeEx. That's
why I'm saying we can trade up to 7:30
if they really really want to.
Let's trap balls up there again. That
last shove. They can't get over the
704s. If they get over 704s, there's a
squeeze available. But that is where
buyers are stuck at the moment. They're
stuck over 704s.
Oh, that was a level I was going to
sell. You going to force me to chase now
[\h__\h]
It comes at 85. Test on spy.
I'd say 8493 really, but 85 gamma level,
but 8493 fail underneath initial
balance. Look above and fail when we
rotate.
Let's say
a bit of a shelf here.
There's a bit of a shelf here.
>> [snorts]
>> gain five. [\h__\h] hell. Get destroyed.
Here
we go.
Big selling down here. Are they going to
still soak it?
There's that 89.
Still soaking. Still passive buyer here.
can see on the last five minute they've
sold 93 down to it's very very tight.
They've sold for a three-point range and
there's a there's a buyer there soaking
for sure there's a buyer there soaking
so
under 89
and then we've got seller stuck 82 to
78. So really yeah under 80 it confirms
a bit more and it's dangerous. that blue
shelf that I just lined up. They're
still soaking that shelf. Still a
passive buyer in that shelf.
Yeah, I'm not short. Like I said, like I
was looking for it, but once I saw the
sellers stuck here, I'll get short when
it when we start to leave volume
trapped. We're not leaving volume
trapped. If they if they've done this
move here
and they hadn't built lots of sellers
stuck here, that rotation might have
happened. But there's a passive buyer in
this blue box. That's why I put the blue
box here for you. All right, if we move
under this, that rotation to here is
possible. Under that, that rotation
here. From here, we can still soak and
go up here. Anything is possible right
now. Momentum is upside. Flow zones are
upside. Protrend at the moment is
upside. This can be target. There's no
doubt about it. I'm just trying to
respect that we're at previous day
value. I don't want to be a buyer up
here. If I'm going to sell it, I want to
sell like a look above and fail or
something like this for a rotation. And
I'm it's going to be a scalp because
we're in value.
I don't want to be a buyer up at
previous day value area highs. Worst
location to buy if we're going on
rotation.
Just caught buyers again into that 700.
They cannot get above 704.
They're stuck. There's buyers up there
are stuck, but the sellers here at 94
and under are stuck. So very tight
10point range. Someone will lose. Once
they lose, I can join in.
They lose value and we go rotation. We
can might go down to point control. If
they lose, we see follow through 85 here
on spy. Like I talked about, here's your
back test of 85 for the first time
today. If they lose 85 on SPY, don't be
surprised if you see that move back down
to 8450.
Starting to lose it.
Watching this. This is where sellers
keep getting stuck where we are now.
They need to see follow through here. If
they don't see follow through, there's
no uh there's no move lower. It's just a
passive buyer on a tape. Still seeing a
passive buyer on a tape down there. So,
this blue box, still a passive buyer,
just sat there absorbing everything
that's coming his way so far.
Probably the same guy that was down here
at 6:30, is now trying to absorb up
here. Maybe if he's looking to absorb,
he's looking for this. Once he leaves
the tape, you probably see this rotation
to here and then here.
If he leaves the tape, might not leave
the tape at all today.
85 still holding so far on Spy. that
initial balance high. Still holding,
still a buyer on a tape.
It's amazing. Bid, bid, bid, bid, bid
this market. It's all they [\h__\h] do.
It's absolute.
All I can think is there's the biggest
retail trap ever coming between now and
end of January. And I think there's a
big sale coming between January and
March. The fact that they didn't sell
this market in December, I think is very
unhealthy. If anything, I don't think
it's good for market. I think it's
unhealthy.
Um, so whatever the next squeeze out is,
I think becomes a retail trap. If this
is institutions holding bids to squeeze
out, I think retail piles in and then
they sell it early next quarter. But
that's just a thought. We will see what
happens. Like I said, December 13th, I
think, is going to be key for this
market. See what the bonds do. JPY carry
trade. Remember, we've got that uh bond
auction at 1:00 today as well. You want
to be aware of that if you're in the
market.
that testing the same level. Is this guy
going to let them through? If he's Is he
still here or is he gone?
I'd say under 80 can get a little nasty.
Here we go. Under 85s now on Spy.
Aggressive selling coming in here. They
need to start forcing it under 80 though
because this is the blue box where the
buyers been. Once we get a snap under
here, I think there's I mean it's not
very big, is it? 20 point rotation. And
if we get lucky down into here at the
moment, there's still a buyer on a date.
Still can't get close. All the selling
is happening at 93. to 90 and they
cannot get a close under those levels.
Yeah. Well, VIX has actually found a
bid. It's it's falling, but it's
actually found a bid the last 15
minutes. So, it's actually gone the
other way. Okay, here we go. This is
their chance now. Can we see the snap?
Is there going to be momentum or is he
still here hanging out? Still here
hanging out. You see this big bar just
got absorbed again?
Come on, sellers. If you're going to do
it, now's the time. There you go. All
right. Follow through or not? Follow
through or not? Follow through or not.
Still absorbing on the tape. Follow
through or not. Still absorbing on the
tape. [laughter]
Oh, sellers, you're [\h__\h] useless. You
are absolutely useless in this market. I
can't believe it's been May, June, July,
August, September, October, November to
7th. Eight months of them being absolute
[\h__\h] at seeing followthrough. They've
got an opportunity here to see a wash.
All right. This is the blue box. Once
this fails, the opportunity is down into
here. The trap level will be 85. But if
they fail that, there's 10 point snap,
but they're still being absorbed, right?
You can see it here. Look at these guys
here. They keep selling, selling,
selling, selling, selling, selling, and
they're being absorbed. This is where
the buyers are stuck up above. So,
waiting to see.
Just one. Just one. Do I'm waiting to
sell this up here, but it's not ready.
It's close.
It feels close.
Tesla's starting to pull back a bit.
This might be the sign. We need a close.
Is this going to snap now? Sellers's
trying again.
Buyers just got stuck uh 94s now. So now
we're starting to see buyers get stuck
lower and lower. We might get a rotation
here if they fail. 94s. Here we go.
90. Here we go, folks. Here we go. Here
we go. Okay, in now. Let's see if we can
get a rotation. Stop. Let's see. Where's
that value area high? 76es. I want to
get down into here if possible.
Don't want it to trap. Want to see at
least 76s and then see if we can wash.
Don't want to see spy reclaim 85 either.
Don't want to see it trap here. Sellers
are stuck from here before from 83 down
to 78. So if we start getting underneath
78, we're going to start seeing like a
bigger move lower. But you want to be
proactive if you're in this with me. I'm
small size because it's counter trend.
It's hard to pick. And like I said, if
they trap here and reclaim, then so be
it.
sellers got stuck there again at 85s.
So it's the candle from 11:10 this
morning causing a problem on a five
minute.
That is the problem. 11:10 candle.
So it can't get through
uh these guys from here. It's these guys
here stuck. So once we get underneath
that, you can see it protected it. Once
we get underneath that, we can get to
value area high until that point. So
buyers are now stuck in here at 95s.
Sellers are stuck here at 82s. And
that's very tight range to be playing,
but that's what we're playing.
Back to those 95s again. If they break
out here, they're squeezed. So I don't
want to hold it above this.
I'd say 700s, I guess.
Yeah, 700s. 700s is the
No, I'm not looking at M andQ. Sorry,
I'm focused on MQ. I don't care about M
andQ. Sorry if you got swiped or it did
something, but I'm not taking my eyes
off this chart.
We get through 700s. They can squeeze
this
reclaim of 85 here. possible
reclaim 85 here on spy. Be careful if
they squeeze through 700s. High days
coming.
I'm already out of this now. Can always
read add in. That's annoying. They had
the opportunity uh just just repeat of
everything. Drift higher. Probably
should probably won't have another go at
this now to be honest. If they had that
opportunity then to take control of this
market
with the buyers stuck here, they had the
opportunity to rotate back to value.
They failed that opportunity. There's
still a passive buyer on the tape. And
730 will probably be the target. And I
don't think I want to have another go at
this. I've had uh
that one attempt or two attempts up
here. I can't even remember. I think
maybe there was one here and one here.
Can't even remember now.
Yeah, for sure. I mean, it like we are
at higher day. It might be coming up
here, but like I'm certainly not buying
up here on a rotation. This is
yesterday's value.
The buying opportunity was the fake out
here and then the reclaim. That was
probably your buy opportunity here. And
this is a slow grind. I've had a go. I I
left all of this alone and I've had a go
at value. Had a go to see if value will
fail. It's not failing. So, I don't want
to fight it. If it's not going to fail,
I don't want to fight it. I don't want
to be in here fighting a market which is
bid bid bid bid bid bid bid bid bid bid
bid b b b b b b b b b b b b b b b b b b
b b b b b b b b b b b b b b b b b b b b
b b n n n n n n n n n n n n n n n n n n
n non-stop like it has been for months
in this range. But what I don't want to
do is bid the top side of a range. It's
easiest way to get hurt. I don't know
what their intentions are. Right now I'm
out of this trade. Let's have a look at
M and Q. See what you guys were talking
about. Yes. Okay. Yeah. So little stop
right down to initial balance. I mean,
that's kind of what I was looking for on
the Q's, but uh we didn't get it.
So, yeah, that was the box, wasn't it?
So, that was where I was trying to
target. So, yeah, M and Q did that move.
NQ didn't. What are you going to say?
divergence like whole markets had red
flags.
Whole markets had red flags today.
Divergence ES to NQ divergence M andQ to
NQ divergence VIX to ES. Like
it's nor it's probably normal before
FOMC day.
And lots of these like medium caps have
found a bid today as well. And some of
these gamma names as well, like
has found a bid today. It's up like
4.5%.
It's stupid. Um,
the basket's not doing that well though.
Inqbts not following the same suit.
RGTI. So, it's only really Iron that's
found a bid today over those uh big
squeezy names.
Netflix still selling.
There's an argument to have one more go
at this, but I don't think I want to. I
think I'd rather just sit still.
every balance starting to hold by side.
Buys are in control of this at the
moment.
I would just be very surprised if they
want to bid above previous day value
area high today. That just seems like a
very dangerous move for institutions to
do.
They just tried to sell the low of this
last candle again and got soaked. There
there is a nonstop passive buyer in this
tape. It's the only thing I could say
which has been present all morning. He
was at 600, 630,
680, and now he's at 690. And he's just
soaking anything that comes his way.
You can see on bit map there. What was
that last cell? 497 lot into 700 and he
like sellside and he just took it all.
We went, "Yep, I'll help you."
Seriously, can you guys hear that?
>> I wonder how long they're going to do
that for a building work outside my
house.
That better not be going on for too
long. They haven't even notified me.
85 check again on spy
that initial balance you're over under.
They might do this failure when they're
ready. It's just whether I had one more
go.
No. Yeah. So you can hear it killing me,
man. It's uh road works outside my house
or some building work.
at previous day value area high
important
94 95ish
initial balance on ES kind of
still soaking. He's still there at the
moment. He's still there absorbing the
lot.
I've just got my hands off everything
because I'm interested,
but they're playing games today and I
don't want to give my day back. So, I
want to be really careful. If I'm going
to get involved, I need to be careful.
And I know that there is a rotation
above still available if they want it.
But, we are starting to taper and go
sideways here. There's no doubt about
it. They're starting to struggle, but I
I need to see this.
It's It feels close, but it's felt close
every time. And he's just gone, "Oh,
I'll gobble you up for that move." So, I
want to be careful.
Right into where we sold on the previous
five minute. It feels so close,
especially with spy at 685 and starting
to fail it. Do I have one more go here?
That's the question.
Looks good. It looks really good now.
Here we go. All right, last attempt.
Don't you [\h__\h] me over,
you absolute [\h__\h] Right. This is
where he keeps coming in. 90s
down to 84s. So, I want to see follow
through under 84 now.
Come on, [\h__\h] Give me follow
through under 84. Get out my [\h__\h] way
and let me have some follow through.
Don't make me TP out here already.
Stella just came in again then and got
caught.
>> [laughter]
>> need follow through under 84. If I don't
see follow through under 84, I'm going
to cut it because sellers just came in
again there at 84 and haven't got follow
through.
Last chance.
Don't look good. I'm telling you,
they've got to reject this volume. This
blue level. We can actually move this up
a bit. It's more like this now. All
right. This needs to basically
reject. All right. Nothing above 93. We
called it 94 above that. We We can't
trade back above that. If we trade back
above that is going to be acceptance. We
need this to reject. This is looking
good so far. What's delta light? Looks
good actually. We just need follow
through. We need a snap here and a
flush. Uh if you feel uncomfortable,
size down or take it off. You're trying
to pick the rotation. It's really hard
trade. I hate rotation. You hear me say
it all the time. My least favorite
trade. If we can get follow through
here, I think there is a trade down.
Especially if we get under 78, we can
see a trade down
into here and then into here.
Here we go. Come on. Come on. Come on.
Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come
on. Come on. Get out of my way. Passive
buyer. Get the [\h__\h] out of my way. 80.
Get out my way. Get out of my way. Come
on. Get out of my way. Don't want to see
it absorb here. Mm- Don't like that.
Don't like that, Mr. 80.
Get out of my way.
Nice. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go.
Right. You've got a chance here, bears.
You have a chance here to take control
of this market for a moment. Let's see
this flush. Let's get this blue box as
your TP1 and initial balance. And then
if we can get under that, we get a
better rotation.
Come on [\h__\h]
This becomes key. This is the edge of
this range. Think about where we broke
out from.
It's like your RBS level. All right. So,
this is why it's a TP1 in here. And if
we get back down into here, I think we
can let go and come all the way into
650. It's possible. But your TP1 is
right here right now. This is what I'm
saying. It's a small trade from here to
here. that you can see they're trying to
hold this little shelf. If we get under
this 650 as possible. If we get under
that uh well then really technically
we can come back into these lows at 600.
So it's available if they let it happen.
But remember main sentiment today has
been to drift higher. We've still left
Gloveex up there. We're now comfortable
in the short for the first time today.
Took a few attempts.
Really nice. Here we go. So TP1 here,
folks. And let's see if we can get some
continuation for the first time today.
Just took a minute. It took a minute.
The the fight was massive in here. This
guy was just soaking these cells, but
now we're starting to see follow
through. Really good. Okay, there's your
initial balance. Make sure you've taken
something off the table here, please.
Let's see if we can get follow through.
Nice failure of 685. So, we poked above
685 on Spy. are now starting to fail it.
Back into this shelf here. Big big level
here for spy. Uh 8450s. If they fail
that, we go VWOP and we can see
continuation. Come on. I want to get
down into here now. Come on, baby.
Don't be a little
You know what?
Give me a bit more.
Yeah, you should have paid yourself some
already. I'm trying to hold to see if we
can get a deeper move here.
43s would be nice. So that's current
volume point control down into here.
Anywhere here would be really nice for
my last TP. Don't want to see this
reclaim this shelf. This this remains
the same, right? So maybe you don't want
to risk all the way up here. I'm risking
this on my runner where I basically got
in. But if we reclaim that, no good.
But if we reject there or in front of
there then we might see more downside.
Just trapped a little bit of buying
there into 80s which is good long as we
don't reclaim that.
Some buying caught into 80s there.
And if spy rejects 85, it would be the
same kind of move.
Want to be cautious because we have held
initial balance. It's worth noting. Said
it's a scalp and if it doesn't want to
do anymore, it doesn't. Just caught
buyers again there. This is looking
better now.
It's giving me a bit more confidence
that we've just caught buyers twice. I
want to see a heavy close though.
I'm going to close through this
imbalance that we just had here at 78.
So, need a big close here. Start
dumping. This is looking better. Need a
big close. Need to get under this seller
who got caught at the low. 222 lot into
72s. Need to close under him. Need to
get under 72s.
Need him to be comfortable. Come on
market. Stop being a bugger today. Here
we go. Buyers now caught. Get under this
72s,
please. I want to see follow through
under here. Watching this very careful.
If there's a bid down here, I'm want to
be cautious, but we should see follow
through if we can get under where this
seller got stuck.
Do I take a TP here?
I just added back on on that pot. So,
I've got to pay myself a bit here just
in case. I want to see follow through,
though.
Yeah, we're holding this 72 at the
moment. Come on.
We can get follow through under here.
It's where this seller got stuck. If we
can get follow through and let him out,
we can see a wash into 50s. If he stays
stuck, I want to be cautious.
Right. He came flying in at uh 71.25.
So, that's where he's stuck at the
moment as a seller. [snorts]
Not seeing acceptance underneath him. He
is stuck in this market at the moment.
That big seller got stuck.
Buying buyers are stuck at 82. So, you
got a 10-point range here. And they're
starting to see some relief here. SPY is
going to go and retest 85 here by the
looks of it. And we might retest value
area higher which be sort of 88. So we
have an imbalance just above that at 90.
Still want to lean sellside on this all
the time. We're leaving that volume
shelf above.
I still think we can rotate lower here.
Nice.
really want to stay heavy versus 82 now.
82 84 somewhere around that. Don't want
to reclaim with it that really
this stupid [\h__\h] seller at 72 is
going to [\h__\h] this move up if he doesn't
[\h__\h] his ideas up
can see how the market moves. Like one
of you's been calling like there's
there's a seller at 62 or whatever. Like
that that's the problem. That's not an
attraction. That's what ruins the move
when they get caught the wrong side. So,
here we go. He got caught and we're
going to squeeze right back up to this
gray box. This is where my runner is.
So, we don't reject this. We're going to
make new highs and we're going to go all
the way up to that GlobeEx level. All
because of the seller down here getting
stuck. All right. All because some idiot
here sold 222 lots at the market and got
caught. He allowed this to happen
because his stop was here and now we
drift higher. It's all because of that
player.
So here's the shelf. Reclaim this. I
will cut and because we will go 730s if
we reclaim this spy 685 retest
now orever for the market. They either
sell this aggressively or we are going
all the way back up all the way back up
to here by holding this blue box. So you
can see the rotation was from here to
here. So I said you have to pay
yourself. And now we're starting to
reclaim this. And this is looking more
and more promising because some complete
[\h__\h] decided he was going to sell
with size down here and he's just caused
this whole rally. So bears, what I'd say
is bears are [\h__\h] They suck at doing
their job. They just absolutely suck at
doing their job at the moment.
Yeah, nice choice. Same same with me.
Same with me. It was a nice win. It was
a small win, but it was a good win. We
just have to wait now.
SPY's
not got back through 685 yet. Just know
that it's not through it yet. It's
tested it. It's like there or
thereabouts.
That's just I would say like I'd use
that as my sentiment for this market.
Above 85, maybe it wants to go to 88.
Below 85, maybe there's a rotation. We
did talk about that shelf on spy holding
into 8450. It's exactly where it held
and it's starting to reclaim. So it's
holding a higher low on like a 5minute
chart. SPY is looking more and more
bullish. Two-leg pullback held a higher
low can possibly complete rotation. This
is probably going to go 7:30 now.
It's all because of like un like
understanding who's stuck. Like I called
it to you here like who's stuck? Why is
he stuck? What happens when someone's
stuck? We go the other way.
Such a shame. Such a shame. Maybe I
should have just flipped to a bid there.
Hard to flip to a buy down here. But I
guess it's the same thing. You could buy
this and sell this and then hold the
runner for this. Same as we sold this,
cover this, hold a runner for this. It's
the same kind of idea.
Those deep pullbacks are holding.
The question is now, do they hold value?
Now we're above this. Do they hold this
and complete that move? They should.
They should. They've done all the hard
work. The hard work is to get back above
this. They should do this now. In
theory, I'm not going to buy it, but
they in theory they should do that.
It's not an uptrend though, Bit Culture.
It's a range.
What part of this
is an uptrend?
It's a range.
It's a range. It's all it is. What's the
range rejecting?
Supply,
right? It's a range. So, if you want to
buy this here, you're likely to get
slapped. If you want to sell this here,
you're going to get slapped. It's why
you play the edge of a range. It's not a
trending market right now. It's a
rotational market.
Yeah. Okay. So, you're going to buy this
here, are you? Cuz we talked about the
buys down here. So, Mr. Smart Bollocks,
you're just you're buying this up here,
are you? You're buying previous days
value area high, are you? In supply in
confirmed supply. Even though I've said
it's possible it's going to go here.
Even though you might have just joined
and we talked about the 600 to 700
trade, but you're here saying we're
[\h__\h] idiots.
All right. Good for you, mate.
I honestly don't know why I bother.
Don't bother.
Yeah, it can be Chris. Absolutely it can
be. But we have divergence,
right? Like I've said, I People come in
here at the last minute and then they
want to run their [\h__\h] mouths. I've
given you the levels since all morning.
I've talked about the failed breakdown
and not wanting to be short down here
and the likelihood of if we fail to hold
this rotation, we will go from previous
days value area low to previous days
value area high. Now, there's [\h__\h]
smart bollocks being like, "It's an
obvious trend." No, it's not a trend.
It's a range rotation. If you buy here
to look for that, by all means, do it.
I'm not doing that. That's not what I
would look for in a range rotational
market. It's way too risky to do that
for me. But if you want to do that, by
all means. But you know, we took this
breakdown from leaving volume to here.
Okay, this is all we got. This is why
the blue box is here. This is why I said
TP1. If it broke down further, Smart
Bollocks would be out of money, wouldn't
he? But maybe you're buying here to get
to here. That's probably the shittiest
trade of the day. But if it works for
you, great. But maybe tomorrow it
doesn't work for you. But [\h__\h] why do I
bother trying to help?
You've been here for like a minute just
running him out. Like it just makes me
laugh. Like honestly, I'm going to start
closing chat and just not not answering
questions or helping.
Then shut the [\h__\h] up, Bit Culture,
because I gave you that trade, didn't I?
Maybe you're joining last minute running
your mouth. But like, we literally
talked about the long from here to here.
So, if you think you're really smart
getting 20 points out of it, and you're
going to come into the chat and start
like acting like that, do one. Go and
join someone else. I literally even told
you where participants are track. Like
there's no one, not one person on the
internet reading the tape giving you the
levels like I they don't exist. They
don't exist. So please don't come in
here running your mouth cuz I'll just as
easily beat you out cuz it just pisses
me off and you've done a good job of it.
It's not a [\h__\h] reversal. Oh my god.
[sighs]
You're on your own, chat. Good luck.
You're on your own.
[snorts]
>> [cough]
>> There's not. It's not moving. It's
saying letting pe letting people on
their own because I don't need to do
[\h__\h] anything for you. Like I don't
need to do any. This is the part that
you guys seem to not understand. Like
you're here yapping
all the time and I'm here to help. I
don't need to do anything. I don't owe
any of you anything. Anything. I'm here
because I'm a nice guy.
If it's not moving, I'm just not going
to call the levels. Like, I'm going to
be quiet cuz I can't deal with people
giving their [\h__\h] two bit every
minute.
It gets really easy. I just do this.
Now, I can't see your chat. So, I'll
just trade what's in front of me. So now
you get no questions and I'll trade what
I want on my time.
Nothing's changed for me. It's been the
same setups all day. It's a range
rotation and can't see your questions so
I can't answer them.
We're in lunch now anyway. So it makes
no difference to me. I'll go and trade
with my community who are decent people.
Same sentiment for me. Same levels all
morning that I've given you for free.
For free.
Same levels. Gray box, same levels. Spy,
same levels. VIX, same levels all day
long.
[snorts]
>> [snorts]
>> I gain something from streaming. I can
see what one of you trying to say. What
do I gain like a whole 400 bucks a month
in YouTube?
Man, it's so amazing. Like, you guys are
all here, but like all the new ones just
yapping.
No, [\h__\h] the discount. No one's getting
a discount this year. Piss me off too
much.
I'm only joking. Yeah, we we'll probably
do a little Christmas discount.
Holding gray box. Same level.
Same level.
[snorts]
Tesla's going for that 450. Same level I
give you.
Same level.
Dragon market.
>> [snorts]
[snorts]
>> Is that lunch?
Honestly, I don't know if I feel like
doing a giveaway. It's [\h__\h] Every day
on this chat is getting worse. I don't
know how people do it.
All
right, FCT in chat for a giveaway. If
you've pissed me off today, [\h__\h]
instantly you're not getting it. Just
going to say that now. If you're one of
the names who's been a dick, you're not
winning. But everyone else, just type
FCT in chat.
I'll give you guys a couple minutes.
[laughter]
All
right, 7:30 is taken. Let's pull a
winner.
Let's get rid of everyone that we don't
like because you are not winning.
All right. JMM 7695, are you here?
JMM7695.
Nice. All right, dude. Just uh shoot me
an email info@flowzontrader.com.
Just send me a I'm going to make a note
of your name. Just send me a screen grab
of your
um YouTube with you logged in just so I
know it's you and I'll sort you out a
free account.
free Apex account.
I'm from the UK as you can probably tell
with the accent. All right, I'm out of
here. I'm going to trade with my
community this afternoon who don't give
me [\h__\h] like this. Uh I'll think about
whether I can be bothered to turn up
tomorrow to be quite honest because I
have enough going on off the charts to
come in and deal with this kind of stuff
and it's FOMC tomorrow.
price probably unlikely to move much
until uh
until after Fed announcement and I think
we're getting a new Fed chair announced
tonight at 6:00 from Trump as well. So,
we're going to get new Fed chair
announced which will come into place
next year. We get a rate cut tomorrow,
quarter point, 95% chance we get a
quarter point which means it's probably
priced in. Um and then we get
uh Oracle earnings, AVGO earnings bond
auction today. But obviously all you
guys who know everything already know
all of that. That's why you're here. Um,
peace and love. Take care. Uh, those in
Discord, I'll see you in there in a bit.
Peace.