Okay team, welcome back. Happy Friday.
Happy Friday. Can't wait to get this
week over. To be honest, it's been a bit
of a drag for price action this week.
So, let's just see what we get at the
moment. More of the same. All right. So,
what are we seeing? Well, we've been
boxed in and every look above
uh sort of the 85s or into the 85s on
SPY has been uh sold into. Right. So, I
wouldn't normally care about this, but I
know the gamma levels like I keep
talking about up there have been
massive. So, I'll be watching to see if
we get over 85 and base over 85 because
if we do that, we go into positive GABA
and maybe there's a squeeze on the spy
and that might drag the market up with
us. Until that point, we keep trading
back inside. If we look at the cues,
we have relative weakness. All right.
So, you can see versus just pull this
down for you. You can see versus the
spy, we are failing to break out above
these levels and fill. We have an old
gap up here, right? An RTH gap that we
have not come up and filled. We haven't
tested any of this true supply up here.
So, relative weakness and you can see
we're just in this slow uptrend.
All right, it was steep and it's just
slowed right down. Okay, but we're still
technically bullish. Uh I'm
cautiously bullish. Let's just put it
that way. I'm cautiously bullish. I've
been talking about much more bullish if
we can come down and hold a higher low
there. Um so I want to be very very
cautious. We have one week, two week of
a balance range. This week in a balance
range. this is your area. Until they
reclaim that, then for me, it's just a
poor location to be buying from. Um,
down here is where I'm interested
longterm. And you can see the volume
still low uh but we still drift higher.
And uh I'm going to get into that
because I spent a bit of time looking at
the charts uh yesterday to just go
through that cumulative delta.
Okay, can you guys see everything here?
Oh, sorry folks. It's not what I wanted
to do.
Make this bigger for you guys. There you
go. All right. Hourlys.
We can still see the hourlys are holding
higher lows and we keep holding these
pivots.
Okay. So, if we zoom out
this edge of previous week value and
this old balance range, two weeks
balance range, we keep absorbing on it.
Okay. So this pin high
right all right became a key level over
under we came over it we drifted under
it on Tuesday absorbed closed back over
it came back to it against Wednesday
double bottom reabsorbed went over it
came back to the same level yesterday
reabsorbed back over it and we're making
this higher low here. All right that's
the channel right now. It's not pretty.
Um it's starting to get tighter and
tighter. All right. If you want to think
about this as a range, if we think about
from
where's Monday's close,
okay, Monday's close, that's your sort
of range on Tuesday, that's the range
into Wednesday, that's the range into
Thursday, and we've had a failed
breakout. And that's the range. You can
see we're getting tighter, but we really
need to see reclaims up here and holds
above to be bullish. You can see look
above fail. Look above fail. Look above
fail. Look above fail. Look above fail.
Look below fail. Look below fail. Look
below fail. All right. You're kind of
just doing a dance. Um I'd say
effectively from sort of 675
and no acceptance under 500. So that's
your dance. That dance might be tighter
today. It might be down to 589. So you
might be in a 100 to 90 point range
until the market proves otherwise. I
want to move up into here because I want
to talk about this cumulative delta
because it actually gave some clues
yesterday and I was a bit sloppy in
looking for it. Um, but if we see
drag this up, right, Delta did nothing
yesterday other than drift higher. All
right, all we did was make higher highs
and higher lows, which means on the
tape, all right, there was no aggressive
selling. It's just aggressive buying.
Maybe the odd bit of passive selling,
but actually no aggression. So when
we're making these moves here of lower
lows, we're making higher highs on
delta. We make another lower low here,
we're making higher highs on delta. That
means that there's no selling in here,
folks. There's no aggressive selling in
here. And it's worth noting because
until we see aggressive selling and
probably until we break down that 500
level, I don't think this market's going
to do anything other than rotate, unless
we obviously close above this block here
and start driving higher, which is
possible. So, even this morning in that
flush, I mean, they're doing these same
gains every day at the moment. It's a
pre-market flush, which is being
absorbed. And you can see Delta's come
back in and we're all the way back up.
Now, whether today is different, you
know, whether they've done this trap
four days in a row and on the fifth day,
they let it go, I don't know. But, uh,
that's what we're seeing at the moment.
So, we're going to respect what we're
seeing because there's not much else we
can do. We're opening up in no man's
land right now. Now, if we think about
what we did yesterday, here's the death
chop that we talked about all day. We
are holding previous days value area
low. We haven't even got there. We've
tested previous days point of control.
We've reclaimed previous days value area
high. We drifted higher, came back, held
it, and went now into no man's land.
Fantastic. I mean, absolutely
nothing we can do. Just bouncing
off previous day's value, which is very
tight. If we think about the value
yesterday, the low was 560. The high was
620. I mean, there's no range there,
folks. There's literally nothing there
to do. That's about as big as a normal
stop right now. So, just be aware of
that. All right, moving into lower time
frame. You can see even more clear here.
So, this is yesterday's mess. The same
kind of area as all week. All we're
doing coming back and back testing it
and holding it. So, I would say shorts
will need to defend 69700. It's as
simple as that. All right. If shorts
don't defend that for a retest of this,
right? And the retest of this, bulls
will want to defend this to go back up.
If shorts don't defend this and we get
back start chewing back through all of
this, right? If shorts don't defend this
level and we get back through and we do
this, then we're probably bullish for a
breakout over 65 757 to uh 830s. All
right. So, just be aware of that. It's
uh it's not a very pretty tape right now
is probably the best way to put it.
Marquez said it is worth watching uh ES
and the spiders. ES coming right back to
that same point. All right, it's the
same dance.
We swept this low. We've held this
pivot. All right, and we're coming back
to this same level. I'm not really going
to even try a short here. I'm going to
be honest. This market's showing me that
all it wants to do is run traps. And
until we're out of a trappy market on a
on a Friday, it's the last thing I want
to do is get caught on a trap. Uh, as I
reminded you at the beginning of the
show, uh, where's my spiders?
85, which we're at now. All right, mark
out 85. Mark out 82, Mark 80. Those are
your big gamma levels. All right, those
are the big options levels. I wouldn't
normally care, but apparently this
market only cares about options right
now. So, you can see we can't get a
close under 82. All right, 82 keeps
absorbing. All right, so that is your
put wall underneath there. There was
another one at 80 where I've got it
marked out in blue. So, we can move this
up. Right. This 82s
basically here. Yeah. Let's get rid of
these. And your call wall right now is
85. So, if they get above 85, potential
squeeze, but every time we've come up
towards 85, failed. Failed. Failed. And
we're there again. All right. So, that
is your call wall is sat at 85 right
now. Right. So, I'd be using these as
over under levels for rotations
and the spy will probably help you. The
reason I'm saying the spy is because
it's the most traded instrument for
options is the spy. All right, let's
have a look at the mag.
Apple slight gap down, but I mean really
this is about as no trade zone as you
get. Drift down yesterday, there's your
pocket and we're opening up basically
flatten it. So, not a great start there,
folks. I'm afraid
Amazon big flush yesterday. Ground back
up. It's trying to hold a pivot here.
This is your box, right? These lows if
it gets through that up here. So, Amazon
again probably just rotation until it
proves otherwise right now and opening
up. Slight gap up, but not much. Goo
trying to find a bounce. So, there's the
flush on Thursday. Grind, grind, grind,
grind, grind. God, that looks like the
market, doesn't it? And uh we're coming
right back up to this pivot right where
we failed from. So, it all depends. Does
Google sell 320 or not? So, you could
set a price alert there. 3 320s um
32060s. Does it sell it or not? That's
that would be my question this morning.
Meta came out with tried to come out
with some more positive news this
morning after this yesterday. All this
was yesterday is them saying, "Hey,
we're going to stop working on our
stupid metaverse. We've wasted money on
it." Go figure. Uh the market liked that
because they were like, "Thank God
they're going to stop spending." But uh
it didn't like it that much because we
haven't done much with it. So again,
Meta not really moving.
Microsoft, there's your gap up on
Microsoft. So that's probably one of the
better looking charts that I've seen
this morning. But again, we're still
pinned in. All right. Pinned in from
Wednesday's range. Thursday traded
inside Wednesday. Friday still opening
up inside Wednesday. All right. We're
still pinned in.
Nothing here.
Nvidia. All right. Pre-market gap up.
We've already closed the gap. So, Nvidia
still
kind of pinned in.
All right.
We have to see whether it can hold the
top side of the range, but still pinned
in a bigger range here. This is the
weekly range. Was that Tuesday's high?
Yeah, still pending. And Tesla.
Okay, a bit of weakness here to start
the day on Tesla, but overall it's been
in a big old squeeze, hasn't it? So, if
we look at Tesla, it's done a fantastic
job this week. It's probably one of the
better stocks this week from Monday,
Tuesday low. If we think about weekly
model, Monday, Tuesday, and all we've
done is break out. Really nice. Question
is for Tesla now. Does it backs stop
into here?
All right. Is it going to retest that or
is this too much too soon? And we if we
start losing 46s and 45s, there's
potential for a move back down into
here. So, if this was nothing more than
a big gamma squeeze, there's potential
for that to move back down into the 30s.
Uh just want to have a quick look at
Oracle because that did find a bid the
last few days.
Yeah, we have seen I would say this week
we have some seen some rotation into
some uh other names again. So some of
the more squeezy type names remember
Oracle has been absolutely slammed. Um
they found a bid and they're starting to
drift up. How we act here becomes key.
So I'll be keeping one eye on that. The
names yesterday which started to go were
all those uh sort of chip names. So your
IN
uh you can see started to find a bid big
squeeze. IQ did the same. Look at that
ginormous squeeze yesterday, right?
Gamma squeeze yesterday. Uh MVTS was the
same. So we have seen rotations into
some of these shorts. Probably getting a
bit caught in some of these. RGTI was
the same, right? This probably added
fuel to the fire. So, you know, I have
we'll have those on a side monitor today
um just to see if they if they actually
intend in like really shoving these up
or if that was nothing more than a big
squeeze out, short squeeze out and we
come back down. And if that happens, my
question is is the likes of Nvidia,
AMD,
INTC,
etc., etc., going to follow suit and
then does that see mean we see weakness
in uh everyone related basically all of
the mag outside of Apple I don't know
folks but it's just something as I was
going through the charts last night
seeing what's actually going on in this
market it's something that I observed so
it's worth saying okay we're about to
open up here good morning everyone sorry
I haven't had a chance to go through all
the good mornings but thank you for
joining again uh nice and cautious today
as we always talk about nice and slow
this morning. Uh you can see we're doing
the same game that we've done every
single day with a slam pre-market and
we're just bidding all the way back up.
There is not a lot to do with this
folks. This is uh for me this is as I've
talked about yesterday and extensively
on Twitter. Uh this feels like just an
options dealers. Um just the hedge
continually taking place. Uh I wouldn't
want to be trying to short against this.
We've had enough opportunities for
shorts to take control and they failed
to take control and that that is the
truth of the matter. Um so we're opening
up squeezing up. Delta looks strong.
Everything drifting higher right now. Uh
all of the MAG currently green other
than Apple and it's about to go red to
green. So big old squeeze out to start
the day. So again, that pre-market
flush, nothing more than a trap by the
looks of it. And through previous day
high we go. And this thing is off to the
races. I mean, it's quite ridiculous,
isn't it, that they're getting away with
this same move every morning this week,
but they are.
So, three previous day high, you've got
globex high above you, right? This is
where we got pinned.
SPY absolutely ripping straight through
685. It's currently 68628. This thing is
absolutely ripping right now.
Squeezes on here and we're probably just
going to gun for this next box. And
again, there is no entry unless you
played pre-market down here. This
thing's in a hurry now to get sort 830s
by the looks of it. And we're just going
to have to let this thing settle down.
That's a big move off the open. 100
points in the first no 90 seconds.
I just want to let it settle here.
All of the mag nicely green.
Let's see if there's a pullback to get
involved with. Uh now that we're
starting to break out,
let's say if they're going to hold this
as potentially blue now. Is there a
pullback
that holds or do they just wash this
whole thing out after taking out
overnight high? This is the danger right
now. It moves so quick so violently
without any structure.
Got long from the bottom with one micro.
Nice one tone. Yeah, I mean it was the
same pre-market trap. The long was here
as soon as as soon as we reclaimed value
in PDC. That was your long. But I can't
join up here. So I need to see now if
they pull back and hold. The problem is
they've just taken out a lowhanging
fruit. So on the opening drive, they've
taken out a lowhanging fruit. So I'll be
waiting to see now. Can we get rid of
that? There we go. Can we pull back and
hold price above sort of that Asia high
or even into this blue box
and see what they do with it once we get
there.
Currently holding right now. We're not
even 5 minutes into the day. 2 minutes
in. So, I want to give this a bit of
time to shake out. This is an exuberant
market that's doing nothing but driving
higher right now.
Still think this wants to move higher.
Come on, Ninja. Can I move my charts?
Can we move some of these lines around?
No.
struggling to get through here at 70s.
It should just squeeze through at this
point. It's done all the hard work to be
quite honest. We should just go for a
scream, but it's struggling at the
moment.
It's held that pull back into GlobeEx.
It should just go for a scream up here
unless it wants to really rebalance
again. I'm not in anything, but I'm just
saying what I'm seeing right now.
was about to enter previous day value
high and missed it. Now I've heard all
the ICT traders on social about the
power of three sweep high. Yeah,
I mean all we did is the same thing
we've done all week, right? We we came
under value, we closed the gap, held pre
previous day point of control. It's just
the same levels as yesterday where we
found a bid, right? Just found a bid and
uh off to the races we go. And the key
thing for me is spies over that 85.
Um, I will be waiting here for a
pullback to see what we do. If we don't
hold it, then, you know, maybe we flush
back into the range. But my uh opinion
right now is we're showing that there's
no strong selling. The market just wants
to squeeze higher. It's successfully
done it this morning. I don't want to
buy the high. It might be a day where I
just missed the trade. And that's also
okay on a Friday if it doesn't want to
play bull. If it wants to be a bugger,
it can be a bugger.
I don't care. Be a bugger all you want,
market. I'm definitely not going to be
trapped. I had a go at the short
yesterday and cut it uh break even in
the afternoon and once I reviewed that
trade uh later in the day and saw the
delta, I just thought, why why did you
even bother? Why did you even bother,
Alex?
Nice, Rich. Yeah. Nice work, Richard.
You should be a payout now. I think I
did message you yesterday. Um, make sure
you DM me about Apex. I will pick that
up with them direct for you and make
sure you get paid out, buddy.
It's one of the advantages in uh having
a mentor which has a good relationship
with them. So, definitely send me all
the details. I will uh get that sorted
for you or I'll at least at the very
least get them to get in touch with you.
at the very least.
Okay, starting to see this come back to
repric. So, we have some imbalances
here. One here at 50, one at 40, one at
72,
and then one all the way down at 700.
So, let's see.
Definitely left a little bit of volume
trapped up here. I'm going to put this
on here.
Okay. I want to see if we can drift down
into this blue box and if we find a bid
there. Apple, by the way, is selling and
Nvidia is gone green to red. Just worth
noting, we have just taken out all the
lowhanging fruit. The only thing left to
aim for now are these stops up here. We
have just taken out a ton of lowhanging
fruit, which is what I don't want to be
long at the high of day. What I'm going
to need to see is some form of bear
trap. Something like this, right? For me
to risk off to get involved in
because I don't want to just long here
and get caught in one nasty flush
because remember this was straight up.
We have no volume in here, no structure.
So, I need to see some form of trap if
I'm going to join in.
Not in a hurry. Not in a rush. It's been
a decent week on what I would say is a
fairly tricky rotational week. I'm not
in a hurry
to give back my money to this market on
a Friday. It's already reclaimed. There
we are stuck inside that volume again
though. This level here starting to
develop.
Right. So we're building out
volume here right now. Can you get
deleted? Yeah. I don't think that's a
strong high. So I think there's a good
chance we will break out and make a new
high here. We'll just have to see.
There we go.
failed to break out or did they just
take the high? Oh, they did just take
the high there in actual fact.
Still liquidity up at 90. I'd be careful
because we're trading inside this like
developing profile. They did just take
that high there without too much of a
shove up. They should be shoving this up
right now. They've got the ability to do
it. If there's a passive seller here
that could get caught in a bit of a
wash.
So, they got stuck there again. They've
had two attempts.
Delta still pretty good.
Where do they keep getting stuck? 75 is
an interesting level.
No breakout there on the spiders. Sorry,
I'm just watching across the board here.
If you see me rolling my head around,
I'm just looking to try and see what's
going on.
Apple's trying to find a bid. Nvidia's
trying to find a bid. Feels very
dangerous up here right now.
feel like they want to squeeze, but
there's a passive seller up here at 80
and 90. So, they keep getting stuck.
There you go. Stuck there again.
Do they leave this volume trapped and
come all the way back down? I mean, they
could. They absolutely could.
holding the edge of that range. What's
that range there? 42s is the edge of
value for the day. If they lose value
for the day, this could get very nasty
very quickly, I'd say. So, just be
careful.
That previous day higher testing
previous day high here.
Be careful. Be careful.
They're losing it. They're starting to
lose a bid here. They need to come in
now, otherwise they're going to get
caught. All these bulls at the top.
So, they're retesting value and they're
losing that bid up there. They might be
in trouble here, these bulls.
We're about to find out, I think.
Nvidia selling, by the way, folks. So,
that's dragging the market. And those uh
high gamma names are also selling the
ones we talked about pre-market. They
are also selling here.
There you go. All the way back down to V
up here.
So, leaving that volume trapped back
down to VWOP. Do they catch a bid here?
If not, the same thing uh will keep
applying. Rinse, repeat,
and we can go right back into the range.
It'll be a fail breakout right back into
the range. And there'd be well,
absolutely nothing we can do with it if
we do that to be quite honest.
God, what a terrible, boring market. Not
really offering a re-short, not offering
a long, not offering anything.
Yeah, Nvidia might drag the market down,
but we're not seeing a roll with the
rest of the market. So, it's just one of
those where it's like a
what what are you going to do with this?
There's no retest here. We've left. We
we poked. We did do a fail breakout. We
poked and we're coming back down to what
can still be bid off. It's just really
ugly, folks. It's really really ugly.
And like maybe they sell this whole
thing off, but you're not going to catch
me trying to force a way in.
Tape has gone heavy, but there's been no
retrace to sell into.
Delta's very heavy. There's just no
retrace though. There's nothing to sell
into.
It's a lack of structure and that's what
we're seeing in this market. One side to
the other side with no structure
back to that New York open. If we flush
New York open, maybe there's a short,
but it's very risky to get short under
here at that point because you you'd
have to risk all the way back up to
750s. We've not retested this level up
here. We've not done this drive up here.
And this can still hold this blue box.
We It's not like we've done this to
sell. All right. All we've done is chop
chop chop. Oh, we flush down to repric.
How we act up here is what's going to be
important. And we're not really doing
much to get up there right now. So,
let's see.
And if they reclaim it, like I said,
that would be the sort of bear trap,
which
could potentially be interesting.
stuck at VWAP now. Not retesting that
high yet.
Stuck at the up again.
Starting to see some follow through
here.
It just feels like no man's land to me,
folks. I'm going to be honest with you.
It feels like the last few days,
we haven't retested this volume. We're
stuck at the edge of this blue box. They
can hold this if they want. I'm
interested if we see some follow through
on the tape, but uh you know, we've had
the chance to set a lower high there and
reject 19s. It just depends whether they
actually want to do that or not. I lack
any conviction that they're actually
going to do that right now.
VIX is trying to find a bid, but it's
not through that 1519 level. So,
I don't have any conviction here for a
move lower at this point. And we're
still above that New York open. We've
just repriced the squeeze and if they
want to go all the way back up, they
will go all the way back up. That's what
they've done the last few days. Here you
go. So, they're starting to go all the
way back. There's literally nothing to
do with this market. This is screaming,
"Leave it the [\h__\h] alone." Honestly,
that's what this market's screaming
right now. It's telling you
it's unfortunate, but that's what this
market's screaming. It's just a trap.
Yeah, I feel the same coupe. I'm
watching this just like what's the
point?
You want to understand what this is?
Flush, rebid, huge squeeze, reprice. Now
you're in no man's land. What you going
to do with this? We're still holding
blue box. We haven't retested this.
There's no short. And if we come all the
way up there, you've got to say that's a
resqueeze with a higher low, haven't
you?
Like
What the [\h__\h] are you going to do, man?
What are you going to do with it?
This is their game right now. All the
way back up you go.
So, testing this volume at the high.
Now, if you don't react there, then
you're going to slice right through it.
And I'm not convinced high days in. So
this is why I just at the moment it's
just a loan.
And again, I just think this is options
dealers. I don't think this is anything
else. And that that worries me when
you've got a market where it's just
being dictated by options. If you look
at that last flush down on SPY, did we
ever get back into 85? No, we held above
85. So they've just moved gamma up from
80 to 82 to 85. And that's the play. So
now really it's about do you lose this?
Can I get this on?
It's about this, right? That's all that
matters. How do we act into that?
That's your game. You want to know the
game being played? That's the game. And
I don't think necessarily the high is in
right now. I just think this is uh
it's just going to keep rotating, folks.
That's what this market wants to do.
I don't care that the options uh volume
today is small. What I care about is
that they've moved gamma up and we're
above it. That's all that matters. Uh
the volume all week has been small and
they've just moved it up, right? So
I the volume's tiny this week. We went
over that right at the beginning. If you
look at the volume this week, no,
there's no players. Like, it's like
there's no one here, but we went over
it.
It's declining volume on an uprising
move. This is bad. It's a bad bad look.
It's what we talked about right at the
start of the day.
There's nothing
we can do with this, folks. I'm sorry. I
can't make the market move properly.
We've talked about it all week. If we're
not going to get PA, we're not going to
get PA. It's uh it's what it is.
I'm feeling the same. I'm getting ready
to go back to bed and shut the stream
down because I'm not going to watch this
on a Friday. This is what we're going to
do.
be another no trade day. Think I've had
one scalp yesterday, one break even, and
nothing today. And uh I will, like I've
said, I've said it in Discord, I will do
this all month. If they want to play
these stupid games, then they can do it.
I am not going to participate. They can
do this as long as they want. I've got
[\h__\h] all interest
in playing stupid games where they're
doing this move premarket every day.
Slam
down, squeeze up, slam down, squeeze up,
you know, with no structure. Look at
this [\h__\h] man. Every [\h__\h] day they
are doing this same thing. This is not
structure. Slam down, squeeze up. Slam
down, squeeze up. Slam down, squeeze up,
grind, grind, grind, slam down, squeeze
up. We're probably going to see the same
thing. It is literally been carbon copy
every day this week. Every single day
this week, we've had a carbon copy.
Yeah. 10 10:00 can move can move it.
You're right. You're absolutely right.
just so bored of this [\h__\h] man.
Is anyone else like really bored of it?
I'm so bored. Look at Look, just look at
these moves.
Back for the highs then.
What's the [\h__\h] What is the point
anymore? What is the point in this
market in December?
Yeah, exactly. Exactly. That's exactly
it.
Oh my god.
There it goes.
How'd New York open? Squeeze all the way
back up. Probably break out now after
doing some absolute stupidity.
I just got no interest now. Like I know
we should now come up here, but I've
just lost interest in the market. It's
put me off so much the last few days by
doing these.
It's like what what what we going to do
now? Join here like you going to join
against that? No. You giving much
structure here? No. Is it going to come
up here? Yeah.
But all they wanted was 685 spy. That's
all this was about. This whole thing was
about 685 spy. That's all it was about.
It's so [\h__\h] dumb.
It's so dumb.
I can't stop coughing. There you go. So,
squeeze, resqueeze up. Now, this is your
target if you're in this. I just know
I'm not trading today. I'm just so done
with this.
So done with it.
stupid. Just stupid.
Hopefully next week's better.
It's annoying because I'd love to
actually participate in some of this,
but I just don't like how they're moving
it, man.
Just feels way too dangerous for me to
put risk on. So, into your 800s, your
next target is this up here. Uh 8 83.
Let's call it 835.
49 bucks away from paying from passing
TPT. My first prop and I'm trying not to
do something stupid yet. Just uh don't
do something stupid. If you're if you're
s if you're in this trade, if you took
this dip here or you found a way to get
in here, I don't think they've really
had any structure, but uh if you're in
this, just make sure you know you don't
want price to come back below this shelf
that we just developed here. All right,
it needs to hold that. Price needs to
hold that.
that that would be my advice anyway.
You'd need to see price hold that
So let's come back to it. So this is
your level. It needs to hold this. Now
failing to hold this level would mean
another failed breakout. So this dip
here needs to hold for you guys.
So, I'm just replying to emails because
I've lost all uh interest
from the Apex account. I won last week.
I passed 1,500 degree on PA closing
taking my first payout. Hey, nice work.
Nice work.
Is the Apex website back up and running
now? That's the other thing I haven't
looked at.
news coming here in 3 minutes, maybe
afternoon news. We see what we get.
So I am to reply.
So many emails here for people applying
for that um indicator, the free one that
I've missed. Sorry if that's you on
stream. I'm getting back round to you
all now.
So, you're still holding that dip for
now. Just remember, you've got news
coming. The book might start to thin out
and you've got some bids down here way,
way lower into uh sort of 70s, 60s, and
50s. So, just be aware of that.
Market's gone to sleep now.
Here comes the news. Then they're trying
to get up for this liquidity up here.
This is your TP up here if you get into
it.
Absolutely. Your TP if you get into
that.
Yeah, PCE.
Just waiting for this print to see it.
It's delayed. I can't see it. Checking
the news.
Anyone got it yet? I've not got it.
Here we go. Michigan's out.
Better than expected on Michigan, but
only just. But that's not what we're
really looking for. We're looking for
that PC print. Here we go. Consumer
spending uh exactly in line. Personal
income apparently a little bit better
but pretty much in line. 5-year
inflation a little bit cooler from
Michigan
consumption zero.
So zero. So under what they thought on
consumption PCE 0.2 forecast is
everything's in line folks.
Everything's in line. Nothing we can do
with it. should be priced in. That being
the case
priced in.
Yeah. I mean, if you're long, you're
still okay to be long. There's nothing
to say to get out right now.
It's just on a drift higher now.
Video trying to find a bid. Still red
half% down. Apple 0.08% down, but trying
to find a bid. Rest of the market looks
okay.
Not making a high hit here high high
here yet on deltas. There's no strong
buying up here yet. Might it might start
to come though.
Might start to come.
This is the liquidity it's aiming for.
But you're into supply now.
you are into supply now. So it's really
depends if they can take out all this
liquidity. The edge of the old previous
week value would be up at 900. That
would be the ultimate target if it can
get there.
stuck at this supply. So, first test of
supply getting stuck. Like I said, your
location to be a buyer right now is
[\h__\h] awful. They've done it on
purpose. Your best location was
pre-market. They've given us nothing.
Maybe maybe a turnaround here, but very
risky off that VWOP, but that's that's
the turnaround. I wouldn't want to
really be a buyer up here, but if you're
a continuation trader, this is your
trade. This is your first tap into
supply. If you can get through this
liquidity here and here, but as you get
into this, this gets thick. This is our
first time coming into it. This is the
the weekly supply all the way back from
Monday the 3rd of November, so about six
weeks ago now.
Oh, my ninja's now frozen.
Come on.
Few days in a row. I might have to take
off some of the stuff on here.
You've got a feeling it's going to drop.
Well, I mean, it's nothing more than a
feeling. I would say you need to ignore
feelings and do what the charts are
saying.
still come out for this liquidity. So,
here's your first grab. There's your TP1
into here above this 900s. All right. If
it keeps going, 900s will be its target.
If it keeps going
So, liquidity tagged. Sorry, I've like
I'm not even watching. That's how little
I'm interested in this. I don't want to
short it and I'm not going to long up
here. So, I'm just sort of sat still
right now.
It's one of those where
if I don't see what I want to see, it's
uh
it's not of interest to me.
there's nothing to do. Any big lots
above? Uh, not really.
Not really.
It still looks like it wants to squeeze
more, but uh you know, it's got that
little We've taken it once here. I mean,
maybe we trade through it again. 900 is
probably the target at the moment, but
it's just like,
how are you going to buy this up here?
What's upset? I think what the reason
I'm is why do they have to keep doing
this premarket? Why do this move
premarket? They're such [\h__\h] doing
that pre-market. Like they won't let us
have it. And they have to do squeeze up
and dump down. I'm like, I'm not playing
that squeeze up and I'm not playing that
dump down. And then once we get to the
level of liquidity,
they don't give us an option here. They
have to break out and retest. You're
forcing me to buy the high of weak to
trade higher.
Like I just won't do it. I'd rather not
trade than do that.
Continuation to squeeze here. That's all
we're doing.
Delta looks good. Really good.
I'll grab a coffee here. Be right back.
Cuz this ain't moving for me.
All right. Are they there yet? Still,
they're trying to squeeze up to 900.
Delta still strong.
Uh Nvidia trying to go back red to
green. you'd be watching that um
previous day close on Nvidia and any
pullback now which holds sort of low 800
is 900 is very very clearly the target
here folks
but you are in a squeeze
four micros long at 798 uh you're
looking really good so you should have
pulled some off into 833s and then 900's
the next uh target so hopefully you get
it buddy
uh no I will not consider a short at 900
um
you know if structure shows it sure but
this is all about we're in a you got to
understand that this market uh all it
wants to do is go higher at the moment
for whatever reason their intentions are
just to take this higher on low volume
and there's no strong selling now if we
if structure changes and we start seeing
this market you know rolling over or
aggressively running through a load of
stops and turning
Yeah, but of course, but like all all
levels are are those they're they're
levels, right? They're just levels.
They're nothing more than levels. What
matters is how we react into a level. If
you got short at 900 cuz you like that
level and this market continues
screaming and then goes for 25,000 and
all the way up into this block, you're
going to get butt hurt, aren't you? So,
it it's it's more about, you know, if we
do something like this, okay, I'd
consider it, but what's the trend on the
day? trends up again after what? Two,
you got to think about this. Two traps.
There's your first trap. There's your
second trap. They want to move higher.
And so, so anything that holds this is
going to continue to move higher. All
they want to do is move higher for
whatever reasons. I've talked about it
extensively on socials. All they want to
do is move higher.
We're just printing higher highs, higher
lows, higher highs, higher lows. and and
anything that's not that is a trap for
them to absorb
No, I don't trade gold.
Let's see if there's a pullback here,
whether they hold this old wick here or
come all the way down here. But you can
see this is developing as like
we're thick here on the profile,
but we have quite a few nuggets here.
This is never nice when they do this
because you never know which one they're
going to hold. So, it's kind of like
them to develop a bit more volume at
this point.
I don't think they're done with it yet.
Don't think they're done with it yet.
I think any pullback probably gets
absorbed. If it's a nasty pullback,
probably even more of a trap to be
absorbed. That would be my guess on what
their intentions are right now. But
I said I don't I don't like buying a
high of weak to trade higher
the the trade don't please don't move
that the trade this morning was
pre-market that was the entry for me I
would say this morning some of you took
this I did talk about this entry but I'm
not like I don't want to take that entry
but you know unfortunately they built
this above it would have been really
nice if they were kind and built it here
so we could have at least had a bit
cheaper but this entry here was decent
and this is your trend up now. So maybe
a pull back into here,
but certainly it's too too high in the
day for me to uh think about doing much
with
So, I'd say you'd be looking if you're
still in this long.
Let's get rid of this. Clean this up.
Hello. There we go. If you're still in
this long, you're looking for up here
into 900. That's your next target,
right? 900's your next target. And then
if you get through that, uh, we have got
another block all the way up here above
25,000. So I'd say 25,000 uh, sorry,
26,000 whole number and then 26,80.
First time we've seen a bit of selling
up here.
Still don't think it's done. Still think
any pullback probably gets absorbed.
VIX has just found a bid. It's first bid
on the day, but
I don't know.
Nice, John. Yeah. So, you were in
pre-market 648. Uh,
yeah, you were in premarket. Really not.
I mean, that was the trade like we
talked about. That was the trade for you
guys. This buy, here's your signal
screaming buy. All right, there's the
previous day PC gap fill previous day
value high. As soon as we reclaim that,
that's your buy and then we're off to
the races. That's the smart money buyers
down there. Absolutely.
Oh,
get rid of that. We're going to need it.
Thanks, John. Appreciate it, my friend.
All right, so current value on the day
is 8:14. So, I'd say bulls will want to
sort of protect that 814ish.
They won't want it trading back into
value for the day. They want to start
moving value up if they're going to
complete a rotation. So, that's what
they're going to want. Nvidia couldn't
go red to green. It tried and failed.
Rest of the market's all green. VIX is
starting to push. Uh, I'd be slightly
concerned with what they're going to do
with the options. If VIX starts breaking
out through the New York open, I'd be
slightly concerned because we're going
to start having huge divergences if it
does that. Let me just check that this
is on the right thing. - 5.
Yeah, I'd be concerned because if SPY is
not pulling back and VIX is starting to
like trade back upside, it's a bit
weird. And again, I would just maintain
I think this whole market is just option
dealers at the moment and it's going to
make it very hard to pull the trigger
doing anything when we're just being run
by zero DTE.
That's the market we've got and we can't
change it. So, we're leaving volume
trapped at this high. Again, the
question is, do we hold value? This
level here is becoming important.
Current value on the session for me on
Ninja Trader is 8:14. So yeah, around
here bulls will want to hold around here
basically. If they can't,
maybe you get a deeper wash. I'd say
bulls will be looking to do something
like this at the moment.
So, how we act at this volume above now
is about to become key, folks. So, this
uh 50s, how we acting to 50s is key. If
they reject 50s, you might get the start
of a rollover. If they reclaim it, then
I would say this was a trap that we
talked about and we're probably going to
go higher, which is what you're starting
to see. So, they're starting to reclaim
it.
So if you're going to get this and then
I think you get 900s, right? So that's
why I said it's a very bullish day right
now. It's a squeeze out.
So through the 50s or into the 50s, if
they get through 60s,
they should come and trade up. If they
get through 60, 60s is where all the
sellers came in.
Yeah, 60 all the way up to 65 is where
the sellers came in. So bulls need to
hold 50s and reclaim 60s. And if they
get through 60s, there's a drive up. If
they reject this volume here, I mean, I
guess you could reject the top of the
range, which would be slightly odd.
If we reject this, then maybe a rotation
back down into search for some of the
structure. If they get through this,
then obviously more upside.
That's a good point, Willer. Uh, let me
have a look where we're at.
Yeah.
So, 6869
spy key through that alltime high.
You're not far away. You're not far
away. You're really not far away, are
you? Crazy.
Just seems like uh
market makers want their Christmas
bonuses. These hedge funds like we need
our Christmas bonuses. They've gobbled
everything up.
Yeah, no worries, Adam.
failing to get through this volume at
the moment for bulls. So, it's starting
to get a bit care. I'd be a bit careful
up here. If you were long from down
here, make sure you've taken some
profit. You should be trying to get up
here into the 900s, but you'd want to
see a push and a push soon. A push soon.
A push soon.
A push soon. If they don't get a push
soon, they're going to get trapped up
here. You definitely don't want to be a
new money buyer up here. That's for
sure.
not seeing that acceleration up here.
We've just had a higher high on delta
without seeing a higher high on the
market. So, I'm slightly concerned that
there's a passive seller now starting to
absorb here for you guys who are long.
You want to see this market break out
and it's got to do it soon. If it
doesn't do it, you're going to get a
deeper roll over because you're starting
to build quite a lot of volume up here
in this gray box. So, if you don't see a
breakout soon, I'd be very concerned
because it means there's a passive
seller is now protecting 60s.
Once you bust through 60s, you'll get a
pop. But if you can't do that,
you've got delta divergence with price
and that's problematic.
And we can see he came they came flying
in at 60 and you you have not been able
to get back into there yet.
You're having another attempt here and
you're getting stuck. I'd be slightly
concerned here for you guys who are
long. You're starting to get stuck.
VIX still
starting to move back upside trying to
get back to its New York open. Be
careful folks. This is uh got a few
danger signs going here. You made a
higher high on delta, not a higher high
on price. You're stuck at 60 through 60.
I absolutely think you can pump. But at
the moment,
you've got a passive seller here. 60 70
75. They keep selling and you haven't
even got through the 60 to test those 70
and 75s yet. Structure is bullish, but
wouldn't be surprised if they need to
swipe it down before they do anything
else. So, just be careful.
Manage your positions accordingly. I'm
still flat on the day doing absolute
bugger all. PC now moved up here. Oh, I
don't like seeing that. You've traded
here so for so long now. This is being
considered fair value. You want to be
careful here.
Now fair value up here. We're not seeing
price move higher. You're seeing delta
divergence start to play out. I'd be
very very very careful at this point.
They've had numerous attempts to move it
higher and they're not able to.
Where did that big cluster come in? 30s
and 800s. Okay.
You're starting to lose it. Delta
divergence playing out. You didn't
reclaim that grade box. You're rejecting
the grade box. We're going to can
possibly trade all the way down here. We
lack structure really. There are a lot
of nodes here, but uh if they want to
drift all the way down, they will
absolutely do that. If they're
exhausted,
they will do that.
VIX back to that New York open.
Honestly, mate, this is not a good look
what you're seeing in the market.
You're not seeing spy at New York Open.
This is uh you got major divergence
starting to play out. Again, it's just
options dealers. That's all this is.
This is why I don't like these markets.
It's really shifted this market from the
last week of November. I'd say the feel
of this market has really shifted in how
we're moving. It's becoming less and
less technical and more and more about
just gamma levels. Uh we're not taking
liquidity. We're just doing, you know,
one move straight one way, then stop,
and then one move straight the other
way. It feels uh Yeah, it feels bizarre.
Doesn't feel
uh normal is not the right word, but it
doesn't feel like the market we've had
all year. Feels like there's been a
major major shift.
I'd still say that gray box above you is
key. You've now got point of control,
the red line there. So, that's fair
value on the day. If you can't get back
above that, there's going to be no more
effort to move higher.
So, where's value on the day? 14s. So,
like I said, 14s will be the level bulls
won't want to see it below. If we go
back below that, you're back inside and
we can trade all the way down to 73.
Might sound ridiculous, but that's what
the market's showing.
Here
we go. They're going to test these 14s
today.
It's just rejected New York open.
You need uh Nvidia to go red to green.
That will really help you guys who are
long
and you're not seeing that yet. Still a
third of a percent down. Relative
weakness in Nvidia. It's not going to
help. Biggest stock in the world. It's
not been able to go red to green.
Doesn't mean it can't. It's just at the
moment it hasn't been able to. It's had
a had a couple attempts at PDC and not
managed to do it.
Starting to see lower lows and lower
highs here. Unless you reclaim this gray
box, be very, very careful. Hopefully,
they can do it for you. But just be
smart.
I want this to get through the gray box
and PC for you guys because then you can
get a squeeze out, which would be really
nice. Didn't quite get to 14s.
still looks like it wants to be bullish,
but it's this level up here which is
key. And see where we've trapped. We've
never been able to get back through
this. That's your level. That's your
over under right now.
Retesting it again. Be very careful if
they fail here.
This is them poking up to see if there's
any more juice. You've made another
higher high on uh delta without making a
higher high on price. It's another delta
divergence here. Yet again, it means
there's a passive seller up here because
it means that you're aggressively buying
without the ability to move higher. So,
we know that there's passive selling
here because Delta's coming in strong by
side and it's not getting follow
through.
It's a retesting point of control on the
day. This is your level, folks. This
level you're banging into
50s and 60s. You need to reclaim that if
you're still long and that will open up
a squeeze to 900s. So, here's the
attempt to get through it. Here's the
attempt of 60s. Like we've talked about,
if you get through this, you should make
a new high of day. Get through this, you
should make a new high of day.
They've got liquidity there to search
for.
You just want to see one like nice swipe
higher for you guys and you'll be good.
No close above 60. Still
still looks good. Now
this is the level. This 60 is the level.
Top of that gray box.
Still no close above 60. You keep
getting stuck at 60.
VIX just turned around and made a new
low. low of day. How How can it do that
in like one minute that I've turned
around from New York Open? [\h__\h]
dealers, mate.
Oh my god.
It just whit lowered down. Turn inside
Vicks. That is awful. That is an awful
look. Yeah. Initial balance now set.
You're trading inside IB. You haven't
poked outside of it. I think you will
break outside of IB. It's just whether
they need to do a trap first. You're now
trading back at point of control. But
this top of this gray box is the level,
right? Get through this. I think you get
a swipe up here. If you can get through
this box here, all right, they've got
stops here. If you get through this, you
should see a swipe there. What you don't
want to see is a move back under and
then you're opening up all this because
you've got a double bottom down here. My
bias would now be potential move up into
here. But they've got to get through
this box. If they keep failing 60, it's
going to be a major problem for the
market.
Spy just made a new high day there.
You've got divergence here as well with
ES and SPY. I think with ES, let me just
double check. Yes. So, just be aware of
that as well. You have some divergence
here. ES and Spy made a new high day. NQ
did not. Nvidia is going to have another
go at going red to green here, folks.
So, this is key. Can Nvidia go red to
green? If the answer is yes,
then uh video goes green on the day. You
might see a bit of influx on buying.
Very very close now. 0.07% down. It just
needs like a one one decent push and it
will do it. And then you might get your
swipe if you're lucky.
0.05. It's It's trying. It's really
trying here on Nvidia.
They cannot get through PDC yet on
Nvidia. They are they are trying. If
they do it, then you should swipe 60 and
get up to uh top of that red box. This
red box is the next liquidity for
still not done it. You're still failing
60.
New lower day on VIX. Market not making
new high day yet.
video still can't get through his gap
bill. Very, very, very close, but it
can't do it. I can show you.
There's your level.
All right. It's been the level the whole
time. It can't get through it. If it
fails here, look what it's open to. If
it fails here after one, two, three is
open to a wash. They need to reclaim
this. This is your problem in the
market. The whole market is watching
this guy right now. Hopefully, it goes
for you. But that's what you're
watching.
That is basically your 60 level, which
you've been unable to break through all
morning.
back beneath the shelf now, which is a
problem.
Another higher high on Delta on the 5m
minute. This is looking really
dangerous, guys.
I think you're going to be open to a big
big wash here. If Nvidia can't go and go
soon, you're open to a very big wash
out.
You got VIX at lower day, SPY is not
breaking out through high of day. You
can't get over 60 and Nvidia can't get
through its PDC. Those are the levels.
As soon as that changes, the market
changes sentiment. But that is what's
happening at the at the moment. And I
don't like that you've just lost this up
here. You've lost 50. You had the chance
here. You've had one. You've had three
goes at it. Obviously, you've had once,
twice, three times to do this move here
and it's starting to fail. I wouldn't
say it's a short yet because you've not
left it, but it's worth noting that you
are unable to do this move. That's what
the market's telling you. Video now
moving away from PDC.
VIX found a bid at lower day. This is
like so many warning signs in this
market right now. You know what's going
to happen? It's probably going to do the
complete opposite of what it should.
Yeah, you've had divergence with CBD.
Yeah. If you look at CVD, you made a
higher high on price on uh on CBD and
not higher high
on price.
Same with ES. ES made a higher high. ENQ
did not. So you got warning signs going
off. You're leaving that shelf now.
Look, you never got back over 60.
So 14s will be the level. And they Well,
actually, they won't now. They've
shifted it. So I would say it can come
all the way down to 786 now and below.
And that is very, very possible.
And the way we built volume out is not
very nice.
Yeah, I'd say yeah, can we can come down
to 770s. If it loses this, we can come
right down because of how we built
volume.
Bit of a vacuum in here. So maybe you
could argue
a little bit higher 780s.
Yeah, it's very It looks very dangerous
to me. Very very dangerous.
Still no reclaim. You can't get You're
not even getting back into 50s now. Not
even 40s.
Here's your box. You're starting to get
boxed in here. All right. Think about
how many buyers are trying and trying
and trying. They need this and they need
it soon. If you snap this, that is very
very open.
I wouldn't be short yet either, by the
way. For me, you're you're probably, as
long as you're managing your long from
wherever you took it here, you're okay.
But you don't want to see this crack. If
you see it crack, it needs to reclaim it
instantly for a trap. Otherwise, that
rotation's going to happen because
you've just shifted point of control up
here. And everyone's buying this up here
looking for that. And if they don't get
it, they're going to be in trouble.
Nvidia is moving further and further
away from PDC now. It's failed that
shelf again and now is moving downside.
It's not a good look for the market
seeing that when you got your number one
name moving the opposite way and VIX is
now drifting back up to uh New York open
again. Again, I'm just going to repeat
what I've said all morning. This is an
options dealers right now. It's got [\h__\h]
all to do with anything else. They don't
care about anything else other than
these options levels. For some reason, I
can't tell you why, but for whatever
reason, they are dictating the market
right now.
Very careful. If you lose this, you're
very thin. You can swipe all the way
down here.
And video selling.
Be very careful. Those of you who were
long, hopefully you've locked in. I'd be
very, very careful about this. Just
absolutely dumping right now.
There you go.
No, there's no one absorbing the book
right now. Buying's been aggressive and
they haven't moved higher. It's the
other way around at the moment.
that changes, I'll let you know. But
I think you're about to see potentially
a swipe and dump here
right into this new edge. They're just
building out more volume in it.
Last chance saloon, I'd say these balls.
SPY's
just got that look where if it doesn't
hold, it's going to go to VWAP
instantly.
I think you're about to lose bid here.
Nvidia now half a percent down. That's
your problem. Your number one stock in
the world can't get back through. It's
not just a PDC. It's a massive level for
it. They can't get back through it.
They need that sentiment to change and
you're not seeing it. It's relative
weakness. This is your last chance to
lose this yellow line for the Bulls.
I'm going to get a refill of my coffee
here.
taking a blast.
All right, you've lost yellow line.
You're in a problem here, Bulls. If they
can't reclaim that yellow line, that's
the shelf that they built out a new
shelf. So that's sort of 820. They need
to reclaim it otherwise it's game over.
This is uh these basically lows here.
You're starting to see
rejection here. Delta here was higher.
So you've got passive seller up here
selling into it. And this is now your
level. You've broken down under it. If
they keep getting stuck here, this is
going to happen. It doesn't look very
good. It does not look good for you
bulls. Now tone has shifted in the last
few minutes. So if you can't reclaim,
you probably should already be out
unless you're managing a position from
down here or something. But and even
then you should have taken a lot of
profit. But you are very susceptible to
a wash back that back to VW up.
And it can happen fast because we're
thin. We are very thin here. Look at
this. This can happen in one swipe.
There you go. So, here comes the swipe.
Good night, market. Back down to B and
now. See if they trap here and then
reabsorb.
Can we go lower? I mean,
I'm going to just say something, guys.
What
do you not listen to yourselves and
think, "What a weird question.
Can we go lower? Can we go higher?"
What am I going to say? No. Yeah, of
course we [\h__\h] can. It can do
whatever it wants. It's a weird thing to
like say.
Of course we can. The market can do
whatever it wants. Of course it can go
lower. Of course it can go higher. It
can do whatever it wants. Oh, it's so
weird when people say that.
Can we go lower?
Yeah. Can we go higher? Yeah. Can we go
nowhere? Yeah.
Of course.
Okay. So, we just did that wash back
into it. Well, towards this gray box.
Didn't quite make it yet. So, these are
your levels now. Trade between these.
Reclaim this. Bullish. Fail. This rot
rotation to this next box.
It's so weird, man. Like, it's so weird.
I'm going to just adjust this red box
because it's looking a bit [\h__\h] now. So,
let's just change this
No.
What do you want me to say on ES? Can
you guys not identify these? I think
they're fairly obvious.
There you go. There are your levels.
There's your gap which is standing out
like a sore thumb right now.
All right. There are your levels on the
S.
That's it. Simple, isn't it?
Not hard, folks. Don't over complicate
it.
Well, this was a [\h__\h] day. There's
[\h__\h] nothing to do.
Guarantee you we close the day higher
after they're done [\h__\h] around with
this again.
Yeah, it's been a [\h__\h] [\h__\h] week of
price action. Two [\h__\h] weeks of price
action to be honest. We weren't here for
one of it, but it's just it's just crap.
This is crap.
Like, you need [\h__\h] balls of steel in
this market. You need to be the the guy
that's like ignoring what's actually
happening. and just go, "Yeah, [\h__\h] it.
I'm bidding here, mate. Yeah, yeah, [\h__\h]
it. I'm bidding here." That's what you
need. Yeah, I'm bidding against every
flush. Right. And at some point, you're
going to do that. It's going to go,
"Fuck you." And take you out. And that's
the that's the problem. You can pretty
much throw technicals out the window on
the flushes at the moment.
I think that's wise Troy. I think that I
think what you've just said is wise.
Like you took the short from the
breakdown of volume to VWAP. Didn't even
we didn't even make VWAP, you know,
which is stupid in itself. And you've
covered. I think that's the right thing
to do. Yeah. Can we go high from here?
Yeah. Exactly. No.
All I know is the daily looks like the
biggest piece of [\h__\h] I've ever seen.
What the [\h__\h] is that?
What the [\h__\h] is that? Get out of here,
mate. This is the most crooked market
ever. You don't believe me? Let Let me
just remind you of what's happened here.
Let me just remind you of it. Oh, no.
Don't move that
nonsensical move up on holiday week. Uh,
what day was it? Was it Tuesday or
Wednesday? It might have been this day
here. Uh, fake news. Was it Microsoft
fake news? Yeah, only joking. We lied
about that. Who's gone to jail for that
market manipulation? No one. No one said
a [\h__\h] word about it. We're just
going to lie about something and take it
higher, are we? Like, hello. Hello,
hedge funds being naughty naughty. Okay,
so this is all they've done. Then
yesterday fake drop. today fake drop
just to run higher on a low low squeeze
out, low volume squeeze out. This is uh
I'm not messing with these guys. I'm
like I just said to my wife next door,
I'm going to stay flat in my swing
account and I'm probably not going to
actively trade until we get to January
because my feeling is if they're
actually going to be as dumb as to do
this, retail's going to come flying in
here and then you're just going to see
that in January, right? And I'll tell
you why I'm saying that. Because it
happens every [\h__\h] time they're
stupid enough to do this move to get
their Christmas bonuses. If they do the
move
in December, we get the move back from
January to March. If they do the move
in December, we get the move back
January to March. If they do the move,
where's December?
There we go. They do the move in
December. We get the move back. January
and March. It's the same thing every
year that they do it. If they do it at
Christmas, here you go.
December, January, March. All right. So,
I'm very aware of this. This is if they
do a Santa Claus rally in December, they
always always give it back. All right.
If we don't, then I'm more open to
January and March having a better push
push back up for a continuation. But if
they're going to be stupid and this is
all about, hey, where is my Christmas
bonus? I need to get paid. I'm [\h__\h] it.
They can get paid by themselves. I'm not
going to bugger around with them.
Oh my gosh, look at this.
Yes, is stronger. Yeah. Well, why why
isn't that breadth, isn't it?
Brethren in the market.
market's too thin for me to have uh
an interest in it.
You got to understand, guys, like how
we're operating. Like, what is this?
What is this? What the [\h__\h] is that?
Where's the structure?
Like, stuck, stuck, stuck, stuck, stuck.
I said if if we if we lose this, it's
going to flush. Boom. All the way back
to here. What are you going to do now?
What how are you going to bid off this?
Who's got the bollocks to bid off this?
Probably only hedge funds. All right. At
some point that stops working. This is
the problem with the market. We're on a
Friday. Like, no, no,
no. I'm all right, thanks. I'm just let
these guys do whatever the hell it is
that they want to do.
It's just uh weird.
a weird market right now. It's it's
beyond
what I would call normal.
There's a lack of volume. There's a lack
of structure. It is all about the trap
and not about anything else.
Yeah, I know. Adam. Well,
I just look at that and go like, what
what do you want me to do with it?
There's just too many there's too many
fighting things right now, right? Like
the hourly's broken out. So, you know,
if we pull back and hold a base here,
technically it's still bullish, isn't
it? Right. It's a breakout and retest,
but like I'm not bidding on that after
seeing that up there. And this is what I
mean. We're just not seeing alignment.
There's no alignment in this market.
Look at this. Every breakout sold, sold,
sold, sold, sold. But bears then come
in. Do we see a breakdown under a key
level? No. We've never seen it. Every
opportunity they've had, we've never
seen it. Maybe next week they do that.
But I doubt it because at the moment,
all this market's saying to me is every
pullback is a bear trap to go higher.
This is probably the same. It's probably
the same thing. They don't have
intentions on taking this lower um as in
like higher time frame lower at the
moment. But you can see they left this
volume. You couldn't get through 60. I
kept telling you divergence up there. If
you crack this, there's a move back down
into this block here. You're losing this
block here. We're going to move all the
way down into this RBS, which is a
higher time frame RBS zone. Now, if you
lose that and we go under New York open,
we're going to go guess where back into
previous days value. All this is telling
me is we're rejecting outside of value
again.
Are you joking? Lines, mate.
Proof of consistency. Okay. Well,
I don't I hardly even post these in
here, but
where are they? Last week. What did I
take out last week? There you go. That
was last week.
Um,
when was the last time I posted? Another
withdrawal there. When was that? From
the week before.
One of my students, number two in
Traify.
Another one there. Another 2,000.
Another one there. Another one there.
This enough. Another one here. I even
post it on the videos when I'm talking
about the prop firms. Another one here.
105 days. Another one here.
Another one here.
Another one here. Here are some more. We
at a year yet? Not even anywhere near.
This is only into August.
Here.
Is that enough?
Do you need more here?
here. These are all the people that
[\h__\h] question me all the time. Here,
like, and I've stopped posting because
it's just it gets stupid for my
students. It would make you like push
too hard. Here, there's another one.
Here, here's another one.
All right. Is that consistency enough?
Here. These are all payouts, by the way.
These are here. We're back to May now.
Here. You asked for a year. I can keep
going. Do we get the point? I think
there's consistency there.
Yeah.
Yeah. It's there. It's there, guys. It's
there. I don't [\h__\h] post about it all
the time because I like it's not going
to help your trading, but I get it. You
want to know does someone actually win.
I understand.
Yeah. When you're in the Discord, I
normally, you know, I post it if it's if
it's of value. I I like posting my
losers more in Discord than I like
posting my winners because it actually
helps people see. Like yesterday, I took
a a break even. I'd rather talk about
those trades in managing risk than, you
know, winning days.
Where's the Lambo? Yeah, no Lambo.
No Lambo. I don't know what I don't know
what to do with my investments right
now. Honestly, I'm
with what's happened in the UK, I really
want to sell up. I really want to sell
up in the UK. Okay, you're starting to
see a bid on this RBS. Remember, this is
what we just talked about.
This can be like a hold of the hourly.
This is the problem right now, folks.
So, everyone's come flying in short
because you've seen this here, but this
can still hold. And this is what we've
done time and time again. This is why
I'm like on a Friday, do I really want
to play these levels, right? This is
technically resistance now because
you're under it. Okay, right here. This
is the problem. Your alignment is an
issue. Right? If they trade back through
this, remember how thin we are here?
Thin we are here. If we trade back
through this, guess where we're going to
go? Right back to this line again. And
then it's going to be like, hey bears,
do you remember what we talked about?
The bulls that are winning are the ones
with massive bollocks right now who are
willing to bid on this. That's not me.
My balls aren't big enough to do that
against momentum. But if we come back up
here, you got to ask, are the bears
going to defend this level? Cuz if the
answer is no, we're going to make a new
high. So bears have two levels here to
defend. This red block here
and put this in for you so you can see
it. And this block here, right? That's
where they need to defend. But this is a
higher time frame RBS. And that's the
problem that you've got in the market.
Now, if we trade under this, I will tell
you now, if we trade under this, we
build liquidity here and we fail, we're
going to come back for previous days
value. These must be cover points. If we
trade under value, maybe we come back
here. Do I still think we have
unfinished business lower? Yeah, I think
we've got unfinished business at Where's
that low?
Where's that awful low that we've left
three times now? Where are you?
It's here, isn't it? Is it this one?
200s. What do we No, it's here. Sorry.
420s. I don't think we do that today.
But my sentiment will shift if we start
taking that out and staying heavy. Then
I think we get a rotation into the old
week's range. I don't think you see that
today. We're on a Friday. But for the
future weeks ahead, that's going to be
the sentiment shift to bearish. But
we'll talk about that in the newsletter.
Prop firm payouts are consistency would
understand if you show
trades or my effects books. I think
nowadays that prop payout makes you
profitable trader. Uh I I don't use
trade zella or my effects books. I've
just showed you all the way back to May
of prop firm payouts. You can go and see
my consistency on videos that I po post
up. Um, I understand your concern, but
if you've just turned up and you're
questioning it, don't do the course. I
don't need your money. It's fine. Like,
it's up it's up to you. That's not me
being arrogant, but like,
I give you so much for free. You're here
for free. You get the newsletter for
free. Everything's for free. If you
don't want to pay, don't [\h__\h] pay. I
don't care. Like
I've just shown you like six months and
you're still questioning all my videos.
Every video about a prop firm when I
talk about prop firm shows me passing
and taking money out. Unlike all these
other guys who just sell you stuff.
It it makes no difference to me, my
friend. Like it's okay if you don't
trust me, you don't want to do the
course, don't do it. Um but I don't need
to do anything for you. I don't know who
you are.
How do I get the newsletter? It's free
in chat. If you just scroll up, there'll
be a link there. Or if you go to the uh
the
uh what do you call it? Smart link or
whatever it is. It's on there.
By the way, I would also say like even
if I was the most inconsistent trader
ever and I've never taken a payout or
any of those things, even if I was just
absolutely dreadful.
Um, sorry. What did I give you here?
What did we talk about here? What did we
talk about here? What did we talk about
here? I've given it all,
but question me all like all you want.
So, we're trapped between these two
levels now. Higher time frame
RBS,
lower time frame, volume shelf. You're
back inside the opening 15 minutes. And
this is now going to flip. If we're here
much longer, we're going to flip this uh
point of control down here.
Does funded legacy show profit? What's
funded legacy? Oh, are you talking about
uh
funded next? Yeah, end of day. I don't
think it changes to end of day. I think
the only ones that I know that change
intraday I don't know if Lucid does. Um
I think Funed
Tix does
think
I think Funded Tick does think that
might be the only one
though.
Catching up with some news here. Let's
see what's been actually said.
The seven talks.
Is there another CL cloud player outage
or is that an old one that they're
talking Oh,
volume on the right. CQG subscription to
trade. Uh well, I pay for CME data on uh
Trading View and I pay uh for the pro
account, so I don't actually know, but I
would imagine Yeah. I mean, all all this
is is anchored volume profile. I think
as long as you've got a pro account and
as long as you're linked into CME data,
whether that be through a prop account
or paying for it, I think if you pay for
it, it's like eight bucks a month on
Trading View, uh you'll be able to get
that data.
Vicks Vick's starting to try and break
out here, folks. It's got a little bit
of a gap fill above.
Where is that line?
1590 to 16. 1590. Big big level on VIX.
All right. So, that's kind of the base
that we based out on. Vixed and we lost
uh overnight. We've peaked back above
it. We've come back under it. We're
trading back into it again.
[\h__\h] is going on here with my hours?
What? What? What?
There we go.
Where's the spiders?
May very well come and check that uh 685
again on spy.
May very well come and check that again
at gamma level.
Yours is showing profit after the trade
on the account.
Henrik, do you mean when you're logged?
Do you mean on the back end of uh
of the website? Is that what you're
talking about? Would I take a long here?
No.
No. This this is what I'm saying is the
problem with the market. Momentum
shifted, right? We're in strong sell
momentum. Is it a possible good
location? Location's possibly good. It's
possibly good, but your momentum isn't.
And this is how the market's operating.
This is what they've been doing. So
really, until you see this, I wouldn't
think about getting long. And even then,
it's going to be really tricky with how
they built this out. There's a reason
they're building it out like this. It's
to make it really hard. Like, you know,
is the location better? Yeah, it's an
RBS zone, but are you making have you
shifted in any way at all? Has sentiment
changed? No.
This can still dive deeper if it wants
until you get a shift.
Delta is sort of flattened out.
There's still someone trying to bid down
at 700. So with size as well. So let's
see.
There was one today, but I didn't see
anything affected by it. Oh, that's the
cloud player thing. Yeah, I didn't I
didn't even know there was one. I just
see the news come out on it.
Volume is trash. Yeah, volume's been
trash for two weeks.
It's been trash for two weeks. I I
agree.
Crazy
jump on gold. Is it we seeing rotation
out the market again?
Yep. BTC probably seeing the same. Yep.
Honestly, I just keep saying it's just
it's a dealer's market at the moment.
They're just going edge to edge, edge to
edge, edge to edge, edge to edge. These
are not markets I enjoy trading in.
Oh, like honestly I'll happily wait till
January. It's absolutely fine. I'm
pretty exhausted from the year as it is.
It's been a decent year. Have I
underperformed? Definitely. I'd say
where I've underperformed the most is my
swing accounts. Waiting to get long with
good size forever this year in the swing
accounts and it's just not come into a
level where I felt comfortable bidding
on the market. And I think a lot of
people feel the same way. And I would
say that's a big reason why we're
squeezing up end of year because I think
hedge funds haven't made their bonuses.
They're probably way way short of where
they need to be because they didn't get
into the market at the right time. Same
as me. Everyone waited for that pullback
post April which never came. And
consequently, they're sat sitting on
cash. And that's not good if they want
to get bonuses. So wouldn't surprise me
if this whole thing the last two weeks
or three weeks now has been about
manipulating price so they can size in
for the move
lines mane [\h__\h] off then
[\h__\h] off then mate
because I'm not promoting anything I
haven't talked about my course you
[\h__\h] have. I haven't talked about
anything. I've been here talking about
price action. You're [\h__\h] talking
about it. So, don't buy it. I don't
[\h__\h] care. It makes no [\h__\h]
difference. Why are you here then? Why
are you here?
We make this really easy. [\h__\h] off to PW
and everyone who sells you [\h__\h] You
don't get to be here to learn from me. I
have not sold you anything. This is
easy. You're done.
[\h__\h] over these people. See you,
mate.
I've not sh I've not [\h__\h] sold
anything. I haven't talked about
anything all day long other than price.
So now you're banned from the channel
and you don't get anything.
[\h__\h] done, man.
I'm thinking about buying your course,
but uh I don't know if you're fleecing
me. I haven't [\h__\h] told you anything.
How am I fleecing you?
It doesn't matter even if it does get to
me. I'm not trading. I'm not trading
this [\h__\h] today.
But like like good luck. Like who you
going to go and learn from? Who are you
going to go and learn from? I love that
you're going to go and watch some other
guy who's sat there actually fleecing
you all day long.
I literally never talk about my course.
Yeah, I have. I've earned the right to
sell what I want like anyone has in
life. But the funny thing is I'm not
here actually selling anything. I'm sat
here talking about price action.
What's the [\h__\h] point, mate? This
world's [\h__\h] It's got people like
that in it.
Doesn't even cost you anything to be
here. You can be here and not do the
course and not use any of my codes. I
don't care. That's also fine. But what
you're not going to do is sit there and
[\h__\h] try and abuse me. Like, suck a
nut.
All right, coming all the way down to
this New York open now. All right, and
if we lose this, so technically we're
inside an initial balance day. If they
want to complete a rotation today, they
can do this. If we lose IB, like I said,
I wouldn't be long here. Someone asked,
would I be long here? I said the
momentum is heavy. If they lose IB,
where are they going to come? Well,
here's your previous day value. All
right, so this is yesterday's tight
balance range. This is what we held in
the pre-market. We held yesterday's
value. Now, we got stuck up here. We
couldn't get over those 60s. Obviously,
I was selling you the course up here
instead of telling you, you know, that
you had delta divergence and that
there's a passive seller and that if you
can't move through 60s, it's going to be
a problem. But no, I didn't tell you
that. I was selling you a course. Okay?
And then you failed here and you washed
to where? Right. Right. To VW up where
we said we'd fail to. And if you don't
catch a bid here, we keep selling. One
of you asked about getting long and for
free I told you no because momentum is
still heavy. Now we're coming down to
New York open. If we lose that we will
come and gut check yesterday's value
where we found a bid this morning. Now
if we lose yesterday's value it's a
whole different ballgame. I wouldn't
expect this market to go in free-for-all
but we can say that you never know what
happens in this market. Someone said can
we go lower? Can we go higher? I laugh
because of course we can. We can do
whatever they want to do with it. This
is what I keep trying to get into you
guys. Market will do whatever it wants
to do.
But you know, I obviously made you lot
pay lots of money to learn these trades
and see them in front of you. You know,
please please give me all your money.
That's what I've said all morning.
[\h__\h] hell, mate.
Why do I bother?
I'll make sure when I come here Monday,
all I do is sell you stuff and I won't
teach anymore. And you can just sit
there and watch a couple squiggly lines
on a chart. Maybe I take the opening
range breakout on a guest for 30 seconds
and you can watch that. And then maybe
we just talk about a couple squiggly
lines on a chart all day and we ignore
all price and uh maybe I just try and
sell you my course all day long and sell
you codes all day long and then I'll be
like everyone else.
What a world we live in where this is
how it is.
Vic starting to test that 15196
level again. I [\h__\h] made you pay for
that level. I told I told you I'm not
telling you that level unless you give
me all your money.
Jesus Christ, man.
We talked about this
All right, we talked about this level
here. This shelf
right here.
This is the shelf that it lost. This is
what's key. Now, VIX reclaims this and
does one of these, this will push the
market lower, right? As in the S&P will
start rotating lower.
The other level I told you to watch out
on spy,
delta level,
gamma level
five, right? Right here.
This level here is key. This is their
gamma level. Positive gamma above it. If
they lose this, where's the rotation?
It's to 82. That's the next level. All
right. So, the rotation, if they lose
it, is at 82. So if they look below and
fail, then we come right back up and
they will want to complete it probably
all the way to 90. Doesn't have to be
today, but that's what they're trading
between two.
Again,
price alerts on spy 85 8280. We talked
about it. Lower expectations of price.
I know, Jose, but
you wouldn't you wouldn't you just
wouldn't believe the amount of [\h__\h]
that I get on a daily basis. Like, I've
got someone commenting right now on my
volume profile saying, "You don't
mention your settings on the number of
row sizes." where I know for a [\h__\h]
fact I say in the video it's a thousand.
And this is what annoys me. It's just
like people they haven't got the
patience to go and watch the education
and then they question you where I know
the answer's in there.
It just drives me mad.
Okay. So, at the moment, they're trying
to protect New York open. That blue
line, the bottom blue line on your chart
is the New York Open.
That's the bottom blue line on your
chart.
Yeah, gold selling off. BTC's been
selling off. There was a big flush in
the market. Someone called it called
about it earlier. But again,
for me personally on a Friday with how
this market's operated the last 5 to 10
days, um I'm not too bothered. I'm not
too bothered about doing anything. From
what I've seen this morning, I would
have liked if this market had been very
kind to us and it had waited and done
this off the opening drive, I would have
thought about a bid off previous day's
value because I knew we built lots
there. But we didn't. We we opened up
went straight squeeze gave the whole
thing back and then went straight upside
and the next buying opportunity was up
here and that is buying the high of week
and I'm not buying a high of week on a
Friday. I will not do it.
So there we go. It's a no trade day and
that's all right.
No, nothing. No, I've literally done
zero. Absolutely zero.
absolutely zero
to the point where I've closed Ninja
Trader down. That's how uninterested I
am.
What brokerage would I recommend for?
What
are you just tra Are you just trading
futures or are you trading you know
stocks and swing swinging stocks and
other assets?
I would say it dep it depends on that.
If you're just trading futures, probably
AMP or something like that. If you're
going to look beyond futures, um, and
you're going to start playing like the
ETFs and some stocks and things like
that, I would look at things like, um,
oh,
why is my brain not working? Trade
Station. Sorry, I had to get my head in
gear. I would look at things like Trade
Station. I would look at uh if you want
something cost effective, you can always
go the retail route um things like 212
and and Weeble and stuff like that. But
I'd say if you want a professional
setup, yeah, things like Trade Station.
Um if you're going to focus more on
stocks like um
I don't know who the big players are
anymore. Um IB maybe um
Think or Swim. Yeah, is Think or Swim
still good? TDM trade? I don't know. I
hear I hear mixed things. It used to be
very good back in the day. It used to be
the one to go to that and Trade Zero for
small caps. I used to trade on Trade
Zero and I used to swing on Trade
Station. All my stuff now I do on um
Trading 212 for my big swings.
Um because being from the UK, they are
very tax efficient for me. But it all
depends
all depends what you're looking at like
in terms of what what products and what
kind of trades you're going to take. If
you're looking to like sw like to take
swing trades on commons, then what I
would say is you just want something
where you're not paying a lot for a
round trip. Um, that's probably the best
thing. So, probably I would say Think or
Swim probably is still good for that.
Um, I know Think or Swim also have good
option chains. Well, at least they used
to. I haven't looked at it for a long
time. Charting used to be really good
there and then everyone moved to Trading
View.
It used to be the go-to for charts.
It used to annoy me because I couldn't
get it when I was uh from the UK. I
couldn't get it. Canadian based, isn't
it? TDM Trade.
Love that, Jeff. I love that, Jeff.
Congrats, mate. Nice work.
Nice work.
All right. So, so far you're protecting.
Where's this low? All right. You've got
delta divergence here. So, we have
positive delta from here to here. All
right. So, Delta made a higher high
here. So, we've got aggressive buying
starting to take place here. All right.
We have aggressive buying starting to
take place here. No doubt about it.
Right? Because we made a higher high on
cumulative delta. If I have a look at
the footprint,
where did that strong selling coming in?
Yeah, they got absorbed. So, we saw
strong selling at 706s, 696,
and definitely 692 and under. And that
all got absorbed and we're starting to
trade upside. So, we had a bid come back
in over 700. So, let's just see. But,
you've got point of control. Like I
said, point of control will flip from
here to here because we spent a long
time. It's what you're starting to see
this here. It's going to get messy in
between this. This is this is the
battleground now. Right in here right
now. If bulls reclaim that, there's
potential for a squeeze high. There's no
doubt about it. But that's what they've
done the last few days. Maybe they don't
do it on a Friday.
Took the rejection from VIX. Nice. Yeah,
it just failed 16s, didn't it? We just
talked about it. That trade up to 16s.
Yeah, I don't I don't blame. That's how
I feel. That's why I'm not trading it.
I've got zero trust in this market.
Zero trust in this market. What I know
is like just based on the daily. Where's
your screen? Based on the daily,
right? If we're if we're doing this
drift up off this and everyone's like
low volume doesn't matter. Um, it does.
Yeah, it does. Because if there is a
reason for them to sell here, if they
find a reason to sell here and they sell
with high volume, right? High volume,
guess what's going to happen? Night
night. Because this there's not a lot in
here, folks. Any structure we're looking
at in here, we can see it's low volume.
If they sell a high volume day, um we
are going to give back most of this
move, right? Low volume, low volume, low
volume, low volume, low volume. If they
come in with a catalyst and a reason to
sell, big if. But if they do, we'll be
back down here in one day. In one day.
Because where are we? We're at 700. Do
you think it's that hard to get back to
sort of 200 500 point move? It's not
that hard, folks. It's It's not that
hard at all for them to do that. That is
my concern with the market here.
So I'd say now looking at this market,
bulls need to fend 715s just based on
what I'm seeing in the tape. 715s.
All right, they came flying in at 715s.
You have an imbalance from 7 720s to
715s. If bulls hold that, you can see a
rotation, right? This
kind of little nugget here, that's where
bulls need to defend. Failing to hold
this will just allow a swipe all the way
back down again. No position for me. I'm
definitely not putting a position on
today. Too rolled up. Too many people
pissing me off today.
It's the same thing that I'm seeing with
like people trying to say like RIPS is
trading paper. It's like the guy's
trading [\h__\h] 50 lots on NQ and gold.
Do you know how much size that is?
Do you know how much size that is? And
they're trying to say he's paper
trading. It's laughable. And he gets
animated and annoyed like I do when
people say stuff and then they try and
take the piss. It's like, dude, you have
no idea what you're talking about.
RIPs is a legit trader. He's trading
[\h__\h] ginormous size
um for a retail trader. He is retail.
We're all retail. He's trading massive
size on the book and you can see it when
he gets in. Anyone saying stuff is just
don't this is what I have to remind
myself. People on internet don't want
don't know what they're talking about.
Stupid don't know it's stupid.
All right. They didn't defend 15s here.
The only place left now is where those
sellers came in with size, which is uh
95 and under. 95 down to the 83. And
we're just going to go back into
rotation by the look of it here. And
we're probably going to do a dance from
to
720 until it makes a decision.
Uh Heath Heath Edger. Uh, no.
Zero chance.
Yeah, Rips has
Rips was up 320 grand on gold on earlier
this week and couldn't close out because
he had too much size on and CME couldn't
get his position out for him.
Legit. Anyone saying it wasn't him, like
he recorded the whole thing. It's It's
clearly him. everything matches and like
people are trying to battle with him
over it. Like he is a legit trader.
Whether you like his trading style or
not is completely irrelevant. He's
trading big size on the book
and he's up like 1.4 plus mil this year,
maybe even more.
That's it's probably peanuts to him
compared to what he wins at the casinos
to be quite honest.
Yeah, he's he just trades momentum and
order flow with size. And he's earned
that right, folks.
I remember him trading small caps way,
way back in the day when Atlas was king.
If anyone knows those times.
All right, more downside here. And if
you lose initial balance here, your
purple line, right, then previous day
value area high is very, very possible
all the way down into here, folks. All
right. And we might come and test that
VIX back through the 16s. Just be
careful now. All right. Like I said, if
VIX holds above 16, starts spiking, it's
going to be a problem for the market and
it's starting to go. All right. So, if
you were short in this, like I said, for
me, I would there's no long in this.
There's still momentum trading downside.
Here are your cover points. Uh this is a
big one here into 23. All right. That's
PDC and its current uh previous day
value area high. That will be a cover
point. If they if they start slicing
through, if for some reason they've
spent all week doing nonsense and they
go risk off today, then we have to think
about
I think it was that 200 level, wasn't
it? I've got to remind myself now back
way back here.
Where was that bottom?
Where was that? Yeah, this guy here.
420s, right? We have to remember 420s
big level. That's sentiment change. If
we get If we get it, it's a long way
away right now.
Should be night. Yeah, it might well be
night. Willow Williams, but
who knows, eh?
Who knows? Right, I'm going to use the
bathroom. Be back shortly.
All right.
All right. You're retesting current
value error low on a session now.
Let's have a look at this book.
Yeah, exactly. Who just said that? Uh
685. Willow Williams. That's it. That's
your level. All right. That's the level.
If you trade under 685, then um 682 is
possible.
That was the the level from the last few
days. All right. So 685 is that sort of
dealers level that they're trying to
hold.
again. You know, obviously you have to
pay the course to find out the level of
685 for me. Made that clear. I can't not
I'm going to tell you without you paying
me money. [\h__\h] me. That's still in my
head. It's just [\h__\h] madness.
Uh, I was going to do a giveaway today,
but I'm I'm at this point just so riled
up. But yeah, we'll we'll do a giveaway.
We'll do a giveaway at lunch. We'll do
another 20 minutes, right? And then
we'll do a giveaway for you guys.
I think that's fair.
You know, you you can only get the Apex
giveaway if you're giving me all your
money first.
Oh,
[\h__\h] me. I don't know how celebs deal
with anything.
All
right, you're starting to see it try and
reclaim current range for value on the
day. You're starting to see a little bit
of reaction from spy. It's a little bit
early, I would say, but it's trying.
It's trying to find a reaction there. Oh
god.
There's a sell side imbalance. They want
to trade all the way out to 720s at the
moment. They can they can come up there.
That's where uh they last came in.
Or was that New York open 80s?
and they need to get a close under 80s
and under IB. If you if you do get a
close under those, then I think there's
a chance to move lower here back to
value. But at the moment, it really
depends how they operate. Here's the
move back down to IB. And I think if you
start to see sellside pressure come in
underneath this, I think you get quite a
nasty wash to be quite honest with you.
big if, but that that's what the if is.
That is what the if is. If they can
close under IB, I think you can
potentially get a wash back down to
here.
This is a sensitive area. You wouldn't
want to be a new money short, but like
if they start rejecting this and they
rotate, then if some of you are already
short,
no, I'll uh we'll do a like a just a
draw in 30 minutes. I'll just give you a
word that you write into chat and then
we'll do a draw for it. It just be
selected by random.
It's trying to get to 685. Yeah. Uh spy.
Well, it's it's there or thereabouts.
You know, they might protect it. If you
were short, you'd be covering into this.
And if they're going to hold it, they're
going to start accumulating in and
around here. If SPY fails that, it's got
a gap filled to 68440. And then uh
previous day high 683
um or 68360s.
And if we wash 682 that's the gamma
level. If they wash it
wants to retest PDH
on this. What is going on with my timing
on here? Yeah. Uh 1618 is the level to
watch on VIX. 1618. Break through that
uh you suddenly get room up to the
1656s.
That's the level on Vick. So if if it
keeps bidding above 16 market like we
might need a pull back on VIX back
towards the 16 but if it keeps bid
bidding above it and breaks through 1618
then the market's going to get heavy.
But you know we are at a sensitive
level. Look we're at value for the day.
We're at initial balance. We've swept
the low already. This might want to turn
inside and test this little pocket here.
Right. We said like 1720. We've got a
sellside imbalance. If it wants to come
up here it can. How it acts there then
becomes key. Remember, it's always about
how it acts when it gets to a level.
Definitely wouldn't be long right now.
Market's still been heavy. It's not
shown that it wants to move upside yet.
Only thing I would say is there's been
aggressive buying. All the time we've
been down here, there's been aggressive
buying
because you're not seeing lower lows on
the CBD.
Seeing the opposite. You are seeing
aggressive buying here. There is
divergence down here, but we just have
to see what happens. It mean for me it
means that there's a hidden seller
walking it down trying to move it lower
for now. That's what it means for me.
But we'll see.
Is that in balance? I said, "Oh, we're
at 1720."
17 17 720 1720 720. Here we go. Here's
the lift up to 7 and 720 is the top of
that imbalance. So, how they up there
becomes key. SPY already back through
its New York open
and VIX coming back down to that 16s
that we just talked about. So, I have to
see if VIX can form a higher low here or
not. I still think there's potentially a
hidden seller here trying to walk price
down. But, uh, we will see.
We will see. If market starts breaking
out, it'll get trapped. I still think
price wants to probably move lower. It's
just whether it needs a shove up first.
We've been in a sell
ever since we put in that rotation
formation up here, right? Ever since we
had the delta divergence here, we had
this here and delta was doing this,
which means we had a passive seller
because you had aggressive buying,
failed to move higher, that six uh 860
was the level. Soon as you lost this
shelf, we talked about if you fail to
hold that, you're going to wash. There's
the wash. And since then, it's just been
a walk down, right? If shorts get
trapped here, yeah, sure, we might see
some relief, but I wouldn't really be
long until you get well above this. Now,
market's in a rotation. We've been in a
rotation the whole time. Is this a
higher time frame RBS? Yeah, but we're
trading the lower side of it. Uh
momentum's been heavy. So, you know,
maybe they come up to here and then
wash. Maybe they just fail already. I'll
watch the tape and try and call it for
you. But, uh it's been fairly thin
volume wise.
Fix finding a bid at 16 like we just
talked about. Again, give me all your
money because I gave you a level. Make
sure you give me all your money.
That's never going to get boring for me
saying that. Now,
I'd say uh 720 is the level that bears
will need to to defend. 720. If they
don't defend that, they're opening
themselves up. 720s, I would say, is the
level
in this pocket.
If we drift, well,
IB2 maybe, but I wouldn't be playing
that right now.
Big starting to lose 16s here. It can
still hold a bid on that level which was
sort of 90ish.
defended the edge of this. Like I said,
1720 is where they have to defend. They
didn't even allow it into that little
gap. They defended the edge of this
right here.
It's a good defend from Bears.
Oh, stop being an [\h__\h] Honestly,
so so far you're not seeing any follow
through underneath 85 on the spy. All
right.
If you see follow through under there,
there is a flush moment probably to fill
the gap. We haven't filled the gap in
the New York session yet to PDC. And if
they get under there, then I'd be
watching 82s. But we are Bears are still
in control. Like I said, look, here's
the defend. Look how simple volume makes
this for you. There's the defend. They
could have let it come all the way up
here. That's what I was saying. As long
as they defend 820s, there's potential
for this rotation. And but you're going
to have to watch the spiders.
That is that
previous day New York open.
Sorry, I'm just having to check a level
there.
Why is it easier? It's not that it's
easier. It's that when it comes to
options, the biggest traded market is
the spy.
So, I'm just using that as a guide. I I
hate doing it, Aani, if I'm honest.
Like, it's very rare that you'll hear me
talk about that. But because I know it's
that that's in control of the market, I
have to pay attention to it. That's all
it is. Normally, I wouldn't give
a rat's ass about it, but just because I
know that that is what's having such a
big impact in the market at the moment,
I'm giving it a little bit of respect.
Let's say, let me just close this door.
Wife just got home.
You'll give me $5 if I pass this combine
next trade. What? You're in a combine.
How much do you need to make?
Can't get below this initial balance.
This is the level, right? Bears need to
get underneath this or that wash. If
they can't do that, they must defend
this. If bulls reclaim this, squeeze out
as possible.
500. Oh, mate. Don't Don't force it.
Don't force it. It's nothing. One good
trade will get you there. Let let the
market funny around for a bit and trap
some participants and then you can uh
get involved.
Alex, that's dead on. SPX is a huge
market that pushes other markets around.
Yeah, exactly. Exactly.
So defending that level again bears for
now.
I just want to see if they lift and let
it through to 20s, but at the moment
they're not letting that through again
at all.
What's this alert going off?
Coinbase just telling me that crypto is
getting destroyed. Yeah. No [\h__\h]
So, still bears defending that level,
but still no follow through for them
yet.
We have seen like an increase in buying
delta start to step in on the tape
recently. But this this candle here is
going to be important this next five
minutes, I think.
Bull's defending 92 right now. That's
their level is 92.
92 to 85.
There are definitely shorts caught at
that low at 57.
The strong selling into 57. So they are
caught under under 57 right now. for the
bears.
Are they going to fill this guy up to
720?
Looks like they're going to try and get
into that little gap
we talked about. And I'd say this is the
area here to make for it to make a
decision. They're going to have to
defend here or hereabouts. They let it
through. Then we're going to go straight
to VWOP
at that key level now 1590s.
So I said this is your level 20s. If
they let it through here, there's a
squeeze potential to come straight up to
point of control, VWAPs, all these kind
of areas.
Bears will want to defend these 20s
here. And if they can't do that, they're
going to be in trouble.
And we're just going to be in an IB
rotation, aren't we? We've failed IB
high, failed IB low so far. That's all
we've done. Failed both sides.
Pretty lame.
What does that remind me of? Oh, every
day this week.
Every day this week.
Set the high and low early of the day
and then just grind it all back.
Right.
Almost at that 20 test. Have we done it
yet? There or thereabouts.
Right. And this is the level. They're
going to have to defend this bears.
Otherwise, we're going to start chomping
through up to 40s.
Now or never for you bears. If you don't
see this uh trade lower now, you're
going to be caught in a squeeze. I think
so there's the trade through the 20s. So
bear's not doing a very good job. So now
bulls will want to take it up to VWAP
and then up to 55 if they can.
Bank keeps pinging off here.
Big strong buying delta coming in here.
Oh, it's the same market again.
No follow through. Just going to stay
inside balance all day. It's just a
balance range market.
I see some news hitting the wire here.
What's this?
Oh, you got Trump talking.
Trump's talking, folks. Be aware of
that.
Well, [\h__\h] knows. All technicals go out
the window now that he's talking.
Who knows what he's going to say?
Probably cancel all tariffs and you're
back to highs in no time.
So there's your VWAP. So they didn't
defend 20s like we talked about. Then
you're going to get to VW up. There's
your VWAP.
Last chance saloon. Uh and if bears
can't defend this, then probably up to
these this next block here. And if they
get through that and the rotation's all
the way up to these 820s. All right. So
that's what you're looking at right now.
And did Spy get under 85? No. What did
we trade down to on spy? 85.
Literally traded down to 85. The gamma
level.
You know what I'm going to say? Should I
send my accounts? Should I put my
accounts in?
Buy the course. Buy the course. Buy the
course. Buy the course. Buy the course.
Give me your money. By the course, by
the course of course,
are we into lunch yet? Can I get out of
here for this week? Oh, can I just
leave?
Guess who's in control of the market?
It's the options dealers.
[\h__\h] couldn't have made it any
clearer.
This is why I'm not trading because the
option dealers are controlling the whole
market right now. Mad. I can't remember
a time where it was like this where it
was this. It was about just these levels
and these levels only. I cannot remember
that time. But that's what we've had
this week. 680 682 685 is just all we've
had.
Like I said, every single flush down, it
just gets gobbled up at the moment.
So, rotation IB to VWAP, bears have lost
all control right now. And if we get
above this red box, there is a giant
squeeze possible. And you have Trump
talking and you're into lunch. So, just
be aware.
If he's saying anything of interest,
we have meetings set up. After the
event, we will discuss trade. So there
you go. Trump saying he's going to
discuss trade with Canada and Mexico.
That will include tariffs. So there you
go.
Getting there, John. Yeah, getting
there. I made good impact on it
yesterday. So what I got done on the
course so far?
So far I've recorded
auction theory, volume profile, profile
shapings, developing profiles, bookm
and delta divergences. Uh the next thing
for me to do is footprint and then to
put all the setups together for you. So
there's probably two big modules left.
Can I explain what I mean by when the
option traders are in control? Yeah,
absolutely. All right. So, if you watch
the options chain,
where's my spy?
Right, if you watch the options chain,
right, this level here, this gray box,
right, was a call wall which became a
put wall. All right. What it means is
dealers don't want price to trade under
there. They don't want puts to come
under there. Before that, it was this
here. It was 82. It was actually the top
of this. All right. It was 82.
All right. This was the put. They didn't
want price to come under it. They've
saved it every time. So, they moved the
put from 82 to 80. Earlier in the week,
it was 680.
All right. Right here. All right. They
did not want price to come under this
because if price comes under this,
dealers lose. All right. and retail
options players win all the money. All
right. So, this is this is literally all
that's dictating this market right now.
80 82 85. That's it. That's what's
dictating this whole market. And I'm
serious. It's the whole market is dict
being dictated by these three levels at
the moment. It's why I'm like very very
skeptical on a Friday to think about
doing anything. But
I mean, look at the low. Look at the low
we just hit on spy.
8502.
It's just how it is. It's how it is,
folks. It's like it's why I've lost
interest in the market at the moment. Um
I'm not an options. I don't trade
options. I hate having to watch the
options, but I'm having to like at least
give it some attention after each
session to see where they're trading.
When do I say everything will be ready?
Didn't exactly what you said, but more
interested in your understanding.
When might when everything be ready for
the course? hopefully this side of the
year, but I lost two weeks to co so
I don't know.
Hopefully this side of the year if not
definitely for January.
I trade options and your strategies work
on options. This is my testimony. Yeah,
that's great. I mean, it should it
should work for everything. It's just
that you're going to have to pay
attention to like other levels.
How do I look at the options? Uh, you
have to check out something like
anything which is offering you
um the key gamma levels, the biggest
gamma levels traded. So you could use
men for Q, you could use Cheddar Flow,
you could use Tide with Unusual uh
whales, you could use uh is there one
called Wave or something like there's
there's loads. You could probably even
use it on on Trading View. Trading View
has a way of checking out the levels as
well, doesn't it? Or
uh
have a look find it.
options.
Where's that gone? You're going to show
it to me.
See where it is.
Never look at it on Trading View. Who
can tell me where it is on Trading View?
I thought it was at the bottom here.
Some of you use it. I know some of you
do.
Do I trade ICT concepts? Not really. I
mean, I pay like I I guess you could say
I pay attention to
what you would call S&T and I would call
divergence. And I guess you could say I
pay attention to what you would call
fair value gap and I would call an
imbalance. But you know, I would
be paying more attention to that
imbalance um
by using actual footprint,
right? Because you have a rough area.
I'd be able to see an actual area.
So,
yes and no. I guess I mean what you call
a breaker, I would just call an RBS,
you know. I don't know what else to say.
The wall icon on the lower right of TV.
The wall wall icon.
I don't see it. Maybe I have to.
Are you on the app? I'm on the app. I
don't see it. Screeners calendar. Where
is it? next to screen as calendar. Maybe
I have to make this bigger.
Maybe I have to go to something which
has an options chain available.
Let's suppose I had to trade here. Would
I buy or sell? Um,
I wouldn't do anything here at VWAP. Do
I have to do something here? Okay, let
me have a look.
Uh, I'd probably sell.
I'd sell. I'll show you why I'd sell.
Because I think you got a passive seller
on the book. Um, so,
all right,
we've got aggressive buyers trying to
break out. And if we pivot to here,
price is not moving higher. I think
you've got a passive seller on the
books. So, I'd sell. There you go. If I
had to do something, I would sell
because I think you've probably got a
passive seller on the book forcing price
lower at this point.
Do I think it's a good position to sell
from? No, I don't because structurally
we're starting to go back the other way.
But we just failed VWAP.
We failed this shelf. There's aggressive
buying and we're failing to move higher.
So, if I had to do something, I'd sell
because I think there's a passive seller
here. And if that passive seller absorbs
the whole tape, then everyone who's been
aggressive buying is going to be forced
to be a seller. And if we take out the
low, where are those sellers trapped
from? All right, there's sellers trapped
under 58. But if we start taking out
700s and think there's potential for a
move lower, but do I think it's an A+
trade? No, definitely not. But like if
you basically saying I have to flip a
coin and make a decision. That's what I
do.
Exactly. Troy,
the waffle icon on the lower right TV.
Waffle. Circle with dots.
Circle with dots. Circle. Oh yeah.
But then it's not bringing it up when I
click it.
What I want is to see the actual
exposure levels.
More on option. Won't open that up.
Maybe I need to reset this. Maybe that's
what it is.
Do I ever use MAC day or RSI? I don't.
I don't use Matt deal RSI. It you can
I'm not against using it, but like if
you were going to use it, I'd use it on
the higher time frames and I'd be
looking for divergences. So like if you
were going to use like RSI on a higher
time frame and
you could you could see a divergence
there. It would be interesting. VIX is
dumping. Not for me. It's just found a
bid. It's just found a bid off the New
York open. I I think you're behind. It's
trading at 1590.
I know, Phenom. I know. I know. But
it's easy to say, but when you wake up
to every day people saying stupid [\h__\h]
on videos or on Twitter or on your live
stream, it gets uh it gets pretty
tiring.
It gets pretty tiring eventually.
If it if it continues, I'll tell you
what, if it continues and it starts to
affect my trading, all that happens is
that I'll just trade for the guys in the
community and not anyone else.
Right. So, that's short at the moment.
Looks okayish.
Is reverse AMD a thing?
What? Uh, I don't know what you mean.
What do you mean reverse AMD?
into lunch here, folks. Think I'm going
to call it here. No trades for me today.
No trade day. It's all right. Is what it
is.
No trades during the stream. We'll see.
I don't think I'm going to even touch it
later. Come back Monday, see where we
close today. Um, I think there's some
weakness in the market at the moment,
though. Like I said, I think there's
been aggressive buying here and you
haven't moved higher. All right. So,
there was a bit of a squeeze out like we
talked about. If if the shorts lost lost
the 720s,
you'd see this squeeze out, but in this
big buying here, there's a passive
seller. So, they tried to move higher
and they failed. And they tried again
here and they failed. And they're trying
again. Now, you're going to need to see
this market break out. And if they can't
keep doing that, if you keep seeing
aggressive buying, which is what I'm
seeing, and thus not move higher, it
means there's a passive seller on this
book. And um if that passive seller is
able to hold price down and all these
buyers get trapped, right, and you get
this move under here, I would not rule
out this, right? I would not rule out
this for the rest of the day. Now, if we
get above here, yeah, absolutely squeeze
back out. This is just not a location
you really want to trade at around point
of control, right? This is the most
traded level of the day.
GG, you're looking for a liquidity
break. Yeah, you you might get it.
Again, like just set guys, it's really
easy. Set price at 685. If you get
continuation on SPY under 685, market
will start to bleed. Yeah. So, that can
be like not necessarily a trigger, but
it's like that will help with your
sentiment. Like one of you asked me what
I would do right now. I if I had to pick
if I had to pick a decision, I'd be
short right now only because I can see
these aggressive buyers are not getting
anywhere. That's the only reason. So if
I had to pick something, if you're like
gun to head, what would you do? I'd be
going short.
Von just said long 10. I mean, I've I've
told you what I think.
I think there's a
there's someone selling into your moves.
I don't think I know. I can see it.
There you go.
Pay me your money. Give me your money.
All right, I'm getting out of here.
I'm getting out of here. Uh, have a have
a good weekend, guys. Oh, it's funny.
Um,
I see I'll see you all on there next
week. Uh, trade safe. Just remember like
I talked about options dealers, you got
to watch this uh 685. If you double
bottom at 685 and find a bid, then
that'll be the end of it, right? That'll
be the end of it. And um, yeah, I'll
speak to you guys next week. Um, be safe
over the weekend. Enjoy your weekend.
Come on, Lando. Come on, Lando. And uh
Ah, thank you. Thank you. We did say
we'd do a giveaway. We did. We did. We
did. I forgot. Let's do a giveaway.
Let's do a giveaway. Yeah, I'm here
every day. Every day, Monday to Friday,
pre-market 9:15 New York time. Okay. We
go over what I'm looking at and why.
Let's do a giveaway.
Yes, you're right. You're right. You're
right. You're right. I know you're all
right. Okay,
some of you doing it already. I haven't
got it ready yet. Give me a second.
Okay, type FCT in chat. You only need to
type it once.
I'll give you guys a couple minutes.
Sorry folks.
So sell del sell delta starting to come
in here. So you're starting to see a few
aggressive sellers stepping in. Now I
would say if all these aggressive buyers
get flipped, they're going to get in
trouble.
Yeah. Every day, Evan. Every day.
Two more minutes, guys. If you haven't
typed it, just type it once in chat.
It's all you got to do.
Starting to see that selling.
All right, let's pull this winner.
Winner winner chicken dinner.
Henrik,
are you here? Henrik, let me know you're
here.
Let me know you're here.
Nice. All right, dude. Shoot me an email
info@flowzontrader.com.
I'll get you set up with a free Apex
account. All right, get you set up with
a free account.
info@flowzontrader.com.
Um, just make sure you send me a
screenshot uh of your YouTube so I can
see that this is you on your username
with you logged in.
You don't understand half what I'm
saying, but you can learn from me. Thank
you for what you're doing. Yeah, you're
welcome. The more you'll hear, the more
you understand.
More you hear, the more you will
understand. All right, team. That's it.
done for the day. We are out of here.
And uh be careful if you're going to
hang around on a Friday. As you get
closer and closer to the close, the
options are going to get more and more
wonky. Just be aware of that. And um
yeah, I'll see you all Monday.
On Monday, trade safe. Peace and love.
Be kind to each other. Use hard stops.
All that good stuff. Take care.