All right, morning team. Sorry, running
slightly behind here.
Let's get ourselves set up for the day.
Uh daily looking like it wants to break
out.
Uh it doesn't look good. I'm going to be
honest with you guys. Right. still not
even past holiday volume. All right,
this week has been awful. There's no
doubt about it. Uh we can't call it
anything other than that. It's very very
low volume. Uh every pullback has held.
Hasn't taken out any liquidity. Hasn't
put in a firm higher low down here. Is
in a straight drift higher. And this is
a very very dangerous pattern. All
right, it's very very very dangerous.
There's no two ways about it. I don't
care what anyone's saying. It's very
dangerous. If you buy up here, maybe you
get lucky and you get the squeeze. Just
as much chance the door gets slammed on
your face because we haven't set a firm
higher low. All right, we we're not
setting if we think about how we like to
move with structure. All right, sweeping
lows, protecting lows. All right,
firm pullback, breakout, hold, double
bottom, go with some pullbacks in
between. All right, that's nice bullish
structure. These are nice bullish
structure moves like big breakout, pull
back for multiple days, hold, build a
base, go. That's what we want to see as
a bull. All right, in a market. What we
don't want to see is a low volume drift
higher without ever coming back. I don't
care about this little white candle
here. 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9. Nine straight
days without any notable pullback on
terrible volume. It's dangerous. It's
dangerous. It's as simple as that. I
don't care what you're trading, what
product it is. This is dangerous. If
you're going to buy now, you're buying
near this pivot. You're buying near
probably the target. And what's your
risk going to be? Probably all the way
down here. So, it's not ideal. So, all
we can do is trade what's in front of
us. The market's showing its hand at the
moment. It's just been well, a bit of a
bit of a knob the last few days, and
that's what we've got. So we can only
only trade what's in front of us. All
right. Hourly. Let's have a look. So
yesterday, double bottom into that big
spy gamma level down here. All right. No
sweep. Protected this block here. Found
a bid and just like slow grind all the
way back up sideways
overnight just like we did yesterday
overnight. Exactly the same pattern. So,
we've got liquidity there to use, but
unfortunately about 15 20 minutes ago,
it just decided it was going to do a 100
point move and hit TP1. So, you know,
this is what I mean. Like on on no
volume, off absolutely thin air, we've
just gone and done TP1. So, if you're
going to buy this now, you better know
that one of your low hanging fruits has
gone and the only thing left right now
is 833 to aim for. And that is the
problem with the market at the moment.
It's it's being very silly doing these
moves. It's probably because there's a
lot of shorts caught cuz everyone knows
this is not a healthy market moving this
way. But what they don't understand is
you can keep guessing short all you
want, but until there's a breakdown and
a retest, there's no reason for it to go
lower. So, you've probably got shorts
trying and trying and trying and trying
and getting blown out. All right, the
target's very clear. TP1's just got
taken, which is this pivot from uh the
13th of November. TP2 is probably this
double top up here 832 and then if you
get lucky the edge of this old balance
range right we talked about this
numerous times now there's a twoe
balance range here we're starting to get
through some of it the very edge of it
will be into sort of 8.91 you might as
well call it 900 once we get into 900 if
we base here we're going to go for
alltime highs this is where we have one
more week's balanced range right which
we've rejected from these are the buyers
that have bought the alltime high and
got caught. It seems to me like it's
adamant on going up there right now. So,
we can't ignore that. All right, we
cannot ignore that. So, you know, we're
bullish on pullbacks. If they hold uh
you want to be very careful, though.
If we don't hold the top of this or the
bottom of this, we will collapse. All
right. So, this area in here becomes
absolutely key for sentiment for the
rest of the day. Bulls have got to hold
this. If they want to go on parade, it's
very simple. They have to hold this blue
box. If they fail to hold that blue box,
all it means is we're either going back
into range in here, which would be very
bad after a breakout, or we're going to
lose that range and come back for these
double bottoms down here, which would be
a failed breakout, a look above and
fail. So, we want to be aware of that,
right? That's those are the things that
we're looking at basically. Why has that
gone red? We don't want that. There we
go.
Okay, let's move up and uh have a look
at what's going on elsewhere.
Yes, same story. Me just zoom out on
this on a daily. Need to get Yeah, same
story. You can see what it's coming
into. We can move this up. I'd say this
is supply here right now. Starting to
get into it. Uh targets will be 93 and
basically the 900s through that alltime
highs. All right, that's what you're
looking at on ES these eyes in as well.
I just want to see if there's any
divergence to the spiders.
Are we gapping up through that? All
right. I know 850 is a big gamma level
or it was yesterday on the spiders. Um,
so we're going to have to watch that.
Where's SPX? Here we go. All right. So,
85 big gamma level. We're through it so
far. If they hold 85, then you expect
them to come and take these out. So,
there are some slight divergence here
with the spy. So, it's looking to take
that liquidity. Let's just call it 86
and then 8660.
Any hold above 85 is very, very bullish.
If it fails to hold 85, this is the old
gamma level all the way down here at 80,
which we failed to close under. I would
say this market is not bearish. I'm
going to repeat this. It is not bearish
until it gets a close, a break, and a
retest of this to stay heavy. This is
bullish range rotation. It's uh adamant
and holding this for whatever reason the
dealers want to hold that level. So, it
is what it is. Market makers do not want
this market rolling under 680. And it's
probably because they need to get their
holiday bonus because they haven't made
any money. So, that's where we're at.
The queue, same story. All right. Tons
of liquidity sat right here on the cues.
All right, that's your level.
Uh there will be gamma at 25, no doubt
about it. And then uh be looking for
mid 26 breakouts there on the cues.
Let's have a little look at Dixie still
falling off a cliff.
So double top played out. Interesting. I
just want to before we get into the mag
30 year, this is the dangerous part for
me. This is starting to base above this
green box which I've been talking about
for months and months and months on end.
All right, you can see from April where
the pivot came watching this carefully
to see how we react here. 10 year as
well.
I'd be somewhat concerned if these start
breaking out. All right, let's look at
the mag.
All right, flat on Apple. Building a
range.
Nothing to do here, folks. Break out of
the high. Didn't hold the pull back.
Back into a range. If it breaks down
underneath. If Apple lose loses 212s,
then you'll see weakness. But right now,
it's just in a range, opening flat. Oh,
that was AMD. What's going on? There we
go. Apple. Okay. Worse. That's actually
worse. Okay. Opening up slightly gap
down. There's the breakout. There's the
pullback. Lost this range here into a
new base here. So, you're watching
Apple. Apple needs to hold 8350
to 82s. If it loses 82s, we're going to
see weakness in the market. So, I'm
going to set a price alert there.
Amazon.
Same kind of story. It looks backside
now, doesn't it? Let's be honest. All
right. Big grind up. There's your
blowoff top. Fails to make a new high.
Has cracked underneath. That looks
backside to me, right? And so until
Amazon reclaims
uh 234, it is possible that it wants to
move deeper.
and try and see if it can find a bid
down here. I would say this is a bit
like the cues, right? Just a ridiculous
push without coming and back testing
anything. And this is what happens. You
leave a blowoff top and you have to come
back and check to see if you can put in
a higher low on a higher time frame. So
that's what I'd be watching. Maybe it
catches a bid in front of it and maybe
they do like a two-legg and go, but
right now I'd be saying it's bullish all
the time. It can stay above 28, but I'd
let this rotate back to it. If any of
you are looking to be long on Amazon,
Google
gap up there on Google starting to turn
the corner a little bit.
You can see this is potential
continuation here. If we can hold above
18s, it's got a move up there. Meta came
out positive news this morning and that
is a bit of a squeeze. I'm bit annoyed
I'm not sized in more in this
That is frustrating. I'm long from the
80s,
so it's not bad. I'm up uh 80 bucks, but
uh I'm not sized in. I'm up more than 80
bucks. Okay, we're into the old gap. I
might need to be thinking about taking
some profit soon. Wow, I'm up 100 bucks
on that a share. Okay,
I got there quicker than I thought. All
right, into the old gap here. So, I see
I'll probably sell some of Meta in here
and I'll see if we can close this gap.
That's a nice move this morning. Okay,
that's what got the market moving then.
All right, big gap up in Meta. Let's see
if it can hold into its old gap. Uh
Microsoft,
that's in no man's land. Nothing to do
there after yesterday. Needs to break
out of that range for anything to
happen. Nvidia is trying to get going,
but uh it's weak. All right, we compare
this to the rest of the mag.
There's your pin high over the 200s.
Can't sustain a bid. Pulls back into the
bottom side of the range. Tried to
reclaim it. Rejects. Bottom side of the
range. Tried to reclaim it. Rejects.
Breaks down under the range. Now just
trading sideways. All right. So really,
it's got to get back above sort of 95s.
If it can't do that, then there is a
range going to be created here. And if
we start losing this, you're going to
have all the balls up here trapped and
there's a breakdown. So bulls really
need to see a reclaim of 95s and 200s.
Failing to do that, I'd be somewhat
concerned because you're seeing relative
weakness in this name, right? So I
wouldn't be a new money buyer here. Like
if we start losing some of these levels,
there's a wash down before it gets uh
taken back up. But let's just see. I
don't know what the market wants to do
with this, but it's definitely weaker
than all the other names right now.
Tesla's still squeezing. It's on quite
the run right now. It's impressive out
of that pivot low. All right. So, it
failed to make a new high, breakdown,
double bottom, importantly reclaimed the
range. That's the big difference. And
squeezing back. So, it should it should
come all the way back to the top side of
the range now because this is a failed
look below and it should in theory it
might take some time, but it should try
and get back up to the top side of that
range. So, Tesla looking pretty bullish
there. I'm going to say pretty
impressive on a squeeze out. Let's have
a look at the mag. Equally weighted
overall. Yeah, meta doing the damage and
in a squeeze out.
All right, so most of them opening up
flat.
Most opening up flat. There's not a
whole lot to do here. I'm going to be
honest, folks. We've um want to be
bullish, but they're not giving us much
of a location to play with.
So, we want to see
I'm going to do this as a gray box
because I don't want to get uber bullish
here. Right, we've taken the liquidity.
This red line was that first liquidity
that I was looking for. Those in Discord
would have seen that yesterday. So, this
level has been taken. The only thing
left to aim for now is about 100 points
higher. That's what we'd be aiming for
if we're going to get going. So, we want
to see do we hold previous days value
area high for that rotation. If we fail
to hold that value, we're going to check
PC. If we fail PC, we're going to check
previous day value area low. If we come
to previous day value area low, we've
just lost the top side of that range
again. And then you're going to expect
it to come all the way down here. This
is why I want to be cautious. It's a
every day this week has been in balance
up where we are now. Right? So, they
need to hold a breakout above it.
Really, they need to be holding 80s.
It's as simple as that. If they don't
hold 80s, we go back into the death chop
range. Right? can see it here is uh
Tuesday here's Wednesday and we're
opening up there Thursday. All right.
So, you want to if you're bullish, you
really want to see them hold the top of
this box. That's what you're going to
want to see if if if you're if you're
uber bullish. If you're Mr. Bull today,
that's what you're going to want.
All right, let's make sure I'm set up
here.
Is there a new Apex sale? Is there?
Didn't see it. My bad. They probably
emailed. And here we go. Bella's just
messaged me. Just as you said that.
Just as you said that.
All right. Back into previous date value
area high.
They've got a website outage at Apex.
So, just be aware if if you're trying to
buy something and it's not going
through. She's just messaged me saying
they've got an outage.
Okay. So, already through previous day
value area high, not holding the top of
that range. That's not what I would want
to see if I was a bull. In fact, that's
quite the opposite. All right. Based on
Ninja Trader, however, value I've got
previous day value area high down at 60.
So, I'm going to respect that. That's
what Ninja Trader is saying to me. No,
it's not. That's wrong.
That is wrong. Move it up. It is at 80.
And just adjust these slightly. Give me
a second, folks.
Okay, so it's lost previous day's value
high. Back into yesterday's range. This
is the range I don't want to play in.
This gray box. I've got no interest in
trading in this gray box. Let's just
wait and see. Let's see what the mag's
doing.
Have a little look. See all of the mag
gapping up so far.
Meta the big winner. 3.77% up.
I'll be watching these 85s on SPY which
they're currently holding. So that's
your overunder.
That's your overunder on spy. Back to
VWAP
on this market and on the spiders
back that whole move.
Looks like a fail breakout to me so far.
Look at that. That whole move gone back.
So dumb. This is what I mean. It's a
dumb market right now. Very stupid
market how it's moving. There's no
volume. No one in control of this
market. It's just a bit of a whipsaw.
So I've lost interest the last week or
two in this market. I think it's very
very dangerous.
Fact that we took that liquidity
pre-market. Where's my mouse? All right.
The fact that we took this liquidity
premarket and bulls did not just hold
this is a big no no. All right. Here's
previous day point of control. If we
come back here and we fail this level,
then a rotation back down to here is
very, very possible. And if we lose
that, then we might as well go and take
that double bottom from yesterday. So
bulls really need to reclaim previous
day value. All right, that's what they
need to reclaim. They need to get back
above previous day value area high.
Otherwise, we're just in a chop zone,
which I refuse to trade. So, you refuse
to trade that.
Okay, just got an email from uh Take
Profit. So, their sale ends Sunday. So,
that 30% off with 100% of your uh money
back will end on Sunday. So, you've got
this week to get that sale.
Well, Apex, so 60% sale, but $6 PA fee.
Basically free.
It's really good, actually. Okay, there
you go. Failed to reclaim. Wow, this is
aggressive now.
Failed to reclaim and uh coming right
back down to the bottom side of this
range. And if we lose this, we're going
to come all the way back down to
previous day value area low. So this is
VWAP from here. So this is heavy. What a
market. This is what I saying. It's uh
open to fail breakouts because there's
no volume being traded. And there you
go. We're coming back down to
yesterday's value area low. Just like
that. One, two, three, four, five
minutes in, we've done a failed breakout
and gone all the way down to the
previous day's value area low after
opening up above it. That is not a good
look, folks. It's a really bad look for
the market. It's really, really, really
bad. It's not what you want to see if
you're a bull. And we are going to take
out previous day value area low. And if
they sell previous day value area low,
you best believe we're going to come all
the way down for this double bottom
yesterday where we've got a ton of
liquidity.
So, this is basically the same thing
we've seen the last two days. Uh,
morning wash.
Let's see if they bid off previous day
value area low now.
Every part of me wanted to take shorts,
but I can't. I'm not going to. I've told
myself I'm not fighting this trend, but
uh
just see. All they want to do is trap
participants both sides right now.
Okay. So, let's see how we act when we
get back up here. Current point control
day point control 640. That's probably
your
control bar, so to speak, or your
control point right under that more
damage can be done. But right now, all
we're doing is trading inside of the
chop, aren't we? Because this blue to
blue is yesterday's chop and the day
before's chop and the day before's chop.
So, you're watching 650s now. and see if
they sell 650s or if they reclaim 650s
and reclaim 680s, then we're going to go
for new highs. And this will just be a
wash that gets absorbed just like
yesterday.
Let's see. So, Apple's gone red,
Amazon's gone red, Google's gone red.
You imagine there is some form of follow
through here to the downside at some
point, but uh who knows?
We all know what this market's been like
recently. sell the morning and then
squeeze all the way back up. Is it going
to do the same again?
[Laughter]
Very, very possible, isn't it? All
right, so here's the test towards that
640, 650. This is the area. If they
reclaim this, they're probably going to
go straight back for the highs again.
Just an absolutely stupid market at the
moment. If you think it's anything other
than that, then I don't know what to
tell you. This market is just dumb,
dumb, dumb, dumb.
So, here's the 40s. Can they get back up
to the 50s? And how do they act once
they get to the 50s? And if they reclaim
the 50s, then I would imagine they're
going to go all the way back to the
highs. That's what you've got at the
moment. They're starting to try and
absorb this to try and get that squeeze.
Ridiculous that we're trading inside
value again. How are we trading inside
value again? is complete groundhog day.
All right, failing 40s and 50s. Are they
going to see any continuation
and we come back for the lows at this
point? So, I'm going to put a small
piece on here. I'm very, very skeptical
about sizing in right now. So, a tiny
piece down to see if we can take out
this value area low. Holding previous
days VWAP, which is right here, 600. So,
this is your overunder. I need to sell
through 600 here. Let me just check
profile.
Big selling coming in there and not
getting their way. So I'm very aware of
that right now. If we get follow through
under 600 then I'll size in. Until that
point I'm not going to size in this
guy's starter on
40s and 50s like I talked about expect
rotation from here to here. If we break
this we should come back for this. If we
break that we're coming down here. Any
reclaim of this is a big no no if we're
looking for shorts. All right. Any
reclaim of 50s is a big no no. So I've
got a tiny bit tiny tiny tiny starter
on. That's it. I want to see if we get
follow through under 600.
Trying to sell aggressively here again.
Here we go. So starting to see a bit
follow through. We've got imbalance down
to 80 and another one at 70. So I don't
want to see bulls step in here. I will
cut this if I see them starting to step
in. It's just a starter. Nothing more
than that.
What a dumb dumb market.
Dum dum is made for dum dums here. We're
trading [\h__\h] four days in this range
that we spent three weeks in before. Can
you [\h__\h] believe it?
Cannot move out of this range.
All
right, out of this now. Basically flat
scratch trade
actually green on it somehow.
This feels like yesterday. It feels
exactly the same as yesterday, just a
bit higher.
All right, we're into value. So,
basically, they failed to hold the top.
They came down to the bottom of previous
day's value. Buyers bid up here. I still
think there's a chance to do this move
because we left it yesterday, but
all depends what their intentions are.
Just want to be very careful if they if
they reclaim 50s, all shorts are off the
table.
Very hard trying to fade these moves at
the moment.
Definitely bears got stuck there under
600 twice. Those last two two attempts
under 600. Let me get rid of previous
days VW, which is also 600 by the way.
Midpoint of range. I'm going to leave
this alone and let it shake out. Had my
first attempt. Didn't didn't go for me.
So, just get up on and leave this alone
for a minute.
Okay. Yeah, definitely those shorts
under 600 got caught.
So, we're coming back towards these 50s
again. Like I said, if they reclaim 50s,
I would say it's a big leave alone.
It's PDC up there. If they reclaim that,
it's a big leave alone short side. If
they reject that, then you might want to
have another attempt.
Blow zone is pointing down. VWAP is
pointing down, but this is a big level
here. Previous day point control. Not
the ideal level to execute at.
Mixed bag on the mag as well. Okay,
they're rejecting it.
Mixed bag on the mag. This is a fourth
day in a row. Nvidia up 1.73. Microsoft
up 0.17. Meta up 4.24%.
Might have to start selling some of
that. Uh Google down 1.14%. Amazon down
0.80%, Apple down 0.57%. So, you've got
a complete mixed bag there.
Check my meta. How much am I up on that
now?
So, anyone that took meta with me in
Discord,
uh, you might want to consider shifting
a little bit of it as we're into that
gap. I'm up about 10%. I've only got a
starter on though. Okay, back to these
600s. We know this is where bears got
stuck on the last attempt. They got
stuck under 600.
Still rejecting VW up. Still rejecting
point of control. Still rejecting
previous day close. So bears are trying
to protect this level here. Balls are
trying to protect 600. That's where
bears got stuck. The rotation right now
is from basically 600 to 650. That's
your rotation.
Heck, yes, you can do it on an ATM
strategy. You can have it automated for
you.
failing 600 here. Back to where these
bears got stuck. Are we going to see
some follow through
back down into an imbalance?
Say 600 now is your under over. Now
we've snapped it, right? If they reject
600 on this retest of it where this big
seller just came in and we might see a
new low of day. If they reclaim this,
we're going to go straight back to 650.
They've got the opportunity here.
Nothing. Just splat.
600 600 600 600 600 600 600.
Come on bears, do something.
All right. Are we going to do something
here?
Current value on the day 80s. Once we
break 80s, I think we see a wash.
Microsoft gone red now as well.
Google giving back some as well. Sorry,
Meta giving back some as well. Market
starting to sort of roll over a little
bit.
But 600's your level. Bears need to
defend 600. Reclaim that. We go straight
back up to 650.
So, we're just dancing in the midpoint
range. This is the old balance. Remember
this gray box is the old balance, right?
Bears need to defend this. We didn't.
Bulls couldn't hold it. We came to the
other side. Bears need to fend defend
this level to get this move and then
this move. If bears fail to defend this
level, a squeeze is available.
That's what you've got. You've got see
money, take money. Nothing more than
just small little scalps.
I'm with you, Zar Trader. This is what
happens when we go into balance. But
what I'd say is once we move out of
balance, we will get some big big big
moves regardless of which direction it
goes.
You see how spy lost that gamma level of
85.
We opened above it and it instantly lost
it. All right. So, we're pinned there.
Can't get above it. If we keep failing
there, there's potential for a rotation
to 80. We fail 80. There's gamma at uh
78 and then 70.
So those are the dealers levels. That's
where they're pinning price at the
moment. And they're just rotating
between them.
What an awful awful start again.
I really don't know what you're going to
do with that. What's your opening
candle?
I guess one, two, three, four, five.
There's nothing to play on a five
minute. So, I guess if you played like a
30 second orb, you probably got a flush
breakdown under there. But other than
that, I don't really see much to play
with.
Apple losing that uh that edge. I just
got a notification. So Apple's crossing
the 82. So if it loses that, that's the
breakdown level. So be aware of that.
Yeah, breaking down. You can see this
level I put on.
This can drag the market down with it if
it starts letting go.
That's why I put price like there.
Yeah, Apple heavy
starting to lose 600s. It's starting to
retest time and time and time again and
starting to lose it.
No doubt about it. It's starting to lose
the 600s.
You might get a wash here if Apple if
it's a big if we lose 600 and Apple
starts breaking down. You might get a
wash to previous day's value area low
and under that there is definitely a
bigger move available.
Just no follow through. Lots of bids
coming in here into 60s.
Wow, look at that. Straight back up to
test the 600s.
That will just get saved. They're trying
to save 82s.
What an awful market, man. Okay, this is
your level now. Sort of 600, 610s. Bears
need to defend that. Failing to defend
that will open up a squeeze all the way
back up to 50s.
Fixes breaking out. Is there going to be
follow through in this market or are we
just going to be stuck inside the
previous range, which is what we're in
at the moment? We're stuck inside
previous days value.
God awful.
So rejecting 600 again.
There's a bid down at 550. I'm wondering
if we come down to him. That' be
previous day's value area low
600. Above 600 they can trigger like a
50 point squeeze very very quickly. Be
very careful there.
[\h__\h]
Don't know why I bother at the moment.
So testing 600 again. Failing 600 again.
These buyers
no bears taking control. There's no
follow through. Apple's now lost the
82s. That's that's a big problem for
this market. It just depends if the rest
of the market follows suit to go risk
off. That is a problem for the market, I
would say, at the moment is lost the
82s.
There's just no follow through. Like
we're just we've just stuck.
Getting skippy here. Whoa. What's that?
Whoa.
Ninja trade is frozen for me now. Yeah,
this is frozen as well. Look at this.
What's going on?
CM me gone down or something? Whoa.
Ninja trader having a nightmare.
Is it going to catch up? There we go.
It's caught up now. Wow. No, it's still
behind. watching price. Ninja traded way
behind on my screen. Be careful, folks.
I'm having data lag issues here. I can
see it because it would seeing different
prices on Ninja versus
uh
bookm Trading View lagging a little bit
as well for a minute. Seems to have
caught up 99ish. Yeah, it's caught
upish. I be careful here. If they
reclaim 600s, there is a 50 point
squeeze out.
Apple trying to reclaim 82s. God, we're
just doing a 30 point dance. This is
[\h__\h] stupid, mate. Just sell it. Just
sell it down to previous day value. Just
stop trying to bid in front of it.
Think we want to come to the 550s.
They're just uh not letting it happen.
Apple lost 82s again.
How long have we been sideways for now?
10 minutes
80s here key fail 80s we probably come
50s
fail 80s we probably come 50s
here it comes probably coming for 50s
here folks
you're probably going to see 50s here
just taking ages to sell
building this out here. Once this lets
go, you're probably going to see this.
And under this, I think we can come down
here. But if you are short versus this,
you need to be covering some into this
previous day value area low because if
they want to bid up off it this they
can. So this will be TP1 and this would
be TP2.
Your Ninja's good. Yeah, mine's caught
up. It just once we had those big
players come in, this guy here, this 100
lot come in over and over again, it just
completely froze. But then so did
Trading View when I looked at Trading
View, frozen there. So maybe it was like
an an internet thing.
Still not getting down to previous days
value.
Oh my god. Still they rotate
20 30 point of chop there.
How are they not selling this?
What I'd be concerned about is bears
have potential control here, right?
Because bulls needed to hold above here.
They didn't. We've sold. We've rejected.
We've sold. Here's the edge. All they
need to do is step in and get under
here. Why are they not doing it? That's
what I have in the back of my mind. Why
are we not seeing sell pressure
when Apple's lost its bid? It's breaking
down under a key level.
Why are we not seeing that pressure?
Bit like April, isn't it? Every chance
they have, they're not doing it. SPY got
absolutely clobbered at that 85, though.
It looks like it's just going to come
all the way down to 80 at the moment.
It's lost its pre-market low.
Yeah, I'd say 80
8280 8260 looks key. So, and then under
that, back to the 80s. Under 80s, this
whole market burns. In my opinion,
you want to see it's starting to get
tight here. I'm just slightly cautious
about taking another trade. I'm not
seeing bears step in aggressively,
and that would concern me about thinking
about a short near previous day value
area low.
Julian, having trouble with my Ninja
Trader closed out my 725 short and
tilted 725.
Oh, you were short from 725. Well, if
you close that out, then you made money
anyway. Don't Don't stress about it.
Don't get tilted about that.
I would get tilted if if you were the
wrong side of it. But you've made good
money on that. Don't even Don't even
stress it.
Oh, please market.
Please don't just rotate for another
whole day. Please
anything else on the calendar? Bowman at
midday. That's it. Still rejecting those
600s, but uh this is not looking good if
you ask me.
Bears should have come flying in already
and they're not. That's the only thing
I'd say.
They should have come flying in. They
had the chance to come flying in. We've
not even retested previous days value
area low. We got close, but we didn't
actually retest it. So, all the time
we're rejecting gray box. I'd say this
move here and potentially this move here
is possible. A reclaim of this. So, I'd
be risk off because then you're going to
see potential squeeze back up 6 650 and
then through that back to the highs. And
this is what we did the last few days,
isn't it? Big sell at the open,
sideways, sideways, sideways, grind,
grind, grind, grind, grind all the way
back up. So, just be aware of that. If
it reclaims this gray box here, I'd be
uh very concerned about looking for any
more downside.
Sorry, I know I know I'm quiet, guys,
but there's there's nothing more to do
than that. Spy did just reject its
attempt to reclaim PDC. So, that's
pretty bearish, actually. See if they
actually get follow through, though.
Still not taking out the 50s. I still
feel like it wants to get to the 50s.
They're sat there.
See all these buyers coming in here. 70
or 60 and 50s.
got room to 500. It's bid down at 500.
They're trying to sell through these
participants. There's just no uh no big
knife, which is what I'd be looking for
of that big big knife sell candle.
Feels like it's coming. Here we go. All
right. 50s are coming up here. This
player on a bit. Let's see if he pulls
his order.
This is better. Now they're having a
good go. They just needed to retest one
more time. All right. So cover point
here into previous day value area low
and then hold your runners because if
you get a breakdown we can look at PD
PDH and we can look at this low down
here into four 418s.
So here's your previous day value low.
So this must be TP.
Take some of your size off here into
this
and let's see if they uh want to let go
of previous day's value and let us
rotate or not. If they hold previous
day's value, then this whole day, right,
if they keep holding previous days
value, this whole day is going to trade
inside this box. All right, this is what
we did yesterday. We traded inside this.
We haven't held it. We've come down and
retested it. All right, if we can't
break down under this or we do a look
below and reclaim, then we're going to
come back up and test these. If we
sustain an auction lower under here,
then my expectation is the low 400s.
And once we get under there, that will
be the 680 on SPY. If we let go of that,
we will get a big big puke out. Big puke
out.
Can we see 398 today? Um,
I mean, yes, potentially. I mean,
potentially we can see zero today,
right? So, I'd be watching for 420s. If
we break this, I'd be watching for 420s.
That would be my first port of call. Can
we get down into this? because we left
that yesterday and I said that we leave
that it looks uh a little bit dubious
but they can still hold a bid here. All
right, this value area is the spike high
from that Sunday open. Is it Sunday open
or Friday close? Can't remember. Is it
Sunday open? Seems like Sunday open.
This is like the Sunday open high where
we are now. So you got to be covering
some here. But what is looking good is
VIX is still driving higher
and it's got room. If we start breaking
out of uh 60 1660 on the VIX, we can
trade all the way back up to 17s.
That will increase sellside pressure on
this market.
Yeah, you should be uh have trimmed some
of your size down here as we traded into
value. And now you can just wait.
Hopefully, you've got room. If you were
entering at 600, you know, you've made
50 points, you've got room to see if
your runners will go for you. And if
they do, you're going to get about 100
point trade out of this. If you're
actually more than that, you're going to
get 200 point trade. So, if you were
short anywhere around these here, either
650 or 600s, here's your TP1. The TP2 is
all the way down here. Do not hold on a
reclaim of this level here. All right,
this is a flat top here. If it reclaims
this, you cut the trade.
Really, you'd want them to reject this
shelf here. Now, 76 is right. So,
really, you'd want this to be rejected.
So, I'm going to do this
as red a bit thicker. And those are your
levels. Really, you'd want that gray box
to reject
so far. They tried to buy into it.
There's a passive seller up there
because we saw some aggressive buying
into it. There is still a passive seller
at 80s, which is good, which is what you
want to see. Really nice. This is much
better now, folks. What I'm starting to
see on the tape is starting to look a
bit better. So, we had some aggressive
buying into 70 and 80, and they didn't
get anywhere. So, there is a passive
seller still at 70s and 80s. All the
time he's there, we can potentially move
lower. If he gets taken out though, I'd
be very, very cautious. All right. So,
this gray box, that's kind of your first
overunder. If we start eating through
that, it's we can still reject up here
into 600, but really we want this edge
to stay heavy, especially now that I've
seen that there's a passive seller on
the book up there.
Spine to 683. Remember 82s was a level.
There was a level at 82s when I looked
last night on the options chain. The
bigger level obviously is 80.
Okay, we're into a new hour here.
Need to be careful. We're into new H1,
H4 here.
Do need to be careful of this. We might
see a rebalance. Rebalance could take us
all the way back up to 620s, which is
not ideal. Do not want to see that.
It's coming back up to maybe test the
edge of this gray box. If we get through
it, then they're going to come and test
610.
I don't want to be in anything if we're
coming up there. Here come the
aggressive buyers again. There's still a
passive seller up here, right? That's
another attempt to break into the 80s.
There's still a passive seller up there.
Don't think he's going to have unlimited
funds.
If these buyers keep going, at some
point he won't be there anymore.
Aggressive selling coming in now.
They're looking for a breakdown. Let's
see if there's someone on the bid the
other side of it.
Oh, it's slow, isn't it?
Always
worries me when we're slow near an edge.
You just think wouldn't take that much
to turn it around.
These buyers at the moment can't get
back through 80. They keep trying over
and over again. It doesn't mean it won't
happen, but they've tried one, two,
three, four, five times here
aggressively as well, market buys, and
they're not getting their way.
Apple trying to reapproach 282. So, I
want to be careful on a reclaim of that.
That might signal that the market's not
willing to move lower.
Uh maybe Zav, but I don't think we will
sit in this same range until next
Wednesday. I think that's asking quite a
lot of the market. I think we'll see a
move out of the range before FOMC.
I think you find we've already priced in
the the cut. It's the something like a
85% chance of a cut now in December. I
think that you'll find that we've
already priced in
because we're back to where we were when
we thought the cut was going to happen,
especially on the S&P. All right, retest
of 80s here. 95% now is it? Jeez. Yeah.
So, that's just getting higher and
higher and higher.
This 80s is where this seller's been
hanging out. And I don't think he's
going to be here too much longer because
they keep chomping through him.
So this gray box and if they get through
gray box, they're going to go red box.
But if they protect gray box, I think we
can potentially see new lows.
We are protecting previous days value
area low right now.
at the moment. No doubt about it.
Creating a bit of a new shelf here. So,
I'd say this little spike here is
starting to become important.
Alls are protecting that at the moment.
Basically 80 to 60 point range.
Just like this. That's your range. this
gray box to box.
We break under value though yesterday's
lows are possible
is back to current value area low on the
session.
Are they going to expend expand current
value on this session or not?
It's rejecting 80s again.
Not seeing expansion of current value
yet.
They're trying to sell this same level.
They've tried these. So, there's been
aggressive sellers at 60 uh for 1 2 3 4
5 6 7 minutes. They've tried to
aggressively sell 60 without getting
their way, which means there's a buyer
here.
There's a buyer at 60. All right. So,
there's a seller at 80 and there's a
passive buyer at 60, which is why we
keep getting blocked in. So, there's
someone just limit buying, refreshing
here, and there's some someone
limit selling, refreshing here, which is
why we keep getting these wicks this
side and wicks this side. Right? And
we're just doing this dance. Once one of
those loes, I think either this or this
is going to happen. Well, I don't think
I know.
Yeah. Well, there you go, JD. I mean,
then it's priced in then, isn't it?
Yeah. You know, if we think about this
on a
on a daily,
all right, this was basically up here.
We were like, "Yeah, we're going to do
December rate cuts." Okay. And then
market came out. We had AI fear and
everything else. And then power gave the
like little sort of hawkish tone and we
lost it. And then down here, Fed came
back in and said, "No, no, no. We still
think we're going to cut." Oh, well,
we're right back to where we were,
right? So, I think it's kind of priced
in.
And I don't think
we can just stay here forever.
I think we either need a drift down here
or it just needs to put on a giant
squeeze and just trash everyone out. I
don't think we stay in here till next
Wednesday. I think that's asking too
much of the market.
But who knows? Maybe you're right. Who
was it that said it? Zar or Zav Zav.
Maybe you're right. Maybe they are able
to do it. But I think that's asking
quite a lot to pin us for that amount of
time.
Oh, I want to go back to sleep. Market's
not moving.
It's just so silly. It's so dumb.
Pre-market 100 point spike takes out the
liquidity, comes back under, goes
sideways, open, dump, pull back, and now
just trapped. My bias really is the
moment we break this blue line, we're
probably coming down to this white line
here.
But it's hard to be bearish at the low
of the previous day value, right?
Because that's where we found bids from
yesterday, isn't it? Think about this.
Where we found bids from yesterday.
sellers got trapped down here yesterday.
We found bids here and the day before,
right? So
be careful trying to get short too late
in the day.
Been down here so long now PC has now
moved down to the 80s as well.
It's red line.
I think there's a big sell coming. I
think it's coming because
buyers are not getting the squeeze out.
I think there's a snap coming soon.
Delta getting heavy. Think there's a
snap coming soon. Here we go. They're
trying.
There's that bitter 50 refreshing 50
buyer.
Has he just caught enough?
Still in a range. Still just 80 to 50.
Feels
like there's a move coming very very
soon. Just watching the wiggle in the
tape. I thought they were about to sell
that violently then. Surprised they got
saved by this guy right here into 55s.
They're coming back to check him to see
if he's going to refresh it again and
buy again.
Yeah, 60 to 80 is the rotation. He's
still refreshed buying net.
Feels heavy, but it's not moving.
Someone's going to get caught.
Retapping this 60. He keeps refresh
bidding. And again he's refreshed. And
again he's refreshed. And again he's
refreshed.
Selling through him now. Now they're
going to come for the 40s.
All right. Are we going to see follow
through?
A decent size bid at 40s that we can't
even get down into.
back to the 60s where that refresh bid
was before.
This was his level
and he's bid again
and again.
Come back down to test him again at 60s.
What a mess. Is he going to save this
and cause a squeeze now? Yep.
What a messy tape.
Oh, what a messy tape.
Well, that says everything you need to
know. He refreshed bid over and over and
over again at 60. Then he pulled his
bid. He let them through and they
couldn't come in even clear out 40. And
then he just went, "Well, if you're that
weak, I'll jump back in again." Refresh
caught 60s and now we're trading 70s. We
never even got down to the 40s. It's
absolutely pathetic. So, they're
successfully defending previous days
value. So, at the moment, you've got to
say all we're looking at is a rotation.
There's no expansion outside of previous
days value. And it's very messy at the
lows. And they've tried to sell it a
couple of times. That candle at what
time was this? That 10:10 candle.
It 10:10. Yeah. The bears came flying in
at 70. They then offered aggressively at
60 and 50 and then in the next candle
down to 50. They got scooped back up.
They had another big sell at 50 at 10:13
and they failed.
Is there a news event we expect to
release this shitty PA? No, not at the
moment.
Uh let's have a look at the calendar.
Um
PCE tomorrow maybe
consumer sentiment
maybe but uh who knows?
We've got all these delayed reports
coming like next week job openings
delayed report employment cost delayed
report Fed rate decision
initial jobless claims I mean the jobs
yesterday uh were bad we lost like
another was it 32,000
market went higher though it's okay
nothing to see here really healthy
market
just uh no one with any work
but it's okay no one with any work,
everyone on credit. Uh we saw more
people not being able to pay their
mortgages again this month. That's gone
up three months in a row. But don't
worry, it's okay because Nvidia's all
right. It's holding on. Don't worry.
Nothing else matters other than AI and
chips nowadays.
Who's going to buy the [\h__\h] AI and
chips or their new computers or new this
or new car or new anything if no one's
got a [\h__\h] job?
It's [\h__\h] stupid, mate. Absolutely
stupid. I guarantee you if we'd done a
pullback earlier in the year since that
April pivot, we wouldn't be up anywhere
near as high as we are now.
Okay, so they reclaimed. So, they're
going to go 80s. Now, they're taking
this box. It's possible they come up for
these 600, 610s. Any reclaim of up there
will cause a squeeze.
So, this is like your channel. You're
starting to see a bit of compression
here. It's something like this where
you're sort of pinned in, right?
And just make it simple for you actually
pin. Oh, didn't mean to do that. All
right. And if they want to come up to
the top of value, they will. And that
will be a fail to get underneath.
Sellers failed to get underneath
previous day's value. Buyers failed to
bid over previous day's value. Sorry,
previous day's value. Which means we're
going to be left with this.
Um,
that's what we're left with today at the
moment until we move outside of value.
That's all we've got.
It's all we've got, folks. We can only
trade with what's in front of us. That's
all we're being given right now is
rotation.
Fun. Fun. Fun. Fun.
Yeah, lots of you saying back to bed. I
kind of feel the same. I'm going to be
honest. Just hanging around in case we
move outside of rotation. I'm not going
to trade inside rotation. If we move
outside of rotation,
I am interested.
Did they just fail 80s again? Oh my god.
All
right, back with flip PC. So, we're
above PC now.
Apple trying to reclaim 82s.
Be a big level that if it reclaims it.
satisfy.
Jack saying you're long. Well, good
luck, mate.
makes sense if you're just playing
value.
Still making uh lower highs though. But
if you're playing versus value on a
rotation, as long as you got your stop
there, it makes sense. I don't trust it
right now.
Still think uh it's a battle.
We are starting to see it sort of go
sideways.
I think that the way I describe it is
there's a lack of control.
There's a lack of control right now.
Target is new session high. Well, you're
asking quite a lot because the session
high is over previous days value.
Doesn't mean it won't get there, but
you're not even through current. You
know, you're bidding on previous day
value area low. You're not even through
current value area high on the day to
try and create a new session high.
You're asking quite a lot. It can easily
come up here and just get slammed and go
here all day.
Back to these 80s where they haven't
been able to bid through so far.
Personally,
I don't think it's anything to do here.
Like, I understand the longs you guys
are taking off previous days low, but
I'm not seeing big bullish sentiment
come in. Not yet. Not seeing like a big
drive higher and then a pullback that
holds a higher low. It's very slow.
Still not even through BWAP.
What's that? Is that a London rejection?
What's the low there? Not even at London
lows yet.
This is bad.
I wish they should just close down for
December cuz it's like no one comes back
after Thanksgiving. Like a week before
Thanksgiving was [\h__\h] volume. This is
just as [\h__\h] Like everyone's just
taking t taking it off. No one's come
back to work.
That's completely mixed out there. Meta
the big winner in the market. Um,
let me open this up in biz or you going
to be stupid.
Yeah, big winners today. Uh,
Meta, Gev,
banks, well, banks have mixed as well.
Banks are okay, but credit services are
all down. Healthcare is down.
Diagnostics are down.
Consumer defensive is down.
Consumer services outside of meta and
Apple are down.
Basic materials are down. Energy is
flat. Real estate's up. Utilities
probably flat.
Just nothing going on.
I think you take meta out the equation
and uh this market is in a bit more of
pain.
Okay, so you need to base here at 80s.
You've had numerous attempts to get
through it. You've got through it. Now
you're pulling back to it and you need
to hold it. If you don't hold it, I'd be
very concerned for those of you who are
bullish because you've just popped
through tap VW and failed
and you're not holding the 80s
and that's what the game is right now
and you didn't hold it. So, back to 60s.
You lose 60s, you're probably going to
see a new lower day. That's why I say I
don't think there's anything bullish
here. Your chance to be bullish would
have needed to hold that level. You can
see here's your compression.
There's the break. Did they hold that?
No. All right. So, bulls are not in
control. We just go back into this death
chop.
The death chop. And uh I wouldn't be
surprised to see a new low of day here
at this point because you've just had a
failed breakout
for those of you who are looking
bullish.
Back into current value area low. If you
lose this, we're going to come back down
for low of day and previous day value
area low. So, current value area low
right here, right now. If we lose this,
I think you probably see a new low of
day. And if you snap that, it could get
very nasty because we've been here a
long time now.
They're trying to desperately save it
here.
They know if they lose this bulls,
they're in big trouble.
So underneath current value, I'd say
there's a new low day coming at this
point.
There's previous day's value.
Guess who's in it short. There we go.
So, I told you.
Don't say I didn't tell you.
In this short, let's see how much
expansion we can get.
It trapped all you bulls who were
looking for the rotation without it
giving you a reason. Here we go.
How low can we go? All right, 520s here.
Let's see if we can get fives. And then
if we break under fives, let's see if we
can get into those low fours. Why have I
not got this marked out? What is this
level? We'll check this level for Ninja
420s.
Covering a little piece here into the
520s and see if we can get another 100
points here or not would be nice. Be a
gift.
Any reclaim value though, I I'll cut the
rest. Need to see this reject previous
day value area low now. Continuation.
Good rejection so far.
Need to see previous day value area low
stay heavy now.
That's what I need to see. That's what
I'm going to risk against
there. Or thereabouts. Any reclaim of
that will be a look below and fail and
I'll cut it.
Nice, Troy.
Good work, Troy. Yeah.
Yeah. That's why I didn't want to be
bullish. Like I get what you guys were
looking at for the hold of value, but
this
we didn't see this. That's your
confirmation to hold above a range. It
never holds above a range. All right. So
you guys buy this. We didn't even get
above current value on the day. Like I
said, they sell into it. Now you got
everyone buying this breakout and they
dump them. And like I said, once you
lost 80s, it was a problem. and then you
lost PC and then you lost pre uh current
value and then you lost previous day
value and then you washed. So
I'm now out of this but if it reclaims
now and bases then you've got more of a
chance long. But this is still bearish
in my mind.
But if you reclaim value maybe go
rotation again.
Apple selling more 1% down now.
VIX did just spike cut through that
1663. Couldn't hold a bid there. Where
did we just trade down to? Look at that
gamma level on SPY. That 82
big [\h__\h] level, man. It's just the
options dealers are controlling the
markets of
in this last quarter. It's very
annoying. Hate having to check options
levels, but that's where we're at right
now.
So they held 82s.
Okay. Now if they hold, you look better
because you've had a look below and
fail. All right. So I'd say for bulls
now, now you've looked below. So I got
short for this breakdown. Now if you
start holding this for rotation, you
look better because there'll be lots of
breakout shorts. You came out in here.
You still really want to get back above
80. That 80 has been massive. You can
see it here.
All right. Trapped, trapped, trapped,
trapped. Break above, failed, back to
it. All right, this is your overunder.
They bulls need to hold above 80. It's
as simple as that.
I'm going to use a bathroom while this
shakes out for a minute.
Oh, yeah. I mean,
I don't even hate what you did, Jack. I
just think uh as long as you cut and and
you know you had your reasons for me
it's not something I take but your
reasons were we were holding previous
day value
it's not a bad reason to look for that
trade I get what you're looking for I
would just say that in here it probably
hasn't given you if this held here
I would say in my mind that's the point
where I'm like okay well bulls are now
defending and leaving trapped sellers,
right? That that for me would be your
your cue. That was a fail breakout.
That's also a fail breakdown. This is
your ledge. Bulls just need to hold
this. If bulls hold this, you've got a
chance for the rotation. Now, set the
same story because if you just think
about how we built structure right here,
here, here, here. Test 80, fail. Test
80, fail. Get above 80 fail. back above
80 needs to hold this range, right? And
really, you want to hold the top of the
range because that will leave all the
sellers trapped and then you can use
their pain to go higher. Much like
the opposite up here, all right, once we
took
out previous days high, there's previous
day's value area high balls. All they
needed to do was defend this for a move
higher today. They didn't defend it. So,
we go back in. So, I'm not bullish
unless we hold this. We said that this
morning. So, it's the same thing just
the other way around. It got to defend a
level and leave sellers stuck, right?
The same way sellers here, right, had
the opportunity to
defend this
and leave all the buyers who keep
accumulating in here stuck. Sellers
would have needed to defend this to
complete this move down here. They
failed. All right. So, now you've got
both sides. You've got buyers and
sellers in here. So above 80, bulls have
control. Below 60s, bears have control.
In between, no one has control. That
well, that's how I interpret it.
Hopefully that makes sense.
You're starting to see them hold the
80s. And it's key. So you bulls now are
holding 80s. You should see expansion.
Here you go. So this is so much better,
isn't it? You see that? Now we leave
them trapped. You pull back. you hold
PC's flip that's helping you. Now my TP1
would be into here because we've not
been able to get above value. So I'd be
looking for 600 610 and I'd be taking
some off because there's no guarantee.
Remember this is the bigger if we zoom
out. This is your bigger range from the
last few days and overnight. Right?
There's your overnight. So you're not
truly bullish until you reclaim that.
Now you want to get back inside that
range. So for me how I would be trading
Oh, don't want to move that. I would be
taking a little bit of profit into this
red box, right? Between this red box and
you got multiple things here. You got
600, you got the red box 608, and you
got VW up there. So, I'd be looking to
lift a bit of size off. This is how I
would trade it. If I was trading it, I'd
be long, sell some, wait and see if we
can get above,
add some, and then try and sell into
these pushes. Right? That's how I would
personally trade this.
Thank you.
Good thing for you is Spyy's reclaimed
VWAP. So they defended gamma level at
82. They've reclaimed VWAP. They're
coming up to 84s now. So Spyy's got
another dollar push in it. All right.
Spy can get up to 85. We know 85 is a
massive, massive level. All right. That
is a big cool wall up there. All right.
So, you're starting to see some good
alignment here. What you really want to
see is Apple reclaim 282s, which we're
not seeing. Not yet.
And you want to defend now the VWAP and
PC. You do not want to see it trade
under there. It's got no reason.
If you're bullish now, it's got zero
reason to trade under this. It needs to
trade over this. It needs to get into
this and then you can start
accelerating. If we get into the red box
and base above it, you can start
accelerating. But like I said, I would
have already taken a little bit of
profit here. If you bought 82s,
I know it's not very much, but I would
have taken 20 25 points, a little bit of
profit, and I'd be waiting to see if you
can do this up here now for a read.
Does that make sense, Jack?
Again,
I don't hate what you did. Like, I don't
I don't think it's a it's a terrible
trade down there. It's just don't think
you got confirmation. Look at the
difference with the flow zones now. They
want to try and support it. All right.
So, you've just trapped all the bears
under here now. Now, you're trying to
support it.
Wicked. Good. Good stuff. Good stuff,
mate.
There you go. This is looking good now.
So TP1 here basically hit here here to
green if you haven't already taken some
and wait and see now if you can base
above current value. If you can base
above this red box if you can base in
here create some bullish kind of move
then you can look for this drive. I'd
say like the 40s point of control from
yesterday. What's this? Is that gap
fill? That might be gap fill.
That gap fill. Hang on. Check my other
chart here. Going confused. What's what?
Yes, that is gap fill. Yeah. So, gap
fill.
All right. So, you're looking really
good now. This is really, really good.
Now, you got the bears caught. Now,
you're starting to see the acceleration.
Look at the difference in candles. Big
candles. Buyers in control. You're
looking really good. So, now you'd be
looking for any pullbacks. Now, if you
want to h hold or add, you want to hold
sort of 608 somewhere around there. And
then these are your targets now. So I'd
say liquidity is here for sure. So 30s,
50s,
60s, and if you get really lucky,
previous day value area high and very
lucky above here. But I'd be definitely
selling some into here because that's
been most of the rotation today, isn't
it? And that's most of the box.
A bit of a battle here. You want to see
this hold the bottom side of this red
box now, right? You want to see this
hold the bottom side of this red box
because that's going to confirm that
we're reclaiming the range from
overnight. All right. So if we move you
move you into a five minute
don't worry about this. This is this red
box is incorrect. If we move into a five
minute
right you can see that we get thick here
from this week.
This right here. Come on buddy.
Right. This right here is where we get
thick this week.
And overnight you can see these lows
right where buyers kept stepping in or
it's those buyers who have become
sellers this morning. So this is their
chance to get out break even. Now if
they don't take that chance and they
rebid it then that's your move 650s. All
right. Don't expect more than 650s.
Hopefully you get more than 650s but
don't expect it. It's very possible that
they reject these levels here. Okay.
It's very very possible. But if you re
get into here, that's your thick area.
You can sell something 650. If you get
above that, then by all means, you can
hold for higher day.
It's looking so much better now. So much
better. Just all you have to do is wait
a little bit
and just manage your expectations.
Manage your expectations. So you filled
that H1.
Remember we said 618s would be fill. So
if we go to H1.
All right. So this did the old H1 trap.
Break below. Failed. Candle goes red to
green back up to fill H1.
And if you get really lucky, you get up
into that wick.
Honestly, it's um
if today's proof of anything, it's proof
that even in [\h__\h] markets, the key is
the same thing. It's just waiting for
one side to get caught.
Just be careful here. Hopefully, you've
locked some good money in. You need it
to hold sort of this edge. If it doesn't
hold the edge, don't be sitting in it
too long.
Just reading that that email from Apex.
That's insane, isn't it? Now paid out
over $600 million.
So all six emails are all priced at
$196.
Is that right? with 60% off all sizes
and 60% first off first month and
recurring month and $6 for a lifetime
fee and $60 for resets.
It's quite jokes.
So all emails basically any size email
right now is price oh that is a good
deal is priced at 78.40 especially for
the bigger ones
and all activation fees are priced at
six bucks. So every single account right
now is priced at 84.40 40 to get by the
time you're funded. That especially for
the bigger sizes. That is very, very
good.
Very, very good. Impressed.
Impressed.
All right. So, you're trying to search
up into these 50s. Hopefully, you get
it. Um, we've got liquidity. I'm going
to just delete this red box. All right.
You know where this red box is, but I'm
just going to delete it so you can see a
bit better. We have some stops. All
right. We have some swing stops sat here
at about 42. All right. So 36 to 42
the book does thicken up a little bit up
here at 35 you have some buy side
offside delta be very very careful if we
don't trade through 35 soon I'd be
slightly concerned because you had a
buyer clearly step in there at 635 you
got a 300 lot offside by side delta and
it's been a heavily traded zone 1,894
contracts traded there and 300 of them
are buyers market buyers who are offside
so you got to get through 35 and you Got
to get through it soon in my mind
otherwise there is a bigger flush coming
and leave them all caught. So, just a
heads up.
Yeah, sorry guys. I was having a
personal combo there for a second.
I'm back. I'm back. Sorry guys. Just
chatting to my wife.
All right. Nice thing you're seeing some
huge bids come on. So if you look at
bookmap
finally we're seeing some size. I mean
this is the first time I'd say in weeks
that I've seen some decent size on the
books. So you're seeing 800 lot down
here. 90s and 600. So they're telling
you they want to defend the range. The
same story. If you look on the right
hand side you see this offside delta
here. 35s around where we are now. You
got to get above these 35s. This is
where we've got offside delta right now.
It's standing out like a sore thumb. You
see, we keep rejecting this. See this
300 lot and and 186 lot. That's what's
been traded by side from aggressive
buyers and we haven't traded through it.
You've got to get above 35. That is very
very clear clearly a key level on the
level two. Once you get through that,
you should trade 42s, I would say,
fairly quickly.
Yes. Ah, I forgot, Adam, that you've got
this now.
Um, you can do a little lesson later on
setting up and stuff if you want,
but yeah, exactly. Stacking 600s. The
interesting thing will be whether these
hold because they've only been on the
book for 2 minutes, right? So, let's see
if if we use them as magnets and drive
down to them, do they actually come in
here? Do they protect these levels or do
they pull the orders?
But so far holding that New York VW up
which is around what we at there is it
20s or something or 24hour view up 17s.
Why do I not have my view up on here?
Oh great. That's good, isn't it? Just
[\h__\h] log me out.
Fantastic.
Thanks. Funded next just completely
locked me out. All right, so let's see.
Let's see if they soak here. So VWAP
24-hour VW up is about here at 17s.
We have an imbalance down to
611s
and I'd say they need to hold the 600s.
So, do they come and use these guys as a
magnet now? Do these guys pull? It
wouldn't surprise me to see these guys
pull. But we're going to find out. We're
going to find out.
See how we never got through
where those buyers got stuck above that
I talked about. Okay, we're testing this
600. It's coming up now. He's staying on
the He's pulled.
He pulled. He left. He left the books.
They both left the book. They got very,
very scared and they left. This is not a
good sign. So, back down to the New York
field one here.
So you got buyers offside now 604 605
600 was a contested level but if you
look on the right hand side the delta
I'd say here is a big contested level
405 if you don't bid back above that
you're in trouble as a bull starting to
bid back above that now and where are
those players from earlier it was 35
wasn't it just get up here yeah they're
still here so added more 35. That's your
big level. If you can't get over 35, it
would be the end of the auction. That's
that's where the last buyer bought,
right? So, right into
these guys here,
right? So, there's still a passive
seller here. Buyers got caught offside
trying to buy up here. Here's the
pullback to view up and point of
control. And this is your last level.
You've got to hold this as a bull.
failing to hold this, you will collapse.
There you go. So, it's starting to
collapse now. So, that was all because
there was too much buyers up here buying
the market being sold into from passive
sellers
and now maybe rotation here. And if you
lose that rotation, downside pressure.
And if we look at spy, did it get back
up towards 85? No, it failed in front of
it. It failed at 8455s on the spy and
it's going to come back down side now
and it's got to hold this shelf now at
83s.
So just another rotation
market rotation.
How do I get the VB PD column? Uh this
is level two. Uh so you will need to go
where's my studies?
on add-ons.
Go to add-ons and then go for Dom Pro.
So, here Adam
uh this little one on the right chart.
Configure add-ons
and then Dom Pro. And then you'll need
to set this up.
set this up.
All right, you're starting to lose New
York view up. You're starting to lose
this little shelf here. You might see
some sell pressure all the way back down
now. So, two leg. They finish the
two-leg. Buyers trapped at the highs.
Rotation back down to this shelf. If
they lose this shelf, back down we go.
What are the levels? Well, previous day
value area low. still just rotating
inside. Remember,
uh this is yesterday.
We're still just rotating inside of
yesterday. It's all we're doing right
now. All right. So, imbalance.
See money, take money.
But the big I would say the big key
there was those buyers trapped at the
highs. They stood out like a sore thumb.
Like I said, once they got stuck at 35,
that was a big problem. That's always a
good sign of a reversal. So, I kept
saying to you, if you guys can't get
over 35s, you're going to get a bigger
rotation down. And then you saw these
guys pull the pull the orders. All
right? And they're doing the same now.
So, they're adding lower, but you know,
now you know, you can't trust this guy.
Look, it's the same kind of size as
above. You cannot trust this guy. He's
probably going to pull the moment you
get close to him. So, do not trust. This
is why I say the passive orders, we
might use them as magnets, but the
amount of people I say see saying like,
"Oh, these guys are going to get filled
up here and a book has to go up there."
No, it doesn't. They're advertising
price to get it down there. There's just
as much chance this is a short seller
trying to attract the market down to him
and that will pull his order the moment
it gets there. Right? We don't know. So,
we're going to find out again now. So,
some front running in front of it, some
covering in front of it.
See if he pulls his order.
So this is an old imbalance here. Now,
from that big candle
for those of you trade valley gaps,
right, we're filling some of this in
that big expansion.
back to PC
and they're going to test BW which is
above us.
Here we go. Testing VWAP.
Testing the 600's.
Much better book. Now, today I know that
we're trading in range, but at least
we've got some size coming back onto the
book. We're actually moving.
I want to see if this guy gets tested at
these 560. He's still there.
again trading at point of control. Most
traded area we've been at because
they're trying to make their decision
now. This is the battleground because
bulls
they want to defend this imbalance for
this move, right? And bears, they want
to sell a lower high for this move. And
we know this is a heavily contested
zone. In fact, it's the most heavily
contested zone of the day.
So, we're going to come and test this 60
guy by the looks of it. Still on the
book here. 370 lot
at 560.
There's a passive buyer here because we
keep aggressive selling and we're not
moving lower. So, someone's refresh
bidding here. Yeah, he can't last
forever. He's going to get caught.
Amazing that they do that in front of
these guys advertising price.
at the PC.
>> No position for me.
I made my money already today. So, just
waiting now.
If there's something A plus, I'll take
it. But just a small base hit day for me
again. D I'm due payout again. So just
not trying to over push it.
I can take another payout tonight.
So here comes the 60s. Let's see if this
guy wants to get filled this time.
along
don't see anything yet personally
to see it as a battle zone.
If the 60 guy loses the like pses bid,
I think you rotate to 50s very quickly
and if you lose that I think you get a
new lower day again. But we will see it
all all depends on what this 60 guy
wants to do. You've got balances got a
ton of balances below. All right. So,
you've got things that need to get
filled. 65 to 57 and 55 to 43.
Come on. Go and fill him
right there. They're all front running
him.
See if his bollocks really as big as
he's saying they are.
13 points left to fill him. I think it's
coming.
You've got sellside del uh delta offside
now at 71.
So they keep trying to aggressively sell
71 and they're not getting their way
under it for a second there. So they're
trying again to sell. They're just
making it worse for themselves at the
moment. These sellers, they've got to
get a close under 71 here. Otherwise,
they're going to get caught.
Here we go. All right, you got your
chance now. Sellers is still being
absorbed. All right, so that's telling
me there is a passive buyer around 70.
All right, who's in front of that 60? In
front of 560. There's a passive buyer at
570 because twice now they've sold 80s
and they've sold 75s and they've sold
71s without moving lower. So there's
there's a big big passive buyer here.
Mad to me that he's trying to absorb
this much, but that's what's happening.
Here we go. We're going to fill this guy
now
under 71s. Retesting 71s. There's
definitely a pacifier here trying to
scoop it up. They're probably going to
get a flush moment soon cuz they're
going to want to feel really see if this
guy's real, which he is. He gets sold
into. All right, so we sold into him
there. We exchanged 568 contracts down
at that low. So he got sold into
remember he was a passive buyer. So you
needed an aggressive market orders to
fill him to match him off, which is what
you got 568 of them.
Feel
some of that imbalance as well.
Apple really starting to sell now.
It's accelerating.
I'll give you a readout. Uh Tesla 0.33%
up. Nvidia 1.16% up. Microsoft flat.
Meta 3.79% up. Google 1.22% up. Amazon
2.14% up. Apple, sorry, Google 1.23%
down. Amazon 2.16% down. Apple 1.16%
down.
Trading right back to that opening range
low. All right, this is 15minute candle
low right here. Right, we've never got
outside of the opening range. All right,
we did it for all of a second.
So,
these are the markets that you'll see me
not really participate in because we're
trading inside of previous days value.
We're trading inside of current days
value. We're not expanding ranges,
right? We're just rotating and we all
know Alex does not like rotating
markets. How can you see it's rotating?
Well, look at the flow zones. Look at
the VWAP starting to flatten out. Look
how tight everything is together,
right? I still think it wants to come
down here, but you know it it hasn't
done it and that's all that matters. All
right, we got another big buyer on the
tape again.
540 now.
That'll be under the imbalance if we get
down there.
Need H1 here. So that last H1, do you
remember we talked about the H1
repricing?
Last H1
repric. Here's your kill candle. Here's
the repric. And here's the GlobeEx,
which they couldn't get back in front
of. Right? So, we sold that. We're back
down to the lows. Now, if they sell
this, this can be used as liquidity.
Now, everyone who bought that, if we
break the lows now, then I'm very
confident we come back down into here.
Here's
current or sorry, previous day value
area low again. So, rechecking previous
day value area low again.
Vickstein trying to get going through
1650s. All right, this is its god knows
how many attempts it's had up here
today. It's had one spike through and
that's it.
So under previous day value area low now
be watching to see they did they fill
that guy? Yeah, they filled him. All
right. So they're adding 500s now. So
this looking like it's going to start
drifting lower at this point
which is what you're starting to see. So
I'm starting to attack this a little
bit. Small size playing with house
winnings here. Let's see if we can get
initial balance low and then let's see
if they actually want to let this go.
Previous week high would be 500.
Previous week close would be
482s
and that previous day low is down at
423. So those are the targets if we're
going to get a continuation
if they're going to reject previous day
value and start getting a continuation
trade.
Um because I do think if we snap this
now then you've got all these bulls now
trapped in and these moves here should
happen right two leg pull back fail
starting to sell.
Bang. Here we go folks. All right so
let's see if we can get that previous
week high 500s and let's see if we snap
that. It would be really nice if we
could snap that.
You can see they're covering some into
that on the book.
spy as well. Got to watch those 82s on
spy. Low of day on spy 8217. Remember
big gamma level 82. Need to be aware of
that in my head. We've seen how big
those gamma levels have played the last
few days.
watching to see uh initial balance low
and previous day value area low if they
stay heavy versus these. This is what
I'm watching to see. Do we stay heavy
versus these? Now, if we do, I'll think
about adding on.
If we just go straight reclaim through
previous day value, then nothing to do.
It's just to look below and fail again.
So, slight divergence here. ENQ made a
new low. SPY did not make a new low. I
assume ES did not make a new low. Let me
just zoom in here. Check.
Did it? No, it did not.
Okay, so initial balance test here.
And uh through that, I'm watching that
previous day value area low. Want to see
if they sell that or not. If they
reclaim it, we go back into range again.
See a bit of a delta flip here. Buy
stepping in.
Where did that big seller step in? What
was his level? 540. 477.
Traded at 540. So that's a big level to
watch.
And if BIS holds 1650 as well, that's a
big level. It's through it and it's back
testing it.
So here's the drive back up to where
that seller was the 40s. First seller
was at 40s. Uh value 45, opening range
low 50. So watching 4550 reclaim that
then no good.
There's the imbalance.
It's 40s.
Zoom this in. Excel there into 40s. So,
it is definitely a level they're looking
to resell that still. But any now I know
any reclaim of 1450 then this thing will
probably squeeze. Right. So, this is
sort of
probably call it 60. So, this is your
level. They need to fail this otherwise
they squeeze up to here and then they'll
look to sell that. If they reclaim this
then they go back upside again.
Big players come back on the book buy
side at twelves
300 lot.
Um, well, you're asking quite a lot for
VIX to get up there right now.
It It's not got above it's not based
above 1660 yet. So, I don't I don't
think there's any sign of it going for
previous day high right now.
Things can change, but you know, I I
don't have the magic uh magic eightball
to tell you. Okay, so they keep
reselling 40s and 50s. Like I said, this
can drift all the way up to 60s if it
wants.
There's aggressive buying here and
there's definitely been a passive seller
here. This was his level before.
Remember, we did a big exchange here
before for the breakdown.
If they start getting through previous
day value, low in 60s, this can squeeze
all the way back up to where it came
from. All the way back up to here. So,
I'd say this 60 is going to be a massive
level.
That's sort of last chance saloon for
the shorts.
Boring market just so pinned
Okay, there's a test towards the 60 that
shelf.
We're back inside previous days value
here, but we're at flow zones. We're at
this sort of gray box there, that shelf.
Anything through here will uh initiate a
new squeeze up, I would say.
Regarding the indicators, are the ones
on Trading View and those on Ninja
Trader the same? Yeah, they're the same.
Exactly the same. Okay. Rejection of 60s
there so far. You need to see follow
through now to fill all these
participants through 25s and 12elves.
And if you see that, you're going to see
downside pressure. So it's big big
levels coming up here. If you see a
flush here, they're going to really
really sell this. So this really is a
big big moment for this market here
because we just rejected 60s and we said
if we squeeze through that, it would
test the 60s. If they get follow through
here underneath initial balance, it is
night night market. Really nice,
right? Can we get through initial
balance low and expand this? Now we're
starting to see aggressive selling
coming in. We got to fill these guys
into 500s and sell through 500s here.
Come on, Mr. Market. Let's have some
fun. Let's do something today.
Still holding that IB. I want to sell
through IB.
So, I've just got a one guy on at the
moment at 45, which is that previous day
value area low once we spiked up and
then come back under it. Sold there.
I need to see us sell through initial
balance. And I really need to see us
where do those big sellers come in?
17s and 11s. So, if we don't get through
that, I'll have to cut it. Break even.
And we're coming back towards my
position there already. Yeah. Okay. So
they can't get through the 17s.
And it's possible if we go through this,
we go back into rotation. So it's about
to stop our break even here.
[\h__\h] market. You've got no follow
through either side. You are a shitfest
to trade right now.
Big buying at the high there. And we're
not moving.
You going to make me reload here?
Big buying at the high there and we
didn't move.
[\h__\h] spy. Can't get back under 82.
I'm flat. I'm flat. I'll get back in if
I want to. I'm flat now.
The last week's made me want to just
start trading options because apparently
it's all you do now. You just get a
gamma level and you just buy the gamma
level and that's it. That's all we do
now. Like too many zero DTE having too
much impact.
What's up Bella?
I saw your message. I just sent you uh
my number. Oh, that's you there. Okay, I
see you.
What day did you get to LA, Bella? Do
you know?
Okay, perfect. Yeah, I've got WhatsApp.
Okay, so back to these 60s. This is the
big level. If they reclaim these 60s,
remember I'm flat now.
I was short for this breakdown and then
I had another attempt here. Stopped out,
break even. Watching this gray box here,
this edge here. Sellers, in my mind,
they need to sell this for the rotation.
If they don't sell it, then we go back
into this area here. And we will just
trade sideways again. But sellers can
resell this here. But they're not doing
a very good job.
They are not doing a very good job.
We've reclaimed initial balance low
after sweeping and here you had
divergence to ES. So it's worth being
aware of
failed 60 again.
Do I have one more go at this? Do I have
one more go at this, folks?
It's just so messy in here.
There's that P3
minute bars are not looking very good.
I'm going to be honest with you. We've
got Bshape, Dshape, Dshape, Dshape, and
uh
we're just moving PC on those 30 minutes
around from like 604 and then it gets
like moved down to 577, then moved up to
595 and now moved to 546 and we're
trading there at the moment. So, it's
not
there. There isn't a follow through in
the market at the moment
inside. We're back inside. So, well,
we're trying to get back inside previous
stage value at the moment. We're not
seeing acceptance underneath previous
stage value. We've had two attempts at
it today. I still think we can move
lower. Um, but I need to see aggression
step in and I'm not seeing that. They
have the opportunity right here, right
now to sell versus 60s
and they're not. So, again, like it's
going in my head. They're not selling
it. They should and they're not selling
it. Why alarm bells? They're holding
82s. We haven't even traded to 682s on
SPY. We've traded in front of it twice
and they're bidding it. So, the options
dealers are bidding us up. They're
pinning us. Yesterday, they pinned us at
680. Now, they've walked up, pinned us
at 682. So, we're pinned between 682,
685. Rotation, rotation, rotation,
rotation. I'm saying this out loud loud
in my head because it's like, stop
looking for continuation. They don't
want it to continue. They want to pin
it. So, probably in my head telling
myself, you're done for the day. You've
made good money. Why are you trying to
trade if they don't want to find
acceptance lower? Why bother? Because my
rule is don't trade rotation. We're now
back inside rotation.
This is me speaking out loud
to myself more than you guys. All right.
To myself more than you guys.
Look below and fail. Probably going to
go to VW in this case. If we reclaim
60s. All right. the initial balance
trade. Look below fail. This is a big
shelf here. They get through this, they
will go to VWAP. That would be the IB to
VWAP trade for me. Sellers have the
opportunity here to sell it. But I've
had a go at it. I'm not going to sell it
again. I've had a go at it already.
Have to make some rules for myself. How
many trades can you take in a day? I
can't keep having a go at this same
trade. If it doesn't want to do it, it
doesn't want to do it.
It's not helping the mag. I don't know
how many days in a row I've looked at
the mag and I've seen this. Tesla third
of up. Nvidia 1.26% up. Meta almost 4%
up. That's like swap places with Google
now having these big days and then you
go Microsoft basically flat. It's down
on the day but basically flat. Google
1.22% down. Amazon 2.13% down. Apple
1.40% down. We don't know what the [\h__\h]
we're doing with this market. People
don't know. Do we want to buy it? Do we
don't do we want to sell it? No one
[\h__\h] knows. But I tell you what,
macro looks [\h__\h] It looks absolutely
terrible out there from a macro point of
view. But all I know is it doesn't
matter how bad it looks under the
surface. They're not selling it. So
there you go. You got fundamental
traders trading against technical
traders right now. That's what I would
say. They're not in alignment. You're
not seeing fundamentals saying, "Hey,
this market's in pain." And technical
traders go, "Yeah, you're right. Sell
it." You're seeing the opposite. You're
seeing fundamental traders go, "Hey,
this market's [\h__\h] There's no jobs. No
one's working. We've got pressure on the
market. You've seen technical traders
go, "We don't [\h__\h] care. Bid it up.
We haven't made our money." And that is
the fight right now. And until they
start agreeing, I think that will remain
the fight. And I think until SPY trades
under 680, there's still a chance for
new all-time highs this year. And that
is my feeling just based on what I'm
seeing in the market. Look again today.
How many chances have sellers had to
take control?
How many chances
have they had here? Failed breakout
here. They're doing a terrible job of
it. All right. They're letting them
reclaim range. They're not even taking
out a really, really obvious level down
here to take out. They're unable to do
it. That's the story for me of this
market since April is sellers are unable
to do anything of note.
No. Are these guys walking up or they
just still? Yeah, they've walked up a
bit. All right. So, someone down here
trying to get filled.
Think he might be waiting a while. I
don't think it's going to happen anytime
soon.
What would you guys rather have for the
end of the year? Would you rather have
this market rotate lower
into end of year or are you guys looking
for alltime highs?
Yeah. Back above 60. We get up here now.
I mean, you can make money either side,
but I'm talking about more from from
what might set up for next year because
it does have an impact on how we move
next year.
I think we if we do new alltime highs in
December, I think January looks uh
pretty bleak
because that would tell me, okay, hedges
just want their Christmas bonuses and
once they've made their Christmas
bonuses, they probably unwind this
thing.
It does make a difference.
Okay, so there's your VWAP, high to
VWAP. What a [\h__\h] market, man.
If you guys like rotation, this is your
market. I absolutely hate a rotational
market like this. This is my worst
nightmare looking left. It's just
This is just [\h__\h] I'm sorry. If you
like this, you're mental. I can't get my
head around people that like this, but
like Oh, slam. Oh, slam.
It's just who likes this?
Someone does.
Someone likes it.
I don't think so. On Friday. Not if we
keep doing this. Think what you'll see
Vicks get crushed and us just keep
grinding higher.
Why are they going to do it on Friday?
They've
they've had the opportunity to do it for
two days. I don't like
probably get the the opposite move.
Probably just get a drift higher.
Just catching up on emails here while
this market does nothing.
I hate these guys like from these prop
firms, like shitty prop firms who just
email you over and over again. Hey, hey,
we're closing our exclusive program
soon. Let me know. I don't even [\h__\h]
know who you are. Please reply no
thanks. No, no, please stop emailing me.
I don't know who you are. I'm not going
to take my time out my day to look at
your scammy firm. Literally inundated
with that stuff at the moment.
Okay, so starting a whole PC now. So
potentially we squeeze all the way back
up to 610s again at this point.
This level here, right? Edge of value.
This is bloody awful.
That's what you're playing today, folks.
That's that's all you're allowed to play
at the moment.
One side to the other side to the other
side to the other side to the other side
to the other side.
Is anyone else bored of this? Is it just
me?
Do you guys actually like this stuff?
I just wanted to get on like just just
get out of theing range.
Just either break out to all-time highs
or go back down. But don't just do
nothing.
Like you're doing nothing. Absolutely
nothing. I don't even stand. Just just
close the market. If we're if we're not
going to do anything, just close the
market.
Let me have an early Christmas.
[Laughter]
What is Meta doing?
I mean, look at that. What's the [\h__\h]
point? Oh, just pin it. Let's just pin.
What's the point in trading right now if
that's what we're doing? That's the
sentiment. We just pin everything now.
I'm telling you guys, it's zero DTE have
completely [\h__\h] these markets the last
five years. Everyone's like, increased
volatility is better. It It ruins. so
many things they they should just get
rid of them.
And we don't need footprint
to help a rotating market. You can you
can see it here, right? You can see it
here, right? We already know we're in a
rotation. It's a see money, take money
market. We we already know that. My
problem is not seeing it. My problem is
that we're in it. I don't want to be in
it. I've got I've got no problem seeing
it. I can see that we're in it. I don't
want to be in it. I want to be in a
trending market.
Okay. So, rejecting. Didn't even get to
610s now.
Oh my god. Blow my brains out. I'm going
to blow my brains out.
So, we're going to come and test this
gray box. This last shelf. This shelf
here. All right. So, this was your
overunder. All right. They dipped and
dipped and dipped and failed and came
back and failed and failed and got over
and now they want to see if they can
hold this and if they can hold this they
can look for that rotation. My danger
would be that could be a two-legg like
this a two leg and if they want to
resell this under here they come back
down for this again. I don't know how
you're going to continue to play in a
tightening range. This is getting
smaller by the way not bigger.
Like I've got no problem, guys. Like I
I'm I'm nicely green. It's the problem
is not being green. It's the fact that
I'm bored. Um I can't size in to
anything.
It's not that I can't read it. It's that
if you ask me a market that I don't want
to trade, I will always tell you a
rotation. I don't like trading rotation
because for me I'm looking for 50 point
TP1 100 200 point bangers which means I
need to get out of a rotation to get
that I need to get out of it. For
example, if we leave value,
right? If we if we trapped buyers here
and trapped some more here and came down
here and rejected this, right, where I
took that first position on and we came
back down here and we rejected this,
that would be my size in point. And then
I'm going, oh, wicked 100 points. Who
knows? Maybe we get lucky and we come
down to previous week value area low.
All right, trend trade leaving volume
trapped. that for me that's my A+
that's what I want to trade I don't want
to trade this man I don't want to become
the volume I want to use people's pain I
don't want to become the volume so and
that's why I had an attempt what did I
trade I traded this down to here
and then I put one on here and we traded
away and came back and I was like no
done not going to hold that because if
they're going to squeeze through it like
I said we come 60s reclaim 60s there's
your IB to VWOP trade so I don't want to
be the side of that.
Exactly, Troy. That That is exactly my
point.
Croc [\h__\h] Did I say that? I do. It's
very English thing to say. It's probably
what I said. Yay. I agree. Inferris that
December's been awful so far. I mean,
I'm I'm green, so I shouldn't complain.
But it's been bad. I mean, let's have a
look at how we're looking on the higher
time frames. Let's just let's just go
back. Let's take stock of where we are
right now. Okay.
This volume looks good, doesn't it?
I guarantee that this is not going to
close higher than this. Not unless we
break out. All right. So, let's just
think about what the daily's done. Let's
think about the weekly model. We can
reset this. Uh here's your
Monday, Tuesday.
There's I don't want to give away too
much edge. Here's your weekly model for
those who have done the course.
We're not getting outside of the weekly
model. So, what are we going to do? Oh
god. You know what we're going to do? If
we can't get outside the weekly model,
we're going to get stuck. Monday low,
Tuesday high. Okay, so we're stuck.
Let's have a look what we've done the
last few days. Right, let's go from
where's Monday? Okay, so Monday, right?
This flush happened overnight,
reclaimed.
Look below, fell. Look above, fell.
Closing side. Fantastic. Okay, next day.
What do we do the next day? Look below,
hold, look above, breakout. Okay, great.
We finally get a breakout, right? We're
closing high. Well done. Tuesday.
Wednesday open, dip back down, hold the
low. Would have liked to seen that sweep
first, but close back inside. Okay, so
we close inside. We peak above. So, it's
a look above and fail again. So, so far
we've done a look above and a look below
and fail. A look above, a look above.
And guess what we're doing today? A look
above and fail. What's that telling you
for me? that what this is telling me is
that as much as we're drifting higher
on declining volume, is that a good
thing? No, it's not a good thing. If we
keep looking above and failing but
grinding higher, what's that telling
you? Means there's passive sellers up
here. It means if buyers were going to
be really aggressive and step in this
market, right? Then they should be
coming up here and smashing us higher,
shouldn't they? They shouldn't be keep
doing that and close and that and close
down and that and close down on a higher
time frame. That is not what you want
you would want to see if if you're
looking for a continuation higher.
That's not what you'd want to see. Am I
surprised? No, because we've got an old
balance range here. Of course, I'm not
surprised to see that. What it tells me
then, stop bidding it here then buyers.
Let it come down to an area where maybe
they're going to be interested in buying
more size and then we've got a better
shot at going upside. That's what I
would like to see happen. That's what
will fill me with confidence. If we can
come down and hold a bid down here and I
can see, you know, an increase in volume
down here and the next day we start
going up, then guess what? We're going
to come for these and we're going to
come for these. That's a much better
look. But at the moment, this incessant
grind but close back down is not good
look, folks. It's really not a good
look.
We have a look at the spiders. It's
probably going to be even worse.
I mean, this is dreadful, guys. There's
your box on the spiders. Those in
Discord, we know we've talked about it.
Look above yesterday, fail. Look above
today, fail. We're just back down to
that same point, right? They should be.
If they're really chomping at the bit
for alltime highs, why are they not
bidding 83s to get us up there?
Yeah, that's how I see it. Why are we
not if if we're going alltime highs, if
they've spent 1, two, three, four, five
days building out this sort of range
here, you can clearly see we're pinned
in. Why are you not holding the top of
this range, 84s, 83s, whatever you want
to call it, for that move to fill this
gap and get to alltime highs? Why not do
that?
Because all they want to do is trap 85
to 80 right now. Well, today it's 82.
Where's 82? There you go. So, we move
gamma up from 80 to 82 and we can't get
through 85. So, they're going to do this
again. What happens if we do this long
enough and then we come under here? I
tell you what happens. That happens. And
that's my worry right now. And that's
also anyone with any common senses worry
is that if you're going to build a range
here for this long and you had the
opportunity to go higher and you're not,
that tells me that it probably is going
to go lower.
So that I'd say how we close this week
is going to matter. It's going to really
matter if we go to a weekly chart.
If we close
under this, that's a look above again.
Everyone's going to go, it's really
bullish.
We're probably going to come back down
and revisit this.
It's messy. It's definitely messy. And
really, if you want to if you want to
make it really simple, we've been pinned
in since se September.
We've been pinned in since September,
really.
And tops, all right, tops take a long
time to form. If this is going to be a
top, I'm not saying it is going to be a
top, but if we get under here again,
you're going to have months then of
trapped volume and that rotation back to
the 200 becomes highly, highly probable.
And you'll see, look how long tops take
to form,
right? It takes a long time. This looks
familiar, doesn't it? What happens when
we break down, retest, big flush, right?
Let's find some more.
Long time to form
retest. Retest move away from it. Right?
They don't happen. Okay. They happen
quick here, but that was unprecedented
events. That was COVID. It's a little
bit different. Right? So, that's what
I'm concerned about when I look at the
charts. If we're not moving higher,
there's a reason we're not moving
higher. That's all I'm going to say.
That's my two cent anyway. That's what
concerns me at the market. That's why
I'm not swinging long any new money
positions right now. It's for a reason.
Affordable indicators. I think it's
should just be FCT. Um,
[Music]
I'll post it in chat view.
There you go. That's your affordable
indicators code should work with that.
But it should be FCT.
Oh my god, more people reaching out.
some dodgy prop firms out there right
now.
Okay, so still reclaiming here again.
I'm not touching this. I've absolutely
promised myself I'm not going to touch a
rotation. You guys, if you like
rotation, you should by all means take
this. This is like yesterday and the day
before. I'm I just don't want to touch a
rotation. I've made my money. If I've
made my money, I'm even less inclined to
do anything with it.
We can have a look at what's going on in
the broader market if you want. Let's
move this to a five minute. See how
we're doing. ES.
Okay. Just stuck. Same kind of story.
All right. There's your divergence
though. Didn't make a new low when ENQ
did. Coming back to VWOP. So, IB to
VWOUP trade. It's got to get back above
PDC uh to have a chance of completing
that rotation. We're not seeing that at
the moment. Let's have a look at gold.
Nice drive. Is it following silver? Is
it starting to reclaim everything?
Not yet.
Not yet. Still can't get through that
supply. Uh let's have a look at the mag.
Okay. So, you can see this level we
talked about this morning on Apple. We
said 82 break. It's going to be in
trouble. That's where we set the price
alert this morning. Why? Because this
was your shelf.
Okay, so this is your classic failure
pattern up here. Right, there's your
fail. Fails to hold this base. We trade
under it. It's got a last chance saloon
right here in 82. It fails 82. And like
you can see this level we put in here.
So it probably is going to come down to
78s. Now this is the market we talked
about pre this is the level we talked
about premarket. Lose 82, you're
probably coming back into these 78s. All
right. And if we trade sideways there,
it's a bigger problem. All right. So
understand like this is sentiment of
whole market right now. If we trade
sideways here, all right, after a big
squeeze, we're opening that up, aren't
we? All right, so if you want to be
bullish, you need 78s to hold and you
need reclaims of of uh 82s. All right,
Amazon
weak as well. All right, so selling off,
never reclaiming, trading near and
around the lows of day.
This doesn't look very pretty. It's
underneath initial balance. So, this is
showing you text heavy, but we are into
an old rotation. You can see here, this
is where they sold from reclaim. This is
your RBS zone. So, I'd say Amazon 27s
down to 23s will now be your area of
rotation. This is why it's trying to
find a bid here around 27s. There you
go. So, just structural. So, if you want
to see how I play these swings and what
I look at, this is what I look at. All
right. Goo falling off a cliff. All
right. huge drive yesterday. They just
said no more. Thanks very much. And
we're coming back to reality. All right.
So, can it find a bid here again? If it
starts losing this bid, what will this
be? There's your peak. Failed to
reclaim. Failed to reclaim. There's your
bull trap. There's your squeeze under
here. You're going to get a lack of
structure for a move back down to the
low 300s possible. So far, I'm not
seeing anything in tech which is filling
me with confidence. Meta. All right.
This is also not great. It's probably
holding a 50%. Let's just have a look.
Yes, there you go. So, surprise
surprise. So, traded upside big squeeze
pre-market off news. Pulls back to the
61. Now, just trading at the 50. Nothing
you can do with that. That's a leave
alone and wait and see what happens
tomorrow. Obviously, I'm long from the
80s, right? I'm long from 580s down
here.
I remember when I got long. I did put it
in Discord for everyone. Let's have a
look. When did I get long?
Here you go. So 19th. So I've been long
since the 19th of November. I put feeler
on today. Super light. Right. So one of
the advantages being in the Discord, I
always say if I'm getting into a swing
position. So there you go. So, even if
you joined me on that from 580s,
well, we were up over $100 a share this
morning and we're still up pretty good.
We're up uh $85 a share. Very good. I'm
not sized in though. Like I said, not
sized in, but I felt like, if you want
to know why, when we came down here,
for me, we were cheap versus the market.
All right, there's our pivot in April.
There's our peak formation. There's the
pullback. This meant made sense to me
for at least a bounce right into the 61
at least a bounce which we've done right
then we got stuck today in the gap. Now
the other thing is we're moving Meta's
announced it's moving from GPUs to TPU
processors which means what in the next
earnings report over here in February
you're probably going to see a really
nice earnings report because it's going
to drastically reduce the costs and if I
can get that gap fill if the market does
want to go again I'm not going to let it
come back underneath my entry but if I
can get that gap fill right we're going
to make what $170 a share So,
we're happy with that. Microsoft, see
what Microsoft's doing today.
Absolutely nothing. All right. Flat.
It's that previous day close. No, no
change there at all. Nvidia, it's trying
to get going.
It's trying to get going. That's a good
thing to see. Maybe it wake this market
up. Right. There's your channel. There's
the hold. Nvidia. If we can hold
pullbacks and start getting back through
these, we can get back into this old
range. Right, we're still in a range. We
can get back into this old range here.
And then through 190s, we've got a shot
of those 200s and highs again. So,
Nvidia's trying to find a bid.
Tesla
looks like it's flat. Yeah, just at the
New York open. All right. So, that's why
market's not really doing much. You can
look a bit outside. Oracle, this thing's
not looking good debtwise. I was tempted
to take a long into this a couple days
ago, but I looked at the balance sheet
and it's not looking great.
They might have a debt problem here on
Oracle. Though maybe the Fed come out
and say that I think we're still going
to see weakness for a gap fill into 170
here. So that's why I haven't bid on
that. Um AMD, I'm still long from 158.
Still long from here, but I sold 80% of
it up here.
That's it.
Oscar, I cut
because we're not doing anything. I was
having a go at long here and we just
couldn't break out. So, should have
taken more profit off that. That's it
really.
Nothing else to look at right now,
folks.
Anything you guys want me to go through
before I leave for the day? 15 minutes
left for lunch.
Oh, sorry. Would be nice for you to keep
giving bookmap info for those of you who
are long. Well, look, you're okay. I
don't know where you're long. Where are
you long from, chat?
You long from IB reclaim or previous day
or this level here? As long as you're,
it depends which one you're long from,
but you know, all the time you're
holding this shelf, potential rotation
into 610s. Let go of this shelf, then
they come back and back. We're just
going to back test. All right. So, it's
literally IB here, here, here, uh, here,
and here. So, all we're doing, if you
think about, all we're doing all day is
testing one level, one level, one level,
next level, next level, next level, next
level, next level, next level. See how
we move? We're just moving from level to
level.
So your risk should be from level to
level. So if you're long here, you're
partial here and you're holding for
here. If you're long here or partial
here, partial here, partial here,
because you don't know if they let go of
this level, they probably come back down
to value. And if they let go of that,
they come back down to IB. And if they
let go of that, then maybe finally they
move down into this.
You're long from right here. I'd say
this is not trying to be a dick. This is
probably your the worst position you can
be long from because your point of
control. So this is the most traded area
of the day.
Probably better off being long from here
or you know on a retest of this. But
yeah, I would say you don't want to lose
60s. If you lose 60s here, you're going
to trade 44s. And if you lose 44s,
you're going to trade 20s. And if you
lose 20s, you're going to trade 84 80s.
And if you lose that, you're going to
trade 420s. If you reclaim 600s, you're
going to retest tens. And if you get
through that, you're going to test 40s.
But remember, we have buyers stuck at
35. This is why being good at numbers is
important. We come back up here on the
book. 635.
So I can see here, where have you got
buyers offside, right? 595, big buyers
offside. I'm going to give you all the
levels. 600 buyers offside. 60
405 big buyers offside. These are all
buyers who have market ordered in and
got stuck. Right. Let's keep going. So,
you can mark these out if you want. 605.
Need this book to slow down for a
minute. D
635 is another level. So, that's the
that was the peak where we had buyers
caught. 635.
All right. So, I'd say all those levels
I just gave you are where buyers are
stuck. Right. 635 up here. Big level.
So, you need this peak formation to come
and close over 600 really. And you'd be
watching this 24-hour view up. All
right. And if you can get through that,
maybe they come and test this block up
here.
But I say the best long was that retest
of IB where I was trying to fight it a
little bit. That was probably the best
long. And then here into 60s. It's
holding 60s though, so you look good.
What is the range for ES?
Well, you're at the edge of one now. So,
we're boxed in here.
80s to 50s. And if you get a sentence
above 80s, we can look for 68. Right. So
80s to is it 80s?
Sorry 60s. God I can't even see 860.
This level here is your edge and the
lower edge is 850. So you got a 10point
range here on ES. You need to find
acceptance above pullback and hold 60
for a rotation all the way up into let's
call it 65.
And that's where same thing as
on cues. I would imagine if I have a
look at the book up there, we find some
buyers who got caught up there. Let's
have a little look.
What was that level
time? 1040.
Yeah. So you had buying into that on the
way up
the size there. So you had
from
64s on ES. You had like a 280 bid, then
a 240 bid, then 176, 150, 143. This
guy's a big guy. So you had a 754 lot
trade at 684
and then after that he got washed out.
So look at that volume. 2,488 lot
dropped it under 860. So I'd say uh you
want to be very very careful if you get
anywhere near 6864 on ES because that's
where they all got stuck above.
So you're you're getting into it now. If
we look at putmat now you're getting
into this area now. So, this is where
that guy got stuck. 64 is where he got
stuck. 64
up to 68.
64 up to 68 on ES. That's where they got
stuck. So, if they become sellers,
right, if you were a buyer up there and
they didn't sell for whatever reason,
this is going to be the supply zone that
they're going to get stuck in.
Yeah. His big order was he had a 491 lot
6864 6865 somewhere around there.
So, I would be taking some profit into
that and then holding runners in case
you get an expansion on a stop hunt.
Like, if you get that, great. But don't
expect it in a range rotating day.
Tanish is asking, can anyone here guide
them on the flow zone course in
indicators? So, any of you here who have
done the course or use the indicator,
let Tanish know what it's like. Better
to come from someone else and you get an
honest opinion rather than whatever I
say.
I'll be right back, folks. Use the
bathroom.
Can anyone here help Tanish? Any current
students?
Must be some of you on here. Maybe
you've all gone to bed.
Do I think this is going to break out?
Uh I think we're going to get a stop
hunt. I think this is going to take out
these highs, these uh internal highs.
I don't know if it can sustain a bid,
but I think we're going to take out
these highs because there'll be lots of
stops here. And so once we do that, uh,
we'll probably get a violent move
higher. Even if it's not sustained,
you probably see like a spike.
Come on. Come on.
There we go.
I think any push through 43s, you
probably instantly get up to 50s.
You probably instantly get there. It's
probably done like that. If they get
through the 43s, probably so many stops
there, probably instantly pushes
through.
Any break through 40s and 43 should
probably instantly get to 50s and 57s.
Probably like if they do it, it would be
a swipe. So, if they pull back here,
they might encourage more shorts to come
in, right? And then I think the next
attempt
probably
just slams through this to be quite
honest because there's too many stops
there now. It's going to be too juicy
for them to ignore. Let me just check
where SPY is trading at. Want to be
aware of that 85 level. All right, we
know 85 is the pin on Spy. Okay, I don't
think Spy probably gets through 85.
Currently trading 8430, so it's got
room. So, I I imagine this will break.
If you want my opinion, this will break
out through these highs and squeeze it.
Like I said, I think that anything down
here probably gets absorbed and then a
stop hunt through here and you probably
just see a swipe up. And if you're in
this long, you better be selling that
swipe. You better be taking profit
because there's no guarantee that it
doesn't do this afterwards.
But, you know, if you're long from I
think Jack and some others were long
from here, you look good. You get a
swipe through here, that's almost 100
points. sell like 80% of it and hold a
runner in case you get all the way up
here.
Or you can front run it if you really
want to.
How many micros are allowed with Apex?
What size account are you trading, Chad?
How do you know when price is accepted
above or below a level? because it will
get above it and then it will hold,
right? It get above it and hold. So, see
this level here?
We didn't
get above it and fell under, did we? We
got above it and held. They held the
base. They tried again. They held the
base. All right. So, that's the new
level. If they want to come down and
test this, they can. We know there's
volume here. They can come all the way
down here. Right. So, if you want to see
price above this,
you would need to hold above that for
acceptance.
Getting through it doesn't mean
anything. That's a stop hunt. That's why
I'm saying if you spike through this,
you better be selling some of your
profit into it because there's no
guarantee
it doesn't do this. And you don't want
to give the whole thing back.
Doesn't matter what time frame you're
looking at. It's a hold on any market.
It's closing above. It's absorbing at
that new level.
How long have I been trading for? Um,
fulltime probably six years, but I mean
I was trading long before that in my uh
early 20ies. I am 40 now. So, okay. So,
like I said, I think we'll be absorbed
here. I think this will be a trap for
bears to come and try and attack versus
this. and you will see a squeeze out
here, folks. So, stop hunt incoming.
Make sure you sell some of your profits
in this stop hunt. All right, stop hunt
should happen from sort of 40 to 43.
We've got liquidity above, I believe.
Yeah, we've got liquidity up above into
50. So, I think once you get through the
40 43, you probably see a little spike
high. Make sure you're taking some
profit in that.
I've just got one eye on spy because I
know 85 is a big big level on spy 685.
So here we go. Stop hunt incoming. First
lot just got popped there. Second lot
will be above 43. And then you should
see a swipe. Should see a swipe above
43.
I look no older than 32. I'll take that.
It's very kind of you.
There's 42s. Here's 43s. You should see
a stop hunt coming incoming. There's
46es. I want to see you trade to 50s and
through it. Make sure you're selling
through this stop hunt, though. I think
you're going to get up there. Remember,
this is previous day point of control.
This is the biggest level traded
yesterday. So, there's your stop hunt.
So if you don't get acceptance above
this, we will just collapse right the
way downside now. So this was your stop
hunt through this and 43s.
There's your stop hunt through this.
Okay, rejecting previous day point of
control. You should have sold the
majority of your position. Those of you
who are long from here, because this can
collapse all the way back down to 600,
and you don't really want to give 40
points back, do you as we're approaching
lunch in 2 minutes?
So you can hold runners, but you should
have sold a a good chunk of your
position for for that move through 43.
Hopefully that made sense for you all.
ES still not done it. All right, if ES
does play catchup,
what's ES got a break here? ES has got
to get through
6875 and really got to get back above
72. But I think the spiders are going to
make it harder for it to do that. That
previous day high on the spiders and
that big uh block above is going to make
it a little bit harder.
So again, we're still in rotation.
I should have flipped long here. Should
have absolutely flipped long there. The
moment I stopped out, I should have been
flipping long knowing that we're going
to be looking at that. But I [\h__\h]
hate rotation.
I hate it. There's previous day value
high value low point of control. Lack of
acceptance below. Lack of acceptance
below. First higher low. Reclaim current
point of control. TP1 up here is TP2. If
you get it,
nice inferrisk. Good work, man. Great
work. Payout coming your way.
still holding. It's still holding. I
hope you get a squeeze here, guys, for
you guys that are long. But just be
careful. This, remember, this is the
most contested level from yesterday. And
we do have supply above, right? So, if
we look left, this is a big level. This
is where we closed yesterday. This is
where the most volume was traded
yesterday, right? And overnight,
right? This is a huge, huge zone in
here. Huge, huge zone. Do not expect, do
not be entering long late. That's a
better way of me putting it. Do not
expect price to get through this. If it
gets through it for your runners,
fantastic. But think about how straight
up you've been since that hold.
Straight up since that hold. We expect
failures here. We hope it doesn't fail
here and you get a squeeze, but we
expect this level to be highly
contested,
would
have, would have, should have. Could
have, would have, should have.
All
right, folks. If you haven't got any
more questions, I'm going to jump out of
here.
Spy uh did just take one of the key
levels. So, the only thing left for it
to trade up to is 85 if it wants to go.
This can this can pull back violently.
It's done its main job here. All right,
you've done the main rotation here. If
this wants to pull all the way back down
into where you have volume, it will.
Where's my pen? All right. So, just be
careful. Those of you who are long, you
don't want it to start flushing
underneath this node here. So, if it
loses 30, you're going to get to 600.
You don't want to give back 60 odd
points, do you? So, you need this to
hold 30 for a continuation. Any failure
under 30, I'd be very, very cautious. I
would not be adding long up here either,
by the way. Those of you who took the
long here or here or here,
congratulations. Really good trades.
Like really good trades. This long down
here slightly tougher if I'm honest.
Like, but you did hold and you got the
buy signal,
sell signal, buy signal. That's all you
had to do today. Just follow the bloody
flow zones when you start getting
openings.
Danny Snites, thank you, Alex. took my
profit one step closer to passing my TPT
accounts. Just two to three dates more
to go. Hey, awesome, man. They're
probably my favorite accounts in the
market. I think they are
so so good. Uh, cannot beat daily
payouts. They are the best. They would
change your lives. Daily payouts, man.
It start building confidence. Even if
they're small payouts, it will build
confidence into your trading.
All right, folks. Any questions?
Otherwise, I'm going to going to jump
off.
Remember that Apex sale has just
started. What day does that end? I
should probably let you guys know.
Here's a good sale. The more I look at
it, the better I think it is.
When does it end? December
9th. Okay. So, you got you got five days
for it. December 9th. Um, I would say
if you want the bigger accounts, now's
the time to do it. still good for 50ks
and stuff, but if you're looking to do
the 150, 250, or 300k accounts, now is
the time to do it because it's going to
cost you
84 bucks all in with activation.
That's probably the cheapest you're ever
going to get a 300k account for. That's
insane.
Absolutely insane.
Does it look like a good time to short
ES? Uh,
I mean, you're at the edge of a range.
Momentum's been bullish. You failed to
break the low.
You could try a cheap short here, but I
don't love it. But, you know, I don't
love range rotation. But, if there's a
short here, it's probably down to this
point here. All right. And if they bid
off that, they're going to go back for
the highs. If they fail that, then
they're going to go back for the lows.
That's the midpoint in the range, right?
So, it's exactly the same as ENQ. We
just talked about this on ENQ. If NQ
can't hold uh this little node here at
30s, which we're about to draw 28, which
we're just trading into now. If it
doesn't hold that, it slams all the way
down to 600. Again, why it's telling you
make sure you're taking profit in the
stop hunt up here, previous days point
of control, previous days close. If they
don't hold here, they will slide back
down into this area of value. I would
not rebid this either. You'd need it to
see it hold the top of that. But again,
we've taken one side, we've taken the
other, right? We've taken this side.
Think about what we've done today. We
take this side, we come this side, we
come this side, we come this side. If it
doesn't hold this, we come this side
again. It's just a rotational market.
It's a C money, take money event. That's
it. All right, folks. I am going to get
out of here. Um those in Discord I will
pop in there this afternoon but all the
way all the time we're trading inside of
previous day's value. I'm not really
interested. Uh let's set some price
alerts before we go. So we set one here,
previous day value area low and we will
set one for a breakout
above previous day value area high.
All this does folks is it messages me on
my phone. It stops me having to watch
the market all the time because I'm only
interested once we get out of value. All
right, so white lines. They will notify
me on my phone. Ding, ding, ding, ding,
ding. And then I can get back to the
chart if I want.
All right, team. All of you good.
Congrats today. Especially those who
just got that long. Really nice. And
that might be trade of the day.
That might be the trade of the day.
Those of you who who took the rotation,
really really good. And uh yeah, we go
again tomorrow. Uh, those of you trading
ES, make sure you are watching 682, 685
on SPY and 680. Those are your levels.
Those are where they're pinning us
between. All right, so your rotations,
those are your levels. All right, peace
and love. Use hard stops. Be kind to
each other. All that good stuff. If you
want to use any of my code, FCT is
always the best code to use other than
on TPT where you can use Flowzone. All
that money just goes back into the
channel. Helps me get editors to create
more content and education for you guys.
And uh yeah, I'll see you again real
soon. Peace out.