Morning everyone. Morning. Morning. How
are we doing chat? Hope you had a good
day yesterday. Uh I think we caught the
best moves in the morning. Probably
could have held those longs yesterday a
little bit longer, couldn't we? Could
have, would have, should have, but a
couple 100 point trades and as ever as
soon as I got off stream, the wash came
in. All right, we got that big wash
yesterday that I was looking for off
those highs which was then the
reaccumulation long moment and today we
are opening up with an inside bar. All
right, so we've had three drives so far
off the low. We can see this 200 day
moving average which we found a bid on.
All right, we came all the way to the
upside, closed inside on that week,
dipped down yesterday which held for
that expansion up and we are going to
respect this today. All right, we're
creating an inside bar. Right, we do
have some targets above if they do want
to continue to keep going. Now, if it is
a full mean reversion, as we know, it
will be the lower bowl to the 20-day.
I'm just having a look across right now
to just make sure, have we already done
that on uh the QQQ? No, we haven't.
Okay, so that's still an available uh
shot. We have relative strength in uh
the spiders and ES with a spy opening up
at alltime highs right now. All right.
So, we have this shot if we're going to
do an outside bar break. We have the 200
day and we have this shelf here. All
right. In towards 600s and then 660 is
this gray box across. All right. This is
from the most recent high. If we go from
the last year, right, we will see the
same kind of shelf as we get into the
600. So, there's 600 and then through
600 we get thin up to 677 or 700. So,
you might want to mark that out. As we
move into the hourlys, we can get a clue
of what we're looking at as we've been
developing a range all the way through
yesterday's afternoon and overnight
here. So, we had a P-shape profile
yesterday and we're now developing a
range, right? So, you can see this
P-shaped profile, right, also being
developed on the current developing
week. Remember, this is our current
developing week value area. So, we found
a bid yesterday, we've ripped up, and
we've now developed a lot of volume up
here, right? So, the edge of this volume
really that we're looking at right now
is
uh I'd say I'm watching the sort of the
330s, 300s, um all the way into this
high. And uh right now we are holding
dips. Okay, we're holding dips. We want
to be careful. This is a big supply
level right here into previous week
value area high. Not just from the value
week, but if we just look back and see
what a key pivot this was, this area,
these blue lines, failed over, flushed
under, failed over, flushed under, came
over, held the dip, drove, held the dip,
drove, failed over, flushed under,
reflushed under, held the dip, drove
back to the same level, dipped back to
the same level, dipped underneath,
pressure over, dip, pressure. Okay, you
get the point. In here, massive level.
All right. Massive, massive, massive
level in here. So, we need to be aware
of this level. We have to be aware of
this level, which means two things can
happen. We can either set a bull trap
over it or we can reclaim it and look
for a bigger move higher. All right. So,
what I'm watching here today is in these
levels in and around previous day value
area high, previous week value area
high, even this pivot up here. We want
to watch how we act into these nodes. If
the market right drives out and turns
this effectively into demand and is able
to hold, we can think about a drive all
the way up to the up to here for a
retest. Right, we have an old point of
control up here into 800. I want to be
very aware of a bull trap living in this
area here. Why? Because I've just shown
you, we like to do bull traps in this
area. If we drove out, took these stops,
came back under, and did this. Well,
that would be somewhat dangerous for a
rotation back down. So, we will respect
this volume as we start to build it out.
But if we drive and we get stuck, there
is a short back in here. And then if
they keep selling through, we'll
collapse this move back down. All right?
So, I want to be aware of bull traps in
here. If, however, we drive
and we hold, there is room for this
drive higher. If we're going to go into
more of a rotation, then I think we're
going to be somewhat pinned in this same
area. Maybe we expand that area a little
bit. The rotation might look something
like this. All right. It might just be
one of these starting to develop. Okay.
And we can watch previous days value
area. Um I don't see weakness uh
particularly coming in here right now
until we start collapsing under this and
seeing us lose a bid back down to the
25,000. So, we can watch that for sure.
We can watch 300s or if we start to lose
a bit under 300s and reject 300s, we can
use this trap volume for that rotation
back down to 191s and then maybe even
the 100s. It's possible, but I think I'm
more interested in what happens up here
this morning. Unless we get a big
morning flush. Unless we get a big
morning flush. Okay, moving up lower
time frame. You can see how we've acted.
Just chop sideways since yesterday. Same
thing. Just pinned in. All right, since
yesterday. There's your sideways chop.
So, we're boxed in. So, we're trading
edges in this box and failed breakouts
of this box unless we break and hold
above. Okay, very very simple. Make it
simple. I do not want to execute in the
middle of this box. Right? I need to be
looking at the edges and how we act at
the edges. If you execute in the edges
in in the edges, you might have some
edge. If you don't, you're going to get
caught. You are going to get caught. All
right. ES like we talked about. Zoom
this out. Relative strength here. If we
look at the daily, right, we are near
all-time highs. I will take you over to
the spiders, which is already at
all-time highs pretty much. All right,
so we're opening up at 64s. Not quite
there, but we need to take out 97s and
then we're there. So spy very, very
close. Uh just know that every time we
get up here, we have failed to see
follow through. What will spy need to
really get going? It's going to need one
of these. All right, if this undercut
was enough, it's going to need to break
out and hold above for that move. Uh we
can go lower time frame. Have a quick
look at the spiders. All right. So
opening up with a bit of a gap up. Same
kind of story. We're in a range here.
You just want to be careful. If you lose
pre-market low, all right, and they back
test and stay heavy, they will rotate
down into this cluster again. That's all
you need to be aware of. All the time
we're doing this though, any reclaim,
that would be the trap to go higher.
Okay, Dixie still losing a bid. All
right, this is still losing a bid. We
are still seeing weakness. We will
continue to see a rotation back into
gold all the time this happens. I would
leave silver alone. Those of you who are
looking for more upside, gold is the one
which is a hedge right now to the Dixie.
So, we have to watch into here. All
right. If this finds a bid here, this
can get going. Gold will start to sell.
If this starts to collapse under here
and we use this liquidity to go lower,
we will see weakness in the dollar.
Uh D Mr. VIX, you can see where Mr. VIX
is. All right. Still in this uptrending
channel, right? But broke out,
collapsing back in. You know, if we
start losing 18s and 17s for that
rotation to 16s, that will help the spy
start to look for those alltime highs.
Right. Quick look at the mag.
So, sideways here in Apple facing out
down here. Remember, it's been very,
very strong, right? It might just be a
back test of this. It's potential. You
could argue it's backside right here,
but I think until we start taking this
out, you want to be very, very cautious.
If we start losing that, that's a weak
sign for the market. So, right now,
opening up slight gap down, but inside
yesterday's range. So, no follow
through. Amazon
slight gap up.
What happens next in Amazon's key? I'd
be watching it into here and do they
resell that back down? And then what
happens in here? So, if that's the big
flush and this is your first B bounce
moment, do they resell that and do they
find a bid there or do we get follow
through downside? So, Amazon waking up.
It's a bit of a no touch for me down
here. It's got to either flush and hold
or drive up and reject or drive up and
reclaim. Otherwise, not much of a play.
Guess a bit like the cues right now.
Goo. Are we going to get a chart here?
Goo. There we go. All right. Goo opening
up inside yesterday's range. That is
looking pretty ugly right now. All
right. You're getting one of these. Not
very nice. That's a leave alone chart.
Meta back up to this pivot we talked
about. You can see we talked about that
the other day, right? The drive down
wash failed to break lower. Shorts get
trapped. We've now taken out that pivot.
Do we hold some form of higher low here
to get going? Big question for Meta, but
it's very very possible if they do want
to do that. Depends on the strength of
the broader market.
Microsoft, look at that. Absolute
killer. Beautiful. So, we talked about
this range being reclaimed down here.
You can see where I've drawn this out.
Here's the old range. We break down from
that range. First bounce like we talked
about. We reject a trade back inside. We
trade lower and then shorts fail to
break down at the low. This is your long
trigger. They fail to break down and we
go all the way back up running these
stops. And we're now looking to take out
this high at 2020 for 2020. I would
imagine they will want to build some
liquidity here for a moment if possible.
And then once they break that, they'll
be looking for a retest at 22s. This is
the big level right now. the first big
levels into 22s here. And if they start
reclaiming that, then they're going to
just keep looking to trade higher and
higher and higher and repric this, which
is pretty thin up there. I'm going to
assume that was their earnings. Yeah, it
is. So, we're going to come back to the
bottom of earnings. Probably 22. So,
I'll be watching 22s to see how we act
there on Softy.
Just clean that up so next time I look
at it, it is okay. Uh Nvidia,
wow. So big pump yesterday trying to
reclaim some of its old range. Chip
starting to get going with that news
that we had in Asia like we talked about
in Sunday and saw the top side of this
range right now. All right, so Nvidia
holding 70 to 90 acceptance over here
and we will get going and we will start
trying to get back up to alltime highs.
So it doesn't look too bad. It's all
depends what happens here. But again, if
you're a range trader, you're probably
looking to fade that. I would be
somewhat cautious today. If we do this,
that thing can get going. We've been
here a few times. There's lots of stops
to get taken out. Tesla,
it's just an awful looking chart. All
right, there's your bid drive up on the
hourly. We've come back down to that
same area. We haven't undercut it. All
right, that's always a bit of a worry,
but they are holding firm in that bid
right now. Uh, zoom this out a little
bit. Same kind of story as we've just
seen. There's the breakdown, right?
Here's all the liquidity being built.
There's the breakdown. There's the
failure to trade lower. There's the bid
up, back up. So, what happens in here?
420 becomes key that are they able to
hold a bid and get going and run all
these stops out now? Big question mark
over that. It's our first attempt back
in since the 4th of Feb. So, we'd be
watching that area. Now, uh equally
weighted. Let's have a quick look at the
equally weighted mag.
No undercut on the equally weighted. And
what we doing?
Same kind of story we've seen on a lot
of these. All right, trying to do that
sort of inverse head and shoulders look
with a failure to break lower, but we're
coming into key pivot. So, location not
great right now. Oracle, remember, I'm
swing longing this off that low down
here. We're looking pretty good. I'm
probably going to get to a point where
I'm going to have to start locking some
in because this is probably going to
come want to come back down soon. I'd
like a retest up here, but I might pay
myself a little bit and look for a
reload if they flush and hold sort of 44
45 that move back up on the retest of
180. I want to get to 180 and then 208
230s if possible, but a nice trade
there. Very, very nice on that. Uh
Netflix
still basing around. No big mover there.
UU still looks good versus 20s holding
on okay.
US holding on okay pretty much flat on
both of those. And then the other one
for those who took the swing just be
aware that we have earnings tonight.
This has been a really nice push up off
these lows. We have earnings tonight
folks. Just be very very very careful. I
would love to get up to these 102s. I
have paid myself a little bit already
because just in case on earnings we snap
that. I don't think we'll break this low
on earnings, but you just never know in
this market. You never know in this
market. I think the earnings will be all
right.
All right, couple minutes here. Let's
get ourselves set up and zoomed in.
All right. So, if you're joining late,
I'll be waiting to see a reaction
ideally up here to see if they're going
to fade this edge or to see if we flip
this and turn it bullish
downside reaction. I'll be watching down
here into this sort of gray box. This is
our developing volume
big level from this week down here. All
right. So, I'll be watching this. I can
even another one down here. Let's just
actually measure overnight quickly. What
that look like?
Be a big D shape.
This edge one of these
here actually.
And previous day
down into 300s.
There we go. All right. I'm watching
these levels coming into the open.
Uh, no big bias today. If you're
wondering what's the bias, what's the
bias? No big bias, guys. All right. Big
P shape yesterday. Technically, a P
shape is bullish, but it's a P shape on
recovery. And we're coming into a big
level. So, no huge bias today.
Um, do me a favor, smash that like
button nice and early so we don't have
to talk about it again.
Let's get through it.
And we've got just over 30 seconds here.
I should say if I haven't said it
already today, go through your morning
routine.
Make sure you've done your morning
routine, whether that be, you know,
meditation or doing your prayers or
rituals in the morning or going for a
run or any of those things. Do not come
to the chart, all right? And just turn
up and expect to be able to trade.
You've got to go through a routine. You
got to make sure you've eaten enough,
drunken enough, got enough sleep, all
that good stuff, right? It's a hard job.
You want to be fresh minded here.
All right, let's see. Here we go, folks.
So, into previous days point of control.
We might come right back down. We're
filling that gap already into PDC, the
yellow line on the screen. Already
finding a bid there, and they're trying
to move it higher. Said I'm not too
interested in that. That's just a wash,
dip, and rip. Opening up on the MAG, we
can have a look. Apple
uh sorry, Tesla 0.66% up. Nvidia 1% up.
Microsoft 0.73% up. Meta half% down.
Google 1.26% down. Amazon half% down.
Apple just under half% down. Complete
mixed bag on the MAG. Uh VIX opening up
right at PDC.
And uh yes, trying to drive higher here.
Right. Spy chart up here. So we can just
have a look. Yeah, SPY not through
previous days high yet or overnight
high. There was a morning wick on spy up
to 9650 interestingly.
All right, back to previous day point of
control and the current developing week
point of control. This red line on your
screen. So, we keep finding bids around
here right now. This is fair value for
the week and for the previous day right
now. So, we just got to watch. Do they
want to bid this or not? Back into the
400s. They're looking for that squeeze
back into these highs. I'd be very
careful as we get back into here if
you're taking this long. It's not a long
that I want to take. Didn't want to take
it yesterday. Don't want to take it
today. I think it's very dangerous up
into here.
broader market. Uh RT YM again YM
alltime highs yesterday now trading at
50,450.
Amazing
for me. It's the most manipulated market
ever. The YM it's got nothing in it.
Okay, back down. Failing that red box. I
said as I said I' not it's not a long I
want up into that today. All right, gap
now filled. Fully filled into this
yellow line. efficient market. Q's
haven't filled the gap yet, by the way.
Spy holding on. Well, sellers getting
caught at those lows at 55s. We are just
choppy, choppy, choppy.
Yeah, very choppy. Um, we we expect chop
today, right? We want to play the edges.
The only attempt to get up to an edge
has been that spike and we didn't get
there and we sold it instantly. We're
coming back down to the midpoint in this
range right now. But we just got to give
this a chance to settle down, folks.
This is not a day where you'll see some
days I want to attack the open. Some
days they trap and set up something very
early. Right now we're trading right in
the middle of that P shape we developed
this week. Right? So since this Sunday
open,
we're just trading right in the middle
of this. We think about this.
Here's your your rip. That was what we
developed and we're trading right here.
There's no edge here, right? We want to
be at an edge. So we can think about a
fail breakout or a break and hold. bail
breakout or a break and hold. We don't
want to really execute in here. It's not
the best setup in there. Very, very
risky.
So, bidding off that gap.
Market starting to go green here other
than Google. So, Apple and Amazon
starting to claw back, fill their gaps.
ES looks like it wants to get going
here. Not quite through
uh GlobeEx yet. It keeps trying. That
7,000 level is probably going to be
massive, I would assume, on ES.
Uh same on SPX. Got a little while to go
to get on SP.
Today, a short day. Today, a range
rotation day. It might end up being a
short day.
All we've That's the only edge yet. I
would like to see a clear out up here.
If we're going to if we're going to fade
it, I'd prefer to see them steal some
liquidity and then dump back inside and
give us something to risk off for a
range rotation fade. I don't really want
to be fading that opening drive in. It's
a bit risky. Um, where could we fade it
down to? Well, potentially down to these
gray boxes, right? And we need to see
underneath this
underneath this level here. So, they
will need to make a decision of if they
trap or if they want to wash. But in
here, I don't want to trade. We talked
about this in the uh first 15 minutes of
today's stream. I'm trying to avoid
trading in the middle of this range.
This is where you'll get chopped up.
How do I determine how wide to make the
gray box? just based on the nodes, based
on the volume nodes.
Jumpy book again today.
Patience, guys. Patience. ES failing to
break out of uh Gloveex there.
I'll wait for these gray boxes to be
attacked and then see what happens.
fix reclaiming PDC.
Just make sure you're zooming out, guys.
That's all I'm going to say to you. Make
sure you're zooming out. We are in
nothing more and a range right now. Just
zoom out. Go to five minute. Look at
yesterday. Look at today. This is all
we're in, folks. This is all we're in
right now.
So bidding off PDC back to New York open
back to previous state point of control.
Let's get some volume in here for the
day now as well.
Remember not every day it will be a
perfect trading day especially when we
need to build liquidity.
volume profile settings. They are
they're in the chat even and they are in
the lessons on Discord. They're in free
lessons on YouTube. Two ticks anchored
volume profile 930 set to the right.
Very, very easy. Right. Sellers last
came in here at 80s. Let's see if they
defend 80s here. Yes, they are defending
80s still. And sellers keep getting
stuck at 62s and 54s and under. So, just
tight 20 point rotations right now. Back
to the 54s again. back to VWAP. Will
they come back down to this gray box
now? Yes. Right. So, those sellers
defending 80s right now
and keep trying to attack here to go
lower. They're not really getting their
way yet. There is some bids down at 25.
They might look for a continuation down
to 25s into the gray box.
Here we go.
Do they absorb this one or the next one
or none of them? All of that possible?
Starting to see some continuation
through this one now. Watching this.
Do we come into this next level and then
how we act at these 300s becomes key.
They can set a bear trap here. We can do
this is coming to sort of the edge of
the range here to here. So, do they set
bear traps down here is the question I
have right now.
If not, what's that? Globeex 280s. 280s
maybe somewhere down there.
So, we'll see if we lose this range.
We're very, very, very thin. Sort of
under 300. Under 300, we can get back to
200 very quickly. So, we're watching
this now to see, do they set a trap
here?
This is coming towards the edge of the
range. Do we trap bears down here and
rip back into the inside of the range or
are we going to come all the way down
here for a retest? Are we going to give
back yesterday's move? That's what we
need to decide. There can very well be a
trap down here. It's been set. Lots of
sellers coming in there at 10. Lots of
sellers coming in there at 10. Watching
these kind of levels down here now.
Watching GlobeEx at 78 as well if they
want to clean that out.
They are adding liquidity lower
now filled its gap. SPY about to fill
its gap as well. 94s on SPY.
Lots of sellers down here. Watching this
10 level. 1012 level. They keep selling
underneath still.
Buyers stepping in back to these 10 and
12s. Watching if we see acceleration
through here or if they defend it.
Still being defended so far. Absorption
on the tape there from sellers.
Think about a trigger long if they get
back through that. But at the moment
they're holding it. Watching this
carefully.
Still sellers defending that.
Buyers bidding down at 80 right now. So
maybe one more flash lower.
We'll see.
These twelves shelf being developed
here. As you can see, sellers still
defending that. They want 280s right
now. So, it's a big sort of battle down
here in this this gray box down here. If
they snap this, they're looking for down
here.
Building liquidity out here while they
make their decision.
They cannot get through. There's a level
here sort of twelves where the seller
keeps defending it the edge of that
shelf and buyers keep getting caught
there. If we get acceleration over it,
there'll be a long trigger. Here we go.
Here's the squeeze. So, in long, very
small size now for the squeeze up
through the twelves. Here we go. Right.
Moving my stop break even because it is
nothing more than a squeeze. I would
want 23s to be protected. Here we go.
Looking for a drive towards VWAP and an
imbalance. Peeling some off there in
case seeing a seller step in at 30s.
Want a bid to hold here into these 22s.
Bid has to hold 22s here. Now
I've seen a big buyer come on the tape
there at 22s. Can we hold this force
through
22s? 22s. 22s. Any flush of 22s? I'm
out.
They're trying to defend it. They're
offer. They're bidding 15s which I don't
like. On that bid step up from 15s.
Out. Out on that. They might retract and
go, "I'm out."
They do it the moment I said it.
Okay. Shelf developed down here. You can
see the shelf being developed. So, once
we got through these twelves here, there
was a rip up that squeeze back up. We
said we might well trap bears down here.
Not convinced that it's done yet, but
the low of day auction into 300 was
really good. Right. to this level down
here. We've started to see bears get
trapped down at these lows right now,
but they're going to have to defend 12.
So that's that was the pivot. This level
there now that we're coming into this
node here, they need to defend this the
buyers otherwise it will be a new low of
day probably.
Maybe one more flush lower.
Dropping more sellers at that low of
day. They should flush lower here. Here
we go. So, they're coming for GlobeEx,
the orange line. Okay. If we stay heavy
under here, we have a move down to this.
All right. Big. This is the big level
where they either trap or we say no, no
acceptance. So, we're either going to do
this or we're going to do one of these
back up for the day and come to the
other side of the range up here. These
are the things you need to be aware of.
This why this level interests me down
here. Both both sides.
See if there's liquidity much lower on
the book. 200s is there.
So Tesla the strong one today 1 point
uh4% up. Microsoft over half% up. Rest
of the market's gone red. We are
bleeding back down giving away some of
yesterday's gains. Coming into some key
pivots here though. Coming into some key
pivots on the hourly.
And we are going we are now undercutting
yesterday's levels. They make the
decision here. Right here right now.
Either we're going to value or they're
going to trap right now. They have to
make a decision. So far, we're staying
heavy, but there's lots of selling
coming in down here. They need to break
lower and soon. Here we go. 70s. So, can
we get all the way down to 18s now and
20s? We have lots of imbalances down
there. Previous week closed, by the way,
is not out of the question. So, sellside
staying heavy and this will be the
target down here now
unless they do a trap in the midpoint of
it, which will be gross. Pivot to pivot.
If we look at the hourly,
all right, this is the undercut of this.
This is an hourly pivot. This is an
imbalance.
We can still do this. It can afford to
come right back here and still bid up
off it. All right. Need to be aware of
that.
Sellers coming in aggressive at those
lows under 86es right now.
Come on.
Do they trap here?
Imagine they'd go a bit deeper than trap
down here. They should have either saved
it or gone deeper. Imagine this is a
little bit no man's land, but we'll see
on a reclaim. Watching sort of 300s and
310s again. Same kind of level. Here's
the 300s. Straight to 310. Watching this
now if we base over it or not. That's
where those buyers came in last time.
Right, this sh rejection of 310. So far,
if we base over that, I will be looking
for a short squeeze.
Got to get back above those three tens
for me to be really interested.
We have trap sellers under 85 right now.
Here's the tens. Little imbalance to 99
which they could hold. There's the
imbalance. Do they hold this?
They're trying.
It's tempting. It's not enough for me
yet. They are holding that imbalance.
They need a break through tens and base
above 10. I'm interested long.
Here they go. Swipe to 10. Can we
reclaim and hold now?
Watching this for a trigger long here. I
want to be very careful.
Got liquidity up to 40 if they want to
go and attack it. There's a dip down to
95 possible here as well. Right at that
level. I'm interested. I'm really
interested here. Not pulling the trigger
yet. I just want to see something on the
tape. Show me that they're trapped.
We have definitely have sellers stuck at
the lows. I can show you this. We have
some sellers stuck down here right now
under 83. This is the shelf at 10s that
I'm watching. All right. They would need
to reclaim this for the squeeze.
They're trying.
They are trying.
What's the time here? 42.
Will I short? Uh, yeah. If there's a if
if I see buyers get stuck, like if they
defend tens, then I'm we could take a
short from 10 down to here. It's
possible. I'm willing to play both ways
in this right now.
We're just basing out down here at the
moment. We're right at the edge of the
developing weeks like
Dshape, let's say. We're still inside.
Remember, we're still inside yesterday,
right? Yesterday's value area high,
yesterday's value area low. We're in a
rotation in here. We failed to take I
would have taken the short if we did
this down to here. I'd be a partial out
in the midpoint. Um, this can come down
here, but you're getting risky. You're
getting risky. It's a midpoint of the
range really.
We're just trading inside yesterday's
value. We expect rotation inside
yesterday's value.
All right, SPY now filled its gap,
drifting a little bit underneath it.
Just trying to find a bid. Watching
these tens again for this explosion
through it. If they're going to get
going, they're going to have to get over
tens. Otherwise, there's no trade for me
to get long into
that drive up again. We're building a
big shelf up there into 10, this shelf
here. And it's mainly buyers. So, I'd
say buyers at 08s and 12s. So, unless
we're above 08s and 12, there's no long
because they keep getting stuck. If we
get above that level, then there's
probably some relief.
Not until we get up there. If we keep
rejecting it, there's an argument to
play a short down here. We've got point
control down here now. Big big volume
area.
Do they come all the way back down here?
Getting 85s, 65s, 55s. It's the edge.
So, still rejecting possible short here
down to this if they're going to be
aggressive. Sellers again coming
aggressive at these lows. We are
developing a big big big node down here
soon. Sellers coming flying in there at
85s. Again,
they cannot make their mind up if they
want to save it here or not. At the
moment,
it's the opening range low. They're
bidding 100 lot 55 right now.
where sellers last came in in this
balance. Still waiting to get over 10
for a trigger for me.
Right back up to the 300s.
Watching this again now in case they do
a failed break of the low here and then
we go back above the 10ens and I can
look long.
Sure. I love the short hair even though
I seem to be caught at those tens. I'd
almost rather sit out the short and
wait. I think
what are we doing?
65 55. flush down sellers at these lows
again. They're trying to fill this 55.
It's 100 lot 55.
Some absorption there. It's kind of a
weird area to absorb. I'm not really
sure what they're trying to pivot off
other than the hourly. Um this can fill
that hole imbalance down to 96s at this
point, but you've just seen another 55
lot get stuck down here at the lows.
They should trade lower, but they are
starting to be very aggressive down here
and we're not moving lower. It's worth
noting,
right? They're being very aggressive
down here and we're not able to move
lower. We can see this is all red. All
this paint is red. It's all sellers. We
keep absorbing this, they're going to
get themselves caught.
Their target will be 220s right now.
Their target will be 220s.
It's the 50s again. They're trying to
sell through. They're trying to see
follow through here.
More absorption.
Big sellers getting caught down there so
far. More absorption. So we will be
watching now 90s and then same levels
10.
There's the 90s. Okay. Are we going to
go? Are you willing to go turbo here?
>> Yep. Okay. Small piece on here. Long.
Watch intends to add.
If they can get above this, I'll add.
Can you get above this and hold? I will
add. If you get above this and hold so
far, rejecting just into this little
shelf here. If we get above this and
hold, I will add long for a squeeze up.
So, I'm long from here. I will add here
for this move back into the other side.
Here we go, folks. Here we go. All
right. A little buyer coming in here
trying to force it up. Be very, very
careful. He might get himself caught.
Point of control is now shifted up here
as well. So, we need to hold a bid here
or I'm going to trim 90% of this. I want
to hold versus 300. Now,
we can fill all the way up to 50 here.
Here we go. Here we go. Here we go. Come
on. Shove. Shove. Shove. Shove. Shove.
Shove.
Go and fill all these guys up to 40s. I
want to hit some TPS here.
Let's go. Let's go. They retract there.
They retract there. Come on, you've got
to break out here. We got to go 320s
here and break. Here we go. Come on.
You've just retracted. Stop [\h__\h]
around. Please. Please.
Please.
Break 20s. Shove to 50s. Let's go.
Thank you. Thank you.
peeling some off here and trying to get
a runner to go now to see if we can get
up to 40s and 50s and then all the way
up here into 60s. And if we get through
point of control from yesterday, I'll be
looking for value area high. Already
trimming a lot off there, folks. Here we
go. So, looking for those shorts down in
that level. Uh shorts to get stuck down
in that level like we talked about. We
saw shorts get stuck on the tape right
down here at these lows. They got very
aggressive. Kept saying they're getting
very aggressive down here. There's the
turnaround in delta. There's them
getting trapped on the expansion. That's
what I was looking for. We use their
pain to move higher. We trim some now.
We trim a lot now. And we wait and see
now if we're really going to get going.
We're in a range rotation. It's why I
didn't want to short down here. We're in
a range rotation. They could have
technically come all the way down here
and bid down here. And we could have
faded if they got up to there. We
couldn't quite get up into there. Do not
be entering a new money long in the
midpoint of this range. If we think
about yesterday's value, right, low to
high, do not be starting to try and get
a new position here. You're right at the
midpoint, right? We're runners only.
Now, if we hold this node, great. If we
don't hold this node, out on the
runners.
No, I can't. Sh. Like, you've got to
understand,
guys. You've got to understand when I
enter off a trap, when I see it, I just
have to get in. I can't say the price. I
don't have [\h__\h] time. It's not that I
don't want to. This is very different to
like I'm waiting for a pullback and a
hold. If I tell you if we break 90, I'm
looking to get in. If we base over 10,
I'm looking to add. That's me telling
you where I'm trying to get in. But here
we go, folks.
What a beauty. All right, let's see. So,
we're going to try and peel a little bit
off now into here with VWAP and previous
day close. This level here is huge,
right? This is current developing fair
value and previous day, right? If we get
through that, I think we can get up into
here.
I wish I could tell you all the time,
sharers, it's it's just like when I'm
watching the tape move, I'm literally
having to play of people's pain right
now. Right. I'm looking for this and
ultimately up here if we can get it. All
right. That would be I don't know how
many points that is. Did it just tell
me? 144. But we're looking gap. So the
gap is here. We're looking I'm going to
trim a lot off here into 60s and 70s. A
lot off here.
Don't want to get caught in a refresh. I
tell you what, I'm going to remove this
gray box now because we traded under and
over it. So here. And then if we get
really lucky, we'll get up here, folks.
But this this is a good area to be
peeling some off. We can look at this
node. All right. This is where buyers
got stuck this morning. We're repricing
to that. We're in thin volume. If we get
over that and find acceptance, we're
going to come up for previous day.
Here we go, folks. Getting ready to
peel.
Refresh setting here.
Nice on ES. Really good.
ES can take out the highs. That would be
good. Here we go, folks.
TP. All right, runners. Now, let's see
if we can go to value high from previous
day. All right, so this was our main TP.
Like I said, previous day point of
control, current developing point of
control. If we're lucky, we're going to
get over here, up to here. If we get
acceptance over this, we can look for a
squeeze up. There might well be a bull
trap up here. So, I want to be careful
about that move.
I've been coming to you for about two
weeks. You are pretty clear what you're
looking for and I've defin become better
fisherman because of your page.
Hopefully, I can retire from music
business, too. Hey, mate.
Good luck with that. I hope I hope
they're kind to you in the music
business. Here we go, folks. We're going
to get a monster here. All right, we're
looking for up here for an XTP. We might
as well hold a little piece past this.
But if we can get up here into 420s,
previous day value area high, previous
week value area high, we want to be, I
would say, at least 80% out into here.
And we can read if they base above.
Okay. But we can they can set they can
set a bull trap in this area, which I'm
very very aware of.
What a beauty. What a beauty.
All right. 400 100 lot there. Just
stepped on the tape. We should trade him
through him really, but you can peel
some here. I'm looking for 420 now.
100 lot on the book there at 400
defending uh ES coming into previous day
high. Spying to previous day high. So,
we're looking for them to spike above.
There will be liquidity sat there. They
might well sell once they take that out.
We don't know. Let's just see if we can
get to 420 and time this. Pass my funded
next futures challenge. Thanks, Alex.
You're welcome.
I'm new to trading. Trying to learn as
much as possible. Hey, just keep turning
up.
Keep turning up.
Buy is definitely getting a little bit
caught here at 400. We need to see
expansion through 400. We can see on the
tape here. There are some buyers caught
up here. We have a spike here. We need
to get over this spike here. This 400.
It's where the buyers are caught over
400. We can come and take out 420, 425,
etc. But there are definitely buyers
getting caught up here right now. We do
not add up here, right? The ad was over
tens, whatever I said it was, tens or
twelves. That was the ad. So, we were
long, we were adding, and we are selling
and selling and selling and selling. And
then hopefully we get up into here with
a runner. Here we go. Four. Here we go.
Let's get the 420s.
Come on, baby. Don't get trapped here at
400. We've taken out that 100 lot. 400.
177 lot, actually, to be exact. We need
to get over that player.
We need to get over that player
otherwise this buyer up here is going to
get himself hurt.
Any new long entry from here? Um I would
say no. Uh I would say no. I would say
the only long entry confirmation now
right would be if we got above all of
this and we turned this into some form
of demand for that reach up all the way
up to 800. You must know that this area
here is a prime position for them to set
a bull trap, right? It is a prime bull
bull trap position. So, or I would
manage that accordingly. Why? You might
ask why. We talked about it in the
morning show if you were here early
enough. We think about the hourly. All
right, if you have swing stops here,
which is probably what we want to try
and attack if possible. This was the
pullback. All right, here's the move.
Doom doom doom. Here's the second leg
pullback and undercut trap under there
back to here. We take partials into
here. All right, they're going to run
the stops. Lots of bulls will come
chasing in here looking for 800. If
bears want to trap all the balls and
then dunk this back down, this is the
area they will do it in. That's all I'm
saying. So, manage yourself accordingly.
How do I learn to read the tape? Is that
something you offer? Uh, yeah. Well,
it's in the volume and orderflow course.
That's exactly what we're doing. It's in
that course. It's definitely in that
course.
Lots of you getting out. Thanks a lot,
man. Passed another account out. Money
made. I caught that trade. Thank you. I
like your strategy of trading. Nice.
You're damn good at this, Alex. I'm so
happy. Thanks, Rasheed.
It's a shame you don't understand
English. I'm sorry, Bradley. Bro, you
are the truth. your insights and market
structure invaluable the rest of this
community don't wait for the alerts Alex
is providing something more valuable
there thanks man what do I trade NQ how
do I read and interpret market and
position accordingly well positions are
all about risk right our job is really
is risk managers our position is about
risk so down here once shorts got to
court at these lows I wanted to use
their pain for expansion because I
understood that what's likely to happen
today is a rotation between here right a
failed breakout could have been down
here. It could have been here between
these gray boxes. It will ended up being
there. I risk according to where I'm
wrong. So, if I'm long here, I have to
risk there. And I'm adding here because
now I know I've been proven right
because now they're all caught and I'm
looking for that upside trade. All
right. So, your risk is about the size
of where that trade is no longer valid.
Interpretation of market. Um I'm
guessing you you mean how do I
interpret? How do I understand it? It is
just Have we got is trading just
stopped? Oh my god. Have we got data
issues? Hello. Is it just on this chart?
388.
Let me save this folks. Man,
it's got to be CME, man. At the moment,
everyone's like, it's tra this, it's
that. This is CME data. There we go. Had
to be refreshed.
Okay. So, now you'd be looking for a
hold over 70s. I'm probably going to cut
the runner here if it doesn't help this.
So, if they're going to complete this
move, ES, by the way, like we said, ES
and SPY took previous day high and
failed. So, they did the liquidity take.
We are looking for this. ES has done
this and failed. So, ES took that
liquidity like we said. It might well
take out the highs and pull back
afterwards. Run the stops.
So, we need to hold this now for a
chance back up. Otherwise, there's a
full collapse in here and I will not
hold for that full collapse. We'll just
lock in.
You know you're doing right when your
levels you drew match the master
himself. Hey, nice work, man. Here we
go. So, nice hold here. We want to just
see expansion back through 400. All
right, we still have that guy at 400. We
got to rip through and try and get to
420 430. ES has got to get back above
previous day high. Same on the spiders.
We're looking to take out that previous
day high in the cash market on the QQQ.
It's what we'd like to happen.
Two two W's. Nice. Dave, would you do a
long short? What do you mean? Would I
hedge against myself? No. My friend
watching has mild autism but got into
trading. We've been watching a while.
Can you say
what's up to Daniel? What's up, Daniel?
What's up, Daniel? That's awesome.
I would imagine people with autism will
be fantastic traders to be honest
because they'll be uh able to read data
and uh pattern structure very very
quickly.
Great call. Grati, nice Scott. Nice
work. Appreciate all the help. Alex,
thanks for all your work. I bought the
course but not had time to get with it
yet. Give it time, Mike. When you're
ready, it's there for you, bro. You
killed it. Thank you. You're welcome.
8751 contract will nice work. Long from
312 out of the red took me two months
using two micros. There you go. Nice
work. Pass an account on that. Thank you
very much. You're welcome. What's the
minimum monitors you need to trade?
Well, one would be the minimum. Um, it
all depends on the monitor size, right?
I trade with one, two, three, four,
five. Well, four four big wide screens
and then one like pad. Um,
thank you, sir. You
I don't know what that said. My account.
Oh, you were minus 1,128 to positive 728
following my plays. You're welcome. Do I
ever look for liquidity sweeps? This is
my second day watching you. Yeah, I
mean, that's kind of what we were
looking at down here, right? If you
think of what we did into GlobeEx, this
this pivot down here, where did they
trap the shorts? Where did breakout
shorts come in? Breakout shorts came in
here. So everyone tried to sell the
market there. They got caught. We used
them to go back upside. Why have we got
stuck up here? Well, if we look at the
spy and ES, all right, they've taken the
liquidity of the high and then failed.
So here is previous day high. They snap
it and they come back down. All right,
trade inside unless they catch a bid.
So it's kind of what we're doing. Um,
but we are aware of uh levels beyond
those pivots of just highs and lows. We
have to also be aware of where volume
is. We're basing out all right here. We
just need to hold this. I'd say any
break underneath 85, I'm not interested
anymore, right? If they because I don't
want to give back to 60s and then 50s
and then maybe the whole thing back
because this is a giant squeeze. So, we
just missed here. We I reckon we take
this out. It's just Do they need a
deeper pullback first? I reckon we will
take all this out.
Uh, sorry guys, trying to catch up with
what you're saying. Have you ever
thought over short-term participants and
long-term participants that might not
care about all the traps? Uh, everyone
cares about traps, especially
uh big participants, and that's all that
really matters. It doesn't matter if
it's the time frame it's on. The big
participants need the traps to get their
liquidity into the market. Otherwise,
they can't get their liquidity into the
market because they're too big, right?
So, they need someone the other side of
it. So, that it does it really does
matter. That's what why and how the
market moves. Do you ever take your I
don't miss that. Ever take your flow
zone indicator into account? Yeah, I do
when we're in a trending day. Right now,
we're in a ranging date. So, it offered
you a great sell there, but when we are
going sideways like this, okay, you can
scalp some of these moves, but this is a
sideways moving market. The flow zones
come into real good use when we're in an
expansive market. All right, like
yesterday should have just stuck all the
way up. There's your first sell. There's
the buyback. This is a nice market out
of range. This is a market in range.
This will just chop. So, I would say if
you take the indicators on this,
sometimes you might be too late.
We're in a rotation, right?
What about the triangle signals buy and
sell on the chart? That's the same
thing. But the buy is going to come
late. Now, this is what I'm saying.
Because we're in a ranging market, it's
going to come late.
Is my price feed. Okay. Yeah, maybe you
noticed it earlier. Try trading topset X
mobile, which was a mistake. Yeah, leave
the mobile trades. Do you ever buy when
it drops? Yeah. Um, only if I've got a
limit order set to a key level where I
know there's liquidity resting. Alex, I
sent an email to you. yesterday about
the Discord. Please check your email
when you have a minute. Uh, okay. We'll
check now.
Maybe it went to spam.
Here we go, folks. Nice, nice, nice.
Held that box. So, coming to 320. So,
320s, 329, 343.
Woo! TP's hit. Thanks for playing. I'm
out of there. I'm out of there. I am out
of there. I don't even have a little
guy. We just hit my level.
Ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding
ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding
ding
ding ding ding ding ding ding 161 points
up the previous week value high. I don't
give a damn what it does now. I've just
locked that in focus too good too early
in the day not to lock in. Right, we can
think about now whether we base and hold
or we trap. All right, a base and hold
will look something like this. A trap
will look something like this. And a
rotation right back down again
underneath.
Ding ding ding ding ding. Right. Who
said they emailed me? I'm checking my
spam now.
H. Is it Zach? Is that you? You're the
first one in spam.
I'm replying to you now, my friend. Give
me a second.
Where are you, Zach? There you are.
Sending you Discord. Sorry. Sorry, my
friend. Sorry that went spam. It's
happened a few times recently with
people. I don't know why.
I'll just reply to you.
What tools do I need to draw to draw the
nodes? I'm tired of using lame
rectangles. I mean, that's what I use is
lame rectangles.
My second ever eval pass. Nice work. Big
baller, Alex. I think lots of you must
have just got this. How much is the
course? How do you teach orderflow
technique? The orderflow course is uh
399. The beginner to advanced course,
which comes with a version of the flow
zones and the discord is uh 649 unless
they've done it, but I think I'm going
to have a meeting with him today to fix
it. It's a 649 until probably tonight
and it'll be 699.
I started using VWAP. Would you say it's
likely to come back to that is what I'm
thinking. Uh if we do the initial
balance trade maybe. We'll see.
We'll see.
Tempted to add short here. I wouldn't be
getting short here. You've not trapped
enough participants yet. It's a It's a
good location, but uh not enough
participants. Yeah.
Is my previous day value high based on
the New York session? Yes, just New York
session, mate. Any spoofers? Uh no, not
yet. Everyone's been getting filled. We
did just hit a very, very big key level.
So, it's possible. I'm out of this now,
folks. It's possible they want to
revisit this. This is thin. Possible
they want to come back down here and
then make their decision. But we did
just take all that liquidity. How we act
here then becomes key. If they lose
this, that's your rotation again.
Alex, what do you mean about a squeeze
when it's when they get liquidity off a
low or a high and then move in the other
direction? No, it's when it's when
you've got one side piling in. So, like,
let's think about this. All right,
shorts from the morning
get short here and they have their stop
here, right? So, we have shorts, stops
here, right? They come back, they add
because it's a first retest. They've
added short and added short and added
short. All right, so we have all these
shorts here. So guess what happens when
we drive through this price here. All
right, when we get through 410s, guess
what happens? They all stop out. When a
short seller stops out, they become
what? A market buyer. That's what
happens. Market buyer. So now we have
breakout longs and shorts stopping out,
forcing the market up. When our entry
was right down here, right? The same
thing down here. We had breakout shorts
being absorbed by longs. Breakout shorts
got stuck. I'll show you it on the tape.
It'll be easier. Uh
thanks to that guy on YouTube who left a
comment on my YouTube yesterday saying,
"I don't know what I'm talking about."
yada yada yada. How do you like them
apples, mate? Okay, at the lows
underneath here, this is GloEx, right?
We have breakout shorts right entering
the market. We also have buyers from
Asia
with their stop here. So if the buyers
stop out, they become sellers in the
market. If short sellers join in, they
become sellers in the market. If we have
short sellers and price does not move
lower and it's moving higher, what does
that mean? That there's a passive buyer
down here. as in there's a big
institution limit ordering buying. Once
we turn around, these guys start
stopping out. All right, they start
taking their break evens. Oh, there's
the run back up to the pivot. We base
above that area where more sellers came
in. They start stopping out. We squeeze,
right? We squeeze because these guys are
all stopping out. They're caught the
wrong side of the trade. So, it's the
same at the highs except we're not
turning around at the highs now. We're
using their fuel to move higher. We're
using the stops. All right, the shorts
from here, we're using their stops. Look
where the squeeze happens above this,
right? We're using their stops to move
higher, right? We have an imbalance
here, which they can fill if they want.
I'm out of this now. Might well keep
going for the day. I don't know, but
hopefully that makes sense for you.
If only I have space for more time zone
other than trade one minute mark, what
would I recommend? Uh yeah, like a 50. I
I use an hourly. So on my screen I have
a one, a five, an hourly, a daily, and
over here I have a five, a five, a five,
a five, and over here I'm watching ES
Spy, QQQ, VIX because I care about the
cash market.
Now that we've broken the range, do we
want to be looking for upside expansion?
I would not say it's proved anything
yet, right? What I'd say right now is we
have this node being developed. we have
just taken out or come right to the
other side of the range. If we cannot
find,
unless it does this, it would have to do
something like this. All right?
Otherwise, we're going to leave buyers
who are late trapped up here. We're
going to revisit here. We're going to
make a decision here. All right? This
this right here is massive. Not just on
this day, on the developing week. All
right? If we hold this and do this,
maybe a squeeze. If we lose this, we can
collapse this whole thing on a rotation
because buyers are now caught at the
high. So if I come over here, we'll
probably find that the buyers at the
high just got caught offside.
We're filling the imbalance, right? So
all these buyers who chase the high,
they come start stopping out under here.
We're now filling this imbalance of
where we did that squeeze, that short
squeeze, we're back into that imbalance
area. So the question is, do more
sellers come in here and get trapped or
do we find acceptance back down now?
right back down into this gray box. Like
I said, this is your sentiment for the
day. I would imagine this right here.
So, starting to lose gray box. So, it
might come down to VWAP now and previous
day point control. And if they now the
opportunity is this, right, they
probably back test this. If they sell
this, they're going to look for this
rotation, right? Because we're in a
rotation between these. All right. So, I
would be watching this for a sell and
this for a sell. If they reclaim this,
I'd be very skeptical about this being a
big old trap, right? Where they absorb
now,
right? So, this level coming up here is
key into 400. If they start rifling
through this, this is a massive trap,
right? So, they have to resell this
right here, right now to come back down
to here. If they don't, and they do
this, I would imagine we are going to
come and rip some faces.
Can you have an opinion about momentum
on the 1 hour market? Yeah, of course
you can.
How long is the discount on the course?
There's no discount on the course.
How do I mark the GlobeEx levels? Uh
just the high and lows. just you can
just you can do the high and lows
overnight or you can do them of those
specific levels based on time. You can
get plenty of indicators online will do
that. So, so far we're starting to see
rejection there, aren't we? So, they're
going to try and force follow through
now. So, sellers will want to trim a
little bit here now in case they in case
they rebid it. And if they see follow
through, they will be looking for a
trade back down to 300 because we're in
a range rotating market. Okay. So, we've
just rejected fours. If you took this
short at fours, I would be covering some
here into these 60s because we have a
developing weak point of control. We
have PDC. We have both VWAPS. We have
lower time frame algo. If we let go of
this, your continuation trade will be
down into here. All right. So, if this
is a big rotating day, which is what our
expectation is, if we let go of this,
they can come right back down into this
Oh, you want a a Valentine sale? Okay.
Well,
fine.
Fine. We can sort something.
Volume profiles from 9:30, guys. It's in
the chat. Read the chat. It's in the
chat. I promise you.
Is it much harder to spot buyers or for
shorts? No, it's exactly the same. The
principle is the same.
Alex, does the beginner to advanced
course include the market order and
volume profile lessons? There is a a bit
of volume profile in there, but uh if
you want to really order uh learn order
flow, you need to do the other course.
Can I show my anchor profile settings?
Yes. Here,
this is like the most common question
ever. All right. Ticks per row, two row
size, placement, right? width 20. That's
all you need.
How long is the flossen course? The
beginner to advance is 20 hours. Uh the
other one is six.
Okay. So, still rejecting here. We're
now building out liquidity, right? We're
building out liquidity between these
VWAPs and this node. All right. So,
sellers are trying to take control for
this move. That's what they're trying to
achieve. Buyers will want to trap
sellers either like this or just from
here like this and then get back into
this and try and go for a rippy rip.
Like I said, I'm done. I'm done. That
rip was all I wanted and uh I will wait
and see how we build out now.
Alex, would you prefer bookmap over
traditional volume footprint? It's
really hard, man. Um I use both.
Um, I really like bookmap for seeing the
passive players. Uh, I both are very
good. Look, you can use bookmap and
footprint on bookmap, right? I don't
like footprint on bookmap. I like just
to see the market orders and limit
orders. Um, I like both. There's no it I
think it's so personal. I think it's
really easy to see the trap players on
the footprint when you have delta on the
side. But I really do like that map. I
think it's really useful. It's a really
useful tool.
So, we're seeing like aggressive buyers
keep trying to step in here at 80.
He's just come in another 80 lot. He's
trying to force up. He needs to get a
break of 90. Here we go. So, they're
trying to get this reclaim of this gray
box. I would say if buyers are able to
reclaim this and hold, they're going to
look to do this. All right. So, sellers
now losing control. They had the
opportunity. They are now starting to
lose control. If buyers get above this,
they will look for more upside. This can
be a giant trap if they're able to do
that. Big if, but uh that's what it is.
Oh, thanks Ninja Trader. You've just
gone down, have you? That's kind of you.
Let's
turn that off and come back on.
Sorry guys, you have to give me a
minute. NT
just crashed on me.
It's the first
Yeah, Trading View is having a sale
right now. I can post the link in for
you if you guys want.
There is a sale.
Great.
Oh my god.
Trying to get this sale for you guys.
Give me a second.
Tech, tech tech issues. All right,
buyers are going to try and defend this
gray box. Now, this is the opportunity.
It's for me like I'm not I'm not too
bothered at the moment and let it do
what it wants.
I'll give you a readout on the mag.
Tesla 1.21% up. Nvidia now half a
percent down. They're just washing these
around. Microsoft 1.65% up. Meta 0.73%
down. Google 1 and a half% down. Uh
Amazon 1.36% up. Apple 0.17%
down. They're just washing these around,
right? Let's see if I can get you this
uh
this in chat for you.
This is the trading view cell.
Um,
the volume profile indicator I could
find does not have those settings. Then
you'll probably It's not an indicator.
It's so hard. It's not your fault. It's
just I get asked the same question every
day. It's a drawing tool. Okay. It's a
drawing tool. Forecasting measuring
tool. You come here. Anchored volume
profile. Anchor volume profile. It's not
an indicator. It's a drawing tool.
Hellet came across your page the other
day. It's good to see you trade very
similar to the way I do TPO volume
profile level two in footprint.
Appreciate your work. Nice work, man.
How do I set up the footprints on
Trading View to look like yours? There's
a free video on my YouTube guys that
teach Here we go, folks. They're going
to try and lift this now. So if you were
long, if you then if you then took this
red dip back in this hold of sort of
400s now you're watching for expansion
through 22s you're going to need to
respect 34s but through that I think
you've got a shot of going now. I think
this is might well be a trap now that
they lift. All right they flushed they
absorbed. They got sellers to get
involved versus this pivot. They've got
above them. Those sellers now stopping
out. They will come up to here and if
they get through that there will be
expansion. Now
this is what we talked about. They can
trap down here. Um yeah there's a free
video on YouTube on my YouTube for it.
Uh
me find it. Where is it? Footprints.
There you go. There are you here. There
you go. There's the footprint one on my
YouTube. Free video for you how to set
it up.
You look at time frame. The candles with
volume imprints are avoid errors. I
don't understand what you're saying
there, my friend. Sorry.
Morning DJ. Yeah, morning.
You really want to learn universal
authorizer? Just keep turning up. All
right. They keep getting stuck here. But
this is the rotation now. It's between
here and all the time balls are holding
this. I think that this is possible. The
only thing I would say that you need to
be aware of is definitely the higher
time frame.
We are right into
previous week value high into here and
current developing. All right, remember
we've got stops here to run it towards
the 500s. If they find a swipe towards
500s, great. If they can't base over
this, right, they will look for that if
they can. If they can't base over this,
I'm telling you, this is possible. It
can be a massive trap in here. So, I
wouldn't get long in here. All right.
You need to be long and selling into
there unless we push and hold because
they can just keep selling the edge of
this all the time that they want to. And
then a push above can also be sold. So,
it's why for me I'm done with it.
Get back to the screen. Oh, they just
rejected. So, gray to gray and they're
they're swapping under gray. Now, we are
starting to develop quite a big node
here. If we lose this, sellers will come
back in again.
It's very washy here. That is a lower
high for sure
versus this. They didn't able weren't
able to reclaim. They've just snapped
right back through PC. If we lose this,
that can happen or this can happen. Why
both? It's just cuz we're in a rotation,
guys. These are the my least favorite
markets that we talk about. They've just
had an opportunity there to go higher
and they failed and a big seller is
trying to drive this down now. So if
they ret be the same thing if they
retest 85s to 80s they will try and do
the same play they did here
they will try and sell this and if they
fail to sell this is the same thing that
can happen again is they're just going
to keep doing this until they've got one
side quarter right these are basically
your levels so from here to here to here
to here to here to here to here straight
through which is nasty back test this
question is this now or this Now,
yeah, Nightbot does. Look, you can read
it. I trade anchored volume profile. I
set it to two ticks. It is anchored to
9:30 New York open. Blue and red boxes
on my chart are high time frame SNR
levels. Gray boxes on my chart are key
levels of volume. learn more of my
course. It's all there.
How does the way you trade apply to
other sessions? Is volume too low? It's
the same principles, just volume's
lower.
I don't like shorts. It's not that I
don't like shorts. I'd like to see it
swipe all the liquidity first, but ES
has done it. Like we talked about, ES
has taken out that liquidity, but
I would like to see it break out first.
For me, like the better short, the same
reason I didn't take the one this
morning. I prefer it if it cleans out
some of these guys first and then offers
it. But it just might it might we might
just build all day. Remember, we're
going to zoom out here. Zoom out here.
Right. I'm watching these. All right.
I'm watching these right now. Right. Are
we going to protect these
or are we going to swipe these and trap
above? I don't want to become liquidity
in here. Remember this morning the long
came because we swiped underneath these
and traded back up. Right? I'm really
aware of these guys here at the moment.
Very very aware of them.
So on the airing on the side of caution
the market looks very like iffy right
now like Tesla one look if I give you
just a read out on the mag it should
read the story like of how much it keeps
changing. Tesla one and a half% up.
Nvidia half a percent down. That was one
and a half percent up at the beginning
of the day maybe 1.8.
Microsoft 1.73% up. Meta 0.70% down.
Google 1 and a.5% down. Amazon 1.38% up.
Apple near enough flat. I mean, they're
just like they don't know what to do
with it right now because we're at a key
level. And tech has had relative
weakness because we've been rotating.
Let me just check some of my swings
actually before I forget.
How am I looking?
Robin Hood holding up. Okay. Oracle
doing all right. Meta doing all right.
Bitcoin doing all right.
I do. I have I have a few monitors.
You suck, brother. Thanks for one good
call at least. Okay.
No worries. Yeah, lots of you want that
anchored volume. No worries. In your
opinion, what is the most accurate time
frame to look at for footprint? I saw in
your video you have a five minute. I'm
trying to add it to my analysis. There's
no there's no that that question's like
not valid. There's no time frame that's
more accurate than another time time
frame. What you should be asking is what
time frame are you able do you like
trading in? What time frame are you able
to digest the information in? If a one
minute chart is too fast for you, if you
cannot digest the delta in a one minute
chart, you should not be looking at a
one minute chart. Look at a two, a
three, a four, a five, a 15, a 30, an
hour. There is no like specific time
frame that's better. It's about what
works for you. And that
is based on what you're looking for and
what your experience is, right? I can
read a one minute time frame. I can see
when they're getting trapped in there. I
can read ticks because I'm looking at
bookmap, which is not even minutes. It's
ticks, right? But that took a lot of
experience. When I first started looking
at this stuff, it would be overkill. I'd
be like, "Well, this is too much
information." So, if it's too much
information, keep going up the time
frames until you find, "Okay, now I get
it. Now I get it." The higher the time
frame, the less information you're
absorbing per minute, the easier it is
for you.
What Trading View subscription is best
for a new trader that wants to trade
like you?
If you want the um
if you want footprint, you will need
what's their version of whatever it's
called pro or whatever it is, which I
think is currently like 13 a month. I
don't know what they call it. They are
building out this node. I still think
Bulls have unfinished business up here
in this gray box. In fact, would like to
just move this up so it's accurate there
and
make sure we go wig to wick here. Right.
I still think they are trying to get up
into there where the liquidity is, but
we will see. They definitely just caught
shorts on that last flush right under
400.
We just caught shorts again here
under 400 in there. I can show you in
there.
This is all sell side under 400. Look at
this candle here.
Right. So, this is a fiveminute chart.
Look under 400. This is all market
selling into an imbalance who just
paired off with where this buyer was.
Right. And they reclaimed 400 and now
we're shoving. So, every seller under
400 just got themselves caught. They
just got themselves caught. I think they
want this gray box. I've been saying it
the whole time. I think that's what they
want. Sellers coming in here at 50 52.
Lot of these highs. I think we probably
get a breakout here. The next pullback
probably holds and they probably go for
it. There is a node up here. You can see
there's a slight node up there. I think
there is a breakout coming.
It's just a matter of time at the
moment. Can they catch enough offguard
to do it is what I think they are trying
to do.
Vivc.
Can they bid above previous day high?
Can they get through this gray box node
up into here?
That's like the big question at the
moment.
So that node sort of 35s is like where
its thickest point is.
ES doing it. ES has broken out. Can it
hold its gains above initial balance? IB
now set. Yeah, IB is now set. So we're
also going to think about a rotational
IB. IB day IB day. AB day. We're going
to think about that rotation. So if we
have a fail breakout of the IB today,
you might get that trade back to VW up
imbalance down here down to 15s if they
do want to do that little wash down and
retra.
I think it looks like it's coming to me.
It's just whether they can get through
this little gray box. And if they can,
we're going to see that expansion.
Alex, would it say it's best to stay out
of market like this? Um, it's just
personal, right? It's like it's personal
preference. Um, I don't love rotational
markets. Like, it's not where my edge
is. I know we got this today because
there was a nice trap towards a low. Uh,
I can think about the same kind of play
reverse up here. I can think about the
continuation if they're going to do it.
But
there's no like with all these things,
there's no like, oh yeah, you need to
stay out or you can't do this. It's just
personal preference. What kind of
conditions do you like trading in? That
will come from back testing. Are you a
trend trader? Do you like traps? Do you
like trading edges? Do you like
rotation? Do you like continuation? Do
you like trades when we're leaving
volume trapped? Do you like trades when
we're creating volume? I like trades
when we're leaving volume trapped. All
right, coming back now to this imbalance
to the 15s again. They're failing to get
through here right now.
They cannot make their mind up. I don't
think we've completed the auction at the
highs, but I could well be wrong.
Maybe they have. Maybe they're like, "We
don't want to go and do it. We're only
going to do it on ES."
Yeah, they trapped again here. Absorbing
again here. Can they get follow through
upside? That last candle just trapped
again in that imbalance. It's washy,
that's for sure. It's not very pretty
out here.
definitely washy. So into GlobeEx. Do
they bid around here again and have one
more attempt? If they can't get up there
soon and break out, they're going to get
themselves caught.
I'm just not convinced that high of day
is in. But
it is looking more like it might be in
on ES, that's for sure. Back to VPO then
we go.
Somewhat surprised they didn't take that
out there. This is not looking very good
for the bulls at the moment. Say last
chance here to save it in this gray box,
otherwise they're going to get
themselves in big trouble. It's a big
rejection after clearing out the high.
So ES has done the move that I would
traditionally be looking for in NQ. Like
when we look for this, see how ES just
swiped it all and then Ben has come back
down.
What's weird is the sellers keep getting
caught down here, but there's not able
to run it higher. It's like how high.
They just caught into 400s and under
again. Same level as before. Exactly the
same level we just went over on the
chart. I'm just unconvinced at the
moment. The lack of strength
You can see it in the mag like Nvidia,
Meta, Google red, Tesla, Microsoft,
Amazon green, Apple flat. I mean, it's
just complete indecision in the mag. You
remember that's 60% of the ENQ. It's
complete indecision right now.
It would just be nice if we would get a
liquidity sweep at the highs rather than
just these uh
how we've set this up. But we'll see.
We'll see. I was waiting to break out
and then fail failure to short back in.
We'll see.
tape slowed right down as well.
What are all the lines next to New York
VWAP? Uh this here is like a lower time
frame algo. This is 24-hour view up.
This is previous day close. This is
developing weeks point of control.
Maybe I can do this one a different
color so we can remember that. I do this
pinky. Like that's better.
So it's like fair value on the week.
down to this same level where these
sellers keep getting stuck. But we're
not seeing follow through downside.
We're not seeing follow through upside.
We're just seeing chop.
I'm not going to go through volume
profile anymore, guys. Rewind the tape.
Go through the master classes that are
free on YouTube. Honestly, you guys are
asking the same questions over and over
and over and over and over and over. It
is absolutely ridiculous.
Read Nightbot. Nightbot literally tells
you my settings. It's telling you what
to do. Please
This is thickened up a bit. We can do
this
back to 400s. Remember, they've trapped
Oh, come on. They trapped under 400s the
last few times. We're just in this is
the chop zone while they decide what the
bloody hell they're going to do with it.
And I recommend a copy trader.
Affordable indicators, I would say, is
probably the best copy trader right now.
What are we doing here, folks? Market's
gone to sleep.
in the mag has caught a bid back over
PDC but it just looks awful on a
fiveminute chart. Lower highs and higher
lows on VIX on a fiveminute chart. It
doesn't look good. Complete indecision
day.
Did we break the high there? Delta-wise,
we did, which means there's passive
sellers up there because we broke it and
didn't move higher so far.
This is ugly. ES keeps finding a bid in
front of new or VWAP. This is ugly right
now. Thank goodness. Leaving this alone
for me. This is exactly what I don't
like trading when the market doesn't
know what it wants to do. So, it has to
build out liquidity. I think we should
move higher, but I it's clear that we're
not.
But I sold into that run into a previous
week value high. I they should really
come and clean out the highs and give a
better auction at that high in my
opinion. But ES has already done it and
that seems to be leading right now.
ES swipe barely. I mean
705s to 70625s. I mean it's enough. It's
more about what happened after it
swiped. It's pretty decent rejection
right on the ES.
We'll see. We will see.
Back to these 400s like this area where
I keep saying the buyers kept getting
stuck. Sorry, sellers keep getting
stuck. Buyers now can't get through it.
So right here you can see just like we
are struggling. Buyers keep getting
stuck over it. Sellers keep getting
stuck under it. We can't make a decision
here. Then price is stuck here. It's why
it's become point of control. It's fair
value at the moment.
How annoyed would you be if I accuse you
of not sharing trades with us? Joking,
bro. I love your sessions.
What a shitty 30 minute. Yeah, I mean,
look at the hourly. It doesn't It
doesn't look good, does it? Just stuck.
Cannot hear me. Turn your volume up.
Am
I mute? Are you guys saying on mute? You
can't hear me. I can see it. No, it's
just one of you. You need to turn your
speakers on, buddy.
Turn your speakers on.
Oh, if the market's going to be like
this much longer, I'm going to go back
to bed. This is uh slow slow. Or we'll
do a giveaway. Maybe we'll just do a
giveaway.
Um, how many likes have we got?
Come on, folks. Get that up towards a
thousand, please. 1,400 of you watching,
500 likes. Let's get those moving and
we'll do some giveaways because this
market's gone to sleep.
Fully gone to sleep. Time for a Trump
impersonation. I don't think Trump's
going to move the market today.
Sleepy Joe. Sleepy Joe's in charge of
the stock market.
Come on.
Stream is lagging. Shouldn't be lagging
more than six seconds. If it's lagging
more than that, that's uh on your your
computer.
What can be done to try and get the
course? And you can buy it on the
website. Links are down below.
flowzonerader.com.
Go for a coffee. I do need a coffee.
Shall I go for coffee?
I do genuinely need a coffee. Maybe I'll
go and do a get a coffee and we'll see
if the market moves. Uh, how many likes
have we got here?
Right, let's get me to 750 likes. I'll
set a giveaway and then I'll go for
coffee.
Get these likes up and then uh we'll do
a giveaway and I'll go for coffee.
Can they do the squeeze? They really
want to, but they just can't get through
these levels up here.
They keep trying. They keep trying and
they want to lift towards 35s. They keep
trying. They just keep getting stuck
over and over and over again.
Are they going to do it this time round?
Right. How many likes are we into?
Almost there. Four likes. We'll call We
We'll say that's enough. We'll say
that's enough. Right.
Set this up for you guys.
Yeah, I I know. I was thinking that I
can put it on the website. I can't put
an FAQ page on um on YouTube.
Maybe I'll make a video for new people
watching streams and I'll just have
Nightbot constantly pushing it. Um
giveaways,
right,
give away the introduction course first.
Let me set it up. I haven't done it yet.
Right. As always, just type course in
chat. Type it once. Please don't spam.
I'm going to get a coffee while you guys
do all of that and then I'll come back.
Hopefully, there's a trade setup and
then um
well then I don't know then we'll uh
pull the giveaway and if there's a trade
set up we'll get one. If there isn't
then we'll give away an Apex account and
I'll go back to bed. All right, folks.
See you in a minute.
All right, coffee is brewing. Oh, we're
finally going. Can we go? Can we go? Can
we get back through these levels? Let's
pull a winner.
Can we bloody go? It looks like it. God,
they've taken long enough to try and do
it.
Where are you guys? Here we go. Pull in
the winner. Five, four, three, two, and
one.
Noi 5550.
Are you here? Noi.
Noi. 5550.
Failing up here again. They still can't
get through this key level. They've got
to get through this gray box right into
the edge of range and failing. Still
think they've got a chance to come and
clean this out. It just depends how long
they're going to mess around with all
this liquidity for. Here. Here. Nice.
Okay. No. All I want you to do, email
me, please. info@flowzonerader.com.
Send me a screenshot of you logged into
YouTube. I've made a note of your name
and I will sort you out with a uh
introduction course to trading. If
you've traded before and you don't want
the introduction course, you can give it
to a friend or something like that. But
it does get you a discount of the main
course if you do do it. If you do want
the main course.
Okay.
Can we keep going here? Is the market
going to give a clear out of these highs
or not on the cues? Yes. Still can't get
up there.
It's trying. It's just chopping between
this gray box and this one here. I don't
like the highs up here. I really don't
think we have enough excess here. I
would like to see a spike into here, but
the Q's just can't get going now. Just
look at this trapping action. It's
awful. It's absolutely awful.
There we go. Back downside we go now.
Jesus Christ. Make your mind up, market.
I'm only interested in short if we fail
to break out up here. The fact that
we're holding in here, it just doesn't
make me like it very much. Honestly, I
don't want to trade it
because they can keep protecting down
here. So, I need to get an extreme edge
if I'm going to fade back inside for
what I'm looking for personally.
Personally,
oh my god, you're so dumb. You're so
dumb. It's not a macro between 950 and
10:10. It is just an hourly close.
Stop listening to this [\h__\h] mate.
It's an hourly close, a 4hour close. A
macro is a madeup [\h__\h] term. Okay?
It's just made up. It's an hourly bar
close. Which means on that close you
have a high low open close of an hour, a
4 hour, a 30 minute, a 15 minute, a five
minute, a 2 minute, a 3 minute, a 1
minute. Like [\h__\h] get out of here
with that [\h__\h] It's nonsense.
All
right.
Yeah, I'm a clown, mate. That's why I
got this whole move. I'm a clown.
Get out of here, mate. Go and watch your
[\h__\h] you know, guy that you think is
a God's gift who's never done anything.
Who's This is what you This is what
you're believing in. You currently
believe a man that thinks he was
kidnapped and told how the market works
and made an algorithm that controls the
whole stock market in the whole world.
Not just this market. Every single
market is controlled by this old [\h__\h]
man. Are you out of your [\h__\h] mind?
[\h__\h] off, you absolute [\h__\h]
Yes, some of his teachings are good, but
if you think there's some [\h__\h] macro
algorithm that works for 20 minutes,
you're just you're lost, mate. You're
lost.
You've completely lost.
Yeah, clown. Clown work. That's why I
get this cleanest work. That's why I get
the cleanest work. But I'm the clown.
[\h__\h] idiot.
AB and you said this was bullish. What's
happening now? What's happening now? Are
you holding through this now? Are you
holding through this?
Egypt.
ES to VWAP. Finding a bid on VWAP on ES.
A real thing that really matters. NQ to
New York VWAP. A real thing that really
matters. Holding a bid there for now.
For now. building out real volume and
range in a rotation for now. Nothing to
do with an a timeline. We've been here
for an hour. An hour.
Unbelievable.
Do you need to subscribe to real-time
data for NQ?
Uh, yes. Um, or at least log if you're
talking about on Trading View or at
least you need to be logged in via
Trader 8.
What would I look for for sales? There's
two things, but I think it's very, very
trappy to look for sells. I would like
this to be traded into up here. All
right. I would like them to clear out
all of this and trap buyers up here and
expand the range and have a good auction
of the high where buyers are stuck and
then look to fade back down into the
range. The issue for me is how we've
built out this liquidity is if you are
looking for sells breaking down from
here and they decide to hold here, you
have no RR. If they let go of this,
yeah, there's a move down to here. But
the way they're building structurally,
the way they've built out volume, it's
not great right now to do anything.
He really said he was kidnapped to show
how the market works. Oh yeah, he was
chucked in a white van and God came down
and talked to him and shown him how it
works and then he wrote the algorithm.
That's really what he said.
Check who you trade with. I use Trade
Station. It gives me real time. Yeah,
Trade Station gives you real-time data.
Yeah, for everything as well. Trade
Station.
I take on Elliot waves. I think waves
are good. I don't use Elliot waves, but
I do buy into the rule of uh measured
moves and two and three waves for sure.
How do you feel about Tik Tok viral
chicks saying day trading is gambling? I
mean, it is gambling. All trading is
some form of gambling. It's just whether
you've got edge.
There are millionaires that play poker.
It's gambling. Millionaires that play
blackjack. It's gambling. It's whether
you've got edge.
You were the one that kidnapped him.
That's comment of the day. You should
get a medal.
Comment of the day. You were the one
that kidnapped him.
So good.
Okay, back down to these levels. Are we
going to test value for the day or we
going to leave this and wash right the
way down? That's the big question.
Here's the wash. So, back down into
value area low for the current session
like I said and PDC. Now, the question
is if they don't bid here, there is a
move down to 300. So, I'm not going to
play it. We are thin in this move out.
Remember, this was a squeeze up. This is
where all the volume is. We've failed to
break out above this volume. At the
moment, we're breaking out below it, but
there's been no back test and leave. So
really the question is do they come down
here for this or not. I'm not playing it
either way. Like I'm quite happy with
how this day's progressed. I don't need
to be forcing into anything right now.
Let them build out the volume. In my
mind, I'm avoiding trading where there's
no edge.
Building some imbalances here into that
PDC.
They can afford a wash lower here if
they want. There are imbalances much
much lower
into 34 to 30 and then 98 and then 86es.
There's lots of imbalances down here. So
they're going to back test VW up here
and then make a decision by the looks of
it. Buyers got caught on that little
back test on that first shove in.
Do they reclaim now? So I'd be watching
this shelf up here into 84s if they if
they could be really nasty and just dump
this here. Where are we trading at on
the spy? SPY is into 95. So into that
gamma level. These are big levels,
folks. These are really big levels.
And here comes the back test. Here comes
that back test.
So in towards the 80s will be the back
test. And how they operate once they get
there will be absolutely vital. If
they've just trapped down here right for
a wash, we're coming into this back test
now. They will need to make a decision
here. If they rip through this, we're
going to go right the way back to the
top side of this 400s and then another
squeeze is on. If they've just trapped
enough sellers down here, it's a big if.
But if they have just trapped enough
sellers down here, it's what they're
trying to do. This is why I'm saying I'm
not convinced. We just talked about this
because if you're playing the trade from
there, all you've got is to this value
area low. So, we have so many stacked
levels here. If we look at this value
area low on the day PDC 24 VWOP lower
time frame ALGO previous day point of
control current developing point of
control New York open shelf no
acceptance above no acceptance below
back into this point right
if we go back above this now you could
argue that they're going to rotate back
for this again and this can have just
washed this tapped back into value
reclaimed this is still a trade which I
think they want to do I will be more
comfortable bought about a short once we
clear all of this out into that higher
time frame liquidity pool up there.
Right? What I'm trying to get up into
today and in this morning is up into
there.
That is based on what I was looking at
on the hourly, those hourly pivots
right into here, right? Where all those
short sellers have their stops, right?
This is where they pivoted out. So, this
is our first test of this since leaving.
If we think about this breakdown,
breakdown, failed to break lower, pull
back held, wash, pull back held. I think
we're trying to come into this and run
these stops. I think there will be a
bull trap in this area here. That's what
I think.
And I'm waiting for them to come and set
it rather than trying to anticipate
anything else.
Still holding the long. No, my long's uh
my long's been and gone, folks. Uh we I
took it the last partial was into the
previous week
uh value area high right here. So that
was my final TP,
right? So we got 162 points out of it.
If you have mathematical edge, would you
work for Citadel or do your own uh quant
shop? No, not for me. Too old for that
stuff now. Uh when I was younger, I was
interviewing at Merrill and Morgan and
Deutsche and um CBC and some others,
Mint, but uh not anymore. Uh for now the
least I do the better. I want to spend
time with my wife and my family. Don't
want to be in an office. Uh even like
one of my best friends he was at Morgan
then left that was uh precious metals at
Standard. Now he trades for a firm but
he trades his own book from his house.
Much better. Gets to see his kids and
his wife every day.
Bro got the coffeeest coffee ever.
It's actually full of mushroom. I'm not
even joking. It's uh coffee with um
what's it called? Everyday dose or
something.
No, no crypto uh acceptance at the
moment for the course. Sorry, mate. Do I
sometimes trade ES? No, not really. I I
if I'm going to trade ES, it's normally
a swing position in the sp S spy just
because I I like the way that we work as
ENQ. I would say if you're a beginner
trader, ES is probably a nicer place to
start. very smooth action. Respects
levels. I actually like because I like
traps so much. I like levels not to be
respected. I like them to be washed and
reclaimed. It's like just something that
I'm comfortable with and I've learned
NQ's personality. It took a while
and I like having confluence of like
when tech's running knowing that if
that's 60 plus%
knowing where the edge is whereas in ES
you've got to be aware of the whole
market.
I hate it raises your blood pressure,
but I really enjoy it that you dump on
the morons. The thing is, guys, you have
to understand, some of you may not know,
I'm going through one of the hardest
times of my life right now. Um, it is an
effort for me to get out of bed each day
right now. It is an effort for me to
turn up here and teach. It is an effort
for me to put risk on. Um, I'm not in
the best state. So, if someone comes and
talks [\h__\h] they're going to [\h__\h] get
it cuz I have no patience at the moment.
I'm not the best version of myself. So,
you will get a clapback and I'm not
going to say sorry for it. If you want
to come to my stream and talk [\h__\h] when
I'm trying to deliver you when to trade,
when to leave alone, then you're going
to get clap back.
What's the max higher think they can go
for? If they really really go for it, I
don't think I don't know if you're
talking about today, but up here into
800 will be a fresh back test,
right? which is that is an absolute
mustdeend level. It is a mustdeend level
for bears. All right, this
it's an old PC
on a weekly. Look at this node here. It
lines up with this. It's a huge level
800s, right? If we are going to do this
whole thing back,
right? This has to be defended. If if no
bull trap is set here, bears must defend
that. If bears don't defend that, we
will break out. Like, it's just too
much. If we start getting over that, we
will break out. There's just too much
momentum being allowed to come back in
at the moment. All right, we can think
about this as a retest into here to
sell. Ideally, a little trap to sell and
then we'll be covering some back down
into here and holding runners if there's
follow through. If there's no follow
through, that's fine. But 800,
it's a big level.
It's big because last night in my dream,
I got kidnapped in a white van and God
told me it was a big level. So, I just
marked it out for the sake of it.
Yeah, Larry, it's it's tough, man. Yeah,
it's really tough.
How old am I? I'm 40. I'm 40.
Yeah, it's all right. It's just part of
life. Like life's not always smooth,
right? Good with the bad,
good with the bad.
I appreciate you guys. I like turning
up. It's fun. I don't even I don't mind
asking questions. It's just when people
want to talk shite, that's when it's
just tough.
Check my spam again when I get a chance.
Okay, sir. I'm checking now.
I don't see anything.
Who just said that?
I don't see anything. Can you email me
again? Hungry Unicorn
info@flowzonerader.com
and then let me know um when you've sent
it and I'll check it again.
Is it possible to chop that? Yeah,
absolutely. We're an inside bar. We're
an inside bar. We're inside value. We
went over this at the very beginning of
the show. Remember my what we
anticipated today. Maybe some of you
have forgotten. All right. We're an
inside bar. Really, we failed to break
out of the highs, right? We've washed
it. There's a little wick. All right.
But really, if we can't find acceptance
above here, this is a big level, isn't
it? All right.
We can very easily traverse in here. And
the moment we're holding top side of it,
we can easily easily easily do that.
Once we go from that and we go to the
hourlys,
we're inside previous days value, right?
So inside
we're inside previous week's value
we're inside previous current week's
value. We're inside previous days value.
Right? It's very very very possible,
isn't it, that we just do this all day.
Okay. And like I said to you, I wouldn't
be surprised as some form of megaphone
pattern up here. All right. It would not
surprise me to see this build out,
right? While they decide what they're
doing. All right. They can trap up here.
They can trap down here. But the main
trend has been down, but we did hit the
200 day. The bigger question is, is tech
going to sell off? Are the ETFs going to
catch up to get to those 200 days? We'll
see.
I'm a honorable person. Oh, thank you. I
first read that I thought horrible
person. I was like, you might have a
point. Do I watch football? If so,
what's your team? Gunners. Gunners can
finally win the EPL. I'll show you my
team.
Let's [\h__\h] go. This year is Oh yeah.
100%. Oh yeah. this year. We're coming
for it all. The quadruple.
The quadruple.
We're coming for it all.
I look younger. Oh, that's very kind of
you. I don't feel younger.
You want whatever is in the coffee. I
can put a link like if if you genuinely
want it. It's for mental health. I'm not
even joking. It's like a mushroom blend.
Um, I think it's called like everyday
dose or something. Google every
dose coffee. Yeah, everyday everyday
dose. You can order it on Amazon or you
can get a subscription.
It's got like all the uh lion's mane and
all that stuff in.
Thanks, Jake.
Discord uh if you've done the course um
s you go to the end of the course
beginner to advanced course discord
comes free with that and you just go to
the end of the course buyers can't seem
to build momentum well we're we we need
to build liquidity guys this is why like
you see how uninterested I am because I
just know we are in a liquidity building
phase of the market like just zoom out
make sure you zoom out just even go to
this remember at the beginning of the
Okay, we said we're going to be pinned,
right? Here's your range. They've
they've showed you the range, right? The
trend the last few days has been up,
right? So, we look for a trap where
shorts get stuck to trade the other
side. You can argue that this is the top
side of the range and then we'll come
back down. The only danger for that for
me in that move like I've talked about
is if we go back far enough
there are these stops here which I think
are ripe. So I'd almost we run those
first before we turn back down. That's
when I feel safer once they set a bull
trap above it. But we can just rotate
all day. It is our expectation is to
rotate all day long. I am probably going
to be a one and done trader here today.
But we will see if we pop up here and
trap. Then I'm interested.
Really interested.
Where do I live in Los Angeles?
Oh, mate. I think it's just Look at my
hair and everything. I look awful. I'm a
tired old man. Tired old man.
who's done far too many bad things in
his life.
If you live in clubs for 15, 20 years of
your life, it will take it out of you.
Burning the candle. Burning the candle.
Did I get World Cup tickets? I didn't. I
tried. I went for all the lottos. I
didn't get any. Only one of my friends
got them. Was hoping he would invite us
to come, but uh he he's taking his kids
instead. But I just I will buy I will be
buying them because a lot of it's going
to be at the Sofa which is just down the
road for me. It's not far. 20 minute
drive.
How long do you think it can take an IC
trader to get [\h__\h] out of their head and
learn a new strategy? Oh man. Um
right. I'm going to I'm going to break
this down. I'm going make this real
simple.
A lot of his teachings are really really
really good. All right. When the way you
learn structure is great, the way you
understand forms of imbalances and gaps
are great. The your understanding of
where liquidity might lie is great. What
you don't understand is volume and where
the traps lie in that. So, you don't
need to forget it all, but you need to
stop looking for every fair value gap to
trade and all this stuff. It's like
no no fair value gaps can be great but
like here
I didn't wait for this to get tapped
back into like some of you would have
because I understood that shorts were
trapped and I took the break over it. If
you waited for that you would have been
waiting a long time and the next gap you
could have taken is here and if it ran
that low which it did you would have got
stopped out. All right so understanding
it so you can use all the teachings
together. My problem is not with the
teachings. All right. My problem is the
rehashing, the renaming, the making
stuff up, the lying, all that [\h__\h]
That's my problem. It's not with the
teaching. Some of the teachings are
good. It won't take you too long, but I
do get what you mean. I do understand
what you're saying.
All right. Thanks, Dominic. Instant ban
for Dominic there. Taking the piss out
of my gunners.
Yeah, I'm with you. I know. I know. I
have to say soccer here now. Otherwise,
they think I'm talking about American
football. It's it's it's hard. It's
hard.
Barcelona, mate. Barcelona are absolute
shite right now. What are you talking
about, Harry?
Can I explain how traps help my edge? I
can. I can. I can do that while we wait.
All right, here we go.
I'm going to clean this up.
Okay.
Trend here for the last few sessions
been upside for relief. I think we can
all agree with that, right? Here's your
upside relief.
Yes, upside relief. We know we're coming
into supply.
We don't want to buy up here. But if we
want to be a buyer, there are some areas
where we can think about buying in.
Those areas would be the edge
of a node. All right, the edge of a
node. Maybe even a low volume node on
the previous week. All right, we can
watch like all these areas. An edge of a
node, right? So, we mark those out.
Hello, gray box. That's why you get
marked out. We can already see overnight
every time we can come under here, we
are being absorbed, right? So, that's
the first thing. What is the location
that we're interested in trading in?
Right? We said if we reject 300s,
there's potentially a trade back down to
here, but we have to be very aware of
under 300, they can trap and go back for
the upside because that's the easiest
move right now. So, the first thing is
the location. Once we understand the
location, we're looking for reactions at
levels and how order flow operates. So
if we now go into like even a five
minute chart
all right we sweep as you would call it
or we steal liquidity or we run the
stops of here right so in under here
right and as we leave here right in this
whole area here what happens in here
like we talked about breakout shorts
come into the market and bulls this guy
who was a bull and this guy was a bull
and this guy was a bull and this guy was
a bull they probably stop out so you get
lots of sellside delta.
What does that mean? It means that you
get lots of people hitting the bid. Lots
of aggressive selling. Market sell,
market sell, market sell, market sell.
What does that look like on the tape?
Right. We have heavy CVD and on the tape
here you can see aggressive sellers.
Aggressive sellers under 300. Aggressive
sellers. Aggressive sellers. Aggressive
sellers. And at the very low of day,
aggressive sellers. All right. What
happens after these aggressive sellers
come in at lower day? What's the
reaction? Do we move lower? No, we
don't. So, what does that mean? That
means right here we have a passive
buyer. Now, if that passive buyer wants
to step up and start becoming
aggressive, we can start moving price
higher and they start stopping out. And
all these guys who were short start to
stop out. And that's why we use their
pain at 310s. You would have heard me
keep calling 310s because they kept
getting aggressive here at 310s. I know
there's a big chunk. Look at the delta
here. I know there's a big chunk of
sellers here. And if we start taking
that out, there's only one way we are
going to go and that's upside. That is
how they set the trap. They wash the
liquidity. They encourage shorts to come
in and then we trade the other way. If
you were waiting for a tap back in here
today, it ain't never going to come.
Maybe it comes towards the end of the
day, but when we leave aggressively
because a seller is stuck, we will not
come back and revisit that area because
they will be rushing to hit cover. All
right? If they are short here or here,
they will be rushing to hit buy to get
out of the position. We are not going to
come back down and pick that up again in
a hurry. All right? We're going to move
away from it. That's how that's why.
That's the edge, right? And you can look
at that anywhere you want. Whether
you're using footprint or bookmap or
whatever, it doesn't matter.
How many years are in trading? Like six
or seven full-time. I started in uh
early 20s.
I don't collect cards or anything like
that. No, I collect watches which is a
worst more more expensive habit. Maybe
re accumulation for the weekly model.
Yeah, I wouldn't be surprised. So that
weekly model, mate, think about the
newsletter, Scotty. Think about the news
coming this week. Think about the high
impact news. Think about how high we can
squeeze and how much of a reprice that
can offer Wednesday, Thursday, Friday.
The higher we go, the better. I think
there is a reprice coming into this
market.
End of week maybe. We'll see if we can
squeeze enough. If they can get too
violent, these bulls,
they set up that weekly model really
well. Especially like you look at uh
yesterday and today if we,
you know, we have already taken the high
today. If we can push a bit higher or
maybe do it tomorrow and then close that
down, then we look pretty good. So, not
telling everyone that because that's big
part of the course.
Um,
do I trade live every day? Yeah. Yeah,
I'm here every day. Monday to Friday. I
know today's slower, folks. And just I
like I said, I will not trade out this
range. I I still think this is not a
good enough high, but we will just see
what they want to do with it. You can
see like ES just found a bid on PDC
already reclaiming VWAP and New York
open. Like it's just it's a little
choppy today.
You got your first payout on Lucid
yesterday. Thanks, Alex. Nice work, Ash.
Lovely work.
You know the growers for where you get
mine. That's awesome.
Should try micro doing. I've definitely
tried micro doing. I've definitely tried
more than more than micro doing.
Alex, thanks for all you do. I always
look forward to your stream every
morning. Glad you have won have won your
start. Of course, it will be put to good
use. Oh, nice. Nice, man.
Soon as I done with stream, we'll sort
that out. We'll do a giveaway soon,
folks, as well for Apex.
Halfway through with the foundation
course. Wish you knew about it at the
start. Nice, nice, nice, nice. If I do
make enough for the World Cup, I
probably won't buy it because they're
going to be so expensive.
What's my ethnicity? I'm mixed. I'm
Lebanese. I'm tech technically Lebanese,
Italian, English, Scottish mix. Quarter
course quarter quarter.
What did I work with before?
I don't understand that question. Sorry.
Do you mean what was my job?
How long to profitable? One of you
spamming how long to profitable? It
everyone's journey is different. It
depends how much discipline you've got,
how quickly you absorb information. I
was selftaught. Yeah, I was self
selftaught.
Does the course explain what I just
explained? Yeah, it's all in it's all in
the course in detail.
In detail.
Sorry, lots of uh messages here I'm
trying to get through as we keep range
rotating here. Am I trading with Apex?
Yeah, I trade with Apex. You know my
five favorite uh prop firms. Apex, um
TPT,
uh Funded Next, Lucid, and Tradeify.
Those are my five favorite firms at the
moment. Each of those are different. You
can trade them differently. There's a
video I've done on YouTube explaining
those. The codes are down below. FCT,
best code for all of those other than
for take profit trader. You can use code
flow zone.
How long did it take me to become
profitable? I was profitable in my 20s
uh on like swing positions
and then I was profitable my first like
18 months going full-time into small
caps. I've talked about this before. And
then once the styi checks came in and my
strategy stopped working, I got
absolutely cooked and I had to like
rework my strategy for small caps. I
think there's a diminishing edge in
small caps right now. I see a lot of my
friends really struggling still with
small caps.
Where is footprint located? Uh again,
there's a free video on YouTube right
here. Go to the candle type. Come down.
Volume footprint.
You're going to buy Skywalker. I do like
Skywalker. I'm trying to decide right
now. Been waiting a long time and I'm
trying to decide right now what my next
purchase is. Um last year I bought this
which is uh No Time To Die AmIGGA. year
before I bought myself uh an IWC
engineer
and those were the first ones I bought
for a while. I've also got a uh B metal
Datejust
and an uh Amigga Planet Ocean Chrono and
a number of other things, but those are
like my big ones, I think. Trying to
think if there's anything else.
So, I'm trying to decide.
Here we go. So, we're breaking down
under value now. We might come and
revisit this gray box.
longs might finally get washed out and
might finally come down to these 300s.
We will see. Um, yeah, I'm trying to
decide now. Do I want a Daytona?
Do I want a biometal
uh
Amigga Speed Master?
Do I want the white D speed master?
I don't know what I want. I'll make a
decision this year. Right. I'd be
watching this for a rejection here now.
So, like, do they reject 357? Same
story. I hate how they've built this
out. They can still trap here and come
back in. But if they reject this kind of
level here, this is a node that they
will want to revisit, but it's just I
really do not like the action that I'm
seeing. You see, every time they're
fading, we're coming back inside, coming
back inside. Every time I pop him, we're
coming back inside, coming back inside.
They might have just retrapped here and
come back inside. It's just not I just
do not want to trade in here. Look at
your initial balance. Look at your
midpoint. Look at your value areas. It's
just there's lack of edge here, guys.
Know when to trade, when not to trade.
For me and how I trade, this is not a
time to trade right now. This was a time
to trade. This is a time to leave it
alone.
How do I look for traps on higher time
frames for swings on stocks?
harder to look for them on higher time
frames, but you can look for the same
thing that we just went over. On higher
time frames, when I'm looking for
swings, I'm looking for overextensions
of a basket. So, if I think about my
swings right now, so let's think about
why am I long software right now? Why
was I long OCL for example,
right? If we look at this,
right, basic
understanding is here's your swing
point.
In terms of a discount from premium,
we picked this up at a 61% discount,
right? And we're looking for a
retracement long upside. Why? Because
this is ridiculous. This stock has some
issues. Like there is a chance that it's
got some debt issues, but there's only
like an 8% chance now. And up here they
were thinking it was like 100% chance.
So we expect this this is deep. What
discount? This is premium. This is
discount. That's a D. All right. So
we're looking for this. We'll sell a bit
here. If we start doing this, we'll try
and hold it into here. Same kind of
strategies, right? We're looking for
deep discount where too many sellers are
too ridiculous chasing the lows, right?
Too many sellers get too ridiculous
chasing the lows down here. Now, I would
We'll have a look. We'll have a look. I
haven't even looked, but we will have a
look.
Put my template on.
Oh, you [\h__\h] I have to do this all by
myself. I thought I saved this
Okay. So, once we pivoted above 40,
that's where the sellers were getting
too aggressive the day before and on
this day and Friday. So, once we pivoted
above 40, we're now driving higher. We
can see we're coming into some of these
key pivots here now. All right. Where
these sellers last come in. So, I did
take a partial yesterday
and we're watching this and if we get
over this, we're going to see if we let
out these buyers. And if we let those
buyers out, we're going to look for the
next level. So, the last place the
buyers retracted was up here at 203. So,
we've got potentially we've got this
move to 70. If we get over 85 and we let
the buyers out, I'm looking for 200. So,
that would be what, a 70 plus point
trade, right? Same principles on the
swings. It's exactly the same
principles. location, momentum, where's
the edge?
All principles of the market are same.
Doesn't matter what market you trade,
what you're looking at, the principles
are the same. Look at this. Already
reclaiming. So failure underneath
current day value area low, right?
Trapped under there back into the middle
point. It's going to keep chopping until
they're done with it. They are just
going to build out this liquidity and
they're going to test people who are
impatient today.
Alex, I pass Apex. Do you have any video
explaining the rules for the PA account?
Yeah, I've done a whole uh video on
Apex. Definitely go and watch it. What's
the Trading View volume profile you're
using? You got to be joking me. Are you
are you joking me or not? Read read the
talk from Nightbot an anchor following
profile. Oh, you guys are kidding me. Do
I trade Asia in London? No, I sleep. I
live in Los Angeles. I have to sleep,
guys.
Yeah, that's fine, Carla. You don't have
to like Apex. Like I said, there's lots
of lots of different accounts. Apex
requires patience to get past the
buffer. Then you can really start
scaling.
Reservoir.
Why would I need to work at Citadel? Do
you not understand what freedom is? Do
you think freedom is just money? Freedom
is not just money.
Freedom is time. I can leave here right
now and go and do whatever I want.
That's ultimate freedom. This is
ultimate freedom. No one else is paying
me. I don't have to answer to anyone. I
can see my wife whenever I want. Freedom
is not finance. Finance provides freedom
in in terms of no debt. I have no debt.
I'm a house owner. I'm an asset owner. I
am married. I have a whole life. Like I
tell you guys, get off the screens.
Freedom, ultimate freedom is not working
for someone else. It is being able to do
what you want when you want. It's
nothing to do with money.
It's also freedom of your own brain. Not
having an ego, not worried about
everyone else.
What do I think about trade day which
has end of day draw down? I like them. I
just think they need to like lower their
uh
the amount of days it takes to pass. I
think they need to change that. It's too
long at the moment.
After studying both courses, what advice
would you give a new trader regarding
setups? What setup should a newbie start
on? What I call a protrend setup is the
first trade you should start on. All
right, a protrend setup. I will show you
what that is.
We talk about this all the time. All
right,
let's talk let's say that this is the
daily.
All right, that's a daily chart. Quite
clearly it's in an uptrend. So the
hourly chart would look like this.
Right. And inside here we have protrend
availabilities. Now I would be looking
for the first and second leg over the
third leg. So I'd be looking in these
opportunities here to get long. All
right. On a lower time frame. So in a
lower time frame I'd be looking at these
zones here, right? This zone here. Think
about this as an RBS. Right? resistance
becomes support. This zone here and on a
lower time frame I'd be looking for
something like this where shorts get
trapped and we can trade back upside
which is the main trend and we have
liquidity to aim for which would be this
high and we would hold runners above it.
Right? That's the easiest trade to start
with when you are learning to trade what
we are currently in. Right? All right,
if we think about what the dy's done,
we are currently here. This is not a fun
trade, right? This trade was fun.
This trade would be fun because it' be
pro back down. This trade is not fun.
This trade is a liquidity building phase
of the market. All right, this is why
Alex is chilling out today and doesn't
really care. All right, because Alex
thinks there can be a trap. If we call
this the 800s
on ENQ, I think there can be a trap up
into there. If we reclaim that, I think
there's a giant squeeze out. I think
somewhere in here, they will trap bulls
and they will look to try and do this
move for a retest down here and then
we'll see if they bid up or let it go.
All right, so we don't trade this. Well,
I don't trade that. You guys can do what
you want. If you like trading the
rotations, trade trade the rotations,
right? Some people love a rotation. I
don't I really don't. Right. And I'm
very honest about that. I talk about
that all the time.
What's my opinion on Jacob Co? Don't
like them. Each their own though.
I hate the Land Dweller. Not a fan at
all. I'd rather have an AP than a Land
Dweller. And I really like my engineer.
So, I don't feel like I need either of
those.
Lucid Flex is best for a newbie. No
reoccurring subscription. $60 for 25. I
get I agree. I put it in the video. I
put it in the video. It's It is a
fantastic account. It might well be the
number one. They are going to overtake
from Topstep who are changing their
rules, changing their pricing, doing
sneaky sneakys. I've told you guys a
long time that guy is not a good guy.
That is a bad actor.
Going to the doctor and dentist would be
a priority for me. I don't know what I
saw there, but okay. I might have missed
something. Sorry, Evan. Helix, what's
your trigger on your buying earlier
today? The 5060s area before it rocked
higher. The shorts, it was the shorts
being trapped. All right, let me show
you. It was
okay. See this?
Hopefully you guys can see this. I'll
move it up a bit. You see how many
sellers came in in this bar? This was
the previous point of control bar,
right? In the previous point of control
in the last five-minute bar. Look at all
the selling down there. We closed up,
right? They try to resell this. They
attack the same level. We get a 50 lot.
Come flying in here at 85. We trade
lower. Look at the selling at the low of
day. Look at the selling. Look of the
Look at the delta. What do we do in the
next bar? Do we trade under these
participants? No. What do we do here at
86s? Do we trade under them? No. So, who
is stuck in here? Who is stuck? It ain't
buyers. There's a passive buyer lifting
us higher. This is sellers too
aggressive at the lows. Tens was the big
level for me. I was looking at tens and
twelves around here. Once we reclaim
that, I I think I put some on here
because I was like, they're getting
stuck. I'll have to rewatch it. I'm
pretty sure I put some on here saying
they're getting stuck and I'll rebid and
add over I think it was tens. And we
push. We hold. I rebid and then we
squeeze. All right, it's these guys
entering short in a bad location that
give me the confidence to move higher
knowing that they are now stuck. That is
why that is what that is why with 90% of
my trades are the same thing. Even if
I'm looking for a pullback trade, I'm
looking for someone to be too aggressive
in the wrong direction to give me
confidence.
Joe, there's a free uh someone asking
what is the setting for the footprint
chart on my trading view. There's a free
video on my YouTube. Just go to um
there's a whole section on
understanding order flow on my YouTube.
Just go to that. There's a video on
there. I talk I talk through it all.
No, Speedy Daytona is best value. I
mean, Daytona is double the price of
Speedy. Don't know if it's actually best
value, but
I don't keep a trade calendar, Gambino.
I literally just don't have one.
But I can start keeping one if that's
going to make people happy. But I just
don't do it. I've been I've been around
for too long. I don't even journal
anymore. I used to journal all the day.
All the time. I have like stacked
journals like full of these are all old
journals of trades that I used to write
down because I think writing down makes
you
able to uh absorb stuff. Let's let's see
if I can find a big loss in here. There
will be some [\h__\h] monstrous losses in
here.
This is like the small cap days.
See if I can find a blow up. We can all
have a laugh there. There's a good one.
Minus4,000
BT BTX.
What date was that? It looks like
maybe the end of March 2021. 14,000 I
got wrecked. It says BTX squeezing no
limits. So, I probably got [\h__\h] in
after hours. There's a good one for you.
So, I keep all these. Don't trust me. I
[\h__\h] journaled a long time.
14,000 BTX in 2021. Should we have a
look for a joke? It's probably not even
here. It's probably an old Chinese
sticker that I just got Chinese sticker
I got wrecked on. Oh, it's still here.
Right, here we go.
This will be fun. 2021. I got cooked on
this.
Assuming this is still the same stock.
March 2021, I think it was somewhere
around here.
Is it here?
I was probably
playing for some failed follow through
somewhere around here. April, March.
Probably this squeeze here.
this gap up. Probably it's probably
somewhere around here or this day here.
I don't know.
Yeah, I got cooked in this. What was the
one? Moxc. I think that's gone now.
Yeah, it's gone. There's another one I
took a huge loss on.
No data. Yeah,
I remember getting cooked by that one
back in the day. I think that was like a
20 grand loss. real money that weren't
[\h__\h] uh sim money. It [\h__\h] hurt.
Believe me, it hurt
is footprint. You need premium access.
Yes, you do. You need premium.
How do I use both volume bars at the
bottom? Well, one's volume and one's
delta. They're not both volume, right?
So, this is volume. This is actually
delta. It's not volume,
right? You don't have to have delta this
way. It's just you have a choice on
trading view. You could have the
traditional delta, which I have on a
five minute, which is right here.
Right? Traditional delta. This is delta.
This is the chart. So, when they're in
line, delta and the charts are doing the
same thing. Yesterday with big delta day
up, right? Big squeeze up. Holding all
day. Price broke down here. Did we shift
this low underneath? No. Buy a step back
in. Try and hold. All right. So, we can
use it for divergence. We go over all
that stuff in the course.
All right. How many likes we got? I want
to do a giveaway soon.
What indicator do I use for volume
profile? You've got to be joking. I'm
going to assume you're all joking when
you ask that. Now,
is footprint chart suitable for MacBook
Air? I mean if yeah I mean if you have
trading view on MacBook Air then yes
I get the sellers at the lows for sure
being trapped but what is the trigger
the buyers the next candle once we trade
above them bud. All right. So, once we
trade above those, I don't even need to
wait for a close. I just want to see us
trade above those and buy step in and
then I'm joining.
16 years old, profitable now in the last
3 months. Averaging $7,000 a month so
far. Scared to size up. Opinions means a
lot to anyone who'd help me. You're
doing great, mate. If you're 16 and
you've gone 3 months consistently making
7K, size up slowly. That doesn't mean
double your size. So, I don't know what
your lot size is at the moment,
but you want to scale slowly. And
remember, if you jump from one mini to
two, you're literally doubling your size
and your risk. You're going to find it
hard to do that. So, if I if you were
using one mini, I would move to like 12
or 13 micros, then 15, then 17, then two
minis, for example.
When was my last red day? There was
definitely one last month, maybe a
couple last month,
but they're not big red nowadays.
They're just small. What are some swing
trades you like right now in the current
market? Well, I'm already long in my
positions. Um, I'm long Apple, Oracle,
but I've been long Apple since 8 uh
August, so I'm up 27.27%.
I'm on long Oracle from last Thursday.
I'm up 17.75%. I'm long AMD from uh long
long long time ago. I'm up 31% and I've
trimmed most of that. I'm long Robin
Hood and I trimmed some yesterday. I'm
up 18 and a half%. I bought that on the
Thursday. I'm long Meta. I'm up 9 and a
half%. I'm long um I bit. I'm up 6.28%
on that. I'm long Microsoft. I'm up 2%
on that. I'm long Open Door. I'm up 150%
on that, but I'm only long on that with
one share because I was long big size
and we got a 500% winner. I'm also long
Uu, pretty much flat on that. I'm long
USA, pretty much flat on that small
size. I'm long Netflix. I'm down 5.43%
on that. I'm looking to add on any big
flushes. And I'm long Amazon. I'm down
5.80% on that. Those are in commons. I'm
looking to hold Netflix and Amazon
forever. I'm not looking to sell those.
I'm looking to buy into deep discount
where possible on those. So there you
go.
Alex, do you have any education on reg
regular technical indicators? I'm sure
I'm not the only one at the moment. I
can't find level two data.
Uh you have to pay for level two data.
So like if you're trading with a prop
firm, I'm sure they have options to pay
for it. You'll need to pay for it
otherwise you won't get it. Um, I use
Bookmap for mine. You can use whatever
you want. You can even pay for it on
Trading View. You'll just need a DOM to
read it. All right. Big seller here. 300
lot at 360. They're looking to test this
guy at 360. This node here, you see this
node? They're looking to test him right
now.
Uh, volume sati uh the indicator at the
bottom. One of you asking volume sati
thoughts on RSI divergence? I like it. I
don't use it. I like it on higher time
frames. I would not use it on a lower
time frame. But where I think people
come stuck is they just I think using it
as divergence is good, but using it as
an extreme and think, "Oh, that that
that can't go any lower or that can't go
any higher. That's just stupid. It can.
Do I see track buyers on the top of ENQ?
I mean, there are, but we didn't take
out the excess. There are. Look, we
still have this node, but we didn't take
out excess. We're just We're just
building like this huge D-shape right
now. It's just gross. Just building this
huge node right now.
I just don't think there's edge here for
me. Like I don't
You can argue to fade this, right? But
there's just not much room here unless
they wash this and come down here and
then snap that and come down there. But
it's just
it's not a trade I'm looking for, folks.
Shua not much Arabic for me. Uh the rest
of my family, yes, because they uh grew
up in Cairo. I didn't. I grew up in
London, but rest of my family do.
Uh these
do I use TPO? I have it on a 30-minute
chart. I don't use it that often.
What's the difference between CBD and
volume delta? Uh cumulative is like it's
growing volume throughout the day. Uh
delta in each candle is just that one
single down delta print.
Edward, that's awesome. And that what a
great dad you have to do that as well.
It's great.
Walmart. I mean, it's a great defensive
name to move into.
A lot of those positions I talking about
in S&P, like I have a lot of uh ETF
positions. A lot of those positions I
just talked about are will be like
permanent holds. any Mag 7 and any buy
opportunity I have if we go deep
discount.
I'm really hoping uh that we go deep
discount this year, but it's uh the
recovery, the hold on ES and RTY is
looking pretty good. I was hoping the
Q's would trade back towards 23,000s and
offer me an opportunity to reby uh ETFs
this year. We might still get it. We'll
see.
Is Thinkle Swim good for level two? Uh,
yeah, I think it's pretty good. I I
don't use it. Yeah, I think it's pretty
good.
No worries, Edward. Thanks for showing
up.
I showed a free level two on NTA. Is
that true? No, I don't have a level two
on NTA. I use it right here. This is my
level two bookm.
That's my ladder.
I use footprint on on uh Ninja, but I
don't have a book that I'm watching. I'm
sure you can get it, but I don't use it.
I mean, I know you can get it. I just I
don't use it. I have it on up there.
You get called Habibi.
You should call her habi.
That's maybe that's why I'm a good good
trader then because I got close to the
primitance. All right, we have a spoofer
on the tape here at 360. He just lifted
his liquidity. First spoofer I've seen
of the day.
NTA free level two video on YouTube. I
don't think so. Oh yes. Yes, sorry. I
see what you're saying. Uh it's more
order flow than level two, but yeah, it
there's a video on my YouTube.
Yeah, order flow is free. Are we coming
down? We're just in a range, guys. This
is very controlled. Look how controlled
this is.
This is not panic. This is very
controlled in here. It's very possible
that they come up to here again and make
a decision here and then do they want to
do this or do they want to do this? Like
I don't care what they want to do. It's
I just don't care. don't care enough
about it right now with how they're
acting.
Yes, volutric chart is one option that
you can use on NT.
What's someone lifting the bid and
spoofing mean? They're taking it on and
off, but it does not mean it goes up or
down. Yeah. So, if we I'll show you.
All right. So,
This guy here was a big seller. He was I
don't know why it's saying 64 lot. Maybe
it was stacked, but we had like a number
of hundred lots here. As price got close
to him, he removed that. So, he was a
seller. He removed that. So, then we
traded through him. All right. So, he
let the price come up and maybe he
filled some of it here and we're trading
back downside. But, he did not try and
put up a wall here. He lifted it hoping
that price would go higher by the looks
of it. There you go. He's up here. So,
this 300 lot moved up here. So he put a
wall there and as price came in, he's
lifted it and he's now trying to attract
price up into the 400. So he's trying to
encourage price to come back up here
right now. All right, he was here. He's
trying to use his size to say, "Hey,
I've got liquidity here. Come up here
and get me." All right, so he could be
two things. He might be a buyer trying
to force price higher.
Or he might be a seller trying to
attract price to come higher to then
sell into. Both of those things are
possible.
How do I clean up this drawing tool?
Clear drawings.
We go.
All right. So, that's the spoofing.
Lifting is the same thing. Normally,
you'll just see them like buyers will
step through like this and they'll just
keep sell sell on the way up.
It's just so ugly this chart right now.
What tells me that he removed just that
that right there, Scotty, when he
doesn't get filled.
So this guy here, see how it's vertical?
It's horizontal. Sorry. And we never
touch him. All right. Because if we
traded through him,
you'd see it like this where this limit
order gets filled down here. So this
buyer here, he gets filled. He moves up
a bit to get filled, right? So, we will
trade through those levels. You'll see
price come through all this orange. This
is us trading through levels. Same here.
We trade through this buyer and then
turn around. I'll try and see if I can
find some other big stuff. All right.
Here, we trade through this buyer and
then turn around. Here, we don't fill
these guys. We never get up into them.
He's been here all day at 450 looking to
get filled. All right. And then he's
pulled it off. And that might well be
him scattering down here looking to get
filled down here. But this guy never
gets filled. He pulls his offer before
he gets filled. Not only that, we would
see that show up in the volume. All
right, we would see that additional
volume here. All right, and we would see
it in the delta. It never gets filled.
He pulls it and look at it's the same
size lifting up here. It's the same
block. The moment he pulls it, look
where he goes. Oh, I'm just going to
skip up here. He moves it 50 points
higher. That's how we know. That's how
we know it's the same size as well. Same
size, same time. It's the same player
lifting. He's trying to get price to
retract up to him.
Doesn't mean he gets it, but it's what
he's looking to do.
Am I going to trade more today? Uh, not
unless I see something I really like.
Um, I will set price alerts for sure.
Which implemented change had the biggest
impact on
trading? Um,
I would say just location momentum,
asking myself that question, right? So,
pl plotting out the locations that I
want to trade and not trading the
locations I don't want to trade. So, we
plotted out down here. We were willing
to trade under these gray boxes or
around these gray boxes today because we
knew there was possible trap levels down
here. Up here, I was willing to look at
trading for the short side, but I don't
like this high of day auction. All
right, we've gone flat there. I would
really have liked us to spike up into
this gray box. All right, if we'd done
something like this. All right, then I'd
be happy to look for a short back down.
All right, so my locations today were
here and down here to trade from. My
locations not to trade from are in here.
I don't want to trade in here. So, that
probably helped me a lot, right? Because
now I have a rule of if I'm not in that
location, I cannot trade, right? I
cannot trade. Yesterday was kind of the
same actually. It made it a bit hard for
me. We took the longs. Anyone that was
here yesterday, we knew, see here's the
location. We knew that if we held blue
box, we'd be looking for longs. It was a
very similar trade setup yesterday. We
washed into the low trapped and we got
long here and I think we got long here
and then I think I was done with it. I
think I got knocked out. Now, this is
hard because we go deep premium all the
way up to previous week high. So, I
think I previous week high. I think I
had a go. It's coming into the end of
stream. I think I might have had one go
here and one go here at getting that
fade back in. We did get it off stream.
We did get it. I didn't get the big
nuke, but we did get this in Discord
together. We got that. I didn't get
this. I was gone for it. Um I can show
you because I'm sure some of you going
to be like, "No, you didn't."
We did. We got it together in Discord.
Um, so I'm going to grab it now or you
will tell me I'm wrong.
Me find it.
Okay. Yeah.
Okay. So, we're watching this big player
right here. Once he got trapped, I was
willing to play short.
talking about into the key level
and then right here. So I say just got
to start a short side here just in case
last trade for me either goes or doesn't
either way. Can't force it and don't
want to. Here we go. So you can see my
short position right using this trap
buyer above me as my stop. All right.
And we're looking for a wash back down
low. So the team start to join me in
here and then I think I draw what I'm
looking for. So, I'm looking for that
trade all the way back down to 300s,
right? For the wash, we're talking about
who needs to leave because there was a
buyer bidding all day at 80 once he left
the tape, right? We're talking about
this shelf. Once we leave the tape, we
can repric this low volume node
and we start locking some in. And I
think the guys catch it a bit later when
I leave.
There we go. Daniel got it. goop
and that was it. All right. So, if I
don't get it here, I if it's still
selling up, I try and get it in the next
trade, but it's the same thesis. So,
it's just waiting for the location. All
right. I was unwilling to buy all this.
Anyone who joined me on stream, I said
this is a force up. I think there'll be
a wash down and a rebid and we're going
to range. There's the wash down. There's
the rebid. And we go back into range,
which we are still in now. Nothing has
changed. We're back in range. have been
in the same range all night, all day,
right? This is how I know it's liquidity
being built out.
What made those locations attractive?
Higher time frame volume areas.
I see where the horizontal red area
doesn't continue stretching. Oh, you
mean on my Ninja Trader? May that those
are imbalances, not um supply or demand.
They're just imbalances. This is when
it's been filled.
Do I ever use 90 seconds candles? No, I
don't.
Do I also trade VWAP bounces sometimes?
Nice opportunities. If not, why? Yeah, I
do. I prefer the IB trade, which is what
I would have been looking for today. So,
I would have preferred that fail
breakout rejection of IB trade to VWAP.
All right. And then if we reject IB, we
keep rejecting there. There is
possibility. We got have to get under
this that we will go from VWAP to IB low
now. It's possible. It's possible.
But again, I'm not going to trade this
today because of the type of environment
that we're in. We're in a rotation. I
don't want to get caught.
I don't I'm not playing uh options. I'm
in commons on USA Army.
What's the best prop firm I have only
ever been with with Topstep? Then I
would say Lucid and Funded Next are
going to be the best prop firms for you.
Do I think it's you can pump back up?
Yeah, definitely definitely definitely
that like this.
Think about this. Have we run this stop?
No. Have we run this stop? No. Have we
run this stop? No. Have we run this
stop? No. Have we run this stop? No.
Have we run this stop? No. Have we run
this stop? No. Guess what happens when
we start running those stops, right? We
run this one. Oh, pop this one. Oh, we
can pop this one. If they get enough,
they pop this one. Oh, they pop this
one. Oh, they pop this one. And then
they get the move. Can absolutely do it.
It can absolutely do it. Uh I wouldn't
be positioning myself for it. But yes,
if we talk about building enough
liquidity to go up, yes, we can get to
here and if we get acceptance over that,
we can still look for that. We can also
reject here, reject here, reject here
and do this. They are just building out
in this giant range. But look how much
easier this is to trade than this,
right? I don't want to trade that. I
like trading that one and done and
early. Thanks very much. We got this
move. Think about this from
950. Final cover was this push up here
to 10:06. We had to wait 15 minutes.
Anyone trading this has been stuck in
this since, you know, the best part of
two and a bit hours now.
Yeah, I use alerts for um for both day
trades and swings. Definitely.
Big picture. Yeah, we're sideways right
now. Big picture. Is Discord free? Uh
well, yes. I mean, there's no monthly
fee, but only if you do the 20our
courses for students who do that.
Okay, it's uh coming into the end of
day. Likes are pretty good here. You
know what that means?
And give away an Apex account.
Just type in FCT. It's the code to use
for all your prop firms. Type in FCT
once in chat. Please don't spam it. Just
type it once. Give you guys an Apex
account.
So that seller come back down. You see
him on the tape above. He he's moved
back down to these 350s. 300 lot 350s.
So he originally pulled 350s, moved to
400, back to 350s. this same guy.
You can see it's the same guy cuz he
pulls his order and then comes back
down. I wonder if it's an algo. Let me
just check. Yeah, I think it might
actually be an algo providing liquidity
there.
Give you guys another minute or so.
I don't think Top Set's closing down,
but it's they're definitely
they're definitely losing market share
and it's hurting them. So, they're
changing rules.
Latif, you don't get the location part
of where I took it.
went over this under here, right?
Because breakout sellers came in under
here and stops got washed. So once we
return back, they get trapped. So I take
it here on the reclaim or this move back
to the upside of this. We're protecting
current week developing volume profile
value towards this node, right? And then
we rinse back up.
I like trader. I think they're really
good.
Possibly newbie. We We just have to see.
Possibly. I think they've got to get
under this node in, you know, this gray
box here first, but yeah, possibly. They
might start bidding around here. It
really depends. ES is holding up well.
We have to see. Anything's possible.
Okay, I'm going to pull this winner
here.
Edward Ruxens. Edward Ruxens, you're the
winner of today's Apex account. Let me
know you're here, Edward.
Edward Ruxens,
congratulations, Edward. Um, just email
me info@flowzontrader.com.
Please just send me a screenshot of you
logged into your YouTube and uh I will
send you a code for a free Apex account.
You can get any size account you want,
any type of account you want. So if you
want the 300K, you can get it. If you
want a static, you can get it. You want
a 25K, you can get it. Whatever you
want.
Ivan, it's [\h__\h] madness that I have
people like you here. So Ivan, why don't
you put your trades on the screen on
YouTube? Anyone can put a box and say
they entered a trade just like you do.
Shown to do this in real time is
different.
I do it in real [\h__\h] time. You
I do it even before it's happening. But
I cannot draw everything on for you all
the [\h__\h] time. I literally tell you
what I'm doing. I execute on a different
chart because I cannot draw all this on
on Ninja for you.
Why are you here asking that? Is it
because you're [\h__\h] at trading and you
need me to do it and you can't listen or
understand and you need me to physically
do it so you can just do the same thing?
Is that why? That's the bigger question.
[\h__\h] me.
It's amazing. You're acting like this is
after the fact. It's before it even
happens. Before it even happens. It's
here. I'm going to look for a trap down
here somewhere today. It's here. They've
just caught the sellers underneath 50s.
If we reclaim 80s, we're looking for
long. If we hold above 110s, I'm going
to add. It's all in there. Lose Use your
ears, you numpty. Use your ears, mate.
Yeah. Anyone can draw that after. Not
anyone can do it during when I told you.
You're right. You're right.
Anyone can also draw it after and say,
"Oh, that was the high day. I told you
my exit here because it was previous
week value area high." You [\h__\h]
idiot.
Gh.
Why? Why? Why?
It's crazy.
Ivan is the reason I love my dog. Quite
right.
It's not that I'm letting people get to
me. It's that I'm going to defend myself
like I'm giving out free edge here. I've
also said I'm not going to touch all of
this. I've also said what type of
environment I think the market is like.
Quite right, JD. Should we go back to
when it was like 20 of us?
That's it, Evan. I can't I can't help it
when the tape moves fast. like the pace
at which the tape moves when they trap.
When a trap occurs, we have a fast tape.
All right? When a trap occurs,
we have a fast tape. I can't do anything
about it. Like, this happened quick. I
can call out what I'm seeing. I can't do
anything else.
Anyway, whatever.
Whatever. All right, folks. Into lunch
here.
I did a course giveaway already, buddy.
I already did one.
How long have I been drinking mushroom
coffee? Uh, only since I've only think
since [\h__\h] hit the fan for me, bud. It's
a new thing for me. Um, my body, uh, my
nervous system shut down early January
and still is. So, I've had to do
anything I can to fix that and this has
been part of it. So, it's working for me
for sure. It's I don't know if it's just
this. I'm there's lots of uh stuff I'm
taking at once, but it's it's definitely
helped.
It will come, Evan. Don't worry. It will
come. It will come.
Can I let yell at you next? Yeah.
Ashwagander. I'm on JD. Ashwagandha and
um magnesium as well.
Ted, love the course. have been so
successful the last few few weeks more
than over the last several months.
That's awesome.
Yeah, I think definitely try it, Nathan.
It's It's been good.
Or just get you can get tablets with it
with it all. Yeah, that spoofer at 350
is still there. I He's just providing
liquidity when you can see we're
bouncing between 300 and 350 now on the
book.
You're so selfless, Alex. Truly one of a
kind speaking to you. That is
inconsiderate and ungrateful. Thank you
for being here each and every day and
being kind. Thanks, Jay. Appreciate
that.
Uh, it varies, Enzo. Any anywhere from
like 10 to 50
depending on the market conditions.
Would
you go long 310? This node here I like.
Right. So if we think about where we
found bids this morning, right? It might
be that they come into here and rebid
it. Um so this gray box has been here
all day. This is where I think I would
cover if I if I was short, if I'd got
this move, I'd be covering into this and
holding a runner. If shorts fail to
break down, now
just have a look at here.
Oh, they got caught again, guys. They
got caught again.
Shorts got caught under 310.
Shorts just got caught under 310.
Look here. Lookie lookie. All right,
these are the aggressive shorts. There
they are. Same level 311. Right, they
just got caught there. If we hold that,
we will bid back up and come and try and
let out all these buyers. You might see
a squeeze here starting. Yeah, you're
starting to see it right into the gray
box. All right. So, under 310s, all the
time we protect 310s. Now, shorts are
stuck. This is your reversion. So, if
they can hold a bid into 30s, you'll get
a squeeze back out into this node. And
then you're asking for the same thing.
Remember, this is very controlled
selling. When they have finished
selling, they can come and rinse all
this this out. There is still that
seller at 50. And we're going to test
him. And if he lifts, this might spike.
So, we'll see. I'll stay with you for
like five minutes here. If he lifts at
this 50, he has been filled here once
before, but he's here. He's here right
now. If they lift him, we might spike
here. ES reclaiming VW up as well. Big
level. 50. Big level.
Here comes the squeeze. They're trying
to lift 50. They filled some of him.
He's staying on the tape this time. He's
actually providing the liquidity this
time. He's staying there. Let's see if a
buyer can just force them through here
or not.
Yeah, I would say now all the time you
protect uh 311s, you've got a shot to
move higher. If the next pullback holds
25s, you could think about getting long,
right? If the next pullback holds
25s,
you could think about getting long for
this move here.
And you must respect 50. So if it does
this, I'd be a partial. And if you do
this, you'll get a great move.
Okay. But you know, you could always
listen to Ivan. Um,
okay.
Yeah. Without being an idiot.
See you. Um, with large moves you try
and catch, what typical point stop loss
do you have? It all depends on where the
moves invalidated. Right, you're through
the 50s now. They you have to see if
they lift this. So, you got this node
here, 57, 64s, and then sort of 90s is
what you're looking for.
There you go. There's the lift. So into
58. They're adding liquidity at 70s now.
You might well get a lift back up. I
would still say if you defend 25s and
30s now, there's still an opportunity to
get long, but you're into lunchtime now.
Volume's dipped. But you can see the
gray box held. All right. So, think
about this same area. This is where the
sellers got trapped this morning.
Remember I kept saying our ad over 10.
That was the ad. So, we bought that. We
added, we've controlled repric down to
this same area. They've rebid this and
they're going to take this try and get
back towards the 90s probably. And this
like we talked about, they can start
running stops. All right, so they've run
this stop now and they're going to try
and run these stops now. And if they run
this stop, they will try and run this
stop. And if they get that, this one,
and then this one, and then this one,
and then this one cuz this is very
controlled with no one being run out. So
they are going to try and lift. You are
okay to buy this, I think, on dips that
hold here. All right. And you must
respect the volume.
Took it from 14. Nice work, Adam. Yeah,
nice work. Nice work,
Edward. Yeah, checking now.
Yeah, I've got it, Edward. All right,
guys. I'm going to get off stream. We'll
do the same thing tomorrow. Um, again,
if you are a buyer and you want to play
the rotation today,
yeah, really, unless you bought that,
you need a pullback to come in to give
you the opportunity uh into some of
these nodes and then look for 90s and
then see if they lift 90s for that high
of day. I don't think the auction at the
high is in not on not on ENQ. It is
looks in on ES. I don't like that high
of day auction. Like I said, I think
there is a chance to get up into this
gray box. We've said it all day long.
Um, all right team, tomorrow morning we
go again.
Let's see what we get set up for
tomorrow. Hopefully, we get a beautiful
weekly model. It would be really nice.
Ideally, a gap up would be great. Would
be great. A gap to fade tomorrow would
be fantastic. And uh, yeah, use hard
stops, all that good stuff. Peace and
love. And, uh, see you tomorrow morning.