morning folks. Morning. Morning. Lots to
get through here this morning. All
right, so uh let's get through it
because things are changing quickly in
this market. Like I've warned you, it's
been a low volume move based on
absolutely nothing. And this is what
happens. and you get one small headline
and the tone shifts. Okay? Because
there's nothing really to prop us up.
So, let's have a look into this market.
What if you had drift, low volume,
right? Nothing. It's literally nothing.
It's inflated on nothing. There is no
bullish sentiment here. There's nothing,
right? They're pricing back in the rate
cut which was already priced in here.
And then we decided we weren't going to
cut and now we're back into no man's
land, right? We're just back into the
same level. Nothing's changed, folks.
Nothing's changed. In fact, macro
sentiment is looking worse and worse.
And the lies and smoke and mirrors that
you're seeing coming out are pretty
horrific right now. And I can give you
an example. Trump's comment yesterday
saying that uh Black Friday sales were
massive and the biggest they've ever
been. Um yes, they might look big, but
the price of product was up 7%. The
amount of products actually bought were
down 11% and 95% of it was bought on
credit. And we all know at the moment
that consumers are being unable to pay
off their credit cards. Okay? So, is it
good? No. It's fluff. All right? Don't
buy a shitty car with no engine under
the hood. Understand what you're buying.
We want to see if this market can come
back down here and hold a good higher
low. That and only then will I start to
become confident in this market. What
we've had this morning is Microsoft come
out basically saying there's not as much
demand for AI as they thought there was.
Oh dear. Well, this is a market
ballooned on AI and everyone's freaking
out right now. We have to pay attention
to what's actually happening in the
charts. Inside bar yet again, we're
going to go and open up inside. Now,
what you want to do is reference
yesterday's value areas, yesterday's New
York session areas because we are
potentially going to find support in
this sort of block here. All right, we
will find weakness if we trade under
this and reject it. All right, and
that's when I expect there to be a
rotation to 900 if we do that.
Otherwise, right, any drift which comes
down here and reclaims these these
levels, we're just going to chop again.
And I tell you what, I will not be
trading that. That would be exactly the
same as me yesterday. That will be a
leave alone day. I am not interested in
trading inside this location here. You
are asking to get chopped to death if
you do that. Bulls want to be strong.
They better start breaking out. Bears
want to be strong. They better start
holding a lower high under here. Anytime
we're just doing this sideways, I have
zero interest in trading it. I've been
around far too long to get pulled into
nonsense like that. All right, into the
hourlys. And you can see how quickly
that shifted sentiment. All right, I
think it was in first 2 minutes we
dropped over 100 points in 8 minutes.
We've given up the whole bar from
yesterday. Right, that shows what
happens when there's no volume, folks.
All right, when there's no volume, when
there's no structure, this is what
happens. So, overnight, what have we
had? Well, a whole lot of nothing. All
right, sideways. Here was yesterday's
dip. Absorbed back up. Sideways,
sideways, sideways. Did they break out
and hold? No, they didn't. So, as soon
as bad news came, what did that mean?
All this low volume that we've had.
Bye-bye. And right back down to the
bottom side. All right. So, now we're
testing yesterday's New York session
low. This is your key pivot and
sentiment. All right. Maybe they sweep
it. Maybe today all they do is grind all
the way back. They can easily do that
and just do a big old inside bar of
nonsense in here. This market will get
fun if we start holding outside or if we
back test value and push down back
towards previous weekly value. That is a
trade setup for me.
Failed look below is potentially a trade
setup. Although I really don't want to
trade inside this. I really don't want
to trade inside that. A reclaim of this
or any reclaim of previous day value
area low. That is my no trade zone. I'm
not trading inside of yesterday's value
and previous uh day's value or overnight
value. This is your death chop range.
All right, it's showing you there's your
death chop. All right, it's telling you
that's death drop. I don't want to trade
inside that. All right, so bears have an
opportunity again to take control here.
If they're going to get really bullish,
they better start breaking out and
holding above key levels, which so far
they've failed to do. All right. So, I'm
going to first be watching this morning
any bat test of basically 540 550 to see
if bears come in and defend this for a
retest of this low. All right. If we get
follow through, great. But the first
trade will be from 550 down to 400. 150
pointer. That's what I'm looking for.
Any reclaim of 550 and drift higher. Not
interested in touching. I just have no
interest in trading inside yesterday's
value. you're asking for it. We move up
to here. You can see it very, very
clearly. All right. This is a whole lot
of [\h__\h] that I was calling for
yesterday. Three drive higher, wash all
the way down, reclaim it. One, two,
three, drive higher. Can't go anywhere.
Wash all the way down. Does that look
similar? It's the same move. We're boxed
in, right? I don't want to trade inside
the top level of this box. I want bears
to come in and offer an actual legit
trade setup now that they've had a
sentiment shift. That's the play for me.
If it doesn't do it, doesn't do it. It
is what it is. Okay, let's move into
lower time frames. And we're actually
going to go through quite a few bits
here today because what's really
important for me right now is these
spiders. All right, you know that the
180s have been a big level. There's a
big gamma level. I talked about it
yesterday. All right, they've got huge
gamma exposure. Sorry. 180s at 680.
All the time they're holding 680. This
can squeeze back up. All right. 680 is
your overunder. You can see you haven't
taken out previous day low. We've got
lots down here. If they want to come and
wash down here, uh let's just call it a
78, right? 680 breaks and you're looking
at 78. And look how ridiculous these
moves are. This is what I'm trying to
get through to you at the moment. These
are not healthy moves. These are asking
to get crushed. All right, that's a
10point move is available there and it
would not surprise me. It will happen at
some point. They cannot sustain this
unless they're really going to break out
which they so far have not done. They've
just gone sideways. We are boxed in in
spy between a gamma level and between
the 84s. All right, if we zoom out of
what of that and see what that means, we
are not creating a higher high. All
right, I don't care about your trend
lines. The count is here. One, two,
lower low, lower low. Until we create a
higher high versus this swing point,
this market is stuck and it will
eventually give up if they cannot break
out. This is why I want to be very very
cautious. All you have here is uh what
four days basically inside building
liquidity. They can stay here. They can
keep pinning and pinning and pinning and
pinning and pinning and waiting for the
Fed announcement. Sure, they can
absolutely do that. All right. to
understand where you are in the count.
This still has the potential to roll
over and maybe here we set a higher low.
Maybe then it finds some strength
because if I was a buyer, I wouldn't
really want to be buying up here, right?
You're so close to the alltime highs
here. You're trying to buy a 10point
squeeze for end of year. Psychopath
move. All right. Psychopath move when
we've drifted what's this? For 30
points, drifted 30 points without a
pullback. very very very dangerous to be
trying to play that on the spiders. All
right, so understand that Dixie starting
to pull back a bit. All right, so failed
to break out and sustain over 100. Uh
the carry trade is still looking like
it's going to be a problem last uh next
month. Let's have a look at the VIX
because we're boxed in on the VIX as
well. So there you go. There's your box
in the VIX. What do I say is dangerous
about this? You can see this two drive.
All right, and failure down here and
we're making higher lows, right? When
did that last happen? There's your two
drive to the same point. Two drive and
making higher lows. And what happened
next? A ripup. I'm very concerned about
that. It can take months. It might take
another two two months to happen. But
this is concerning. The VIX really needs
to start breaking down back into this
box down here for bulls to really
continue this. If we keep holding here,
the tighter and the tighter it is, this
low here. I don't know why they're
holding that, but they are holding it.
And I'm observing it because this
Looks like a bit of a replication and
I'm very concerned about this move
happening. Either this side of Christmas
or early January. So I have my eye on
that. All right. This move here is the
same setup at the moment. So I am
concerned about it. No doubt about it.
Also got one eye on this 30y year. All
right. if we get back into these levels
and I am watching uh the JPY trade like
I talked about and looks a bit
uncontrollable breaking out at the
moment. All right, that's it. That's
what I'm watching. That's what I'm
looking for, folks. I couldn't make it
clearer for you this morning. All right,
we need to see a rejection of previous
days value. If we see that rejection of
previous days value area low, I'm
interested. If we don't see it, I'm
probably not interested in doing much.
All right. So, I want to see a lower
high created either here or in front of
there. I really don't want to see us
drift back into this. All right. We will
lose edge if we drift back into that.
So, that is what we're looking for in
this morning's session. I want to be
very careful if we start reclaiming it.
You guys like trading range and you want
to consider that a look below and fail
and go, by all means. But again, we
haven't taken out this low, right?
because we've left liquidity there,
which is why I want to be more focused
on this trade here before anything else.
If they protect that low and do this,
this will be a dirty move, but I won't
get caught in it because I will not
participate up here. All right, that is
me making it as clear as possible for
you guys and what I'm going to look for
today and the reasons as to why. There
has been a sentiment shift. You know,
this market, it's very resilient. It
might well just shake it off. It's done
a pretty good job of shaking it off uh
the last few months. I would say a
pretty good job.
We will see. All right, let's see who's
in here.
Morning everybody. See if my chat can
catch up. Morning Jim, Jeff, Toby,
Christhorne, Larry, Inferris, Sylum,
Otus, DK, Gerald, Sergio, Patrick,
Christy, Fall Forward, Troy, Gangster,
Garbar,
Ken, Bart, Myron, Jerry.
Trying to catch up. Green,
Toby, Idris, Array, Danny Snipes,
Miguel, Prrisca. Oh, this is jumped
around a bit.
Noah, oneonone, Brandon, Mikey, the Law,
Ajeto, Arrow King, Dim Derby, what a
great name. Uh, Rosco, Clint, Willow
Williams,
Ty Turner, Niko, Greg,
Patrick, Jake, Rock,
Lou, uh, Lou Riley, Mark,
Live Your Purpose, Thunder, Austin,
Patrick, Jason. Good morning everyone.
Good morning. Good morning. Good
morning. Right, let's see what we get.
See, starting to see a reaction here
without sweeping that low. All right, so
same thing here. Let's just see if we
can drift up this morning. I guess the
one thing we didn't look at actually was
the MAC. We can go through very very
quickly. Um, but you would have seen the
same sentiment starting to come off. All
right, Apple good sales. All right, so
that's holding in a range. Going to open
up flat. Here comes the weakness. All
right. Anything chip related. Remember
Apple safe haven from chips. Amazon gap
gapping down. Google gapping down.
Meta gapping down. Anything chip
related. Microsoft getting absolutely
hammered. Nvidia gapping down. This is
why I didn't look at it. And Tesla
gapping up. All right. So, the safe
havens away from chips are are Apple.
Everything else is getting clobbered on
that um Microsoft news.
Right. So have to just wait and see.
First couple minutes might be a bit
shaky here folks because that was a
pretty big wash
in what 5 10 minutes. You lost 240
points. You lost the first 100 points in
two minutes, right? So just be aware of
that. Volatility will be high. Just have
to see what they want to do here with
this. They might consider it an
overreaction. We will see.
We will see. Did any of you get any nice
trades yesterday afternoon?
A couple washes and a couple grind backs
up. That's what this market seems to be
liking like or enjoying doing at the
moment. Snapd downs and grind all the
way back up and then snap downs and
grind all the way back up. Just what
we've seen this morning. Same thing.
Snap down. Looking to see if it can
grind back up now.
[cough and clears throat]
>> [cough]
>> Just going to get a tissue hit.
[snorts]
Just bought my wife stuffing her face
full of pie this morning. [laughter]
6:30 a.m. [snorts]
Peacon pie on the go. [laughter]
Leftovers from Thanksgiving still
getting Still getting eaten. All right,
here we go.
10 seconds here, folks. [snorts]
Watching this area, watching VWAP,
all those good things. Let's see how we
act. [sighs] Shelf is all the way up at
600. Really if they can get up there.
Let's see. Sell pressure so far coming
straight away this morning.
They didn't take out the low. Remember,
I'd love to see us squeeze higher first.
All right. Lots of imbalances above from
those big washes. Love to see us squeeze
higher first, but at the moment failing
to even reclaim 500. Mega weakness in
the market.
bits getting stuck in front of previous
day's high right now.
They might well try and wash down for
these lows, which it looks like they're
trying to do right now.
And we've got errors. Can I get orders
out here above? Can I move this? No.
Secondary Ninja Trader being funny at
the open.
Okay,
I would love to see this squeeze higher
first. I want a straight failure, but we
might just get straight furious here.
Booklet's heavy.
Want to let this shake out a bit longer
before I get involved.
We did base down here before curling.
Sorry, move this up a bit for you.
Would love a retest of 540 before we do
anything else. Really would, but we
might not get it. At the moment, we've
failed 500s, but I want to see if we can
get up into here. Come on, market. Go
on, do it. And then see if we can get a
reaction up there. That's what I'm
waiting for. Waiting patiently to see if
we can get up into here. Maybe even
above, but ideally not above. Ideally a
failure here, but they might drift it
into VWAP to start the day. Let's see.
Apple finding a bid. Remember, Apple had
positive news. It's hanging around its
all-time highs right now. Sales looking
better than expected. More shipments of
the iPhone.
Google's gone red to green. Tessa having
a good day. Everything else getting
hammered. Microsoft over 2.33%
down. Right. Failing that high again.
Back to the New York open. Failing the
New York open again. Still haven't
tested that uh 540 that we're looking
for. Still not tested it.
We will have to see.
Apple might do a bit of the leg work
here if so
failing that New York open again. Not
through it. Just hanging sideways in a
range at the lows. This is dangerous,
dangerous, dangerous here.
Big failed previous day high. Got
absolutely slammed at the open back
under 17. It's coming back towards its
flow zones. Is an ugly ugly open to the
day. If I look across,
not what you want to see across
everything right now.
Spiders back over those 680s. So that
gamma level holding that we talked
about. Here's the move into the 540s. If
they squeeze through this, they will
probably go for VWAP. You would want
them to sort of fail up here. This is
what I'm looking for. Some form of fail
up here. If they squeeze through it,
they'll probably go to VWAP. And that's
going to make it pretty hard to trade
because we're be going to be back inside
of yesterday's value if they do that,
which is not going to be ideal. We are
seeing some sellers come and try try and
join the tape here. So, let's see if
this is the move. These 500s are going
to be key now. Don't trust this market
one bit. I've made that very very clear
for a few days now. And that has not
changed this morning. Even worse, I
would say this morning even more
dangerous
given what they've done the last few
days. if they reclaim value, they can go
right back up to those highs as as if
nothing happened, as if the news was not
important. And leaving that um previous
day New York low is not going to be
pretty if they do that. Let's see here.
Make your mind up, market.
Still holding these 500s. No break below
the 500s.
Still holding 500s. Big buyer just tried
to come in here. He might get himself
caught soon.
Gosh. Market, what are you doing,
back to these 500s, back to this New
York open. This is the key level.
They're still bidding off that for now.
We start flushing this, I think we're
going to go for that uh previous day low
that we talked about.
It's trying. It's trying to stay heavy
here. I'm watching this carefully now.
Still keeps finding a bid at that New
York open. Watching this carefully to
see if we get follow through downside.
Here we come.
Here we come. Much better. Lovely. Okay.
Can we pop up and fail 500 now? Don't
want to get caught in a range seeing
heaviness come to this tape. Can we pop
up and fail 500? Don't want to play for
a reclaim of 500. needed to fail this
500 that we just washed from.
Be careful. Don't want to get caught at
this low of day or New York low of day.
So there's the pop to five
just in front of fire that New York
open. That's your over under. If they
reclaim it, there's no trade here.
They're trying to reclaim it. God, are
we going to open up Boxton? Really,
market? You going to open up Boxton?
Really, market? We're going to open up
Boxton and do this this morning. Here's
your range.
We should come down for this, right? If
they're going to be heavy versus this,
this is what we should do. We should
come down for that white line. They are
struggling here.
Sellers currently off the opening move
this morning are caught under 75.
Sellers currently are caught underneath
75. They're going to need to see follow
through under 75. Otherwise, they are
going to cause a squeeze higher. That's
where they are. Once they get followed
through under 75, we will go for that
previous day New York low.
That just paused on me. Great.
They're caught. There's going to be no
trade here for me.
Two-way tape. We're just not doing
anything.
Oh god. [sighs]
Hands off the mouse.
They're coming their [\h__\h] minds up
again. Oh my god.
Why [\h__\h] market?
There's no strength. There's no strength
from the sellers. They got themselves
caught that opening move this morning
underneath. Yeah. 76 77. They had two
attempts. Got themselves caught there.
We've never traded back into it with uh
with strength. We've held it every time.
So buyers are in control from 73 right
now. And I don't like the auction at the
high. It doesn't look like buyers got
trapped up there. So we got to wait to
move outside of this box right now.
We're boxed in. We're going to have to
wait to move outside of this box we're
currently in. Nothing's changed. Look,
we're still at the New York Open.
This is a terrible open, folks. You want
to see what boxed in looks like? This is
it. This is a terrible open.
Google about to go green to red. bears
have a chance here to at least take out
that low and they are just failing to do
anything.
It's the same story. I feel like we want
to take out the low but we're just
failing to do it and that's what's
notable at the moment and it's probably
because those sellers this morning got
trapped at those 70s that we talked
about. Once they get out the way there's
probably a wash but the moment maybe we
want to go all the way back to VWAP at
the moment is what it's starting to feel
like. Just chop here. Lower highs,
higher lows.
Once something snaps, it will get nasty.
They've got to get under the 70s, these
bears. That's what they're looking for.
If they keep poking down here and being
absorbed, they're going to get
themselves in trouble.
And again,
no follow through. Okay, we're just
still
here in the 70s. This is the level. This
is the level they've got to get through.
This is where the bears are stuck.
They've got to get through this for
downside action.
Like I said, the opening two minutes
this morning, they got stuck under 76
776.
That's what they got stuck. These two
wicks here are full of sell pressure and
there was a buyer absorbing them. They
need this move here. This is what
they're looking for. They've got to be
very careful cuz I know that they got
stuck here. That needs to flip.
There has been a passive buyer here.
They're trying again. This is heavy,
heavy tape and they're being absorbed so
far. So, there's definitely been a
passive buyer here. If they snap through
this, we're going to go for that New
York low. All right. Here's the
expansion in New York. They're trying to
get down to this now. We should get
follow through down to there now. That's
what I'm looking for now. Can we see
follow through down to there? Please,
please, please, please. Market.
Don't want reclaim of those 70s because
we came in very heavy there.
Still no trade for me in this second
attempt. Looking for this second attempt
to go lower. Still no trade for me. If
these buyers get caught in this shove up
into 80, I'll consider it. But just
waiting for this candle. We got a long
time left for this candle to close right
now. It did just expand the lower date
and they did just find a bid. But I'm
waiting to see if this sweeps. Watching
the New York open again.
Need this candle to close. Another 30
seconds left. Don't want to be premature
here.
RTY strong because you're seeing a
rotation out of chips. Every time you
see a rotation out of chips, you're
going to see movement into Apple and RTY
and stuff like that. [snorts] Relative
weakness in the cues. We're half a
percent down. Everything rest of the
market looks okay. So, the breadth
elsewhere probably okay. especially
[snorts]
with the cash injection from the Fed
into the banks to try and save them and
their positions in Bitcoin. There you
go. Reclaim this. That's why I didn't
touch it. Still, we're boxed in. All
right. Still we're boxed in.
Just got this feeling they need to get
up to VWAP and see what happens. Maybe
even close the gap. But I really don't
want to trade like I've talked about.
Don't really want to trade up here. They
may may be that they need to come up
here, but I really don't want to take
that trade. I really need them to reject
this if we're going to play lower.
The Tesla and Apple the only ones red.
Everything else getting hammered here
this morning.
Big still trading downside since the
open. It's not good.
Yes, grinding back up to VW up. So that
might come into play here if they start
rejecting VWAP and cause sell pressure
in the cues here. Might well come into
play.
Spy closed its gap I believe. Yes,
closed it gap pretty much there or
thereabouts
and still we're boxed in.
[sighs and gasps]
Smaller range there. 85 points range.
The draw for me is that low that white
line that is the draw. Like finding a
way to get get involved in this now has
become hard because of how they've built
it out this morning.
Good rejection of the gap there.
Well, the level was good.
The value area high value area low from
yesterday was good. Now we're just stuck
at the open.
Still think this wants to trade lower.
It's just when is spy done pushing. It's
over its VW up. It's pretty much closed
this gap. Maybe
scent or two away. The VIX is still
dripping downside. Just waiting to see
if there's a sentiment shift coming.
Yeah, we do have PMI 945 and ISM at 10.
So
yeah, there might be PMI 10 at 9:45 at
10. So might well be waiting for that
back down for those lows. Big rejection
on spiders there. SPY still above its
New York open. So, I'm just watching
that to see if sentiment comes uh to
stay heavy for the day. We start losing
those New York opens on the spiders.
So far, it's held that 680 at big gamma
level on SPY. So, I am aware of that.
That's been propped up so far. It has
been propped up for a number of days
now.
We opened under it or we traded under it
pre-market. Reclaimed it in the open.
Traded to it at the low of the New York
session and uh found a bid.
Found a bid at what's that 95 or
something on spiders.
[snorts]
Still we're boxed in. Still we are boxed
in.
We should be taking out the lows here
and we're not. That's uh that's the
story of the tape so far. We should be
taking out the lows and we're not.
That's been the story of the tape since
April, isn't it really? When we think
about it, rejection of New York open
again there. We really should be taking
out lows and we're not. So spy back to
VWAP. Let's see if it finds a bid
through VWAP or if they sell it. This is
the third attempt it's had here. So, I'm
slightly concerned that a squeeze is
coming here.
I'd love to see some follow through in
this market today after a day of no
follow through yesterday. Uh here comes
the squeeze because reclaimed VWAP and
we might go all the way back up to
previous day value area low and if they
reclaim that VWAP is possible. So,
markets
just got nothing to do here. No way I'm
trading this long side. You would have
to be a psychopath to trade this
underneath value long side in my
opinion.
Kind of amazing how how this market's
acted for I'd say quite a while now.
These like big moves like these two 300
point moves and then we get served with
this
sellers keep trying in these 80s and
they're not getting their way.
They're not getting their way.
Coming right up to that old pivot from
yesterday into these 500s.
Incredible the lack of follow through.
Market shrugging off the news by the
looks of it. Nothing to see here. The
market saying everything's fine.
[sighs]
Still at this New York open. Nothing's
changed, folks. From the moment we open
New York, we're still just in that same
exact same point. Waiting to see if we
see a sentiment shift here. Follow
through. There's I'm telling you now,
sellers cannot sell under 80. They tried
a few times this morning at the 70s.
They've been absorbed. I'd say the key
trigger now will will be those 70s. They
need to get followed through under 70s,
and they're not seeing that still.
Still not seeing that. There's the 80s
again.
There's someone absorbing the tape down
there.
Back to the 500s.
I'd be very concerned about squeeze out
all the way up here right now. They
tried and tried and tried and tried and
tried and tried and they're trying too
low and they're not getting their way.
They have the chance to take control,
but they are struggling.
I want to see if Spy cracks 680, you're
going to see like more follow through.
All right, so you can have that alert
there. I've still got it from yesterday.
680 is the level on spy. You get
underneath that and uh know we can see
all hell break loose
that 70 again here.
Can they trade through this 70 and trade
down to these sort of 420s or something?
They trade under 70 and get down into
420s. So far this morning the answer has
been no.
It's back to that New York open. If it
lets go this New York open and it trades
under 80s, you will get follow through.
But at the moment, you're not seeing
that.
They're trying here.
450 is the next spot that they need to
break down. Here we go.
Here's the trade down to 450s. Can they
find? No. Still a pacifier down there.
They still can't find strength. Instant
reclaimer 70s and attempt to 80s. This
is messy. It's looking better for a
short, but it just
watching spy in 680. I think it's
coming. You just my c my why I'm careful
is last time we traded into 680 on spy
the reaction was ginormous, wasn't it?
We know it's a huge level. And look at
that. Absorbed again and spy right back
to that New York open again.
Come on, bears.
Today's your day to take control. You
have news to help you. You've got to
have some follow through.
We're not trading a catalyst. We're
trading price action. We're not trading
a catalyst. I'm not trading the news.
I'm trading the chart in front of me.
There's a big difference.
I'm not a fundamental trader. I'm a
technical trader
otherwise I wouldn't be looking at order
flow and calling it out for you.
Buyers step back in again there. So 70s
and 80s reclaimed again from buyers.
Sellers failing miserably to do anything
today. SPY held in front of 680
reclaimed New York open traded straight
back to VWAP. Found a rejection so far
in VWAP. This is getting messier and
messier and messier by the second. Big
selling coming in this time. They're
having another a go another go to trade
lower failing there again at 70 and 80.
So I'm giving you the levels
but the sellers I'm telling you they
keep refresh selling 70 and there is
someone absorbing that until he's out
the way you're going to struggle to move
lower. Someone with endless funds is
passively on the tape soaking everything
up from 70 and below. I'm telling you
can see it in front of me.
Spy back to view up again. I'm still not
having another attempt at this. This is
far too risky with how we're ranging.
You're looking at 30 and 40 point ATRs
like that and it can change to 100 plus
very quickly.
Sellers should take control but are
struggling.
Big rejection on the view up on spy, but
you need a fivem minute close.
And again, your 680 is is your level on
spy until we trade under that. That's
where you're going to see weakness if we
close under 680. Currently trading at
680.57.
But what it can't do is reclaim its VWAP
right now. That's clear as day.
68030s.
Do they drop the floor on this?
They're trying to sell hard here again.
Aggressive selling here in 66. Still
being absorbed. We're not moving lower.
They are trying. Honestly, they're
really trying and they're not moving
lower. Still someone on the tape here as
you can see every attempt now. It feels
like it's getting close. That was the
first shift. There you go. Okay, let's
see if we get follow through now. Bang.
Thank you.
Thank you, market. Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you. Nice. All right, watching for
this white line there. Can you hear me
say it? Now we're close. Now we're
getting follow through. Can literally
see it happen on the tape in front of
me. Right. So you need to see a
rejection of 60 now for follow through.
White line is your target. This is your
target TP1. And then we can get down
into these. Boom. Here you go, folks.
Here we go. Just have to be patient.
Much better. Much much better. You're
going to get this low here. So be
looking for a cover point into 15. And
then you're looking for 320s and then
previous week value area high 290s and
then we see if we get weak.
Well, it's a good good first trigger.
You need to see this reject now. If they
reclaim, you got to be flat on this
position. You just cannot afford this to
reclaim and start squeezing
news in 7 minutes. Uh yeah, there is
news. Top of the hour 10:00
right back to V1. Wow.
Um, well, you're asking for a lot for a
25k drop right now. It's 500 points
away, I think. Be realistic.
Look at this squeeze out.
We flip on the tape there.
That delta flip was massive. That was a
massive delta flip.
I'm leaving this alone for a bit.
again. They protected that low. That's
uh not a good look. I think we'll come
back for it later. There's no way we
protect that.
There's just no way. But
clearly someone quite happy to absorb
the tape down there all morning.
So, we sold hard through that uh seller
at 7080. Got down to 30. Big sellers
came in from 45 to 30. Then the delta
flipped on the next candle. Aggressive
buying stepped in.
50 60 70 80. And now we just have to
wait and see.
[snorts]
Did we just tap? Oh, there we go. That's
why it's the gamma on spy again. So, we
traded under 680. We traded a low for a
number of seconds to 7974 and then we
closed straight back above it. Right? So
that last 5minute candle traded down to
7970, got absorbed, closed right back at
68061 and we're currently trading there
right now. It's all about that gamma
exposure on SPY right now. It's the
dealers. They don't want it under that
level for whatever reason.
You do not want it under that.
I did catch my money in that flush
though. I got aggressive with that. So,
I'm up about 600 per account right now.
So,
I'm all right with it. I can show you
before you all like whatever. Yeah. All
right. So, I can just sit still if I
need to.
[snorts]
Let's
buy back a VWAP here. Let me check the
breadth out. How long we got through
news? 3 minutes. Let me check the bread
out this market. [snorts]
I mean yeah spider's looking very strong
financials are all green software
application is green consumer
electronics is green healthc care
consumer services sort of consumer
defense is green real estate is green
energy is green utilities are green
basic materials are green whole of
market's green outside of of big tech
basically
big uh the big losers today. Crowd,
Microsoft, um LRCX, basically all the
semis. STX, WDC, uh Micron, MU, AMD,
Nvidia, INTC,
um Empower, those are the big losers,
big winners right now as I look across
the board. Um well, copper, all the
metals are trading up. Um MLK, PFV, so
the healthcare sector trading up.
Is that accurate? Tesla trading up.
Tesla's trading up 2% up. Um,
so yeah, the breadth looks pretty good.
It's it's only tech week, so you want to
be concerned about that. It's not like
we're having a very weak market. It's
just the cues have relative weakness
right now. All down to that news. And we
found a bid. So I'm currently just
leaving this alone. News coming out here
in 90 seconds. We're already back to
that New York open. So failed to take
out yesterday's New York low.
Do I ever trade gold? Uh, I have taken a
short on gold earlier this year, but I
was long on GLL. Is it GLL? GLS? One of
the ETFs, can't remember. a short gold
ETF. I was long uh once we peaked out,
but I haven't touched it since.
When did I enter the short? Once I saw
the tape change. It was only a quick
short somewhere around here. It would
have been once the tape changed and I
saw the pacifier get nailed. So
somewhere in here wherever I called that
wherever I said the tape started to
shift. Okay, I'm ready. I'm like looking
at it now. Here comes the weakness.
Probably just in this 2 minutes. That's
all it was.
It didn't get to my target. TP1 was
here. So I had to take some off on the
flush down and never got anywhere near
down here. And we're seeing strength
now. So, I mean, I have to obey the
tape. If the tape doesn't want to move
lower, then we don't move lower.
Uh, trade whatever you're better at
trading, like whatever your stats suit,
back test, however that you like to
trade. I mean, like NQ is very violent.
The ATR is up right now on NQ. So, you
can make a lot of money, lose a lot of
money. Here comes the pop. So, we might
be going back for this previous day
value area low and New York session
VWAP. Again, if we start reclaiming
this, this is the zone I don't want to
trade in today. Some of you like
rotation traders, maybe you like this. I
don't like this as a long if we've left
this, right? If we' taken this, then
maybe I'd be more willing to take this
trade up here. But right now, the fact
that we've left this in with so much
liquidity built, uh, I'm not taking
that. That is a high-risisk trade in my
opinion. So, this is previous day's
value. So here is yesterday's volume.
Yesterday's volume is traded here. These
are your levels within that volume. If
we don't reject this to come lower and
reclaim it, maybe you want to trade this
move to point control. I won't be
trading that. But if that is a range
rotation that you like, then you can
take that, right? So I'm telling you
what's available there for those of you
who like trading those rotations. I'm
watching Spy back into close gap right
now.
buys just got caught up there into and
above 20 on that last shove.
That last shove up 520. Buys got caught
above 520 there. No doubt about it.
Doesn't mean it's the auction stops
there. I'm just telling you what I've
seen.
depends whether they uh lift this offer
and let them through. There's lots of
liquidity all the way up to 50 right now
sift
this offer at 25. It's only an 83 lot.
Imagine they lift it and just let them
squeeze out here. Why would you stop it
short?
Here you go. Lifting that offer there.
Here they go. Yeah, lifting it. This is
what they should do. They should just
let them run through now. No point
stopping it short. You're a short
seller. You wouldn't want to short here
right now.
So, you can see VW and previous day
value area like this is going to be a
massive level right here is a massive
level. If they protect this, maybe a
range rotation back down. But, you know,
I can see them doing this at this point.
It's not a trade I'm going to take, but
I'm making it clear for you in case it's
something you want to do.
Spy now back through its gap. So
officially green on the day for the
spiders. So RTY, YM, and Spy all green
on the day. Yes, I should say all green
on the day.
We talked about the broader market.
Healthcare and finance is very green
today. Big aggressive buying stepping in
here.
You go to the 50s.
I'm going to come right up for GloEx by
the look of it, which should be 70s. Big
aggressive buying. So the bulls stepping
back in. We need to zoom out here and
see like you might very well have a W
here which sets up this rotation back to
previous day point of control if they
get that previous day value. Like I said
I have no interest in trading in this
area today. I was very clear yesterday.
area yesterday for this reason. Right?
It's too risky. They do this. This is
not a trend. Same here. I don't want to
trade here. We've got buyers trapped
above us right now. sellers trapped at
the lows trying to force down. This is
no man's land. Just want to let this
peter out and see what it wants to do. I
am not going to get caught in rotation.
There is no chance you will catch me
getting caught in rotation. Anyone who's
joined me enough times knows I do not
like trading rotation, especially in
markets where both sides are trapped.
All right, it's very different to
trading like an IB rotation. This is a
market currently where we have many,
many buyers trapped up here. Remember
this is a two week balanced range up
here as well of supply. They got caught
washed on. So buyers are trapped over
here. Sellers are trapped from 80 and
below. All right. And now we're in
between these these levels. All right.
So you'd expect some reaction up here.
But the market's been very very
resilient. It has been very very
resilient.
Right. If you're bullish and you like
trading rotation, what you'd want to see
is some hold of this to complete that
move to previous day point of control.
Now, let's get some volume on here.
We've gone [snorts]
right. You'd want them to hold previous
day value to get to previous day point
of control. Gap fill is the yellow line
here and then previous day value area
high. If you are playing a bullish
rotation, that's what you'd want. I'm
somewhat skeptical knowing that above
this everyone's stuck. All right. So, I
think that's still possible, but I will
not just be trying to frontr run this or
get front side of it because if they
want to keep going higher, they will.
Bit like yesterday
took the rotation from yesterday's IB
low. There was a buyer there holding it
with a with a passion. There was indeed
a buyer holding it up with a passion.
You're right. Every drop from 70 and
below he just absorb absorb absorb. So
that's a good read on the tape from you
forward.
Do I look at the tick chart? No, not
really. Not really.
Tick an ad I don't really use, but I've
never found edge with it, but uh many
others do. It's just not I've never
found edge with it personally. VIX
getting absolutely crushed, right?
Coming all the way down to 1650. Closed
its own gap now. Coming back down
towards previous day low on the VIX. So,
if you're bullish, you would want this
to hold this previous day value area low
VW up somewhere around there. It's what
you would want to see.
[cough]
>> [snorts]
>> needs to hold this kind of level. If you
don't see this hold, it's going to drift
all the way back down to its shelf of
volume, which you can see on your chart.
Uh same for spiders. You want to see it,
if you're if you're bullish, you'd want
to see it hold PDC here. Okay? But
remember the reason I don't like this is
we have a huge amount of everyone who
bought
right by the close for the gap up is
stuck right now. So these buyers
equal resistance or supply. This is why
I I don't like the rotations in this
market. But if you are very very
bullish, if you're seeing something
higher time frame, then that's the move
for you. But this is annoying because
it's peaked out. It hasn't got here and
didn't fail here. It's peaked out in the
middle of of the two. So from a
technical point of view, it's not very
nice.
[snorts]
Wasn't a bad auction at the high. I
don't like that we've had three candles
up there, but uh I would say like I
talked about se 70s. All those candles
we had market buying above 70s and we
didn't move higher which means there was
a passive seller up there. He's actually
still on the book up there at 80. Let me
take check the delta
map out 50. No, we need to go up to 70.
Yeah. 65 69.
Yeah. 69
70 was a very highly traded level.
stands out like a sore thumb on the
profile.
[snorts] Spy back coming back to its
VWAP. So, it's back to PDC. If spy does
not hold PDC and VWAP, that means it's
rejecting those participants who were
stuck there from pre-market. Same as on
NQ. All right, it's just unfortunate ENQ
didn't get all the way up to previous
day point control. If you start failing
previous day value here, value area low,
if this is a look inside and a fail, you
want to be careful. If you are very
bullish about this because we still have
not taken this has been building
liquidity. If you see a failure here,
I'd be very, very careful, especially if
we trade back underneath this. This is
where that buyer had been trying to eat
and eat and eat. There's your two leg.
If they fail here and you see that
rotation, you'll see heaviness. But the
broader market has been green.
[snorts]
They are trying to buy this back up
here. They're not getting their way. I
can tell you that now. They're trying to
buy this back up here and they're not
getting their way. They've had one, two,
three attempts in this sort of 30 to 50
range to participate as a buyers. So, I
would say sellers are in control all the
time. We're rejecting
46 to 53
all the time. They keep rejecting that.
Sellers, well, they're not in control,
but they have the ability to take
control of this range for a rotation
lower. Any reclaim of that, then I think
you get a new high of day.
>> [snorts]
>> passive selling on the tape here. You
can see they keep trying to bid it up
and even with the delta we are not
moving higher.
Here you go. There you go. So delta just
telling the story there folks.
[snorts] So a little flush down to VWAP.
I'd say the same levels again now. So
buyers got trapped there from 30 to 40
now. 30 to 44.
All right. So they're going to retest
these areas where all those market
buying participants, aggressive buyers
came in and they didn't get their move.
And that's going to be the level 30 to
sort of 44. Might as well just call it
45. All right. 30 to 45. Buyers need to
reclaim that. Failing to reclaim that,
they will catch themselves and get
themselves caught. Like I said, this can
be a look into yesterday's value. drift
under rejection of what? Previous day
value or a low. If they keep rejecting
this, this is the shelf that they're
going to trade back and forth and back
and forth. Buyers need to see this.
Sellers just want to see this right now.
They've got a clear target below. And
there has been a passive buyer down here
in the 70 and 80s. Even before we put
this volume on, I kept talking about him
to you guys here all day. All right. And
I played his pain point and once he
reclaimed, I'm out. But this is the
rotation between these right now. Buyers
need this and sellers really want that.
Maintain your price alerts at 680s.
ES currently, sorry, SPY currently
trapped between
uh close and VW up right now. So, it's
starting to coil and get a bit tight
down here. Can still still looks good.
Still intact here on the spy, but
definitely you're in a rotation. You've
got buyers stuck above and sellers stuck
beneath.
So, I maintain what I said on Twitter
last night. I maintain until we see spy
let go of 680, I don't think you see
more pain in the market.
That is definitely a dealer's level.
All right, I'm going to get a refill on
coffee while this shakes out.
Tricky market today, folks. You're still
inside of the 15minute range. All right,
so
we're not really finding acceptance
outside of this right now. All right.
So, that's telling you
sellers have the ability, they have the
ability to finish this, complete this
rotation. If you took this, I don't
blame you in taking this. Like, I'm kind
of okay with where I'm at at the moment
on the day, but I don't blame you for
taking that as a sell or look above and
fail, but that needs to be TP1 and this
is TP2. And weakness can be all the way
down here. But we're not really seeing a
weakness come into the market, broader
market, which is why I'm just waiting.
You are starting to see spy come back
down and try and test New York open. I
think if we start flushing New York
open, if we see a rotation out of the
broader market, let me just check what's
going on here.
I lost that page.
[snorts]
Still looking okay. B market is still
all right for now. Just tricky [snorts]
these 500s. [sighs] I think there's a
flush potentially coming in this market.
All depends. We get a rotation border.
still holding on right now. DWP
problem is what we're seeing again just
happened the last two candles sellers
tried to sell those lows at 500 didn't
get their way. So why we're just getting
these whip whip saws. So in here you had
aggressive selling and we didn't move
lower. So you have got that passive
buyer probably the same guy was at seven
70s and 80s probably sat here now trying
to absorb. I'd say all the time this
rejects though if we can reject and come
under here any any liquidity built under
here will be used to sell. I don't think
they save this again. I really don't
like they can save it here where we're
at and they can save it above this but
if we get stuck underneath here and we
start building volume down here this
will be used to trade lower because
bulls would have had the attempt
rejection of value look above and fail
rejection of value we reject this
especially if uh broader market rolls
over with it. It's a bit early right
now, but if you took these, I kind of
don't blame you for taking those as long
you should be covering some into VWAP
and New York open and then just waiting
and seeing. But for me, it's beyond my
risk appetite right now.
45 minutes into the day, we're just
we're basically still where we started.
We've not moved really.
[snorts]
There's someone trying to step in there.
It's these guys that are stuck down here
in 40s. I don't know if you can see this
in bookm
side
coming back into this shelf at the
moment where they absorbed.
That's this is this big participant
here.
you can see.
Okay, we used this buyer's pain, roll
over, sold back down to the lows, but we
had big selling down here without the
ability to move lower, which means there
was a passive buyer sat down here. He
got his breakout above 500s. Okay, and
we're coming back and testing this same
level where he just absorbed and
absorbed and absorbed. Right. So, just
this level here
where he's just been gobbling everything
up. And you can see like he got pained.
He probably passively bought even more
here, came back above. We're still
holding this level. So, until there's a
break underneath this level where this
guy's been absorbing the tape, we're not
going to get a bigger move. He's
basically putting his wall down saying,
"Hey, I don't want to move under this
right now." And this basically coincides
with New York Open View up on SPY as
well.
same level.
I'm going to clear it.
That's that same guy probably for now
[cough]
indicator at the bottom on what on
bookmap. Uh that's just delta cumul
that's that's your CVD cumulative uh
volume delta. I don't really pay too
much attention to it. I actually look at
it more on a five minute chart.
It's funny you say that about bonds. I
was looking at bonds yesterday because
they've been really weak
and no one's had any interest in bonds
and sometimes I just wonder
take the opposite side of the trade to
everyone.
Bookmap's always been a big part of my
trading. [snorts] I've always used it.
You've just not always had it on the
screen. Even from my small cap days,
I've always used bookmap.
I tell you why. Because I can't read the
the level two and the tape without it.
Like if I see the tape, like when you
see the tape flash red and it moves
really quick,
I can't see the size going through that
quick enough. But I can on bookmark
because it leaves it there for me to
hover my mouse over and recheck.
So, I don't care about it like while
we're just sort of doing nothing like we
are now. I care about it when I come to
a level. So, I care about, you know,
bookmap or footprints or anything like
that or level two, however you want to
read it. When we come to here, I care
about it when we're around here. When
we're around here, in between this, I
don't really care so much because I
don't really care about the charts at
all at that point. I try and turn my
brain off when we're not at a level,
wait for it to come to a level of
interest, and then I start caring. Same
about the one minute chart. Like I'm
looking at the five-minute chart most of
the time until we come into a level or
one or even an hourly chart until we
come into a level.
We have just gone wick to wick on the
hourly. We just missed it. All right.
So, if we go to an hourly,
we're trading into this right now,
right? So, we're leaving these
participants stuck. Imagine you were a
buyer here overnight or yesterday at the
close, right? And and just think about
what the tone's been. If we go to a
daily,
think about what the tone has been.
Buy the close, buy the open, sell the
close. Buy the close, buy the open, sell
the close. Buy the previous day close,
buy the open, sell the close. Rinse,
repeat, rinse, repeat. Think what
happened last night. If you bought the
close or bought the open, that you're
underwater right now. But the pain's
going to come when we trade under 400s.
That's where we get the move underneath
that. Before that, like I talked about,
this is still an inside bar. All right,
we can if they just want to pin this.
All right. If market makers want to pin
this and do this until next Wednesday
and maybe we do the cut, all right, and
then they drive it up into this and
maybe they resell it from there on the
Thursday. Or maybe, you know, Pal says,
"Fuck your cut. Was only kidding." And
we drop down. I don't know. But we can
pin in here a while. And we can do
something like this. All right. We can
do something like this. Pin it in here
all the way into Christmas. It can
happen, folks. It can absolutely happen.
We're just trading like basically at the
mean like 5day, 20-day, 50-day. We're
not at the top bowl. We're not at the
bottom bowl for me. This pullback is not
enough. I want to see like a two-day
pullback or something into here and have
this protected for buyers. And then if
buyers protect that, then I know, okay,
game's on. We want to go back to highs.
But buying up here, I don't think any I
think this is the problem, right? I
don't think you're going to see any
institutions really want to buy up here
right now. Right? If they're going to
get a pullback, they want it down to
here to bid up for the rest of the year.
If they re if they really are adamant on
buying, that is my personal opinion,
what I think.
So that's a second look into value and
fail here.
Two looks into previous day values and
This just feels like much much heavier
move right now.
[snorts]
>> [snorts]
>> you like Nvidia for NQ because they're
heavily correlated. I mean they they are
correlated but like you just need to be
aware of things like if you look at the
mag today. All right, Tesla's up 2.77%,
Google's up 0.60%.
Apple's up 0.44% and trading at, you
know, around all-time highs. Nvidia's
down half a percent. You know, the chip
names are down. Nvidia, Microsoft, Meta,
Amazon, with Microsoft being the weakest
one, you're in a mixed bag. So, while
you might say there's correlation there,
uh, if you look at it as a whole on the
MAG, if they're equally weighted, we're
0.17% down on the day and NQ 0.28% down
on the day. It's, you know, we're not
selling off everything. The mag is not
selling off. The breadth is not seeing.
Let me open this up for you if it will
let me.
If I if we look at the whole S&P,
right? We're not seeing the market sell
off. All right. We're seeing a few names
sell off. So, if we're trying to be
short on NQ, what are we really short
again? One, two, three names, four
names, maybe. It's not a lot going on.
All right. So, market's not in a sell
right now. It's in a holding pattern at
the moment. All right. And this is why
that you're seeing strength in the S&Ps.
Look at finances which are not in the
queues. Look at healthcare which is not
in the cues. All right. That's why
sector rotation is happening. Not a bad
thing to see to be honest because we've
lacked sector rotation for a while.
[snorts]
So whilst nothing's happening, we should
probably talk about some changes in the
industry or in the prop firm world. You
might have seen Tradeify launched today
um a new product, well two new products
actually. So now you
can have a go at Prop Firm with Tradeify
Pass it and you don't have to choose the
type of account until you're funded and
once you're funded there are now two
different types of accounts. All right.
So when you're doing the the select,
you will have the choice of once you're
funded of choosing a daily payout system
or a flex payout system. So for a 50k
account right now, it's going to cost
you 95 bucks. Let's do the select.
Uh your profit target is 2 a half th000.
Your u max end of day draw down is
2,000. There's no daily loss limit. You
have a 40% consistency rule in the eval
$95 reset fee. No, no activation fee.
Once you pass, you can now choose to
have daily payouts, right? So, that
would be $1,000 a day. Daily payout on a
50k. No consistency rule in that. Daily
loss limit $1,000, max end of day draw
down $2,000. Or if you'd rather, you can
do the flex account, which will give you
a payout every 5 days, max payout
$3,000, no consistency rule, and no
daily loss limit. So, those are the
choices. So, if you want to move to
daily payouts for $1,000 a day on a 50k,
you can start trading with tradeify.
Now, I actually really like the flex
account. I think $3,000 every five days
is really good without having a
consistency rule. That's the key thing
there. No consistency rule. So, lots of
people starting to pivot towards uh that
kind of product at the moment.
All right. Market still in a holding
pattern. Uh SPY still holding VWAP now
reclaimed PDC gone green on the day. We
still have all of pre-market stuck
above. All right, so this is the thing.
We're just trapped right now. Nothing's
changed from what I said this morning.
Zoom out. All right, here's your supply.
We can see what we're trapped against.
Where's the wick, Mr. Wick? This guy
down here. All right.
And this is where we got thick up here.
The profile will be way bigger up here
from previous day point of control. This
is your resistance or your supply,
however you want to think about it. And
intraday, we have shorts stuck down
under here.
And really, I'd like to see them come
all the way down, wash these guys out,
and bid back off the 200s. That would be
a nicer move, but there's too much
strength in the broader market to see
that today.
Yeah, we talked about this at the open,
didn't we? It wouldn't surprise me. This
is the type of market that we have. Big
directional move,
grind back up, and it wouldn't surprise
me at some point then to see this.
That's kind of what ENQ likes doing at
the moment.
About this
big directional move.
Grind back up. More of a directional
move. Grind back up. Wash. Grind back
up. Wash. Grind back up. Wash. Grind
back up. Wash. You get the picture. It's
just how it's moving. That's the market
we're currently in.
Yeah, it was it was Microsoft news
basically saying that I think they've
just said there's lack of demand for uh
the AI products, less than anticipated.
So obviously that affects all the chip
makers
because we're investing so heavily into
chips and data centers and all this
stuff for the AI. So if there's lack of
demand then suddenly your books don't
look so good because you're investing in
something which isn't as popular as once
thought. So that's what it was. I can
try and find the actual headline for
you.
Come on, softy. Where are you?
AR companies are realizing there's no
real world demand.
Microsoft lowers AI software sales
quotota as customers resist new
products. So there you go. So there's
not that much interest from customers or
not as much as originally anticipated.
Still, we're really not really above
that 15minute all.
Well, Peter, well, to be fair, news does
normally come pre-market, but yeah, I I
I feel your pain there, mate. I mean,
I don't know what to say.
There's a rhyme and reason for
everything. All right. It's probably the
the reason probably is is that someone
was short and needed to get rid of or
wants to get long down here and has been
pissed off with having limit orders sat
here forever and not getting filled. So,
you know, they pay their mate to release
the article. Like, it [\h__\h] wouldn't
surprise me in the slightest.
It like NQ or the market to me, it just
feels like a small cap. Since Trump
comes in, it feels like a small cap. I'm
I'm not even joking. I'm being deadly
serious. The moves we're seeing feel
like small cap moves. They remind me of
dirty Chinese tickers where it's
completely corrupt. That's how it feels
at this point, you know. release loads
of news to make sure everyone dumps it.
Absorb, absorb, absorb, absorb, absorb,
absorb. Tariffs are off.
Send it to the upside. Get to the
upside. Want it to become cheaper again
and to trap sellers, release some
horrible article which lasts all of an
hour, reabsorb it, go back up. It
literally feels like a small cap ticker.
That's how it feels.
back to VWAP. This just feels like a
VWAP day. We're in balance here. We We
cannot
This is how I would note it. We are not
finding acceptance inside yesterday's
range for me. That shows weakness. All
right, that shows weakness. Failing to
find acceptance. We've built lots of
volume out here, which is not the
prettiest all the time. We cannot get
inside of yesterday's range. That's
showing me weakness with the possibility
of coming lower. That's how I would read
this book right now. We are not finding
acceptance into yesterday's range. It is
simple as that. This remember this is my
level where I wanted to be short at.
Right? So, I probably made my money. I'm
all right with where I am at the moment.
But all the time we are rejecting this.
This is possible. But you're not seeing
a sell-off day where all the markets in
agreement yet. That can change.
that can change.
[snorts] We're starting to see some
weakness come in back down to this New
York open again. All right. So, if we
don't protect this, we go red and we
come back down probably towards at least
value area low. You can see this is your
level where Mr. Million bids, right,
wanted to bid up the market. So, we can
put this in here. This is where he wants
to pin. He wants to hold this value
area. If this participant here,
right, sold here on these pushes and
he's no longer here to absor um absorb
it, then you're going to see us just
come under, aren't you? And then these
are the targets and we've got previous
day low, previous week value, area high.
But until we see that, I'm just going to
sort of remain flat. There is a chance,
I guess, to fade here to here and bid
this to this and keep doing this in this
value, but it's not what I want to do.
Don't want to play range rotation.
Oh, I know. Troy know things can change.
Like, have we got news here? I mean,
this feels heavily manipulated. What is
this? Look at this volume stepping in.
It's got to be It's got to be news. Save
the market. It's got to be news. That's
a big shove on big volume.
[laughter]
Like I said, feels like a small cap.
Feels like a small cap. I'm searching
for this. Whatever this is, Trump. Oh,
Trump's posted. Fantastic.
Such a terrific victory for Matt Vaneps
and his wonderful family last night. It
would be fantastic. Representative
Tennessee.
Seeing him comment on Biden and the FBI.
Not seeing anything else. So just just a
truth social post is all I'm seeing.
News alos like that. Do they apparently?
So
just a casual 85 points out thin air.
[laughter]
That's the only news I can see is the
truth social post. I don't know if
anyone can see anything else.
Maybe close the gap now and into this
previous day point of control. So, this
is where everyone's stuck. Like I said,
I'm not touching the rotation. I'm not
interested in touching the rotation.
It's far too dangerous for me.
But this is the next key area. All
right. So, this was key area one. This
is key area two.
I still think they can sell this, but
not if the market is going to have
strength today.
the broader market that is
[snorts]
previous point of control coming up and
close.
This is all buying so far. Straight
upside.
Yes, it's going or spy not too far away
from previous day high. So that 680 that
gamma level they held it again and back
inside previous day's value we go.
A little rejection into that gray box.
You can see this gray box here. This is
your level, the volume from yesterday.
I'd say this whole zone, right? This
whole zone. GlobeEx PDC point control
that zone there. That's what sellers
must defend. Failing to defend that,
they've lost all all uh power that
they've had. They will lose all power
that they've had if they fail to defend
this level.
[snorts]
Initial balance now set is it as well?
Yeah, that's a look above IB and fail so
far, but they can still absorb this.
This is just a very very iffy market.
The thing I find hard with that is you
would have to have a limit in these
levels for it to drive into because they
are not giving you nice price action. Um
or but or we haven't seen it recently.
We haven't seen something like
this to risk off to come down. Recently,
they've just done these sort of straight
moves.
It wasn't too bad. At least that was a
crack off two sell signals, but it was
messy.
It's a bigger problem as well is higher
time frame at the moment remains
bullish, doesn't it? Like the daily is
just in a in general just in a drift
higher.
So reversing those drifts higher become
quite hard.
Patrick, did you if you've bought it uh
there there's a link. Have you gone
through the
If you open up the uh Ninja Trader
course,
it tells you what to do once you once
you apply for it. There's like a Google
drive and it gets sent to you. So just
like open up that course and then follow
it.
Any issues, just shoot me an email
info@flowzonerader.com.
But as soon as soon as you open up that
course, it tells you what to do. And
then I get not a notification and you
get emailed everything you need. And
then you just need to send me your uh
Ninja Trader machine ID.
But it's all in it's all in the in the
Ninja Trader course once you open it.
Microsoft denied the quotas. Did they
really?
This is what I mean about a small cap.
I mean, how so this would be my opinion
now. Who legally put that news out
saying that they'd lowered the quotas?
And then you want to look at what was
their positioning before the news and
after the news drop.
Dirty. It feels like a small cap market,
a manipulated Chinese stock. It's
exactly how this feels. And there you
go. There's proof of it. Fake news. Make
the market do something. Bid it back up.
Release the news afterwards saying, "Oh,
everything's okay. Make sure you make
enough money." For example, I'm not
saying this is what happened, but let's
say Mr. 470 460 all day. Needed to be
long down here to meet his quotota for
his clients because he hasn't been able
to get long. Okay. Release the news from
your hedge fund. Big dumpama. Absorb
everything. Finished absorbing it.
You've got your quot of as many shares
or contracts as you needed. And then get
the news to be released saying, "Oh, but
by the way, we're only joking." Boom.
There's your quot. Gaps filled. Thanks
very much. Fulfilled my client's
obligation.
If you don't think things like that
happen, you're mad. It's exactly what
happens.
Good luck proving it, though.
Good luck proving it. Same way. Good
luck proving the spoofers we see on the
book all the time.
Indicator name. This is the Flowzone
Pro. Comes with the course
available on the website
flowzonerader.com.
Everything you're seeing here,
banksters. Yeah, exactly.
Yeah, exact. But it is it is like an
episode of But that that's how it is,
guys. That's how it is. If you like
just think about the tariffs,
who do you think was buying the lows the
whole time? The same guy that said,
"Now's a great time to buy." Right? If
you don't think that was done on
purpose, you're mad.
Everything is done on purpose. It's
calculated. It's not by chance. It is
not by chance.
Pelosi. Well, Pelosi's gone now.
Retired.
the richest Congress woman and the best
trader ever retired.
Seeing another fail to move higher here.
It's just it's just dangerous. You see,
I'm not really interested in this at the
moment, but we are rejecting previous
day point of control and the gap fill
right now. The structure is still
bullish though. This is the problem. But
this is the contested level that we've
drifted into.
Tell me about that.
Okay.
Oh [\h__\h] Yeah. Yeah. All right, darling.
Have a good one.
Going to get rid of this gray box just
to clean this up a bit cuz you've got
this here. Anyway, so the rotation now
is between these like we talked about.
This is the resistance level. This can
now potentially become a support level
because now you have VWAP previous day
value, current day value. This is the
rotation from 600 to sort of 540 in
here, right? While they build out
volume, bulls will look to reclaim this
to get up to previous days value area
high. Bears will look to fade underneath
this to complete the rotation back down
to here. We've had numerous drives up
this morning, but not seeing enough
weakness. This is the tough thing for
bears right now and talked about they're
having to sell these drives in and
they're not getting followroughs. They
never get to add size on and if bulls
hold this they get squeezed out and you
get the same thing. Same as here. Same
as here. Right. First test fade reclaim
squeezed out. Never gets washed. Reclaim
squeezed out. And if they hold this
reclaim squeezed out,
Kevin, I'm sure from previous day point
of control, Gap Bill would
be a valid target.
Clean up the New York vote. Gap Phil is
is above you though.
What do you mean? You're short here.
How's that your target? That's your gap
fill. Gap fills above you.
We're still
bullish in structure here. That's what
I'm saying. You're not seeing weakness
underneath initial balance. You're not
seeing weakness,
you know, you're not seeing this here.
Everything's holding. Even this hold
here didn't even come all the way down
value.
Remember, they've just said all that
news this morning that caused the flush
is not true. They can walk this thing
right back up now if they want. I don't
know what their intentions are. I have
no idea what their intentions are.
Just reading the news, I just think it's
wild. How can you roll back such a big
statement?
[cough]
We can drift all the way back up. You
know, if the reason we dropped was a
news piece and they're saying, "Hey,
that's not true." We can drift all the
way back up. And this looks like the
last few days, doesn't it? We talked
about this in Discord. You know, these
kind of drifts,
shallow pullbacks should probably get
one tug at some point.
We go back to last few days.
Drifts, [sighs]
tug, drift.
Last week was the same.
Drift
tug.
Tug. This was the other other way
around. Drift into range. Seen the same
thing every single day.
tug, drift, drift, drift, drift, drift,
drift, drift, drift. It's just we are
where we are, folks. This is the market
we have.
Oh, short at the gap fill. Sorry, I
thought you said no, it says I'm short
at the previous day point of control and
gap fill with valid target. Would be a
valid target.
That's what I didn't understand. But
anyway,
there's your gap filled
there or thereabouts. That yellow line.
Oh, I see. I'm short from previous day
point of control and gap fill,
would a valid target be clean up the New
York light? I understand. Sorry. I
understand. Uh
I mean you're front running it
structurally. We're still moving higher.
Like remember you're now short outside
of initial balance. This can be a
rotation back up. You're inside
yesterday's range. Where would a valid
target be? I'd say the edge of value.
I'd be covering something into 550. If
you're short up here, your counter trend
versus what we're seeing currently. If
you're short up here, it'd be TP1 point
of control TP2 value area low TP3. And
if you get really lucky, you get down
here.
But I would imagine any flush gets
gobbled back up now,
unless you see a major shift in
sentiment.
VIX giving up the whole giving back the
whole 9:00 a.m. push that it's had.
See, I'd be covering if I was you, I'd
be covering into each value area. You
want to see this get underneath IB high.
If you do not get under this, this is
going to be a problem for you. So, if
you're short here, you need to see this
breakdown. If you do not see that, then
we're basing above IB and it can
reaccumulate here to go higher.
Right. So, you need a break under this.
For me, it's not a short right now.
We're trend up in a high time frame
liquidity building stage. So, I'd be
very, very cautious.
[snorts]
If you get under IB and they sustain and
walk down the offer, then maybe you get
that flush to view up 550. That would
definitely be a cover point if you get
lucky. But right now, it's not showing
me that it wants to do that move. We're
at a point of interest, but I wouldn't
say we've had an entry.
Definitely have supply overhead. There's
no doubt about it. What it really comes
down to, do those buyers at the end of
day yesterday and in London and Asia
want to get rid of their position?
That's what this comes down to. Do the
buyers overnight and at the end of day
yesterday want to close out their
position or not? If the answer is yes,
you will get a move lower. If the answer
is no, you're not going to see that
because it means that supply of ahead
are quite happy to sit in it.
I would say so far
it's first time I've seen selling into
actual market selling. It's the first
time in this candle.
Not convinced high is in but we'll see.
Do you indicate in a trade now in
Discord? Just wondering if I'm in a
trade or looking at something. Yes, I
always I always post it in the
afternoons. You mean? Always. I don't do
it while we're live and stream.
I think I had two attempts. Was it the
day before?
I got stopped out on both,
unfortunately. Uh into end of day. I
think it was the day before. So, you can
see here. So, [sighs]
uh when was this on the first? So,
Monday.
So, I call it first long here needs to
punch 420 otherwise a scalp and then say
that I'm flat and then I have another
attempt at it. It didn't go either time.
Didn't go either time. So, break even
both of those. But yeah, if I'm trading
in the afternoon, I will always say what
I'm looking at.
Even if I'm not actively trading, I will
say the levels that I'd be looking at
and what we're looking for. But you can
see everyone here is where we talk about
the breakdown of the trades.
The last one I was away most of last
week with co so it hasn't it's been a
little while
and even other people
I
Yes. I show I show it in in the video,
Eric. Yeah, I I won't promote firms
until I get payouts from them. So,
Funded Next, I passed and got a payout.
I'm currently working on a [sighs]
few more of their plans. We're actually
going to do a giveaway. I've got to
organize it. We're going to do three
Funded Next giveaways a month. We've
done a deal with them. So, we'll be
doing three giveaways a month. I have to
work out how to do it because we can't
do it live on stream. They do it
differently. Um, so it's probably going
to have to be a Twitter giveaway or or
maybe we do a YouTube post and people
have to comment, but it's just how they
operate. So, a Apex we can give away
live on stream funding. Next, we're
going to have to do giveaways with some
form of competition. Yeah, in the video
you'll see. I think I take I can't
remember two and a half thousand. Same
with uh funding ticks. I took the
maximum ones available. So, I'm
currently working I'll be honest with
you, I'm working on some funded next and
funed tick evals. I want to get fully
funded for next year.
It's my job at the moment. We we just
took some big payouts in Apex. So,
uh I really want to start scaling up
with uh firms where I don't have
consistency rules. That's that's my uh
target for next year at the moment is to
do that and to take some bigger or some
more swing positions. I feel like I've
been in cash in this market for most of
the year. At the moment, that's where I
normally traditionally make a lot of
money. This year has been a good year,
but I feel like I've way underachieved.
So, my only positions I'm still long
Apple from 202. So, and I'm with size.
So, that's a good one. Um AMD, I'm still
long, but I'm down to very small size in
that. I was long from 58, 158s. So,
still up nice on that, but I sold most
of my position into that alltime high
push. Amazon, I'm still long, but I'm
barely up on that. Um up 7%. That's a
long-term position for me. Meta, I took
a starter position. I'm up just under 7%
on that and that's it. So, I'm really
want wanting a bleed out in this market.
I'm going to be honest with you, but I
don't think it's going to give it to me.
This feels to me like this market is
very very very resilient and uh all the
time people are calling for top and a
bleed out. I just think it's going to
keep going higher. The point of max pain
is higher right now, I think, rather
than lower. I think you've got probably
more shorts trying to force this lower
and uh so a good chance we go higher
whether it whether we have divergence
with the spiders whether spy makes a new
alltime high in cues don't I don't know
and we'll see what it all depends how we
close out this year and how we open next
year January can be nasty in the market
but we'll see um I have my own concerns
macro worries for this market people
were talking about QE posted last night
the Fed injecting capital into banks is
not quantitive easing. That is because
there is a liquidity and credit issue.
All right? So, they are protecting the
banks which are clearly overleveraged. I
think especially in crypto, I don't
think I don't see that as a positive
thing. People like, "Oh, yeah, we're in
quantitive easing." We shouldn't need to
do it. All right? We shouldn't need to
do it. Which means there's a problem
under the hood. Uh can't remember which
one of you was short uh from PDC and
Gapatville, but I would take a little
piece off in this sort of area we're at
now. Especially if we reclaim this. If
we sell this little node here, you're
going to be okay. But I would reduce
your size a little bit. And if you
complete this rotation, you can hold on.
All right. So, can't remember who it was
was taking the short around here
previous day point of control. All
right. There's 30 points in the bag.
VWAT will get you like another 20 30
points and if you get really lucky under
here that's where a bigger rotation can
happen but I would pay yourself along
the way here.
Looking good for you now. Looks really
nice. Just make sure you're covering
some or if you haven't already maybe
into VWAP.
Which props don't have consistency on
funded? Uh funded next.
Um
funding ticks.
Uh sorry, my brain's like so fried.
Funded next funding dicks. Uh take uh
take profit once you get over the buffer
doesn't. Um well, it doesn't have it
anyway. Um
what else?
Uh the new Lucid one I don't think does
either.
My Funded Futures. There you go. Yeah. I
don't trade with them, but My Fun
Futures as well.
Uh I don't know, but hopefully soon. I
mean, I've been I'm two weeks behind
schedule, unfortunately, because I've
had COVID. So, I'm still feels like long
co because I'm still absolutely
exhausted um energy wise. So, I've been
struggling to make the content. So, what
I've got left to do is uh bookmat and
level two and footprints and then the
setups. So, it's not that much left to
do. It's just
because I've not been well. I wanted it
pretty much done by now. That's a good
rejection of that gray box there. We
just put this in this gray box. So, that
shelf is starting to reject. So, your
short now is looking pretty good. All
right. So, now I'd say we're getting
confirmation of trap buyers up here.
Here's your TP1. You must must must take
some profit off here. Even if you took
some there, that was a reload
opportunity. Profit off here and then
hold in case they let this thing go. But
don't expect it to be let go. But you
can hold some runners in case they do.
But here is a big TP. Same as here. So
VWAP and shelf here. This is the edge of
value right now. And here is a TP. And
here is a TP. All right. But this was a
nice rejection of this shelf. Really
nice. Right. It came back up, rejected
it. You would not want to see them
reclaim that shelf. All right. For those
of you who took the short here or took
this back here, you do not want to see a
recla reclaim of sort of 75s to 80s.
That must stay heavy.
When I'm passing different props, do I
execute at the same time or take your
time by passing one by one? Uh, normally
do most at the same time to be honest.
Most at the same time. I quite like the
new um and this isn't a sales pitch, use
whichever copy you like, but the thing I
like about the new affordable indicators
trade copier is you can put in the
targets for each account. So if you're
trading
accounts which are different, say for
example, if I'm trading one which my
target is 2500 or uh and I can pass it
in one shot, I can put that in. If other
ones my target is I've got 40%
consistency rule, I can put in like $600
or $800 target for example. So I think
they can be quite useful.
Still rejecting that box. It's still
looking good. I don't know why it's gone
blue. I don't remember doing that.
Still looking good.
What I'd be looking for here is this to
stay heavy. This area here is your TP1.
Hopefully, you've already got some off.
Point of control TP2. New York open. And
I think if we come, in all honesty, if
we come under this, they're going to be
in big trouble. I would be somewhat
surprised if they let that happen now.
But you never know. You've got a new
hourly bar coming in about 90 seconds or
something, maybe less, 70 seconds. Just
be aware of that.
They have a better rhythmic sync too.
Yeah, they've uh fixed lots of issues
and they now have it so you can trade if
you want to trade on uh trading view you
can execute on there as well. Quite like
it. It's quite easy to manage.
Just be aware new hourly bar coming.
Think about this last hourly bar. We are
uh definitely confirming supply above,
which is good. All right, so think about
this. We talked about this this morning.
This is where buyers are stuck above.
All right, this is why I said if we're
going to rotate, this would be the
maximum level I'd want to see us rotate
to. If we sell this now, you'd want to
sell back into these lows. And then
you're holding runner for a breakdown
because we have equal lows down here.
But they might well just pin this. They
can pin this here today.
passing apex yesterday. Now focused on
passing TPT counts, but I feel like the
jump between
the two, it would be too much,
especially when I haven't passed the
buffer yet. What do you mean the jump
between the two, Danny?
[cough]
Yeah, it's so much better. I agree.
That's what I've started using. I need
to do a video on it again. Just COVID
has really just zapped it out of me.
Zapped the energy out of me. Be careful
on a reclaim here. You need this level
here that we've just traded into to stay
heavy. If this level stays heavy, you
can possibly get rotation lower.
Remember, your overall trend is bullish.
But here is your count. I would say
your legs currently. This is internal.
Did we make a new high there? Yes. All
right. So, we're trading inside this.
You want this to see a rotation in here.
If you're if you're bearish any reclaim
up here, I would leave it alone. I would
cut cut the trade. You start to reclaim
this. I would leave it alone because
they can try and force a squeeze.
So you want this to stay heavy versus
basically IB
like having trade of eight open on both
tabs and go between the two tabs with
Apex
and one with TPT. Oh, okay. So you just
have your two different accounts. I get
what you mean.
How do I manage the integer draw with
multiple contracts? Are you using
micros? Uh yeah.
Well, it depends on the account size. On
50ks, I use micros.
How do I manage the intraday draw? Just
don't oversize. Simple as that. Build
your buffer.
So you've reclaimed now be I'd be risk
off at this point. I wouldn't like what
I'm seeing. You can always re-enter.
Well, some of you are short versus five
days. So you want to hold to that point
because you're taking a TP then that
makes sense, I guess. So those of you
who are short here risking this, you got
the TP1 off, I guess that makes sense.
But I'd be somewhat concerned now they
hold this that they're not going to come
higher.
They have the chance to reject here and
they didn't. You can see multiple
attempts, right? And shorts didn't get
their way. And now we're reclaiming
I am seriously thinking about selling.
everything in London given the new
budget. I'm just going to get hammered
now on tax.
What a bunch of knobs.
So bulls will want to defend this box
here now. All right, bulls will want
this to hold. That will leave these
shorts stuck. So if bulls hold this,
they will look to complete higher.
So they're still in control. It's why
it's saying structurally we're still
bullish.
This is what they're trying to do now.
And if they get back through this
previous day value area high, previous
day high, globe x, it's not all out the
question. Remember, they've just unwound
this whole thing. The reason that's
caused this from a macro point of view,
they've just said doesn't exist. So they
are trying to do this. I don't know
whether they succeed or not, but that's
what they're attempting to do. This why
I say on that short, it was very much
you had to take some profit off the
table because you were front running it.
There's so many there's so many issues
in the UK now. I was looking at the um
big sale came in there at 600. They just
defended that aggressively. No follow
through though.
So I'm just watching the tape here. That
was really aggressive.
They're still trying to get follow
through
this purple line where we're trading
into now. This is where bulls want to
defend is right here. Right. That's your
over under. That's your sentiment. Um,
[snorts]
yeah. I was reading the new legislation
which is going to come in 2027 on ISIS.
I mean, it's a [\h__\h] joke. It's just
like I can't believe. The problem is
people don't read nowadays. they just go
by a headline that they see, right? So,
ISA is down to what 12 a.5 th000. You
can still put 20,000 into a stocks and
shares Iser, but they're going to get
rid of a load of products, right? So,
any leverage products probably going to
go, which is fine, but they're probably
going to get rid of like a load of
things like T- bonds, bonds, um,
anything where you can passively earn
safe because they want you to just
invest. And they're saying it's for the
good of the UK. No one's investing in
the Footsie for [\h__\h] sake. Everyone's
money is going in the Q's or in the Max.
So, it's got nothing to do with the UK.
This is about having people invest
poorly in Black Rockck taking their
money. It's so crooked what's going on.
It's so so crooked. And then they're
they're now saying that if you leave
your money um like because historically
you could leave your money saying
trading 212 or whatever and not be
invested and you're still going to earn
4%. Well, they're going to tax you on
that. So, in your ISER, if you put your
money in a stocks and shares Iser in the
UK from 2027 and that money is not
invested, they are going to tax you on
that. I mean, the scumminess of it is
insane. What a [\h__\h] country. I'm sorry
all of you living there, but you are
being fleeced by an absolute thief who's
trying to make herself out to be, you
know, robbing from the rich and giving
to the poor. Absolute bollocks. absolute
[\h__\h] bollocks. It's all going to her
mates. It's so bad.
Thank god I'm not there. And I've talked
to a few of my mates and we're all in
the same position. Just sell everything.
Just you're going to be left with an
economy where no one is contributing
because anyone who's innovative, who's
got cash and would historically open
companies and employ people and invest
in businesses and people, they're going
to leave and do it elsewhere. What
you're going to be left is 95% of the
population putting their hands out being
like, "Help me. Give me money. Give me."
There's no money to give. Everyone's
left because you've punished them all
too much because the mega rich don't
care. It's the people who are creating
businesses. They're the ones getting
hammered.
Yeah. I mean, I've got lots of friends
in Dubai. um Emirati friends and lot
lots of my mates move from you know a
Saudi over there and Egypt over there
but it's great I think Dubai is great if
you're from
North Africa in a suppressed state but
actually if you move from Western world
to Dubai it's fairly restrictive
it's pretty and the taxes are good but
actually beyond that in terms of being
able to do things freely
It's not the best. Remember, I used to
DJ there and go there four or five times
a year. I I've seen it all. I've seen
how much it's changed. But
short stint, maybe good for tax, but
beyond that,
pretty tough.
You're not having a good blowout party.
Put it that way.
I used to DJ at the F1 there. Moshi is
and Atlantis. I used to play and uh was
it the Queen Elizabeth in the engine
room? Used to DJ in there loads but
played there loads. Gravity
used to DJ there a lot.
Mambo
still drifting low. This aggressive
selling now. They've lost that level.
So rotation now. So this overunder still
exists. So they successfully defended
this high.
Balls had the chance to absorb here.
They didn't. All right. So new rotation
rot. So first rotation here, here, here,
here. Second rotation between this and
this. Reclaim top rotation back to here.
This rotation between here and here. Now
if they lose this back down to PC in New
York what
we doing for time 50 minutes seeing more
aggressive selling coming on a tape
here. This is like it's starting to be a
bit more aggressive. They are actually
someone looks a little bit more upset.
They're starting to aggressively come in
here on a tape. This is probably the
first time today I've seen it like this.
Someone's not very happy.
Well, yeah. I mean, this is it. Like,
here you go. Here's your TP.
So, those of you who got back in, here's
your TP right in here. Flush moment will
be down to clean out these lows. All
right. So, TP1, TP2
runners for unfinished business down
here. I doubt they come down there for
it, but just be aware of that.
Um
yeah, price is trading. I agree. And um
it's just become a joke.
It's become a joke that place.
It's you got to ask yourself if all you
do is put the taxes up all the time and
people aren't happy, how about you
change it? How about you do something
different? Because it's clearly not
working. And this constant excuse
of, oh, we're we we need you to help a
bit more. Why? For what? And then I read
today, more money going to Ukraine. You
can't even fix your own [\h__\h] country
and you're giving all your money. You've
just asked them to contribute a ton more
tax and you're just giving it away.
It's absolutely ridiculous what is going
on in that place.
So yeah, as you can say, I I'm really
happy about it.
Yeah. I mean, I think my my mom was
quite upset. I said to her last week,
"I'm never coming back. I'm never ever
ever ever coming back." They've just
absolutely made that clear. I would
rather close my two businesses down,
sell my London house, and uh spend my
money in an economy where it's valued
more than do something there and be
punished for it.
Still flushing. So, point control coming
up here. You're it's just flipped point
control. So your cover points here now
and you can hold now for New York uh
open. This is starting to look very very
heavy because these buyers up here now
got trapped and all the time we're in a
thick node here. So we can rotate in
here for a little bit. Once they lose
this, it's night night. So this is your
big node here now.
And we chopped here earlier, remember?
Because they're trying to protect this
big buyer who is here.
So, you should be locking in some good
profits here, any of those of you who
are short for that.
But the difference in Italy is your cost
of living is very, very, very low. And
that's the big difference in Italy. Your
cost of living in the UK is very high.
Just notice my M Ninja Trader completely
gone offline.
Close this down.
We open it.
So PC VWAP holding
coming back into like I said this node
here is pretty thick. I would imagine
this is where they'd want to protect it.
Your runners only. Now if they wash it
for you then fantastic but uh no
guarantee of that at all.
And bulls will need to reclaim up here.
Bears will want to defend right this
level here. Bears will want to defend
especially up here. So any lower high
that's produced here will cause a
rotation back down to test PC under here
in New York. We're literally just
trading in rotation here today. Leg to
leg to leg. You've just defended the
previous day's value area low. So you
need to be aware of that. Once we get
back underneath this, this would be a
look above and fail just like this was.
and we can develop some form of weakness
if we do that. But we're not seeing that
yet.
Yeah. I mean, that's the big difference
is the cost of living.
My my dad lives in Rome, has a place as
well in um Anio.
It's the cost of living. That's a big
killer in LA as well is cost of living
and the tax.
Yeah, true. You have low wages, but if
you can earn an international wage and
live there, you'll be okay.
they're trying to sell this. There was
excess on I'll tell you what, there was
excess on that low sell side at 530.
There was sellers stuck underneath 28
right now,
but we can come back for it. We haven't
tested it really yet. So, I'd say if
they come back to 28 and hold it, if
you've been short, if they come back to
28 or 30 and they hold price and go back
upside, you want to cut the trade.
740 for a chandi. At least they can pour
a pint properly, though.
I had a beer in Palm Springs last week.
It was 15 bucks. It was flat.
It had no head on it.
It's fuming.
It's literally a joke. I have Why can
Why do they not know how to pour a pint
in America? What is up with that?
Why is every pint flat and never has
head on it? I don't understand.
It's so It's the easiest thing in the
world to do is pour a a good pint, tilt
the glass, pull it on, make sure there's
some head, leave it to settle. It's
really not hard.
Miss a good pint, man. And a good roast.
I tell you what, I went out for um I
told my aunt this yesterday. So, we went
out for uh Thanksgiving lunch in Los
Angeles. There was like eight of us, six
of us, six of us. [snorts]
So, I paid for me and my wife. We had It
was fixed menu, starter, main dessert.
Starter was a big plate of salad. It was
distinctively average. It was like
rabbit food. There was a few leaves and
some sweet potato, right? The roast was
roast turkey. It was good. I'm not going
to deny that. It was decent size. Roast
turkey, potatoes, like parsnips, some
veg, maybe some Brussels, and a mac and
cheese. And then dessert was a small
like small pie like this with a little
dollop of ice cream on it. I had two
drinks. Had a martini and a glass of
wine. I think my wife had one drink.
What did it cost? What do you reckon
that cost? tip was included. Meal for
two, three courses, fixed menu wasn't
the best. Have a guess what that cost.
This is going to shock you guys in the
UK.
You're not even close, SG.
You're not even close. 420 bucks.
The [\h__\h] is that? 420
bucks.
Outrageous.
[snorts]
Yeah, it's nuts, isn't it? Me and my
wife were saying, remember living in
London? We used to go to Nou and do like
a bottle of champagne and like have a
decent meal for like 200 quid.
It is a joke. But that's Los Angeles
now. I don't think you can step out
outside your room and get a meal for
under 100 bucks anymore. It just seems
like
just seems stupid now.
And I'm on a moan today. Oh no. I'm on a
right moan. And I feel like when you do
shop at the supermarket, all the food so
bad.
You buy like fruit and lettuce and it's
gone off the next day. You're like,
"What did I just pay all that money
for?" Moldy cucumbers. There's no
quality control here either.
Oh, I would have loved that.
420 B.
Wild.
Oh, me too, Rosco.
That's somewhere I could live in Asia.
Definitely. No doubt about it.
Timing is not the best.
I've got a couple friends out there. Um,
they love it.
One's actually living between uh
Bali and Dubai and this between the two.
Cold in Buffalo though. No.
Okay. Ball's trying to reclaim this blue
level. This IB high can see like we just
talked about the rotation. All right.
Rotation from here to here. From here to
here. From here to here. From here back
reclaim back to the top. Straight fail
back down to the downside. Now they're
going to try and reclaim. This is what's
being built out
[snorts]
relative strength in the spiders still.
Let's have a little look across the
market. See what's going on.
Have a little look. See?
So ES coming back into this sort of
supply zone where we've been failing
from. You can see it's reclaimed
everything though. Chomping through. You
can see this pre-market pivot. This is
your level on the ES. All right. Gets
through that. It's probably going to
start squeezing. All right. This is sort
of last chance saloon for bears to
defend. We've had relative strength in
there.
YM straight ripper. RTY straight ripper.
Let's have a look at the mag.
Apple. Nice squeeze up to start the day.
That's what held this market up when we
should have washed. It was all in Apple
coming back down. If we start giving way
here,
you want to watch out. All right. If
Apple does start giving away and getting
trapped under here, it's got a dunk
coming in it for about $3. So, you might
see a bit of weakness and it looks like
it's trying to. So, you want to be
careful with that.
Amazon as well trading underneath close,
not reclaiming
New York open. So, bit of weakness
there. Trying to base out, but weakness
there, Goo. That's a nice recovery,
right? It's a good strong recovery.
Here's your pivot. You can see we're
boxed in here in Google, but that's a
good recovery off the low. They get
above this box, has got a chance to go
leg up. Meta
weakness, right? So, Google, the only
half decent strong one today. Meta
weakness. Microsoft.
We can see where that news came out.
tried to find a bid. Question is, do
they put in a higher low here now and
try and reclaim the move? If they fail
to do that, I would say I would watch
Microsoft into 81 sort of 25. They fail
that rotation as possible because this
can get stuck. Mag not looking too good
right now. I'd say outside of Goo.
Nvidia doesn't look too good underneath
New York open
selling into GlobeEx. This is not a
pretty look there. This I'm starting to
see weakness here as I look through
these names. Tesla starting to roll over
as well. I would say this market's
looking dangerous for a give back. If we
look at the equally weighted,
yeah, starting to look dangerous equally
weighted on the cues. So, if mag starts
to roll, you're going to see heaviness
come to the market.
While we're doing that, it started to
happen by the looks of it. So, it's
still doing the dancing range, but
doesn't look too pretty, I would say,
out there on the mag right now.
Yeah. Well, Vegas, you get a tax break.
That's probably why.
That's nice. Exploit the vibe. It's
funny like we I have like actively been
talking about that. The hard thing is my
wife works here so a move away from
California is going to be very hard.
Yeah, I'm the same. I need ocean as
well.
You're seeing that roll back to point of
control and VWAP, but you're seeing
these uh mag names we just talked about
start to rotate a little bit.
I didn't have a choice, Richard. I
didn't have a choice. We moved my wife's
work.
It wasn't up to me.
Right, I'm going to be right back.
Rotation continuing.
>> [sighs]
>> I'm in Ply Vista. Rosco.
Yeah, I get it, Adam.
I get it. It's got to be tough there
at the moment. I've got so many friends
just fuming. Absolutely fuming with it
all.
Like one of my really good mates there,
he's a a firefighter and his wife's a
constable. So, public service. All
right. Public service.
Liest people.
new baby, they've got another kid who's
four, having to remortgage their house
at the moment to make payments, are
absolutely broke and they're going to
get taxed more. And you're like, that's
the person getting hurt. You know,
someone in the public service sector
getting absolutely destroyed, struggling
to put food on the table for their two
kids. I mean, it's just devastating.
This whole thing about we're helping.
You're not helping people.
Like they're not helping people.
They can't make their mind up this
market. You can see chopping around. you
are starting to make lower lows and
lower highs, but we're still holding. I
would say that this part down here is
still remains like a really big key key
pivot in this market. All right, this
can just be a liquidity build. I don't
know if they want to complete a rotation
up here or if they let go. I genuinely
don't know what they want to do. All I
know is that currently in the cues,
buyers are trapped up here and sellers
are trapped at these lower days and the
rotation is just happening between these
two levels until we make a decision,
right, of okay, we're actually going to
start selling this and come back down to
a reasonable level to bid it back up or
hey, this was all fabricated move so
that we could buy everything really
cheap and this is going to act as a
rotation height. I don't know which they
want to do. I just don't no way of
knowing that right now. You can see that
in price, right? Buyers exhausted down
here, sellers exhausted down here and
the chop inside current day range inside
previous day range creating a new
balance range. And if we zoom out on a
weekly,
we are probably still within the
previous two weeks balance range. Let's
have a look.
Uh, actually need to get to higher time
frames.
Yes.
Right. So, we're still
within this big section here of supply.
All right. But the longer we're here,
the more likely this move is because
we're not seeing, for example, a drive
back in and a big reaction. So, the
longer we're there, the more chance
there is. the longer we're here of
chewing through this
and they if they find acceptance over
the 900s, then I have no doubt all high
is coming. But
we're just at a decision-making point at
the moment. And you can see it right
here. I mean, look how gross this is.
Think about it. Dump yesterday, drive it
back up. Dump this morning, drive it
back up. No lows taken, no highs taken.
You're at the midpoint. This is very
tricky to trade. Like I said this
morning, I made it really clear. I don't
want to trade in this zone here. I don't
I want to see reactions to trade lower
or reactions to trade higher. I don't
want to get caught up in this. This is
pretty much like the same thing I posted
in Discord yesterday, folks.
Um, if we go over what I talked about
yesterday, the no trade zone yesterday
for the same reasons because we don't
want to get caught in liquidity being
built,
right? Same thing yesterday.
Same kind of zone sort of 500s to 600s.
Same zone, right? Same zone. 500s
600s. Same zone. Dangerous. Dangerous.
Dangerous zone. Looks like they're
trying to force this now,
but it's not something I want to touch.
Yeah, exactly. Rosco. Yeah, super close.
[sighs] Super close to the beach and
airport.
Well, that that's the bit, Adam, that
makes me laugh. This whole line of we're
lifting kids out of poverty.
Bollocks.
You think that money is going to be
spent on the kids?
Get out of it.
Get out of it. What a load of crap.
Can't wait to see these kids lifted out
of poverty. And also, you're stifling
people's,
I don't know, want or need to have
success.
You know, if I want to sell all my
assets because I don't want to be there
anymore and I'm going to close down if
I'm going to close down my record label,
that's going to affect five to 10 people
who I'm no longer going to give money
to. All right? So, times that by
millions of people, you know, you've got
a vacuum. You've got money leaving the
UK and going elsewhere. And you've got
less people making money because people
like me are taking jobs away.
Who are you taxing then?
It's just stupid. It's just stupid.
Stupid. Stupid government. Stupid.
But what do we expect? You know, they're
all a bunch of idiots. Doesn't matter
what party they are, where they're from,
they're all a bunch of pricks.
All right, squeeze squeeze up now. So,
failed to break lower. They had a re
attempt to break lower, failed to break
lower. That's the continuation. And
they're going to look to come all the
way up here to test previous day value
area high, previous day high, and
GlobeEx. So, they're going to try and
walk back this whole move, right? This
was probably heavily manipulated so that
they can buy it cheap to get all the way
back up.
It's just
like we said, we're trading a small cap.
We're trading the biggest small cap in
the world. That's what we're trading.
[snorts]
[sighs]
What level do we need to break to call
this a bare higher time frame? Oh god.
Uh, a lot. I mean, it's not bearish
higher time frame. I mean,
bulls have the impetus right now.
Uh, I would need to see a breakdown
inside of previous week's value and
really like let go of 950s. If we start
let go of 950s, then I think bears have
got a case. But, you know what? All I
want to see is a pull back to 950 to buy
it at the moment. And we're just not
seeing that. Bears
failing to do
their job. Um,
and this just seems like it was a big
manipulative trap. Release some PR,
which is [\h__\h]
Protect the low knowing that everyone
will look for that rotation.
And then release an article saying,
"Hey, this up here was wrong."
Okay. And up we go.
If there was a governing body,
wouldn't you investigate this?
Problem is the people doing this, people
in charge of the market.
[laughter]
Dirty dirty games.
So, back above the close price. VIX is
getting absolutely pummeled right now,
folks. And ES is not too far or SPY not
too far from previous day high. Where's
ES? Is it there? It's not too far
either. It's at GlobeEx.
So, you've got like a triple top up here
on ES. So, every push into 64, 63, and
62 so far has been sold into over the
last what's that four days, five days.
But, you know, we've been up here many,
many, many times. At some point, it's
probably going to bust through it. Can't
keep doing this forever.
[snorts]
What a market.
Who's in control right now?
>> [sighs]
>> 20 minutes left. Get out of it.
Sorry, I'm just catching up on the news
here.
I don't know why everyone gives a [\h__\h]
so much about this fed appointment.
Like,
we know who it's going to be and we know
he's going to be a puppet. So, why does
it matter?
So stupid.
We won't need a 50-year mortgage if they
lower rates. And I don't think the
mortgage has got anything to do with
rates. It's to do with the housing
prices and the lack of capital. I don't
think that's going to make a difference.
Save one or two% on the mortgage, it's
not going to make a difference.
Do you guys think they actually get rid
of inflation of inflation in um
uh what do you call it? My brain's gone
dead.
um tax on your earnings. He said Trump's
saying he's going to get rid of it. Do
you think that actually happens because
they're making so much money? What they
said?
You don't think so, Miguel?
That be it' be great if they did.
I don't think there's a hope in hell of
it happening, but
they'd find it somewhere else. No doubt.
Oh, still in control here. They just
held previous day point of control there
and the close the 600s. That's your
overunder for a resqueeze higher. they
can afford a drift back into this gray
box and shelf. So you can see current
value on the day. They're now trying to
hold current value on the day. So bears
had the chance for this rotation here.
We got absorbed at the time. This was
value low on the day. I'm pretty sure
there's your higher low and they've gone
for a squeeze. There's your continuation
pattern. Now if they hold this, the
completion will be previous day value
high. Previous day high globeex. That's
what they're trying to do for a
completion.
Your buying location is obviously gone.
Like I've said, I've maintained since
premarket. I'm not trading in here. Not
interested in trading in that do
whatever it wants.
Let's
go to sleep.
Slow drift.
I really want to see where that news
came from on Microsoft. I I can see the
news. I'm looking for the source, the
original piece of the news.
>> [snorts]
[clears throat]
>> Sorry folks, I know it's been a slow
day, but I promised myself I wouldn't
trade in here. So, I'm I'm going to
stick to that promise.
I don't want to be in pain.
I want to get chopped up in that zone.
It's too thick. previous two two week
balance range current week balance range
previous day range
Microsoft didn't recover no but the rest
of the names did and no might it might
yet still recover
in fact I'm fairly sure it will if
everything else recovers might not
recover today but
>> [cough]
>> Isn't it wild how we've just gr grinded
all the way back? We talked about that
right at the beginning. Very possible
that's what they're going to want to do.
Just grind the whole thing back.
And they're doing a pretty good job of
it.
Oh, really, Miguel? Mine seems fine.
I've got it on I I always have it up
here on another screen actually
streaming from YouTube and it's been
okay. I haven't seen a problem.
They're trying to resqueeze this buying
trying to come in here. Depends if
they're able to hold. They're being sold
into at the moment. So, they just c got
caught again trying to resqueeze it
above 13. Passive seller up there. Just
met them and said, "Hey, no, you're not
coming up."
This is why I don't want to trade in
this zone.
You can see the edge of value here is
gray box. So what buyers want to hold
this here to force a squeeze out.
Failing to do that, we go back into
rotation. That's your level that they
can rotate to between these two
underneath that between these two. Same
as we've done here. Right? It's just
level to level. It's back test level to
level. Buyers still in control for me.
Right. main pivots sort of like this
right now. Right. So, all the time this
is being held by is still technically in
control. And I'd say they'd want to hold
definitely this and possibly this.
And you're running out of time.
Yes. Coming into that zone where and spy
where it's sold off every time it's
approached it. At some point that's
going to give. I don't know if it's
today.
Let me check the daily.
They close it.
I'd say break 673 opens you up for 720
and then 830.
This is your old box. Just do on a five
minute All
right, that's your supply.
Never broke the low. This is gross.
Never broke the low.
Held this old volume edge. Clearly
didn't want to let this go. So, we know
this is big demand pocket down here.
The only thing left for them to do is
try and get through this.
and start this squeeze and then attack
some stops from here. All right. So,
sort of 716
and 8:30. That's what they want to do.
Whether they can do it today session or
not will have to remain to be seen. We
can see it's a big big thick area.
Yes, Apex uh finished.
Um they haven't told me if there's
anything else. I haven't heard anything.
I did say yesterday I've had no
um information from them regarding that.
So, uh as far as I'm concerned, it will
just be 50% sale for a little while at
the moment. And as soon as I hear
something else, I'll tell you.
You just got long into 595.
I mean, you're a little late in the day
and we're coming into lunch. Where's
your stop?
I mean, you're asking for it to increase
value.
You're looking for that. Don't be
surprised if it wants to come down here.
I'm just Don't be surprised if this
whole area just rotates, right? Because
it's told you
that's what it likes doing in this area,
right? And if I went back four weeks,
there's more here.
Got a long way back cuz it's three weeks
ago now.
All right. in here. Same level. Look how
it rotates in this area. Rotates,
rotates, rotates, rotates, rotates. All
right. So, just be aware of that.
Really big area. It's why I'm trying not
to trade in it. It's what I've said all
day. I'm not going to trade in that
zone. It's uh I don't like trading
rotation. I like markets which have trap
traders in or in breakout. Here we go.
So, rotation starting again. And if it
loses gray box, it's going to come down
to this blue box like I just said. All
right, so you're late in the day trying
to long here and you're liable
to come down into this node here.
All right, so they might reject this and
come down into this. Now, if they fail
that, they come right back down into
here because this is where you've
rotated all day and every look above
here so far has failed. No different
now.
And S&P just failed that same level.
It's failed four times now over the last
I know five, six days, [snorts]
right? And there's the rotation again.
This is why I don't want to trade in
this area, folks. This is exactly why I
don't want to trade in this area. So,
here's your blue box. If they fail this,
they keep coming down to the gray box
underneath. If they find a bid here,
they're coming back and back test that
gray box above.
It's just understanding the conditions.
This is a rotational market. These are
the conditions we are being dealt at the
moment.
I find these very frustrating. So, I try
and get my bag and uh leave the rest
alone cuz if you're trying to sit unless
you are the guy with the knowledge who's
like look this is all [\h__\h] and then
we're not going to take this out. If we'
taken that out and then reclaimed, I
would have been happy about taking a
long because we'd have no reason to come
back down here. The fact that we left
that made very hard to think about
taking longs.
But if we think about the structure,
rebase,
tried to rebase, failed down into here.
Tried it again, failed down into here.
All right, this is still moving upside.
This whole thing, if they want to
collapse this whole thing and come down
for here, they can because they haven't
taken out this low. That makes it very
hard for me to be convinced about taking
a uh big bullish move higher right now.
They've got targets above.
Think about the spy. It keeps failing
these same levels.
The same level just talked about it.
This is your box.
Think about those in Discord. Think
about what we went over this morning.
Here's your box on Spy.
Where's my Discord? Where is this
morning?
There's your box. All right, we talked
about it this morning. We're still boxed
in. Nothing's changed. We're boxed in.
We've traded to the top side of that
box. We failed that box.
VIX still boxed in as well. It's
dripping lower, but it's still boxed in.
We're not breaking out, right? So, we're
just seeing exactly what we expected
today.
It's all about how much frustration can
you deal with
because right here
we're building liquidity higher time
frame.
big head and shoulders on a daily.
That's what everyone's calling for. Um,
but you know, until we break down,
I think it's very hard to call for that.
It's what everyone's trying to call for.
But I would argue, right, the big loud
mouths on Twitter who were calling for
that here saying, "Oh, we're going to go
back up and we're going to form the
right shoulder." Right? You're already
above that right shoulder line. I'd say
there's two problems with this. One, we
swept this low. Damage was done. Lower
Ballinger band. Two, we're above the
shoulder line.
doesn't look too good because if they
keep holding this all these guys who are
like we're going to go back to lows,
we're going to go back to lows. We're
short. We're short. We're short. We're
short. We're short. If we go here for a
week and then we break out above this,
guess what happens.
All right. So, this is why I'm
apprehensive right now about having too
much bias because I know how many people
are short calling for the collapse of
this whole thing. Oh, it's the end of
the market. It's the AI bubble. All it's
done or like I had the same argument
with my dad yesterday, right? He's like,
it's this is going to nothing. All I
know is we swept that liquidity. That
was a big kill candle on volume and the
next day we came back with a big buy
candle and since then we've drifted
higher. There have been bears have had
the opportunity. They could have come in
in the holiday week. They could have
come in on Monday and Tuesday. They've
had plenty of opportunity to come in and
slap this back down. All I know is we
swept liquidity and we've traded higher.
We're through that right shoulder line.
If they build out liquidity here for
long enough, those bears are going to
get themselves caught in big, big, big
trouble. Would I like it to come down
here? I absolutely would love it to come
down here because then I think we can
make a better decision, higher time
frame about what we want to do. But all
I can do is what's in front of me. We're
not doing that. And beyond that, if we
look at the spiders,
don't look like a head and shoulder to
me on the spiders, right?
Same story. If it holds this, this is a
bullish rotation back to highs. And
markets can stay rational. And this is
building out a huge range. Now, if you
think about what we've actually done
since September, this is just a giant
range. Okay, tops do take a long time to
form. If this is going to be a top, all
right, you don't need to pick it up here
because once we break this liquidity, it
will offer that trade back down to the
200.
We don't need to be trying to force away
being like this is going back down to
here. There is nothing in this right now
to suggest it's doing that. I'm just
being honest. I'm a bear at heart, but
there is absolutely nothing in this
market suggesting that's what it's going
to do. And we have to be observant of
that. Now,
can the Japanese bonds cause a liquidity
problem? Yes. Have we probably already
priced in a rate cut? Yes. Is it
possible we have a freak event and find
weakness? Yes. But we don't trade
possibilities. We trade what's in front
of us.
So, you go, there's your second
rotation. So there's the flush to the
blue box that we talked about. There's
the failure of the gray box. There's the
flush through the gray blue box down to
the next gray box. And your rotation is
between here now. And if they start to
let go of this, you have this is your
target down here. And if they let go of
this, I think you have unfinished
business down here. But it all depends
if and what they want to do because
we're in a rotational market. We are
still trading inside of yesterday's
value. Until we let go of that and see a
sustained auction lower into these
levels, I'd be cautious.
be cautious.
So, if it drops to bottom of gray box,
would you consider a long uh on the spy?
Yeah, I mean, you'd have to technically
all the time it's holding it, but uh
you know that like you're looking at
it's basically the 680s, right? The
gamma level. If we start getting closes
underneath that gamma level and we start
rejecting that gamma level, then I think
you know the market might find some
problems and then you're going to see a
rotation to 78, 75 and maybe even 70 and
then we get a deeper pullback in the
market. But yeah, I mean
how many times we going to test 680? I
don't know.
W on that failure of the gray box to
previous day value area low. Oh, nice.
Lovely. So, you took you went from you
took that. Really nice. Great trade
range rotation trade point control value
area low cover point here.
Expect it to try and test here.
Otherwise, if they build out here and
you find weakness, New York open and
this blue box down here. And if they get
through that low day,
[cough]
couple minutes left for lunch now.
So, nothing's really changed, right?
Zoom out. Nothing's really changed. Just
a bit of a dunk like we talked about.
Grind up, grind up, grind up, dunk.
Probably grind up. That test of 75ish is
going to be key. Now, do they sell that
or not? That's what I would have in my
mind. Do they sell
that blue box above you where the red
line is the point of control on the
session? Do they sell this or not? If
they recover this, then guess what?
We're going to go back for rotation
again. This is just washing backwards
and forwards. These are uh if you like
trading trend or continuation, these are
not your markets. All right? If you like
not your markets. You just need to
understand that and respect it. Just
don't try and force a trade in a market
which is not there to be traded if
that's what you're looking for. If you
are looking for continuation, this ain't
it.
[snorts]
coming in to fill some of these
imbalances. Now,
Spy just found a bid on PDC and VWAP, by
the way. So, it's got an imbalance all
the way up to sort of 83 now on spy.
Does it make sense how we go level to
level, level to level? Are you able to
identify that? That's what really
matters
because that's the market we're in. And
until that changes, that's that's what
you've got to get used to.
So they're trying to uh defend this blue
box here. Now that I say they're trying
to defend it, that will be their
ambitions. Bears will be to defend this
blue box. All right. Somewhere around
here. they fail to defend this, then
we're going to go right back up to the
600s. If we go through that, you could
see a new high day. It's very, very
possible.
Uh I all I do is I look at the options
data the day before the before the open
and I just look at like the most heavily
traded level. Where are where's the call
wall? Where's the put? All I know is the
most traded thing in the market is the
spy, right? So, what I care about is
that spy level, that 680 level. That
that's just basically my guide at the
moment, right? The spy is basically my
guide for whatever might happen next in
the market.
All you want to do is look for the
biggest chunkiest levels. All right? And
look at how we've reacted there for
quite a few times. Look at 680 on the
spy. They do not want to let it close
under that level.
We talked about that same level
yesterday, blue box.
They do not want it under this level. It
is clear as day. Look, every single time
once we got over it, that was it. So
from the 26th of November, they have not
wanted the spy underneath this level.
They've saved it every time.
Right? So that is your telling you
funds don't want it under here. If we
trade under and reject it, sure we can
see downside like I said to 70. It's
probably a 10point move in that. But
that's not what we're seeing. So all
we've got to do is respect what we're
actually seeing.
So back towards the gray box now.
Previous day point of control.
drifting all the way back up, isn't it?
And if they don't meet this with some
heavy volume, then we probably reclaim
it all. So sellers need to come in
around this level that we're at now.
It's current point of control on the
day, I think. Yes, it is. Which is means
it's the most traded level of the day
where we are now into lunch.
Yeah, exactly. Same same for me, Rosco.
I'm going to try and drag myself to the
gym. Really struggled postco. have lost
so much weight. Gross gross amount of
weight lost lost. Losted.
Um all right, folks. That's it. I will
set some price alerts, but until we move
outside of value from yesterday, I'm not
really interested in touching this. I've
made that abundantly clear um pre-market
and during the session. This is not
something I want to touch. Not when
we're doing these kind of things. You
can see it here. It's just you're
pinned, folks. Right. This is your pin.
You're pinned. Till that changes, leave
alone. Why bother? Why even bother?
That's what you got to ask yourself. Why
bother?
All right, team. And uh those in
Discord, I'll pop in later. I'm going to
have a break. Get coffee. Walk Luna. The
weather light. Not too bad. Drag myself
to the gym. We'll chat later. Um good
luck those who continue to sit here.
Just ask yourself if you don't see your
trade. All right. If you haven't seen
your setup, if you're just sat here
staring at the screens, why bother?
There's a whole world out there. Do
something else. All right? Don't sit
here giving your money back to what
frankly is a [\h__\h] market, right? Don't
do it. Don't do it. Peace and love,
everyone. Speak to you tomorrow.