Good morning everyone.
How are we all doing? How are we all
doing? Hopefully you had a good
afternoon because yesterday morning was
rather boring, wasn't it? And uh you had
to be ready for that fail breakout
yesterday for the turn inside.
And uh that is the scary thing in this
market. As you can see on this daily
chart again, look at this low volume.
All right, very very low volume. Again,
yesterday, very, very low. Yes, we're
walking up, but it just has me
questioning. For sure, there is a higher
low. I would call it a soft high low on
a daily yesterday. But really, there's
no gut check of lower. It's a slow drift
higher. You don't want to be caught
buying a high off a low volume move
because if they want to dump it, it
won't take a lot to rotate it. And that
is the scariest thing right now is
trying to get long in this market
without seeing a daily higher low at a
decent area is a little bit scary. But
we are where we are. We can only trade
what's in front of us. Let's get into
it. We are opening up inside. Yesterday
had a fail breakout and a fail
breakdown. All right. Look below and
fail. That's what happened first during
the overnight session. And look above
and fail and trade back inside the
range. And today we are opening up
within Monday's range. All right. So
we're going to be aware of what breakout
versus fail breakout. It's really that
simple. And you really your key levels
are sort of 550. 550 here has the
ability to trigger a squeeze up towards
700 and if they get really trigger happy
900. All right. It also has the ability
to do a little look above and a big
dumpama back to where that low was put
in yesterday. And if it wanted to keep
washing to 25,000, it can. So, I'm very,
very aware of both sides of the trade. I
don't really want to action new
positions in here. That seems like a
very, very risky move. So, I really want
to wait to see if we do this or one of
these. All right, that's going to be the
easiest two trades that we get today.
And it is very much a C money, take
money kind of environment as we get into
that. Um, and we can look at that in a
bit more detail on the hourly chart.
Okay. So, let's just move this down so
you can see it properly. There we go.
All right. So, still trading inside
yesterday's range, but key is we are
trading outside of the previous week
range. All right. We held previous
week's value area high yesterday and
we've created more liquidity in this
same sort of pocket here. So I'd say
sort of the the 300s
uh yeah the 300s will remain key. This
little node here if we're going to
continue to hold it. Now you can see as
we get into an old two week balance
range right one two that's where we're
trading into. And you can see the supply
here. And this is the problem for the
market right now. To be truly bullish
we're going to have to get above all of
this supply. Everyone's calling for oh
we've broken out of a trend line. Yeah.
Whoopydoo. Um, we have, but it's not
like we've broken out and this is thin
structure. All right. If we had
something like this on a profile, you
know, then we would have plenty of room
to run upside. The problem is we're
trading into a very, very thick
contested area right now. All right.
This is a thick area and we still remain
all these buyers trapped above with
relative weakness in the QQQ. I want to
be very very cautious because getting
long for the 550 break, what are you
getting long into? All right, just
remember that. All right, supply,
supply, supply, supply. Can it keep
going higher? Absolutely it can. But
it's unlikely to keep going higher off
very low volume. All right, so they
either turn that buy algo on and they're
like, "Right, we need to get back up to
alltime highs for Santa Claus rally so
we get our bonus." And if they don't,
then be very aware of that failed
breakout or even just more sideways. All
right, we are into December. We can do
this. All right, December usually
[snorts]
is a slower month. It normally closes
up, but this is not a normal year.
That's one thing I would keep saying.
Everyone looking for that up close.
Let's see.
Sorry. Reminiscence of CO still here.
So, yeah, these are the areas I'm
looking at. Do we break out over 515,
sustain a bid? um or are we just going
to come and test this old point of
control 625 and find rejection around
there? I don't know. I don't know folks,
but these are contested areas. We will
trade accordingly. Overnight, you can
see not a whole lot happened really. If
we look at yesterday's
value area low from yesterday,
right? All we did all day was just slow
grind up, right? And eventually it had a
fail breakout and then guess what
happened? Well, we give back 50 plus% of
that move and then we went sideways. I
did try a long here yesterday to see if
they wanted to reclaim. They didn't have
the juice to do it. So, we went sideways
and uh Asia couldn't take out
yesterday's high, failed, came back down
to this pivot low. London washed Asia,
found a bid and has come back up and
taken out yesterday's high. All right,
so this is where we're at now.
We are bullish in this rotation but as
you can see big red box up here right
into that big chunky supply. We have
that overnight high from uh Sunday
still. So 550 is still a level where
it's left stop. So I am aware of that.
Let's move into this lower time frame.
You can see here the London traders
grabbing that pivot and dragging us
higher. Uh notably as well that pivot
was right on sort of the top of that
value. Let's just go back to it so you
can see it on top of this value previous
week value. This area here is the
contested area. I say all the time we're
holding that bulls have the ability to
rotate. But if we take liquidity and
fail under that, you want to watch out
because you can see notice how thin we
get down here, right? So if we start
losing these levels, it shouldn't take
too much to get us back to there. So
that's why I want to be cautious about
getting long at the highs. All right,
let's go through some of the other uh
key levels on the other indexes. Move
this to a 5m minute ES. All right, ES
has had relative strength in case you're
not aware of that. All right, we're
right up near the highs right now on ES.
It's an impressive move again into a
supply zone.
But if you know we can get one of these
looks and they are going to sustain the
bid and alltime highs really isn't far
away and neither is uh the 7,000 which
you've got to imagine is where it's
trying to go right now. All right, two
leg pullback.
Can it hold right? Can it hold or build
liquidity here to get up to 7,000?
That's what we're looking for in ES. The
one thing I do want to go over is the
spiders.
Spiders has a couple big gamma levels
right now. Uh 80s is one of them. 680s.
Now we're opening up above that. But
this level right in here, all right,
that is a big gamma level. If you lose
that, there's gap fill potential. All
right, so just be aware of that today.
If they fail to break out, I'd say
probably the 85s and they lose 80s and
back test it, there's a deeper wash. So
it probably worth setting a uh alert
there.
>> [snorts]
>> All right. So, that's where weakness
will come in if we start staying heavy
under 680 until that point. You can see
we're gapping up. So, it looks pretty
good. Uh Q's the same thing. Dixie,
it's starting to get messy on the 10
year and 30-year and Dixie, but here you
go. It's trying to form this base.
All right, it's trying to form this base
to go higher.
GC lagging now behind silver. Silver,
the one broke out of alltime highs. That
thing will probably have to stop at some
point soon. But you can see we're just
going into like a two, three month
consolidation before it will have a
reattempt higher at the moment. And
whether it can break on out or not will
be key. VIX. All right, VIX still
absolutely dumping.
All right, back down into the sort of
mid teens. Remember, the volatility dies
down as you can see once we get down
here. So, VIX can't find a bid. We
expect lower volatility days and
probably more slow, grindy days like we
had yesterday. Uh, the one thing I do
want to keep one eye on is this guy
right here. All right, the 10-year and
the 30-year. I've been calling for this
for a while. I think they're going to
need to be very careful. If this starts
breaking out, we are going to see
weakness come in the market. There's no
doubt about it. All right, there's the
30-year doing the same. So, you want to
be careful. All right, we've just
washed. We're starting to reclaim. If
this starts going, it's going to force
some pressure on the market. So, one
thing I'd be very, very aware of. All
right, let's get into the mag.
There we go.
Right, Apple gapping down and it closed
yesterday at those alltime highs.
There might have been a wick higher
based on uh I think there was an
earnings there we go the earnings up to
85. So there is a wick higher but in
terms of a close and a daily it closed
at alltime highs and pulling back
because Apple dragged the market up
yesterday. You can see just this squeeze
all day long once it got outside of the
initial balance. All right. So probably
going to offer a pullback today and then
see if they bid off sort of 280 or not
for a continuation trade on Apple. So
pretty strong there but pulling back
this morning. Amazon starting to like
get going here which I'm pretty happy
about. I'm still holding my core
position from months ago now. But this
level here is going to be key. All
right. You can see this old wick here.
38s all the way up into sort of 50s.
That's supply. That's your blowoff top.
That's where we failed from. This is a
back test.
You'd expect some sell pressure to come
in here soon on Amazon. Just be aware of
that if you're trading Amazon, but still
gapping up. Looking good, but you want
to be careful as you get into those
levels. It's been a nice drive off these
lows. You can see from last week really
really good drive. That's uh no joke
there. About 10 10% drive now. GooG
still giving back after that froth. All
right. But still holding. This looks
very controlled still on Google. All
right. bouncy ball getting slower and
slower. If it starts to turn around, you
might see an explosive move. If it can't
turn around, then you know, watch out.
Below
back into 306's,
but h opening up flat there on Google.
Nice gap up on Meta. That's good. I'm
still long meta from uh 580s.
Only a small position. Didn't size into
this yet. So I want I still thought it
was going to give back more weakness but
apparently not. So gap fill potential
here. See how we act at high of day. You
have to be watching for a fail breakout
on a turn back inside. Same kind of
story. Target right now is back towards
these 90s. Right. That's the target. It
can still put in a lower high but was
due this bounce here. I want to see how
we act if we can get up to 690 ideally.
Might not even have the strength to get
there but let's see. But gapping up on
Meta.
Microsoft opening up flat and this is
not setting up for a good day so far.
Just a bit of no man's land.
Break out here. Consolidation breakout
starting to come back down to this. And
can they find a bid for that
continuation? And this is the liquidity
that they're going to need to use. So
all the time they're holding 80s,
they're going to look to try and bid up
through 95.
Yeah, you can see we're not in
multi-time frame alignment and that's
the same story on the Q's right now.
Great bid yesterday on Nvidia. All
right, so held this low. There's your
higher low and now trying to break out.
All right, if we zoom out a little bit,
you can see where the supply is. 84
to sort of 82s. That's your first level
to get through. Base over that, you've
got a shot of getting back to 200s. But
that's the level to get through. All
right, that is absolutely the level to
get through.
For me, I'd be very cautious about
thinking long on Nvidia at the moment.
Um, I think you're in just in a range
here. It might coil and go
and it definitely has put in a higher
low, but this is still a range. This can
come back down and test the other side
of the range. And we can do this for a
long time. Like I talked about December
has a nasty habit of doing those kind of
moves, which is why had a really good
year. I want to be cautious going into
the end of this month. How we doing?
Couple minutes left.
and Tesla pretty much opening up flat as
well. Yeah, no real big gaps across the
uh mags.
Nothing there that's making me
want to jump in with anything right now.
Not seeing huge strength in the chip
names.
And we're opening up right by this
supply with that overnight high there.
Feels like Groundhog Day at the moment.
That's exactly how it feels. Let's have
a look on the book. Yeah, no big numbers
on this book either. Might be another
slow day, folks. Just to make you aware.
Market opening up here in 40 seconds.
Not going to have time to get through
all the good mornings, but good morning
everyone. Thank you for joining.
Remember, today is the last day to get
the sale with Apex. 80% sale on Apex
code FCT. All the other sales are still
running. Uh best sales right now, I'd
say. TPT 30% off and if you pass and get
two payout they will give you your money
back so you can basically get that for
free. Funded next fantastic sale
happened there over Black Friday that's
now gone but you can still if you're a
new user get some decent chunk off using
code FCT
and Lucid worth checking out the new uh
Lucid Flex accounts as well. I think
they still have a 40% sale on using code
FCT.
All right and here comes the open folks.
So, we're opening up right into
that old sort of supply.
I'm going to have to move this red box
on Ninja, aren't I? Yep.
Sorry, but just make sure I get all
these colored correctly. So failing off
that first push.
Double top up there first. I would be
interested to see if we can take that
out before washing down.
Everything opening up green here in the
mag. Biggest winner at the moment is
Nvidia 1.25% up.
That's a big winner at the moment.
But yeah, I'm not uh
not too eager to do much this morning
given where we're opening. I want to see
if we do a failed breakout or a breakout
really. And uh I'm not really too keen
to buy this market back until we get
down into sort of 25,000 24900s. Really
24900 is a better level that I'd be
interested in taking a buy position.
So yeah, that's a lot lower right now,
isn't it? right 5 600 points lower. So,
let's just see. Let's just see
see if the uh market can inject some
volume today or not because yesterday
was a very lackluster.
Felt like a holiday hangover
and right now we're just opening up
inside Monday
and uh not too far off from Friday as
well. So, let's just see what they want
to do with this market.
Did anyone trade yesterday afternoon?
Did any of you catch something good in
the afternoon session?
What are you guys looking for today?
Same things as me or have you got other
plans? Is it buy and close your eyes?
Are any of you in that kind of
territory?
[snorts]
All right, here's the 500 test. [snorts]
Let's see how we act
at those uh 550s. And if we get going
through that, then imagine there's 100
points in it for that old point of
control check to 650.
So if they get over 550 in base, I'd
imagine there's potentially a move to
650. If they get over 550 and they fail,
imagine there's a rotational play back
down.
Nice address. Uh, one thing I also
wanted to say, do any of you know how I
change your names back? Is that is that
setting I need to look at? Because it's
uh I can't tell who half of you are now,
which is a shame
after we've been streaming for 15
months.
So, SPY failing to take out yesterday's
high as well here. Yesterday's New York
session high
didn't quite fill the gap yesterday on
SPY. One thing to be aware of, we did
fill it on the cues.
So, buyers stepping in here. Can they
come and take out the the uh 550s?
Tesla's gone red. Apple's gone red.
Nvidia's found a bid. All right. So,
it's Nvidia driving this market.
Surprise, surprise.
It's a one stock market again.
Everything else not really moving. If
anything, it's given back. But Nvidia
with a bit of a squeeze on this morning.
It's a YouTube thing, is it? It's quite
annoying that they've done that
cuz now I don't know who half of you
are.
I'm just waiting here to see if we take
out 550s and then how we act.
SPY trading downside still while the Q's
are squeezing. So relative strength in
the NQ today. That will all just be down
to video.
All down to video.
[cough]
Yeah, big old squeeze this morning from
Nvidia. Starting to break out through
that balanced range. And you'd imagine
it probably going to test 88. If it
really gets going today, it can really
have a shove up.
Yeah, it's taking out a week a week's
worth of uh pinned in action and video
is just broken out through it trading
back up to Thursday 20th kind of levels
getting close to those 550s now. So, you
want to watch these. You want to watch
in case Nvidia does a failed breakout
here. And if we do the same or if we're
going to sustain a bid all the way up to
that old point of control pre like from
what's that 3 weeks ago, an old uh
weekly point of control 620s,
right? All right. So, how we act here,
this red line is important.
And if we get through that, maybe 620s
if they continue to squeeze squeeze.
Alex, do I use a trade copier? Yes, I do
use a trade copier.
I'm currently using uh affordable
indicators. Was using Recanto, but they
changed everything to try and be a
subscription like Greedy Buggers. So,
they got binned off.
Okay, through the 550s.
Vid is still sustaining a bid for now.
And this thing is in a squeeze.
All of the mag now green again.
So, I'd say how we operate at 550 now
becomes key. All right. Can we get up to
620s?
No position for me yet. Like I said, I
didn't want to particularly get long for
the first test into this supply, even
though it was likely to potentially do
this. I'm just trying to stick to my
rules here this morning. This is a
decent squeeze out
120 point range so far in this opening
drive. No, I just I just told you it's
affordable indicators. I don't use a
web-based trade copier. I think if you
do that, you're asking for trouble. But
each to their own, but means you have no
control if something goes wrong on their
server,
which is fairly common.
Nvidia now through the 85s. All right,
it's a big squeeze out this morning from
Nvidia approaching 3% up on the session
video already.
Next level is is actually do have some
liquidity sat at 86
or just in front of it.
VIX getting crushed. Everything moving
upside here. There's the 600 test.
Remember 620 is an old point of control
which I would be watching.
This thing is just in a hurry to move
higher right now.
We are still going.
Like I said, this is supply. We are
thick here. It's a two weeks balance
range. I'm interested how we act. 620,
maybe even 680.
Look how we're very, very extended from
the flow zones here. Very, very
extended. Doesn't mean it can't keep
going higher, but this is a squeeze.
It's nothing more than a squeeze.
This would have to pull back and hold
for me to be interested in buying it,
not go straight up.
It's uh you ask me, it's a bit of a
stupid market right now in terms of
structure. Just thin up for five days.
We did produce a higher low there on the
daily yesterday, but of no volume, it's
kind of hard to uh give it too much
credit, but uh let's just see. Market
will do whatever it wants.
First hesitation here on Nvidia that
we've seen this morning. Not at the 86s
yet, but still above the 85s.
still think this can get up into this
old point of control. So 620 to 680 is a
level of interest if we get through
that. Well, you can't rule out the 800s.
You really can't. But I don't think we
do it in a straight move up, but or we
shouldn't. I should say we shouldn't do
it in a straight move up. It might well
do it in a straight move up. You've seen
this market do it before.
Look at this. Just straight squeeze.
This will end at some point. There's no
structure being built out here
whatsoever.
Struggling to find buyers above 600
right now. I don't think that will last
too long. I think they will find buyers
above 600.
Doesn't look like an end of auction yet.
I'm watching a video at that 185.
It holds a bit there or not.
Big transactions coming in here. Vidia
under that 85. Here's your first
pullback. How they operate now is going
to be key. Let's get some volume on
here.
There you go. It's your edge.
I don't think this has finished
auctioning high yet. I don't think we
high yet.
Failed another attempt up there, mind
you. But
get it back over 185. I still think this
potentially got more in it before it
pulls back. And when it pulls back, it's
probably going to get pretty violent.
It's a decent 50 point pull back there.
So, just be aware of that.
Starting to see heavier delta come in
here sellside. Trying to flip the book
here a little bit. Still just dancing in
this range. I'm still not convinced
we've had a high put in, but there we
go. back down into the edge of this
volume. Nvidia giving up 85.
Watching the edge of this volume in case
they lose it or a 50 point drift down,
but I'm still not convinced we put in
that high yet. Just looking at the
volume up there. There's the loss of it.
Oh, we missed that.
Just talked about that. Probably missed
it. Want to be careful of the bear trap
here. I'm not convinced that high days
in, but we did just flip the book delta
wise.
Can be a deep drive here if they let it
go.
One 185 on Nvidia still been reclaimed.
So, I'm not convinced yet. I think
Nvidia's going to do a five bar and then
one more shove up. And I think ENQ still
needs to get to that 6 20 P 620 to 680.
That's what I think. So, I think this
might be accumulation and another shove
up. So, I'm just waiting.
If you're asking why am I not buying up
here, well, we're nowhere near any form
of structure to buy off.
This is your build out.
See, so far they're absorbing underneath
it and turning back inside every time
they get the chance. [snorts]
Volume is very slow on the book again.
It's a bit concerning, guys. I'm going
to be honest. This looks very, very slow
on the book again.
This is literally like yesterday.
Nvidia is looking like it wants to make
a new high day here. Mac is all green,
so I don't want to fight the tape.
They're going to do low vol and drift.
They are going to do it. It is what it
is.
Still absorbing down here.
Um, yeah. I mean, I like trading the the
10:00 exchange, Jack, for sure, but
beyond that, not really.
If there's volume and price is moving,
I'm interested. Doesn't really matter
what time, but yes.
I am interested in those exchanges
very close to that 20s old point of
control there. Get through that and
there's room to 80s I would say which
would be the week before.
Get through that you're looking at 800.
So,
or at least you're looking at 720
liquidity there and then 800s.
[snorts]
Morning DK.
620. Old weekly point of control. Just
got stuck just in front of that so far.
Nvidia new high day. Like I said,
thought we'd do a 5m minute bar and then
go. That's exactly what we've seen.
So, accumulation here. Probably one more
shove up and then see what they how they
act there. We've had no retest of the
550 where we just broke out from. Right.
So, we are now in an outside bar. Daily
is trading up. We've had a higher low
put in yesterday. Want to be aware of
that. Don't really want to fight the
trend. This is more me talking out loud
here as well.
Unless there's a big exchange and a big
failure for a trade back inside the
range, we have to be aware that we are
now breaking out on a daily after
putting a higher low. There's the fail
on Nvidia trading back down to these
85s. Now we're testing the edge of this
range again, the edge of this volume
range. If they leave this volume range,
we can trade about another 50 points
lower. If they reclaim this, it's going
to be another bear trap and a trade
inside. All right. So, just be very very
careful. There's a trade back down
towards the New York VWAP. We're holding
flow zones. We're holding edge of this
range again. Nvidia still holding uh 185
for now.
This looks very dangerous to me. That's
annoying again.
It's under 185, but we found a bid here
on the market. So,
just feels like it's teetering on the
edge here.
Do they leave this volume and trade 50
points lower is the question right now.
Back to point control. Back inside the
volume, testing this volume. They need
to sell this. And if they don't sell it,
Nvidia's reclaimed 185. You want to be
very careful about a new a resqueeze
higher here. This looks very trappy here
this morning in my mind. Very very
trappy here this morning.
Remember they've not taken out the 620s
yet.
Yeah, this is low volume dangerous
market. Honestly, this is screaming
don't touch it to me for two days in a
row here. I think market makers are
going to have some fun with this market
and rotate and rotate and rotate and
rotate offload of very low volume for a
little while here until we're in a
multi-time frame trend.
reclaimed 80 185 here. Still not getting
to that 620.
[cough]
Building out more volume at these highs.
Low zone starting to catch up. VWAP is
not really pointing upside. It's
starting to flatten out here a little
bit. So, they need to squeeze this
higher and soon otherwise it's just
going to chop for a long time. 85s again
here on the market.
This is uh
pretty ugly I would say at the moment.
The book is thin. It's thin thinning
out. Not a lot of volume here. Back to
test the lower side. Are they going to
snap this now? Nvidia back under 85.
Starting to see that failure starting to
come in. Shorts. We need a new low here
for a rotation back down towards the
VWAP.
Why have I lost my New York viewer on
here?
Here's the test of it. Lots of buyers
stacking up here with passive orders
trying to absorb the book down here in
front of VWAP.
That I'm telling you that 185 on Nvidia
is key. It's still holding it for now.
This can still be accumulation to go
higher if they want to. But we have
started to leave this this volume here
at 84
85,
but we've got VWAP right underneath us
now.
Use a 15-minute jack. Okay. So, what's
your 15-minut telling you? Because for
me, you're just trading inside of the
15minute right now. So, if you're going
to take breakout outside the 15-minute,
you're going to buy the weekly high.
still stuck here. BC up here now as
well.
Nvidia under the 85, but no, you know,
you're not seeing huge sell pressure.
Meta also gone red. Google having a
decent morning now. Found a bid.
Still think this has got that room 620
and then see how it acts.
Holding 185.
Just feels like nothing. Just feels like
absolutely nothing again.
Low volume trap again. Just like
yesterday. Just like last week.
And remember, we're in breakout on the
daily. So, I don't really want to be uh
thinking too short on this. At the
moment, we're in breakout on the daily.
Daily is a nice big green bar above
Friday's high. We're breaking out. Want
to be aware of that. It might be a
rotation back in, but it's not a short
on a daily right now on a breakout.
We certainly haven't come back to a
level that I would feel comfortable
buying at.
Tesla fighting to stay green right now.
Meta the same.
Nvidia losing that 85 at the moment.
Might see some uh more downside pressure
here on Nvidia if it starts to really
get going.
620 is that level, that old point
control.
Yeah. 620ish. And then what's the other
one?
86.
[snorts]
Here's a test of date.
No dice up there so far.
All just got slammed in their face.
Still don't think we've left enough
excess as a high. Still think there's a
new high coming. Don't think we've left
enough excess by side as a height.
Oh, mate. [sighs]
Straight move and then sideways
market honestly. [snorts]
All right, back down towards VW up. Do
they buy the VW up again and take us
back upside? Look how quickly these move
were so thin. That didn't take a lot to
move us straight back down to the other
side of that range. Then
it really took nothing. They bid VW up
here. Still don't think there's enough
excess at the high, but
just back down into that imbalance from
that first big candle on the way up,
right? This imbalance here. We're
holding that imbalance right now.
No follow through on VWAP. Yeah, VWAP's
flattened out. Like I said, it's one
thing I'd be concerned about. It's
flattening out.
Is there any liquidity hanging lower?
40. That's about it.
This looks so bad, folks. This looks
like another day where I want to go back
to bed. It's got that feeling at the
moment.
Hope the whole of December isn't going
to be like this. Really do
just holding on to VWOP right now.
There's a bigger rotation if they let go
of it.
It's an old imbalance. If they let go of
that first squeeze, they can go right
back down to the beginning of the day,
honestly. But uh we just have to see
tape looks dreadful again. Just so slow.
But that just so slow
and we're absorbing off no size.
Uh,
this doesn't look good, folks. Looks
like a no trade situation at the moment.
Unless we leave volume one way or the
other, we keep going sideways just under
volume. There's nothing we can do.
There's no play here to be had.
And looks very dangerous.
Very, very dangerous. And we still
haven't hit that 620, remember.
And we're not leaving. Unless they leave
aggressively this volume and we just
hang out. If we just hang around between
VW up in here, all we're going to do is
build a bigger volume shelf,
which is basically what we did
yesterday. We just kept building more
and more volume.
They need to leave this volume to trade
lower for a trade inside and then a buy
back. Once they do that, I'm not going
to buy up here. There's just no way.
Yes, your view up is down here. This is
a New York view up.
That's why this is anchored off the
opening print. This is cash. I care
about cash. You can see market cares
about cash. Doesn't care about this down
here. It's too far away to care about
right now. Might care about it later if
we get there.
failing PC there on that last push. Now
they need to trade away from here now.
They're stuck between New York View up
and PC.
This is about as dreadful as you get.
Chance to breathe. Um I don't really
think so. Consolidation. What? after a
five or six day squeeze higher a
consolidation for 10 minutes on low
volume after low volume squeeze for six
days I wouldn't say it's a chance to
breathe it's more a chance to play
stupid games
to breathe is a pullback which
consolidates into a good area not the
nonsense that we've seen for six days
and it is nonsense that's exactly what
it is
this is ridiculous. Just either break
out or break down. Please stop sitting
here for [\h__\h] whole day.
Someone trying to bid it up now. Trying
to walk up. He's got no size on his
tape. So, I'm just interested if they
actually fill him and Oh, he's moved.
Yeah, they're playing games on the order
float. It's It's actually just stupid.
It's like yesterday. They're playing
games with tiny lot sizes. This is what
I mean.
I don't think this is not tradable,
folks. Like, if you all think this is a
tradeable, if you're watching the book
right now, it is so slow with such
little size.
Yeah, it will be like this till
Christmas. What I said at the beginning
of the day, December tends to be choppy,
low volatility, low volume. Everyone's
like, "Oh, we close higher at
Christmas." That's [\h__\h] great, isn't
it? It makes me laugh. Oh, yeah. We
close higher. It doesn't matter what we
do. You can keep giving stats. We close
higher. Unless you're buying it at a
good level to close higher, doesn't mean
[\h__\h] You're going to get shaken out.
That's what makes me laugh about these
guys on Twitter. Yeah, we're closing
higher at Christmas. closing higher than
what level that you buy at.
Everyone's a statician. No one's a
trader. It's hilarious.
All right. Still not hitting those 620s.
Still don't think there's a strong high
in here. Still haven't left the volume
either side. Still trading sideways.
This is absolutely terrible.
Dreadful.
I'm going to get a refill of water here.
We're in a 30 point range.
A 30 point range. That's what we're in.
Here's the break. There's the 620. This
is the old point of control.
Now, if they get through this, the next
weekly, the week before that is
675 and there is liquidity to come and
run up to 720. is undeniable.
It is undeniable.
Yeah, of course. Well, any
anything's a potential spoof. It's if
it's above us or below us, anything's
got a potential spoof. Of course it is
potential. I don't know if he gets
filled until we get there.
Yes. Like anything you see above or
below you is obviously a potential
spoof. But again, that's not big size,
is it? Like we just saw someone come in
with 113 lot and pull it instantly and
they come back in again with a 50 lot
this time. I mean 100 lot is not is not
particularly big size.
say bulls will want to hold this 620 now
like this edge here
higher on map on
Ninja Trader so always want to hold this
edge this volume's going to become key
as your over under for the rest of the
day
edge of your profile Oh,
[cough]
it's just so slow again. Just look at
this sideways action.
Oh my god. [sighs]
holding value right now.
Building out a new ledge up here.
Like we said, bullish on the day,
breaking out on the daily.
Market's all green. No significant
pullback, though. Here's
the flush down to the area I said they
probably need to hold that 620 now for a
continuation trade higher.
Look at 8:00.
8:00. What? New York time.
So what?
I don't understand what what you're
trying to get at that there. Jack
doesn't take a swing low. It's just an
inside bar.
Yeah, I did read that. Ralph Trump with
a big announcement he said last night.
Huge announcement
and then the White House came out oddly
and said they're going to comment on his
what did they say on his account or
something really weird
news piece.
Okay, more volume being created up here
now.
We just held that 620 on the pullback.
Like I said, that old PC, if they're
going to hold, they're going to need to
hold 620, which they held successfully
for a drift higher.
There's a pacifier on a tape.
Even that little flush just got
absorbed. So, and you've got lots and
lots and lots of liquidity below now.
So, very very dangerous market at this
point off low volume in my mind.
They're going to have to trap to move
higher. I don't think they can just keep
gently is gently the right word walking
it up or however you want to put it.
And we've just stopped again.
[sighs and gasps]
This tape's awful.
This tape is like hilariously awful.
I really hope we get a shift from this
tape at some point this month because
the la last two days I've watched this
has been dreadful.
I literally don't have a [\h__\h] clue
what language you're talking right now.
Current 15 mini UT candle decisive 8
mst. I like I literally You're talking
different language. I don't know what
you're on about, bud.
The only word that makes sense there to
me is candle.
Okay. Can they get up to these 80s now?
Is it 80s or 75? So point control
and 75.
[laughter] Oh, time zone.
There's just no size. There's no size
being traded. It's such a low volume
walk up.
This is really, really slow.
There's a player spoofing now as well.
Oh my god. 100 lot just spoofing up and
down. That's four times is moved in the
last 5 seconds.
Five times,
six times,
seven times,
eight times, nine times, 10 times. What
a bell. 12 times. What an absolute [\h__\h]
[laughter]
Oh my god. Look at this guy. Is he
stuck?
What is he doing?
[\h__\h] hell. I don't know if you can
see this on Look at This is all one guy.
Can you see this on the book? This is
all one guy. I've never seen anything
like this. What are you doing, mate?
1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12 13 14 15 16
17 18 19 20 21 22 23 24 5 26 27 28 29 30
31 31 times he's just moved it in one
minute. And I'm not joking. And now he's
pulled it all together.
31 times he moved his order in a minute.
[laughter]
Yes, I know they don't need to be high
volume, Jack. Thanks for educating me.
Thanks, mate. They don't need to be high
volume, but I'm not going to trade until
I see high volume come in
because this is what happens. The snap
very, very quickly.
Okay, coming back to old point of
control. My god, we've got King
Educators in in chat today.
I want to see how we act at this ledge
here. If they find a bid here or not,
it's my first trade. It's my first day
ever trading today, guys.
Make sure you tell me all your all your
secrets.
Oh yeah, you've just taught me so many
new things, Jack. You just taught me
that we can drift higher off low volume.
[\h__\h] I never knew that, bud. I I've
never known that. That Thanks. I've
learned something new. Tell you what,
you can learn someone new something new
from someone else. [\h__\h] just pissing
me off. All I'd want to do is watch
order flow and all you're doing yap yap
yap yap yap. Well done. You took a
15minute bar breakout from here to here
and got retested. Well done. Like
[\h__\h]
something new. I don't know how to trade
that.
It's just annoying. It's always the same
people.
Okay, Nvidia losing 85.
Just drifted into its imbalance and
found a bid. I'm still watching this.
We're still holding volume. So, this
first back test has just happened. We
are bullish overall on a daily because
we broken out above previous day highs
which are here. We're holding balance
above the daily. But we are thin
regardless of what people say. We're
thin on the book. All right. We are thin
on the book and they are playing games.
I'm literally watching them play games
on the book. You could learn something
new, Jack, by learning how to read tape.
But hey,
so how we act into this node becomes
important now. We're still making higher
highs and higher lows.
Thank you, darling.
Still no trade for me.
still think this is a very very
dangerous tape because if you get stuck
the long wrong wrong side of it on low
volume it will not take a lot for them
to move this. It was just like yesterday
we saw the same thing. I'm going to get
rid of this. We don't need that now.
Once they went into rotation that was
it.
That high is looking better than that
last one though. There are buyers
chapped over 50 right now. There's no
doubt about it.
And we are starting to see a reaction
there. So they're starting to walk this
down now. It's more aggressive.
Let's see if this retest holds or not.
So it's trapped between these two sort
of imbalance levels. So we got imbalance
here. We're trapped between them. How we
act here becomes key. This high is not
too bad. We did leave some buyers
trapped above 50. Like I said,
the market very, very bullish overall.
We're in a breakout on the daily.
So, really should be looking for areas
to buy at, but really want to buy up
here right now. Not into this old point
of control on the weekly.
We're into a really dense area from
where we are now really all the way up
to 900 but definitely up to
680 is very very thick resellers. It's a
highly traded area for you know for 10
days we traded here
point of control twice in a row on
weekly
still holding flow zones, still holding
volume.
Nvidia is starting to struggle a bit
there into its imbalance. If it rejects
85 again and starts washing, it's going
to be problematic. It's just a question
then of do the chips see weakness with
it or not. Still well up on the day. It
is still well up on the day.
As a seller keeps coming in here
and he's being absorbed into 25 over and
over again. He keeps trying.
25 is a big area. They keep absorbing
off 25 right now.
Back down towards it now. See if a guy
shows up again and absorbs at 25 again.
Yep, he's trying. He's trying. He's
probably going to get washed to 15 here
if he can't hold.
Trying again at 25s.
He's still soaking.
Back to 25s again. If he if he gets
stuck here, there'll be a bigger wash
because he's been reloading there a lot.
I don't think they finish their business
higher, but uh they're building out new
volume here. And if we start to leave
this volume, we will rotate back down as
you can see. And if we lose that next
shelf, it will get very, very nasty
because Nvidia is starting to lose
everything
back down to the old PC's. Very very
possible here. Now 95 if they start to
lose these shelves.
right into that low volume node.
How can I contact the team? You just
just email me, mate.
info@flowzonerader.com.
Back to these 25s again. So sellers came
in under there, got caught
elaugh offside in this current candle
under 25. They tried to force him out
and he's reclaimed. It's going to get
it's going to get tricky here. is a
sensitive area. They're going to make a
decision very very soon because it's
first time I've seen Delta start to get
caught offside both sides. There we go.
It's a stronger selling back down to
where those sellers just got caught a
minute ago. Nvidia starting to crack a
little bit here like we talked about and
I think there's a rotation all the way
back down to point of control and VWAP
here. Very very possible which would be
sort of 95s and below if they can
sustain this auction. We're coming right
into this edge of volume, but I think
the back test of here is possible if
they keep rejecting 30s. And then how we
at there will sort of determine what we
do the rest of the day.
They're trying to buy this and protect
that low. I don't think it's going to
work. I think there's deeper coming in
here.
I think there's deeper coming.
We go
feels very close here to a wash back
down to 93. All the time it can reject
that. But we are trying to balance
between these two shelves right now. I'm
just watching the book. I think there's
a wash
back in on the next uh if the pop
rejects here, but it depends if it
rejects or not.
Nvidia is trying to reclaim.
Yeah, more sellers just came in here.
They're looking for that rotation back
down to 95 probably. And then you're
going to probably see some absorption
start to take place as we get into that,
I would imagine. Anyway,
here we come.
Have they got any strength to follow
through? They got to break that low. If
they can't break that low, they're going
to get caught. They just try it again.
If they can't break that low, they will
get caught.
I sell side imbalance up to
28.
Mag's still all green. We're still in
breakout
time there. 8 minutes left until the IB.
Yeah, that 2829 is going to be key here.
Over under, they reclaim that. Uh say
bears are in big trouble. They reject
that. There's still a chance to move
lower.
They're
starting to reclaim it. They hold a bid
here, they will squeeze out. No trade
again then.
They didn't reach
for the lows and didn't offer the sell
versus here reclaimed.
What a uh
weird market not to retest, reclaim and
then probably reg.
So will they go for that next point of
control is the question which would be
80s or 75 somewhere up there.
Buyers will want to step in here. They
will not want to lose this edge again.
30s. They lose that edge again. The
rotation still possible.
Got sweet coffee.
Yeah, exactly. Same story all year. It's
not even like the bears though at this
point. It's um more just like
how we're reclaiming is very very ugly
and very very very dangerous. Uh this is
what I mean. Low volume markets
they're nasty because we don't respect
uh levels very well because this might
look big but it's tiny. You know that's
like there's not not much here. More
down here because it's a bigger area but
still like we're trading very light
volume. It's uh it's really dangerous.
Really, really dangerous.
[cough]
There's no follow through, you know?
There's no follow through e either
direction. Like, we we're drifting, but
there's no real follow through. We're in
breakout buys. Remember, we're in
breakout buys on the daily. We want to
be buyers, but we want to be buyers.
Like down here, you know,
again, it's another day again where Asia
has had all the fun. You know, they get
the rotation, they get the cheap buy,
and we go, they get the buy. Everyone or
London gets the buy. Everyone else is is
trying to buy very very high right now.
It's
it's not it's not ideal. It's really not
ideal to be trying to trade higher up
here after a six day squeeze out on low
volume. It's uh about as dangerous as
you get. It might very well keep going,
but it's very very dangerous cuz it
would not take a lot if someone gets
stuck. It would not take a lot to see
this thing slam on faces, you know.
Look at that failed breakout there again
of the high right back down into that
25. This is where that guy's been
absorbing all day. If he gets stuck
here, like we've talked about this,
this can trade lower. If he gets stuck,
this can trade lower.
There we go. Someone's stuck. This is
his level.
This is his level.
They're trying to wash
Oh, if he gets stuck, it's going to
wash. This is what I mean about so
dangerous.
If he gets stuck here, this is the same
guy. This is his level 25s there, there
or thereabouts. And he's been soaking
and soaking and soaking and soaking and
soaking.
He's trying again. He's trying to absorb
the tape pit. If he gets caught, it's
going to get a nasty candle down.
Here we come. And it's going to it's
going to hurt him. He's tried so many
times here. Like I said, I thought we'd
move back to point of control that first
attempt, right, and VWAP. And you're now
going to see it. It's odd that they felt
the need to come back here one more
time. How we act here now becomes your
over under. If we fail under this,
there's a deeper rotation back into
here. If they hold this, then this is
the transition from this edge to this
edge, from this to this, create this,
come back down to this, test this.
He is now officially stuck, though. He
is stuck. He's getting absolutely
hammered. He just sold. That would have
been him on the book. 139 lot and he
keeps selling now. See, he's stuck.
There we go. Blah blah blah blah blah
blah blah blah blah blah blah M15 blah
blah blah blah blah blah blah. [\h__\h]
warn you.
Warn you.
[snorts]
Told you he's at 25. I told you if he
gets stuck, he's going to get in
trouble. There you go. You just got
absolutely annihilated.
They do things in one single candle.
Same as this one single candle at the
moment. There's no retest for it. I
mean, yeah, it's so risky. It's risky to
take that honestly when we're being a
directional move. But you can see they
didn't want to trade up into the last
point of control. And there's the dunk.
So any rejection of uh this area here
now will see lower prices. they reclaim
this then we'll use this liquidity to go
higher. All right. If it's this we use
liquidity to go higher but any rejection
now of sort of 93 to 600 that will be
your telltale that this market has
squeezed too much and they're taking
risk off.
There we go.
[\h__\h] knew I should have sized him. He
was stuck. I could feel it that there
wasn't actually an entry there.
And this is the old high now. All right.
So, we're now protecting the breakout.
Once we get under here,
all right, then we're no longer in
breakout. This would be a look above and
fail, which is what I've said all
morning. Be very, very careful about
failed breakouts in this market on low
volume. This is your Friday high. This
can be a look above and fail. If they
don't hold a bid here or if they sell
this and we get under this, this goes
back to an inside day. Understand? This
goes back to an inside day. This would
be a look above and fail if we let go of
that. It's why I'm so cautious in this
market at the moment.
They're not done selling this yet. I'd
like to see this pull up a little bit if
I'm going to sell it.
Like to see this come back up into this
node here
somewhere around here would be ideal.
[snorts]
and see how we act.
90.
[snorts]
What was the imbalance there? 600. There
is one above at 13. All right, let's see
how they are. Let's see if they squeeze
up there and if we see refresh sellers
come in.
Let's see if we squeeze up there and see
refresh sellers. If there's no refresh
sellers, then that's their only job was
to get back down to that previous day
high, which they've done. And you might
see bullish continuation. Like we said,
we can see an inverse head and shoulder
if they reclaim that range above and we
can go again. But at the moment, what
I'd like to see is to see if there's
some refresh sellers in this market.
I've just got a load of
issues on Ninja Trader here firing off.
Let me just close this down and reopen
it. Give me a second, folks.
Come on, NT. Get open, please.
Nice, Troy. Nice work. Yeah, I didn't
catch it. And I just put a limit order
up here and I just got a load of error
messages. So now I'm a bit concerned
that my NT Oh great, it's put me in a
position. Has it
on one account? The [\h__\h]
Are you joking?
Sorry folks. Just waiting for my NT to
reopen it. I can see it's put me in one
position and it won't open. There's the
failures, guys. You're going to give the
whole thing back. This is what I was
warning you of.
Come on, market. Can you open please?
Oh, it's TPT causing the problems.
That's weird.
Where are they?
[sighs]
Sorry folks, I've got some issue here.
can't find my TPT accounts. I can't log
into TPT.
I It says I've got no accounts and I
have I've got three.
I'll deal with it afterwards then.
Very bizarre. Anyone else having that?
It's TPT down today or anything via uh
trader bait?
Can't log I can't log on to it via Ninja
Trader at the moment.
Yours is all good. Okay. Maybe it's just
an issue my server somewhere.
That's bizarre.
So, my connection's gone on TPT. I
cannot log into it.
I'll deal with that mate, I guess.
Okay. Well, we're holding previous day
high here. Sorry, I'm going to have to
get my head back in the game now. That's
I can't figure out what's gone on there.
Holding previous day high here. There's
the wash down to this point. This is
your breakout level. This is your daily
breakout. This red line on the screen,
this is what caused the squeeze. Here's
your daily breakout. Here's your edge of
volume. How we act here now becomes key.
If we're going to see continuation
lower, this this is where we're going to
see it from.
If they reclaim this shelf here, all
right, if we reclaim this and build
liquidity out here, this would be the
move to go higher. This is your
overunder this level here. Now, bears
will want to defend to create a
rotation. That's their job right now.
and underneath previous day high as we
start getting underneath here. This will
be your fail breakout. This will be
confirmation of fail breakout.
But don't worry, I need to learn
something new every day. I don't know
what I'm talking about. Haven't made
this absolutely abundantly clear all
day.
[snorts]
You're good. Okay. [sighs]
It's almost like they've changed because
I can't even log in. It's like there
something's gone wrong with my um trade
vape, but I I'll get it fixed as soon as
I get off stream. [snorts]
Okay. So, if they keep failing this edge
here, they will expand range. You'd be
looking for under this VW will be a move
back towards these 493s.
Where's the rotation happening? Well,
you're still seeing some weakness in
Tesla's gone red. Nvidia
coming back down to where it sort of
came from, but you can easily be a bid
up
in this market at some point. Let's have
a little look. VIX has found a bid is
back over its New York open and it's
trying to squeeze to close the gap back
to 1725s.
And if it does that, you'll see
increased pressure on this market.
So PDH is absolutely key. Bulls want to
defend PDH to continue having a uh a
breakout on a daily, right? This level
above this New York VWAP and that volume
shelf is key. Bears will want to defend
this. So the rotation right now is
happening between higher time frame
bulls trying to defend this lower time
frame bears trying to defend this. This
is the rotation. How we act here becomes
key. If they reclaim it, bulls can take
control of the market again.
And we have an imbalance up here all the
way up to 600. Same area that I talked
about before. All the way up to 600.
There is a imbalance here from this big
kill candle. So there we go. very close
to this gray box now. How we act into
this is pivotal.
Do I have any thoughts on the F1?
I mean, yeah, I think Zack Brown's a
[\h__\h] idiot. Does that count?
[laughter]
He's an absolute joke.
And I think if they don't pick a winner,
a a a premier driver going into this
race, which they said they're not going
to do, they're liable to lose the whole
championship,
you know, and I think given what
happened with the car, not the weekend
just gone, the weekend before where they
cost Lando, well, it cost both points,
but they cost Lando more points and then
the bad decision at the weekend just
gone. I think they've uh well, they've
absolutely
gifted Max the ability to come into this
race or or championship I should say.
And it wouldn't surprise me to see him
win it. It would it like it just
wouldn't surprise me at all at this
point to see Max
Max be Max.
I still think higher than yesterday's
high. We are higher than yesterday's
high. Jack, you you are trying to wind
me up today. Chronic mate. You're
literally talking gibberish. This is
yesterday's high. We are higher than
yesterday's high. We are protecting
yesterday's high.
[\h__\h] me.
Oh yeah, I'm tired of it. But like Max
is, as much as I hate him, it's very,
very impressive. You're starting to
reclaim this range now. So if they hold
pullbacks into here now, bulls will take
over. All right, they hold pullbacks
into here now, they will look for that
continuation I've been talking about.
[snorts]
So this is the same level that buyer was
trapped up earlier into the 620. This is
where he let go.
Yeah. Apple alltime highs and Nvidia
finding a bid here. That level for
Nvidia we have to test is this sort of
uh 84 8430
big level for Nvidia. And you can see
this market just one directional one
move down consolidates one move straight
up doesn't reject here cut straight
through it. Why? Because there's no
[\h__\h] volume like I keep telling you,
right? That's why we're cutting through
levels. Cut down, cut up. Can it hold a
bid here is the question now?
Can it hold a bid there?
>> [snorts]
>> Yeah, I felt really like
I'm absolutely disgusted with that Red
Bull message about Kimmy. Um, they
should be utterly ashamed of themselves.
Utterly, utterly ashamed of themselves.
Um, he got a load of death threats which
had to be reported to the FOA because of
Hem coming out saying that he let them
through, which he didn't.
Alex, you have some connection data on
top left of your screen.
What?
I don't know what you mean. Sorry, mate.
Okay. So, [sighs and gasps] does this
pull back into sort of 600 to 90s now
and hold a bid? That's what we're
waiting to find out here. Do we pull
back in and hold a bid? Do they slice
right back through it all the way back
down to the downside again?
>> [cough]
>> They Didn't even get down there to hold
a bid. [sighs]
Aggressive buyers coming in right now.
Trying to force this back up.
I want to be a buyer in this ideally
here
for this move.
Yeah, I agree with you, Miguel. I really
like Isaac Hajger. I really really like
him. I think he's got good temperament.
I think he's driven well. Not a fan of
Liam Lawson, I tell you that much.
Think he is a bit of a knob.
Looks like they just want to squeeze
this. I really want to see this pull
back first because this is like what
530s is a 100 point squeeze out since
that pivot low without pulling back.
Love to see this pull back with this
market. It seems uh like it just goes
one way then stops. It goes the other
stops goes the other stops.
to see this pull back a bit.
Please, Mr. Market, come and pull back
me.
Does trade of eight have any good
indicators to identify liquidity? I
don't use trade of eight, but I'm sure
it does because it has order flow.
So, if you're using prop firms, you will
get order flow for free. There's a video
on my YouTube right now, maybe two weeks
ago, explaining how to get all of that
free.
So you could I don't know maybe you can
even get a heat map on there. I don't
know. I don't use it. But you can
definitely get
uh level two and footprints and volume
profile and that's all you need for uh
seeing liquidity.
Please market please come and pull back.
Don't just squeeze straight out here.
Come on.
Well, squeeze out. It is new highs
coming.
You out.
New highs coming here.
And once we get through this, I'd say
680 to 700. That's uh the next level.
It's an old point of control on a
weekly.
So, ball's successfully defending his
pivot.
Honestly, this is going to go.
Such buggers, man. Here
it goes.
Will you pick me up first?
This is what we talked about earlier. I
said if it reclaims this and we build
this, we can go. Unfortunately, it's
done like a couple of tiny bars here.
This is the move versus this. This is
why I didn't want to buy up here. I
wanted to wait for a retest of this
daily level and then I was hoping to get
a higher low here to get get higher but
again this market just uh adamant in
squeezing and I'd say
680700 is the level and you've got
confluence here for a squeeze through it
into sort of 720s
measured move will get you all the way
up to 780. Where would 780 take us?
Well, 780 will take us through
an old uh weekly value area high 770.
And we have liquidity resting at 825s,
827s. This thing is just squeezing.
Straight squeezing now. Nothing I can
do. It's gone. It's gone. This is the
market right now.
Won't pick me up today. finally wanted
to get pulled into it and it won't pick
me up.
[cough]
Yeah, go Mr. Market. Well, thanks very
much. You You're all making money. I'm
not. I'm sat here waiting still.
still it goes. If you're long, you can
just hold on. Your TP1 was uh that
initial balance high. You're if you're
if you're already long, you can hold on.
We get very very very thick. I'll show
you what I'm looking at in case you've
forgotten from this morning. All right.
This is where we get thick. This is
where we're currently trading at this
green line. This is an old PC. We're
very, very thick in here. So, this is
why I wanted to buy. I didn't want to
buy in here. It's way too risky. I
wanted to buy way cheaper all this
rotation and you can sell into it. So,
I'd say next TP
probably into this 80. You're pretty
much almost there. Once you get through
that, we've got liquidity resting at 25
725.
old value area 770. You can mark these
out. So I'd mark out
80s,
725,
770,
and uh 835. And then after that, you
might as well call it 900. Liquidity
resting at 896. That's what you're
looking for.
That's what I'd be looking at.
Those are based on previous week levels.
We're trading into previous week levels
here. Do not be a dick for a tick as
you've just come right into that sort of
680 675. We talked about
video coming back up to that 8450.
[cough]
What do I think Max news could it could
go up to today?
I mean, you could easily see it at 900.
It's only 250 points more. It could do
it. If it really wants to do it, it can
do it. Market would do whatever it is it
wants to do. I'd certainly say shorts
have been caught offside.
Question now is, can it hold value here
or are we going to get a rotation from
initial balance failure?
I'm going to use the bathroom. Well, it
decides to tell you that much.
[cough]
>> [snorts]
>> Am I going to get picked up with
anything today?
Okay, what needs to happen now then?
Well, really either bulls are going to
hold this for a continuation, but we
have just come into the towards that 680
or you're going to get a basically look
above and fail and get trapped under
here for that wash back down to here
again. Remember, we haven't retested
that yet. This has been one straight
squeeze. Here's your compression. Here's
the previous day high. Here's the hold.
And there's one singular move without
coming and retest retesting. So, maybe
they come down here. I don't know.
I really don't know what their games are
today, but there are definite games on
the tape.
Would I have this areas 4hour supply? I
would imagine so based on I've got it as
a weekly supply and a daily supply and
yes I would imagine it's a 4 hour
supply. But what I would say is it's not
that fresh. I mean it's fresh since when
did we create it? Monday the 10th all
the way into Thursday the 13th. So we
have three days of supply and this is
the first time testing it since we left
it on let's just say Thursday the 13th.
We le we left it. This is our first sort
of test of it since. But that supply
that was created from the 10th to the
13th was the same supply that was
created from the 4th to the 6th. So
while it's thick, it just depends. Are
there passive sellers sat here anymore?
Or are they, you know, have they had
their rotation for that weekly low that
we had two weeks ago, right? Maybe they
exited down there. We're going to find
out.
I will repeat myself though. The market
is in breakout. You got to understand
the market's in breakout.
But
went over this this morning.
Market is in breakout over this area.
Right? There's your consolidation.
There's the breakout. Make it simple.
It's a flag and go.
The problem is this, right? You're
breaking out into
resistance, right? And we don't know.
Well, like I said, if it did this and
came under the breakout level, then
you'd get a collapse. We came back down
to that breakout level. Remember this
level here, 547 or whatever it is, it's
the same level.
It's this,
right? That's your daily breakout.
Breakout, retest, held, singular move.
That's ugly when we do this. That's
ugly. You want it to do this so you can
join in for that move.
I don't control the market. The market
will do whatever it is it wants to do.
We can see the levels. We can see the
plays, but we can't control how it acts.
[cough]
Alex I'm seeing the same pattern these
days on ES sweep the H1
then sweep sweep the H1 high then sweep
the H1 low before making the move. I
mean that that is more a sign of of a
rotational market. It's actually not
that common to sweep both sides.
Bitcoin 7% move with extreme fear. Well,
let's have a look.
I mean, it's coming to a key area
and this can price back up to here and
still find a lower high and be sold
into, right? Because this can still do
this and there's your neckline. So, you
know,
is this a demand level? Yeah,
absolutely.
that, you know, Bitcoin really has got
to reclaim this area here, 99. You might
as well call it 100,000. Uh, this can
just be a move back in for them to
resell. Absolutely can. You know,
there's your higher low on a daily, but
uh I'd be very cautious in Bitcoin right
now. It's done its thousand day cycle
like I talked about, you know, number of
weeks ago here. We expect the bearish
move because it's had a bull trend for a
thousand days. That is the cycle in
Bitcoin. thousand day bull trend and
then 80% give back.
So NASDAQ is saying one more retest
24,000.
Uh we're not coming down to 24,000
anytime soon.
It would be nice, but uh it's a long way
away right now on the cues.
Get back down into here. It's a long
long long long long way away. But uh I
want to see how we act at 25,000 24,900.
I think that's the the more important
level. Do bulls defend that
just like we talked about in the
newsletter. That's going to be the
level.
Okay. So, probably going to come back
down now to this area here unless
they're going to do a bull a bear trap
under here. that this area here will be
of interest to me if they step in to buy
that or not.
But we are now inside of initial
balance. We can just go into a
rotational day. This is not a trending
market. You might all think it's a
trending market. We're in breakout. But
so far today, all we've done is create
rotation.
I've not traded not traded. Tyson
missed the short and then NT went down
for me. So, I couldn't get anything and
I wouldn't have got the long anyway to
be honest because it didn't come back
and give me the test of here. I think
there's probably more upside in this
market. It just depends how low does it
want to go right now
before resuming that uh that uptrend.
That might have just been it.
Nvidia is getting absolutely whacked
here though, folks. I will tell you that
much. So, it tried to reclaim like we
talked about the 90 uh 8450s and it got
absolutely slammed.
Tesla's still red and rest market still
looking good. I'll give you a readout.
Tesla corporate percent down. Nvidia
1.83%. 83% up. Microsoft just over a
percent. Meta 0.70%
up. Google up 3/4 of a percent. Amazon
1.81% up. And uh Apple 1.02%
up. So MAG looks strong. Want to be a
buyer ideally down here. It looks like
they've just trapped bears on that
little wick under though. So we'll see.
We'll see what it offers. Is there a way
of getting involved?
Looks very bullish right now.
Long off VWAP. Um the bottom VWAP or the
New York reclaim.
Yeah, this was nice.
I mean, even this break here,
but I mean, I really wanted this. I
wanted to buy that for this move. It's
just not come. It's done it now, but
that's uh that's just a better trap into
the low volume node, protect it, and go
higher. So, looking for ways of joining
this to move higher at this point, but
uh we're running out of room because we
know that 680 is that old point of
control.
Nice work, Tyson.
And video just flat now. It's just
stopped moving at these 83s.
Apple looking good. Up almost 40% on
those commons.
Still not sold those
Still this one's higher.
Was that last auction?
Yeah, it was strong sell day delta at
68. I think we can take that out. It's
potential to take that out
if we can go into a trend day. Big if
right now. I really want to buy down
here.
Nvidia looks pretty weak.
It's just dripping back down towards it
New York open at the moment. Slowly
seeing aggressive selling in Nvidia
here. They've got to hold these lows
for Nvidia otherwise the whole market
will rotate with it.
We're currently trading around the 8263s
on Nvidia. New York open was 8176es
under that. Remember we gapped up on
Nvidia. It can close the gap all the way
back down to 79s. It's possible.
So, if they don't find a bid soon on
Nvidia and it can drag the market down
with it, we start seeing a rotation out
of chips again. Remember, we're trading
in supply
and no doubt about it on the weekly.
I just want to see how we operate if we
can get down here.
Does it give me something to play off or
we just going to see complete weakness
and a complete rotation?
So, IB to be up looks like it's about to
play out.
There's BWAP.
And how do we now operate then? Are we
going to slice through this level?
Nvidia is getting absolutely clubbed. A
little bounce off VWAP, but I'm not
fully convinced watching Nvidia right
now. And that is starting to get
absolutely diced up
into its pre-market high here. It needs
to hold a bid here in video otherwise
it's going to be in trouble.
I just think we're going to keep
rotating. This is just ugly
because now we can get stuck here and do
this and then we can lose this or we can
gain this and it's just
oh it's just not not a good market.
Not a good market. New lows here on
Nvidia.
Oh, I'm not going to buy this. This is
too dangerous, man. This is way too
dangerous.
Think if anything, we might sell off.
We might sell off here. Big selling
coming into the book.
This is the level they need to hold. But
because they built that shelf now,
everything has to be a scalp today. At
this point,
VA coming right back down to its New
York open at this point, folks.
And it is still selling.
I don't think this is done selling this
market. If they retest this sort of
point of control area and it stays
heavy,
we can rotate further again. But uh
yeah, having to be adaptable in this
market to what I'm thinking it might do
because
the environment is changing very very
quickly. But I don't think they're done
with this. We'll see. Bulls need to
defend this gray box. Bears need to
defend this gray box. just can't make a
decision until it gets outside one of
those
video trying to find a bid at that New
York open and pre-market high. I'm still
unconvinced on it. It was a big sell
though. So, here we go. Retesting this
level up here. Let's see if bear is
coming in to defend this or not or if
we're actually going to make new highs
and weekly level. I don't think we're
done selling at this point. Just well,
just based on what I'm looking at on the
tape, I think we're going to move lower.
They're trying to bid. They are
attempting to bid. I'm not convinced.
I think they're going to get slammed on.
Here we go.
There we go. There's Bwap.
There's more pain coming here. Here we
go. Here's the pain.
Back down to where we broke out from
this imbalance here.
I'm still not convinced they're done. I
think there's more pain coming here,
folks. I'm not convinced they're done.
Big exchange down there into 80.
Be watching VW up in 610. 610 was the
level. 610 is 6. Yeah, 613s. That's kind
of the level that bears wanted to bend
now.
I still don't think they're done. I
think there's more pain in this. Again,
they're not done selling this. No way.
Here we go. New lows.
[cough and clears throat] Like I said,
had to be adaptable for the environment,
which just changed very, very quickly
there.
It's mainly being driven by Nvidia,
which is uh under well, it's coming back
down to its New York open. And if it
remember if it loses that we can go for
gap fill on Nvidia and if if we lose
previous day high this will all be
considered a failed breakout and we will
move back inside previous days range.
Remember this is weekly supply previous
two week supply up here.
This is current demand on the day. All
right. And this is your edge of value.
If we lose this it's night night.
We are in a rotational market at the
moment though.
More selling here. Strong selling on the
tape. They're trying to get back down to
those 50s at the moment by the looks of
it.
And we might get all the way back down
to a New York open if they keep selling.
Nvidia underneath its open price now.
underneath its low of day, new low of
day into its pre-market action. And
remember, it's got gap fill potential
all the way back to 7973. So, just call
it 80. And this is strong selling,
folks. This is very strong selling on
the book
into that area of demand, this yellow
box. Sorry, this here where we broke out
from. If we do this here, I wouldn't
consider that bullish. I'd consider that
building liquidity to go lower. And any
rejection of this now can force their
hand to move lower.
And you've got buyers trapped in this
now because we're in a rotation.
I think you're going to see some
liquidation starting. Here we go.
They're looking to test 50s and then
underneath what was that previous day
high? 45. Weakness can really come
underneath 45. And I'm not joking. And
that would be a failed look above after
one retest already. Here we go. Can we
get to 45s? And can we sell through it
now?
Come on, baby.
Some covering here into 45s. I still
think we're going to sell through it. I
think New York open is not out of the
question here. This is very strong.
Here we go.
Alex doesn't know what he's talking
about
into lower time frame. Algo see if bears
defend previous day high now
and if they can then you're looking for
a move. Previous week high will be uh
499 and the New York open will be uh
920s.
Really nice.
Remember this is a straight cell. All
right. Once they lost this, they
defended this, they lost this, this is
your cell. This blue line is your next
cover point. And we can come all the way
down. Honestly, it can keep selling.
We're in liquidation mode. So,
any rejection up here or even here, I
expect to be sold into.
They would need to reclaim this for
bulls to have a chance. And we're not
seeing that right now. [snorts]
Quite the opposite.
Lower time frame algo here.
Still think there's more weakness in
this. I think pops will be sold into
at this point.
>> [snorts]
>> Yes, absolutely. You your first target
was the previous day high. Absolutely.
You have to be paying yourself some.
Absolutely. You just took out previous
day high. Now, you want to see if
there's sustained weakness. I'd say from
70 to 90. All right. is their sustained
weakness or this rotation here. There's
uniwalk open. There's initial balance
high. And we've got lots of stuff down
here that we can come and back test. All
right. So, definitely if you took this
short from here or here, any of these
levels, TP1 and TP2, TP3, and then run
us down into gap fill.
We expect a bit of a bounce and then we
want to see if they sell into it.
Nice pass. Nice a
lovely work.
I want to see a pop up here and then see
if we get some uh
more sellers come in so we can get some
size into this move.
They're still selling it. want a new low
here. They will want a new low here for
that move back down to previous week
high and the open. Here we go. Here's
trying to get them. We're trying to
force it.
Want to be careful. There's a lot of
selling at those lows. That's twice now.
We've had a lot of selling uh from 30
and under. So, if sellers don't get
their way there, they will probably get
a squeeze back out to 70s. They just
tried twice
to sell the low.
They almost had it and it got saved. So,
it's definitely a passive buyer down
there at 30 right now. And I'd say how
we operate at 70s is what's going to be
important.
They're not even letting it that high
right now. Okay, 30s is key. This is
where sellers have been stuck. They need
a breakdown under 30. Sellers keep
getting stuck under 30 at the moment.
still not sellers not getting their way
under 30. You need this to get under 30
for continuation. Failing to
[clears throat] do that can cause a
squeeze out to 70. All right. I'm not
looking for longs in this, by the way.
I'm just letting you know that's what
I'm seeing on the tape. All right.
defending of even 38 now. Even 38 key
this can afford a squeeze all the way
back up to 70s.
Just be aware of that.
There's 38. If they close under this,
they should go to 30s and then under
that, they can get sell pressure. Major
sell pressure.
Big battle there. You can see it between
38 and 30s. Huge battle. Sellers keep
trying at the lows. They're not getting
their way. If they don't get their way,
they get caught. They're trying again
here. It's huge [snorts] battle down
here. There's someone trying to absorb
it. If he moves out the way, it's going
to be quite a nasty flush, I would
imagine.
At the moment, he's doing a good job of
absorbing 38 to 30.
Feels like the flush is coming. Here's
the 30 test. New load probably coming
here if he doesn't get his way. Keeps
trying to soak. He's tried again. He's
loading up 30. He's added more in 20.
Here comes the flush.
He's doing a pretty good job right now.
I think he's about to get hurt though.
There he goes. So, back down to the
lows.
[cough]
When is power speech? Power speech was
last night
and it didn't no comment on monetary
policy. Here you go, folks. There's the
flush.
All right. So, some TP in here. You're
looking for New York open now. New York
open and initial balance low. You're
looking for that to get run out.
Really nice.
sellside pressure coming. Can we get to
New York open which is sort of 92 and
then lower day into 70s? That would be
fantastic.
Getting reload on coffee here.
I'd watch Nvidia here into its previous
low day in New York open if they sell
that.
And I'd watch us into 70s if we can get
up there.
Still wouldn't mind a resell if we can
get up there. Remember this been a
straight move down. This is this has
been the story of the market.
Unfortunately,
this is what happens when we're low on
volume. Straight up. At least this had
some consolidation. Straight up and
straight down and straight up and
straight down. You know, we're not
really seeing one of these. We're just
going from one side to the other. I
would imagine we're looking for this
move down here right now. New York open
initial balance GlobeEx previous day
value very high. I want to trade lower
at this point.
We're underneath previous days high.
Remember? So what we're basically saying
right now is today was a failed
breakout. I wonder who thought today
could be a failed breakout.
Wonder who said they don't want to buy
the high today. We're in supply. This is
low volume. It's a good chance fail
breakout.
Okay, here you get very close to
previous week high here.
And I'm looking for that flush now
through this. There's previous week
high. Someone's trying to sell previous
week high. Be very careful here. They
can get themselves caught. Someone just
sold that right into previous week high.
Looking for this flush here now into 93s
or 92s, which would be the New York
open. Here we go. Give me it. Give me
it. Give me it. Give me it. Get me into
the 90s. Come on, motherucker.
Here we come.
Come on. Come on. [laughter]
15 minute boss. Suck a nut, buddy.
[\h__\h] talking [\h__\h] to me all morning.
Next stop, initial balance low, GlobeEx
previous day value area high. We can
drift all the way back into that gap
fill is not out the question. New low of
day on Nvidia failed to reclaim what
lows. The New York lows failed to
reclaim it. Came right back into it.
Like I said, watch for that retest of it
to see if they sell it. We're in a
one-stop market. I've said it as long as
I can go on about it.
There's your initial balance low. So TP
here. The next thing to hold on to is
these uh
D50s.
looking good. Looking really good here.
So, just hold on to your runners now and
you should have paid yourself a ton of
money.
And until we reclaim previous day high,
we are in a failed breakout and we are
trading back into old range.
All right. It was ready. It was planned
for. It's very aware of this move.
You got lured in and suckered into
buying high today. You ignored
all that chunky two weeks worth of
supply that we traded into up here.
It had a chance to trade higher, but it
didn't. So, we just have to be adaptable
to the tape. Two TPT evals pass 1,000 on
the funded patient pays off. Thank you,
Alexander. Nice work, Chris. All right,
GlobeEx here, folks. All right, big
GlobeEx level. This is also a VWAP from
yesterday down here. So, I'm expecting
some form of reaction here. Guess what?
Spy, I just got alert. Spy is crossing
that 680 on the spy. That is a massive
gamma level. So, if they hold 680 on the
spy, that this would be a big cover
point. All right, there you go. All
right, there's your gamma level on spy.
If they hold this, we will squeeze back
up. If we trade below this, I'm telling
you now, this is a massive lookout below
scenario. All right, this is a big gamma
level on spy. If they sell this off,
this market's going to get really,
really, really nasty. We went over this
right in the at the morning before the
market open. We talked about it. is how
I know that just got crossed because I
set a price alert there.
Okay.
Well, at least if you're new here, you
can see that I know what I'm talking
about. This is not a guesswork.
This is all planned out before we get on
the charts. We plan all this out before
we get on the charts.
Still they sell it. So Globeex's now
tested here. London Hide just got
tested.
Where's the spiders?
We're underneath that gamma level. If
they start losing this gamma level, it
can get really, really nasty.
And they are under it right now. I'm
waiting to see if we get five minute bar
close under it. 3 minutes left in this
5minute bar. It's a massive massive
level for hedge funds.
Yeah, W's in chat if you caught any of
this.
Expect some relief at some point around
680. There you go. They're trying to bid
off it. So, I'd be watching spiders now
if they give it give it if they give
some relief up towards sort of 81s and
if they resell those 81s,
but we know this is a massive level. You
must must must have been paying yourself
some money down here. Okay, you do not
want to, you know, get down into these
key levels. We've traded underneath
initial balance now. We've traded
through the New York open. Remember, our
target was previous day high, New York
open, initial balance, and then hold on
to runners. That's where you're at.
We're trading into the GlobeEx high
right now and we're trading into that
680ish on the spiders. They might very
well find a bid off here. We do not
know, but we are going to be protective.
Nice jump
by reclaiming 680 here. Still no fivem
minute bar close. Got two minutes left.
It's a honestly it's a huge level. If
they start selling through this
aggressively, this market's going to get
really, really, really nasty.
Look at the daily now. Look at the wick
on the daily.
There we go.
Uh, [sighs]
let's move you into the daily chart so
we can go back to what I was looking at
the beginning of the day.
Okay,
this is the balance range, right? Two
weeks, one week, two weeks. Buyers still
stuck above here. This
right here is a failed breakout on a
daily, isn't it? Because it's come above
previous day high and we're coming back
inside. So, we can see sellside
pressure. Where can we come to? I don't
know where we come to today, but if we
have trapped a lot of buyers up there
and they want to sell this, this has
been one straight move up. I said, "Yes,
this is a higher low on a daily, but I
wouldn't really consider it much. I want
to see this market drift down into these
900s like I've talked about and see if
buyers really want to defend that. Maybe
a 50% pullback of the range and then if
they defend it, we're off to the races.
But remember, the macro environment
right now is not looking good. All
right, talked about it numerous weeks in
the newsletter. It's not looking good.
So, if we go to that higher time frame
chart in the hourly, you can see this is
the thick area. All right. We don't want
to be a new money long into this area.
We want to be a new money long down here
for the rotation in so we can take
profit and then hold some. Not in here
getting trapped with all the people
today for the rotation back down.
[snorts]
Okay.
>> [cough]
>> Still not got a fiveminute close under
680. I'd be careful now. They they've
attempted for the last five minutes and
they're failing. All right. So big big
gamma level. Might get a squeeze up out
of this. It can still be sold into after
a squeeze out, but you might see a
squeeze out out of this because I know
that is a huge huge level. All right. I
know it's a massive level.
[groaning]
They're reselling it. It's a big big
seller up there into 80.
O, this is getting whippy now. This
might get nasty.
They're retesting these lows again. This
can get really nasty really, really
quick. I've said it numerous times.
Under 680 now. They might well let this
go. If they let this go and they can't
defend it on spiders, I dread to think
what happens with this market can have a
pretty big flush.
Here we go.
So, previous day value area high
probably the next level and gap fill.
I wouldn't rule these out. I would not
rule these out for your runners. Very,
very possible.
previous day value area high 24s
and we can sell through that. We can
close gap into 390s.
Hurry up and catch up please.
What we got there? 30 minutes.
New low day Nvidia. I think we're going
to sell it. Come on. Just got two little
guys left. Can you get me at previous
day value high? Here we go. Okay,
covering one here. Let's see if we can
get gap for. In fact, I'm going to see
if we can come under the gap. I'm going
to move my runner lower at this point
because we've locked in some good money.
Can we keep selling to that gap and
under?
Looking good.
They're selling every pop right now.
We're well under that 680 on SPY. I'm
going to use that as my risk. All the
time we're trading under that. Think
we're going to melt.
Let's go, baby. Let's get this gap and
under. Let's see if we can really wash.
If we come under this gap, I'm going to
look for move all the way down here. To
be honest, so many bulls are now trapped
in this
Come on, baby. Let's flush all these
guys. Here we go. Do it. Do it. Do it.
Do it. Do it. Do it.
Want to get through 400s. Through 410
and 400s. They keep rebidding 410 and
400s. Can afford quite a big pop up
here, so I want to be careful. Again,
I'm going to use 680 as my risk on
spiders. I want to see it reclaim that
now. Can come back and retest it. No
worries. But if we reclaim it, I'll just
cut this last little guy.
Yesterday's VWAP is at uh 50s or 48
actually.
448.
There's yesterday's VWAP.
Almost at that 680. Going to use that as
my overunder.
There's 680. 1 minute left. The clos
inside this I will cut the runner.
Don't want to see this reclaim
because we can still afford a squeeze
all the way up into here. can absolutely
afford that. I don't want to sit through
that with a runner and give too much
back.
Still trading around these 680s.
Still selling. They're still selling at
the moment.
down like spy. It's holding on. 10
seconds left here in this 5minute
candle. It's uh trading right at the
680s. I don't like what I'm seeing
there. No follow through since trading
downside. So might see a squeeze up
here. Be very very careful. Okay, out of
this now.
Had the chance to close under on a five
minute. might still might still do the
move. Can always read in
despite trying to find some relief here.
Here you go. Relief we just talked about
that might happen at 680. And it can
afford to come all the way up here 40s
and even up here. So let's move this up
to here.
We've been in a straight cell and you've
got uh 25 minutes left till lunch.
This has been a straight dump without
retesting anything. And there are stops
above 83s and they can afford to drift
back up above these 83s and come back
into this if they really want to and
then see if they want to resell that.
And we're well under previous day high
now. So they can afford to back test it
if they want to. Been a big strong sell.
VIX closed its gap as well by the way.
So VIX did close its gap.
We're starting to see a bit of a squeeze
out here.
Nice protection of what is that?
Previous day value high so far. If we
lose previous day value high. All right.
Here's the gap. If we lose this, this is
point control from yesterday, then we
should rotate all the way down here. All
right. So, if we lose this, we should
rotate all the way down here for later
in the day when I'm not here. Should be
aware of that. If they hold this, then
we're going to create new range above
it.
But this level here is what's key to me.
Just call it 550 is actually previous
day high. That is a key level.
I say that New York open as well will be
key.
trying to get up to that New York open.
Trying to pop these stops and get up
into here. And if they can get through
that, that's not unachievable. But flow
zones all pointing down.
Here's [cough]
the New York Open like we talked about.
Rejection of New York open so far.
Just want to see and wait to see if they
want to come up to previous day high for
retest or not.
Is that someone at my door? Give me a
second.
All right. [sighs and gasps]
[snorts]
Yeah, just trading around that New York
open.
Still under previous day high. So, I
want to see if we can retest that sort
of previous day high area and see if
sellers come back in and defend that to
confirm the failed breakout.
[cough]
God, I know now that we've uh traded
into that 680 inspire and defended it.
So, you know, if we want to bid up the
rest of the day, if the goal was to
retest that 680 gamma level and defend
it, then they've done it. So, we've hit
a low hanging fruits. The only thing
left to do was to close the gap, which
we didn't do. Did we do it on the ES?
Yes, we did. All right. So, we had
divergence there. We closed the gap on
the ES. We didn't close it on the Q's.
Let me get my uh that come up here so I
can see it. Be a bit useful, wouldn't
it?
>> [snorts]
>> Will they lift this to previous day high
and VWAP? So, right here, level of
interest for me, 540ish. I want to see
if sellers actually come back in here or
not. If not, we go back into the range
created.
It was a nice long interest. If you if
you took that from here, if you wanted
to take previous day value, just make
sure you're selling some into this
because uh we don't know if it gets
defended. It might not. It might be that
you get a squeeze all the way back out
into the range that's been created
today. All right, so if they defend
previous day's value,
right, that's previous day's value.
They'll want to reclaim this. But if we
defend this, we're going to come back
down for this. All right, so remember
this is one move. this can still happen.
So, just make sure you're paying
yourself. If they reclaim this, then
yeah, potentially they drive it back
upside. But I'd be very very cautious as
you get into this levels, this level
here address into sort of that previous
day high, that gray box, edge of value
area low on the current session. You got
24hour VW up there, deep pullback flow
zones and previous day high all in one
level. If I was long, I'd be taking
profits into that
because I would expect sellers to defend
it. And what you want to see,
all right,
is this hold up. All right, you need
them to defend this area here for you to
get this kind of move. If they can't
defend this and we build liquidity out
here, we will move lower.
[snorts]
We did just reclaim IB. So, we literally
went from
Look above IB and fail. View up. View up
IB. IB. Maybe to VW up. Maybe we'll see
what happens here. You can see it's a
big pivot. Huge, huge level here.
[snorts]
It's starting to see some selling coming
in at these levels like I talked about.
Watch that New York open. If they leave
New York open, we're going to come back
down towards initial balance low.
Very cautious here as a long dude. Very,
very cautious.
The main trend is down after a failed
breakout. We're underneath that previous
day high. That can change if we reclaim
those levels of defending New York open
here.
>> [sighs]
>> Co cough, man. Feel like I have half of
the year with this thing.
There's a battle here. You can see it.
starting to battle over these levels.
For me, I'd still be short biased,
honestly. Like, it's it's been a strong
sell.
until we put in a higher low down here
to confirm like we're done selling. I'd
be somewhat cautious.
That news just dropped.
You're losing New York now. You're
losing the New York Open now. Be very,
very careful.
If they can't defend the New York Open,
this blue line, I'd be very, very
careful. Bulls will try and do this move
here. If bears defend this and you get
stuck under here, they'll look to rotate
and close that gap. You do have
divergence. Spy and ES did close the
gap, but like I said, I would be uh very
very careful here.
Putin talks have just started.
Trump to announce proposed roll back in
auto fuel economy rules on Wednesday.
Meeting with GM and Ford
major battle here, folks.
This is your London high kind of zone.
>> [snorts]
>> It's buy coming back down towards that
680. I want to see if it holds the
retest or not.
It just rejected the old pivot into sort
of 81 8150. So far, it's holding PDC.
We traded under it, traded back over
PDC, just pulled back. Just found a bid
at PDC, which is pretty pretty good move
from SPY to hold that. It could be an
indication that it's we could follow
them on the cues.
Lots of them mag everyone but Tesla now
green again.
I'd still be watching that sort of third
that last previous 30 minute bar we got
thick. So five
525 up to 550 525 to 550.
The previous 30 minute bar basically
it's a big V shape. All right. And this
is the level.
So how they act here is important. Do
they resell that or do they get an
escape?
I'd be looking for potential shorts
here. If we reject it or if we break
above and hold it, you could play the
long back into the range. I don't think
I'm going to play that today.
Big rejection here
back down to that New York open again.
Big rejection. Big rejection on supply
as well. Still holding PDC
>> [snorts]
>> I don't think sellers have given up yet.
I think it's too early to say that
the day is young.
I'm watching this 680 on uh spiders.
This is nothing more than a pullback to
resell into in my mind until it proves
otherwise. I wouldn't say that the
sellers are giving up yet. Let's have a
look what that lower day looked like. I
mean there was
so a little bit of excess under 17s but
not a whole lot. But we did flip like we
got that delta flip aggressively but
it's too early too early to say that
Peter we're uh you know you're 10
minutes till lunch.
Just want to wait and see how we act or
react. Just hope it doesn't happen in
one big candle like it's been happening.
Don't give me a chance.
One more leg up into here. This is what
I'm waiting for. Waiting to see if we
can get into here. If it offers me a
trade once we get into there.
Feel like I'm going to run out of time
though because it's taking so long. It's
going to come into here into lunch,
which is not going to be ideal.
Can we get uno duo and a fedo?
Should be nice. We'll see.
I think I'm going to run out of time.
Trump's talking, is he?
China.
That's such skewed uh stat saying that
it's the biggest online sales we've ever
done for a Black Friday. It's also the
most expensive Black Friday we've ever
had. So, are you going to include
inflation in that or we just going to
pretend inflation doesn't exist?
I think we're going to run out of time
for the next trade. If he's talking and
we got lunch coming up 7 minutes,
probably just going to sit flat here on
the rest
and just
you're down here much more. You're going
to pull the uh current value area load
down. Spending quite a bit of time here
now.
I think there should be a rule with
politics for how long
you're allowed to be in power for before
like you have to stop talking about the
previous people. It's the same in the
UK. Labour's still blaming everything on
the Conservatives. He's still blaming
everything on Biden. It's like, how long
do you need to be in power before, you
know,
let's focus on what we're doing now.
It's not blame the people before
anymore.
It's just the easiest uh scapegoat for
everything. Whether it's true or not, it
doesn't matter. It's just nonstop.
He's talking about car car investment in
the US at the moment.
Direct quote from Trump. I'm right about
everything.
All right. So, here's a retest of this
level. I don't think I'm going to take
this just because because of time. I'm
running out of time now. But here's the
level. The second leg. This is the
retest. How we act here, I think becomes
really important for the remainder of
the day. If we reclaim this, you're
going to squeeze back into all of the
range. If you reject this up here, then
I wouldn't rule out, if not a retest of
the lows, well, if not a new low, a
retest of the low at the very least is
what I'm trying to say. Wouldn't rule
that out.
What's that previous day high again? 46
46 somewhere around there. We're
starting to see some reaction here. Some
sellers trying to come in here and
defend it.
So, seeing that second leg, this is what
I talked about, a second leg up. This is
the area of interest for me, but that's
just timing wise. Four minutes left. Do
I really want to pull the trigger with 4
minutes left into lunch?
Slacking off power now.
about pattern rates. Getting rid of pal.
Big battle here on the on the butt.
Big battle.
So, they're trying to sell this
aggressively here. There is a there is
someone trying to soak it in front of
500,
but I'd be very very careful. This is
the area where I'd be thinking about
getting short. So, I'd be very careful.
Those of you who are long off the
rotation, you better have sold a big
chunk of your position.
Big battle here.
You can see it on the volume shelf here.
We're starting to build out a bit a
shelf here at 508 down to 490. You lose
that and you wash.
Can you say that?
[snorts]
Wow.
They're testing the edge of this range
now, folks.
Seeing weak bit of weakness coming here.
This is the edge of this range. If they
let go of this, they might trade to the
other side of this range, sort of the
90s. If they lose the 90s, you would not
rule out a new lower day. I'm being
deadly serious. If you lose the 90s, do
not rule out a new lower day.
done. See, this is exactly what I talked
about.
It's just going to be a time thing.
Retested this. I think it's very, very
probable. We talked about this gray area
here being the area where bears will
want to defend, didn't we?
Uh, it's not uh it's not the the 50.
It's It's rolling fibs.
They're trying to lift it. This is
interesting battle.
It's an interesting battle.
He's talking about a Zenic. He called it
the fat drug for fat people.
Oh, you got
[laughter]
this guy doesn't give a [\h__\h] All right.
All
right, new hourly. This is what I mean.
You're into lunch now. Volume's gone,
guys. You'll see volume start to taper.
You might get like a shove one way or a
shove the other, but
I know it's amazing. So much material.
And for South Park,
they need to do another special. It
would be hilarious now with the with
everything that's happened.
He's a funny [\h__\h] man.
He is a funny [\h__\h]
All right, I'm out of here, folks. Was a
decent day in the end. Not too bad. It's
uh
pretty ugly market.
This is what you call a range rotating
market.
There's your breakout.
There's your trap. There's a straight
reclaim. That's ugly. There's your
failed move higher. And there's your
straight puke. And now we're coming back
to test. This is your pivot. This is
your your overunder for the day. Above
this, bulls maybe can form some form of
rotation. Below this, bears can try and
test that down here. But edge is gone.
Like
the edge is gone. And I wouldn't be
surprised to see this just taper off
again. The market doesn't it doesn't
really know what it wants to do. That's
what you've got to understand. Like do
you really want to be a new money long?
Just think about institutions.
Do you want to be a new money long when
all we've done is do that after that?
No.
That is your new money long trigger. A
hold down here. And that is the problem
that you're going to continue to see in
this market until they offer the
pullback and we come to a decent level
and we see big money and big inflow come
in here. Then this is just going to keep
doing the same thing. Fail breakout,
failed breakout, fail breakout, failed
break. It's just going to keep doing the
same thing. Rotation, rotation,
rotation, rotation. And it's unfortunate
and it's very very common for December
to see that. So, I'd be very very
cautious being too biased in this market
until you see some form of higher time
frame uh alignment. And what I mean by
that is a daily pullback which holds and
an hourly pullback which confirms a long
or vice versa. Until you see that, I'd
be very very very cautious about getting
overly bullish or overly bearish in the
market. It will build liquidity until
it's finished. [snorts]
And um yeah, see you guys tomorrow
morning. Nice day in the end. Thank
thank goodness for that. At least we got
something after waiting all day. But uh
I don't know if we're going to get
something this afternoon, but I'll be in
Discord anyway. Those in Discord, I'll
pop in there in a bit and um we'll have
a look at some key levels and I'll set
some price alerts. I'll leave that price
alert on 680. That's going to continue
to be key. We're well above that now.
681 on the spiders. So that gamma level,
it's a big big level worth watching. All
right, folks. Peace and love. See you
tomorrow morning. And don't forget
today, last day of the Apex sale if you
want that 80% off. I doubt there'll be
another sale for a little bit. Only
reason being they've extended this
twice. Okay, they've already twice
extended it. Take care.