Morning, morning, morning everyone. How
are we all doing? Hopefully you had a
great Thanksgiving.
Some nice time off the charts
and are relaxed and comfortable feeling
good back on the charts. We got one
month left to close out this year
strong. We've had a great year and uh
let's just make sure we stick to the
same rules as always. close this week
out and close this uh year out really
strong. All right, let's have a look at
the charts then because uh I haven't
been here for a little bit of time since
being off with COVID. As you can see
last week, Monday, Tuesday, Thursday,
Friday or Wednesday, Friday I should
say, just a low volume drift up. You can
see it down here at the bottom of the
screen. Make sure you can see all that.
All right, very low volume drift higher.
All right, one thing to be aware about,
there were no bears coming in, but there
was in fact no one joining in at all
really last week, which is why you had
decent range. And we've taken out some
of the pivots, filling in some of this
imbalance, and this was the area that
we've been getting stuck in. Right over
the 500s is the key level. you will see
last night is the first time we tapped
into over those 500s into the 61 or
golden zone fib and uh well there were
some sellers waiting up there passively
quite clearly on top of that you had the
uh JPY bonds breaking out which I've
talked extensively about on here. Um I'm
really looking for that trade to come if
it's going to come to fruition over the
next two weeks. So, but definitely
as it was breaking out last night, you
saw uh a little bit of fear enter the
tape and um off the low volume pulling
back. Where are we pulling back to?
Well, you can see this cluster here. All
right, this is uh very interesting here.
You have the 5day, 20-day, and 50-day
all at exactly the same point. And guess
what? We bottomed off it. All right. So,
this is a very interesting area to watch
as an overunder as this week develops. I
don't want to be too aggressive on a
Monday after a low volume week. There's
nothing to say they don't shove it all
the way down here. There's nothing that
to say that they don't find a bid to
take it higher. All right, so we just
have to wait and see. What we can say is
there were no bears there last week. But
I'd say this week I'd be looking for
dips to hold either where we've held or
sort of down into these 975s. All right,
if we come down into here and we can
produce a daily higher low because we
haven't done that yet because we haven't
pulled back. If it is a big if if we can
do that, I'd consider a bullish rotation
up to current high of week. And if we
really get going all the way back up
here, remember we've got relative
strength in the uh spy or the ES versus
this because we've been rotating into
some more defensive sectors which are
playing catch-up. So the breadth is
actually getting a little bit bigger
which can be positive for the market. If
this market just wants to keep slamming
down, then you know this is just nothing
more than a wave up to be slammed back
down. But this is what I'm saying. We're
going to have to be somewhat cautious
this week. So, I'm watching these areas
here.
And uh I'm watching those 500s. All
right, let's get into the hourlys. We
can see a bit more in detail.
There was actually a very nice trade
just set up then while I was talking,
unfortunately. But there we go. Okay.
So, in the hourlys down here, this is
previous week's profile.
All right. You can see we're currently
and we just now rejected previous week
value area high. All right. So, I'd be
watching this developed profile as well,
but basically 300. You can see we
created some liquidity here at 300. This
would be on Friday last week, I guess,
before breaking out. Failing. This is
the big supply zone coming back under.
We just failed to reclaim this level
here. This is a level of interest. This
is your probably your overunder
this morning. All right. We can draw it
in something like this,
right?
One more time we're under it.
Potentially fade back down into this
rotation into the 200s. If we let go of
200, you can see we get very, very thin
on the previous week profile. Right.
Make sure you can see this. Yeah. All
right. So, we're currently rejecting
this. How we act here is going to be
key. Is it going to be a look below and
fail or are we going to come under, look
below, stay heavy, and complete a
rotation down into this sort of 930. And
from there, I'd be potentially looking
for longs, but again, it would need to
put in some structure to come back up.
I'm less interested in longs all the way
down here this week. Um, but would not
surprise me. But if we're going to do
some kind of break and come down here,
that's very heavy momentum. Yes, bulls
stepped in there last week. But really,
you'd want this or this to hold for
bullish structure to come back up. All
right. I wouldn't really want it to see
it visit previous week value area low if
I was a bull, which I'm not really, but
we will see. I'm happy to join in on the
bullish side as we set up. All right, so
those are your levels. Make sure you're
taking note of all these previous week
and previous day levels. They will
become key, especially as we start
getting through this session. But you
can see the volume that we created last
week. That's what I'm watching as my
overunders this morning.
And let's get into the lower time frame
and start looking at everything else. So
you can see really this is your
rotation.
All right. This is based on the previous
week's profile. Here's your rotation.
All right. So look above and fail. Look
below and fail. Look above and hold.
Look below and hold. All right. Look
above and fail. Look below and fail.
Those are the moves. And in here you've
got a 250 point rotation. All right.
You're pinned in here. Fade the tops.
Fade the bottoms. Fade the tops. Fade
the bottoms until it proves otherwise.
All right. That's what you're seeing at
the moment. But we are gapping down off
that JPY
bond trade. All right, that's why see
all sorts of traders talking about why
cryptos gapping down. That's why that's
where the pressure came from. It's not
from some news article or something like
that. It's genuine sell pressure.
Okay, let's have a look at some of the
other indexes a second. Yes, right.
Remember we had relative strength here
to five minute. Same kind of story. You
can see we're finding some bid support
off here for now. Um, but that's most
certainly a failed look above again. So
860s, no acceptance above previous day
high, previous day close. That was a big
wash. You've had one bounce, two bounce.
Here's now your range. All right. So
very, very similar. So your range you're
looking at, you might as well just call
it 30 down to 800. So 30 point range
here. All right. Look below and fail.
look above and fail. Those are probably
going to be the easy trades. Otherwise,
if we stay heavy, know you've got
liquidity to aim for. 88s.
That probably needs developing a bit.
Hang on. Let's clean this up a little
bit.
Yeah, you're way too big, my friend.
Right.
That's what I'd be looking at at ES. And
we can put a block in up here as well.
900s.
So, the same thing, exactly the same
thing.
Uh, let's have a quick look at the
spiders. Very, very clean on the
spiders. Big gap down.
I'd be watching to see how we act at
this level here on the spiders. If we're
going to stay heavy, think about how
much you squeezed last week without
really putting in much structure. All
right, this was Friday last week, but as
we came into Monday, there's that first
dip and grind and grind and grind and
grind and grind and grind and grind and
if we're going to see a failure to
reclaim, we're probably at least going
to come to here. All right, so that's
what I'd be watching. And if they fail
there, we'll come deeper.
Okay, but once we uh come to here, it's
possible that we continue this trend. If
they let go, maybe down here, it's still
possible that they continue the trend
up, but this some of this needs to be
washed out. That's a strong buying
channel of no volume like we've talked
about.
Q's exactly the same like we talked
about. You can see they're back testing
that RBS zone. Let's have a quick look
at the Dixie. O
crushed a little bit there as gold
popping them. Yeah, that's a nice
recovery on gold.
VIX back into these teens.
VIX is due a bid. All right, it is due a
bid just because once we come up to
these 30s and we just go straight down,
this is not really normal. Normally,
you'd see like a retest like that. So
maybe today we might get something like
that. Doesn't have to be the whole way
up, but I'd be watching VIX for a hold
of 17s.
It's down. Yeah, I'll be watching. Yeah,
1740, 1750 is a hold of that. A break
over 1875 is where we're going to see
strength come in. Make sure these are
all correct.
This up a bit.
[cough] But starting to see that sort of
turn around on the VIX at least for now.
At least for now. But I have to see if
it can hold pull back into 1740s. All
right, let's have a look at the mag
range here at the highs in Apple.
Looks pretty good. It looks pretty good.
Obviously, there's a gap down. There's a
gap down in the whole market, but we're
just in a range here on Apple. Nothing
else,
right? Seeing as a bit of a safe haven
in the Mag 7 at the moment because it
doesn't have too much exposure
to AI. All right. So where they've
lacked the growth this year, it also
means they lack the exposure. So just
some consolidation at the highs at the
moment.
Amazon
pretty much flat. Slight gap down.
That's looking strong. And just zoom
out.
All right. Amazon's got to get back
above this level here, 38. All right.
That's where the real strength will come
in.
All right. It needs to get back above
this and prove itself if it wants to
move higher. Otherwise, this is just a
retracement which can be sold back into.
So, I'd be very cautious about where
you're trading Amazon. I don't think
it's opening up in a particular great
area right now based on higher time
frame. Possible sell from here to retest
uh 28s to 25s probably. All right,
Google
consolidating at highs. Yes, lower highs
and lower lows, but we all know what
this can be. All right. If it wants to
keep going, that's alltime highs, is it
for good? Just want to double check.
Yes, it is. All right. So, it's got some
back fill if it really wants to
come back into the 300s. Have we looked
back there since we broke out? And when
did we break out? Monday last week. Same
story. Hasn't looked back. So, we would
consider a back fill here. Yeah, we
would absolutely consider a back fill
here on Google. So, again, I wouldn't be
putting risk on on that right now.
It's done the move. Let's see if it can
back fill and offer a better setup. But
a slight gap down on Goo Meta O. That's
a nastier gap down. All right. You can
see up here it's left balls trapped at
highs.
Already faded underneath that next pivot
and it's getting stuck at it. So if Meta
keeps failing 640, there's probably a
deeper wash. I am long on this. I think
it's from 580 something. I'm small size.
I bought it all the way down here. Yeah,
580 something only small size. Just got
a feeler on it, guys. So, about 60 $60
up on that, which is nice. Um,
same story here on Microsoft, right?
Trapping bulls at these highs right now,
coming back down into a level where it
can find consolidation. Remember, tops
can take time to develop, right? This
can take time to build out this week if
it is going to need a deeper wash. They
don't all have to do it. the, you know,
the sound of the bell on a Monday
morning. It can take time for some of
this to develop. Nvidia, that doesn't
look too good.
That does not look too good. Let me zoom
out. All right, everyone looking for
that Nvidia recovery. Jensen trying to
hold everything up, but uh
we keep failing reattempts here. So,
where was last week? Monday.
Yeah,
I'm not too convinced on Nvidia right
now.
That is getting sold into on every push
still. Yes, it's basing out a little
bit, but uh it's probably quite a long
way down.
Just zoom out here. Give this a second.
Yeah, you want to be careful there. You
want to be careful. There's your top.
And every attempt to get back into that
range is being sold into so far. If we
start losing 64s, uh, we can come and
back fill some of this. Right. So, every
time we've come down into 60s, 70s and
60s, it's found a bid so far. But the
fact that we're not reclaiming 95s is
saying a lot right now. It's attempted
one, two, three times doesn't look too
great to me. Tesla
just trying to build out liquidity here,
isn't it? Very simple. trying to build
out liquidity back up here to go and
break these highs. And that's what it's
looking to do.
Is that an old gap? Has it filled it?
Yeah, filled an old gap. Consolidation
looks okay.
Definitely a failed attempt on Friday.
So maybe pull back into 420, which has
been the level for as long as I can
remember now. As you're over under.
Let's have a look at Oracle. Just give
me an idea of Gordon name as
AMD.
Big gap down on AMD.
Still holding range there. It's tricky
out there, folks. It's definitely
tricky.
I think for me, I just want to let this
develop this morning. You've got the
levels in here. Like we said, that
previous week value area high was
probably a short while I was talking.
There you go. So, it's rejecting value
from last week so far. [snorts]
So, we're inside previous week's value,
rejecting the highs from last week. We
are outside previous days value. So, we
might see some further weakness to start
the day, but we will have to just see
how we act because we're in these ranges
from the previous sessions. All right.
right here.
And I kind of just want to let it open
and make its decision. Let's say
we can decide what's next. Oh, I forgot
my uh
forgot my water. Good morning. Not going
to get a chance to go through all the
good mornings. Market's now open. Let's
just see what we get here. So, all of
the mag gapping down here this morning.
Give this a minute or two to get through
the opening print and then we'll go from
there. [cough]
These same lines drawn on Ninja before I
forget.
[snorts]
Not able to get back towards that
previous uh week value area high yet on
the morning drive. Failing short of it.
Not able to get up to previous day low.
Not able to get up to the viewups yet.
Get an anchor on my screen as well.
Big buyers coming in there and getting
sold into as well. That's strong
selling.
So 85
>> [sighs]
>> not taking out that pivot yet into the
300s.
Strong selling. Like I just said, that
is very strong selling. Big buys came in
at the highs and they just got
absolutely sold into very, very hard.
Here's the New York open all the way
back down then. And this range is pretty
decent.
So volatility is still present right
now.
Holding that New York low so far.
Big selling here. O, big wash
underneath that New York low.
And are they going to take out these
pivots and come back down and visit
here? It's a shame. I would have liked
to have been short up here. I just
wanted to give it a minute or two to
redevelop. Uh, seeing as I've not really
stared at the screens for at least a
week now.
You're underneath that New York open so
far. So, uh 50s basically that was your
open shove up this morning. Got sold
into trap buyers at the highs. And let's
see if they resell these into 50s here
or if they're going to squeeze this back
out. Amazon's found a bid. Everything
else looking weak so far this morning.
Tesla 1% down. Nvidia 1.65% down.
Microsoft 1.1%
down. Meta 1% down. Google 0.75%
down. Apple quarter% down. Amazon has
found a big a bid quarter of a percent
up. Everything else looking pretty weak
right now. So, let's just let this
develop. So, reclaiming that New York
open. Maybe they go and test back to
where we just came from again.
What is this? Is an old V up. No, it's
previous day low then. Is it? Okay. I
need to get my bearings. It's not been
here for a little bit.
[cough]
There we go. It's in the New York open
reclaiming it. Maybe comes and revisits
this. I want to see how we act up here.
Previous week value area high and maybe
all the way up into 350s. That's where I
didn't want to get short this first move
this morning.
[snorts]
All
>> [snorts]
>> right, retesting these levels again,
these 300ish.
And if they get over three, let's just
call it 350. That'll be either the look
above and fail or it will be a squeeze
and breakout above here. So, just
waiting to see how we operate down there
or up there, I should say.
Just rotation so far this morning. Just
seeing edges play both sides. Didn't
quite make it to the blue box. Didn't
quite make it to the red box yet.
[snorts]
Delta positive so far this morning other
than that pullback candle.
a little bit stuck up here. Amazon still
going. Good. Great bid on Amazon.
2/3 of a percent up.
Not the rest of the market is not
joining in yet. Tesla's trying to get
back. So that's trying to find a bid as
well, which is helping the mag out. Same
story on Nvidia, but none of them have
gone red to green yet. They won't take
too much. They They are attempting it.
There's no doubt about it.
[cough]
Messi here.
This is where that big buyer came in at
85ish
and got stuck. Let's see if they hold
him.
and allow him to uh drift this up higher
into the 300s to 350s.
Somewhat messy here this morning, isn't
it? Just inside the old range. Not
getting above previous week's value area
high.
tempting to hold that pivot on a 30
minute but not not convinced yet. I am
not convinced.
Tesla are having a good go here. It's
trying to get that red to green.
Can they get back up into sort of gloex
would be the question I guess
struggling at least 300 so far. No
acceptance above 300 so far. Back down
towards me. Up we go.
reattempting 300s here. Tesla now red to
green. Tesla's gone red to green, folks.
[snorts]
Not a lot else happening
at previous week value area high and
then through that. Can they have an
attempt at uh 350 will be the attempt if
they can get there?
There's the attempt to get sort of
somewhat up into it
into the red box at glowbox level ahead
or above I should say Sorry.
Amazon looking good. Test are now red to
green. Rest of the market still not
there.
trying to lift it. They're trying to get
it up to those levels. Not there yet.
Still holding above 300s.
See what this market wants to do.
Very slow here this morning.
300's your over under right now.
Watching these 300s to see if we're
going to see weakness come in here back
down towards these VWOPS now.
Yeah, I'm watching this red box to see
if I want to fade it. Sorry, someone
asking what am I doing? I mean, it's a
Monday morning after a very low volume
drive higher. Um, we're in a range. I'm
waiting to see if we take one side of
liquidity first to see if there's
weakness coming in. So, if we come up
here and I see strong failures or I see
buyers get trapped at the highs, which
we did just see into 22s, but I really,
you know, I'm interested to see if we
can take out these 40s, then I'll be
looking for that fade. Right? So, if you
were here for the pre-market show, what
did we talk about? Look above and fail.
Look below and fail. Look above and
fail. Look below and fail for that turn
in. Those are my sort of first thoughts
at the moment.
We didn't quite get up to where I wanted
and you're starting to see them slam
that door a little bit early. So maybe
the sign was there this morning. Same
kind of thing. But here you go. So
that's why I said 300's your over under
your previous week value area high.
We've just gone back above it, failed,
come back below, back to the New York
open. You can see all we're doing here
is building out a range. We're not
getting above previous week value area
high. We've not come back below the New
York open. Right? This is the range. If
they keep selling this, we're going to
rotate into here. So there might be a
short coming soon, but just think about
what we've done. This is all we've done
this morning. All right? There's no real
trade in there for me. There's not that
much edge. I want to fade up here to the
blue box. But once we came here, I
really just wanted them to take that
out.
I probably just missed a trigger there
to be honest. That downside
probably missed a trigger there. It's
okay.
Yeah, 10 o'clock
uh 9 9:45 and 10 o'clock, isn't it? I
put it in Discord this morning. Let's
have a look. [snorts]
Yes. Uh PMI 9:45 and 10:00 and then PAL
tonight at 8:00 8:00 p.m. There's your
weakness. I probably just missed that
while I was talking.
That was it. All right. There's the
grind up. That's the look into supply.
There's the failure. There's the failed
to reclaim previous week value. And back
down we go to blue box.
I probably just missed.
It's a good trade actually. It's about
60 points in that.
Oh, but Matt, why why are we playing
these games and not catching up again?
Yeah, just in balance right now. I would
say if you zoom out you will see that we
will get further moves if we get
sustained auctions underneath the blue
box for a rotation back down or
sustained auctions above here. All right
for a move back up towards those 500s.
But right now we're just trading between
red box and blue box. That's all you've
got right now. That's all that's
available.
How am I feeling? Not too bad. I'm I'm
very weak still, but uh pretty pretty
much better, but just not not full of
energy yet.
A little bit of COVID left, I guess. But
uh just the weakness, nothing else.
Other than that, I feel all right.
Just trading around that New York open.
Should have, would have, could have on
the fade for that. But look, all the
flow zones flat. New York flat. New York
view up flat. We're in 95 points of
range so far. Not too bad. Back down
towards this blue box. So, red box to
blue box like we talked about
pre-market. I'd say the best move was
this. We should have paid this. All
right, let that come in. That's the only
time today we've had decent RR for this
move down into here. They might very
well bid back off this and reclaim this
and go back that side if they want.
Tesla back red again and selling harder
now. So three quarters of a percent
down. So that went red to green and they
shut the door on it. So worth noting
that Amazon pulling back now as well.
We've got couple minutes left in news.
Here's low of day expanding low of day
now. And if they want to come down into
190s, they will. That's your uh GlobeEx
low.
So 200s here like we said 190s would be
that GloEx low. I'm kicking myself for
not taking that trade.
They keep rejecting New York open
without taking Gloex and I think you'll
probably get down into it.
So we missed GlobeEx high failed the
rotation for GloEx high. Got buyers got
stuck up there coming for GlobeEx low
which is the orange line on your screen.
So, if the next push fails the New York
open, the blue line, and I would imagine
they would go for Globeex low, but yeah,
you've got news coming out here in 50
seconds. Just be aware.
We did leave some delta stuck above
315s. So, there are buyers stuck up
there.
And again,
they tried to join in 260s to 280s and
got sold into.
And I'll say there are sellers stuck at
the lows right now into 214. So just
that rotation that rotational market
very very present this morning. Probably
a lot of people like me just waiting to
see how we develop this week before we
go risk on
especially after a thin volume week.
Yeah. If you just zoom out remember the
high time frame
why we're looking at this. We just think
about what we did in the previous week,
right? You got a node here and a node
here and here's the low vault. And we're
just trading between these until we get
a look below and fail or look above and
fail or look below and a wash or a look
above and a squeeze. Then we're just
going to keep building liquidity in this
sort of 150 odd point range. Right?
That's all we're doing right now is
creating liquidity
that test this New York open. So if they
fail this, there is potentially a trade
down to here. But got this news should
be dropping right now. So, who knows?
Get that up.
Came in pretty much in line. 52.2 versus
51.9. That's pretty much in line for the
manufacturing.
Let's squeeze all the way back up. Now,
we come and test this wick high here at
85. Like we said, the buyers did try 65
to 80s. And if we get through 80s,
potentially squeeze back up towards a
higher day as we just go from one side
to the other side. Neither side
completing a rotation. So, no rejection
off B off uh New York open straight back
into no man's land right now. Nothing
I'm seeing here that's making me want to
pull the trigger yet. There's probably
one B setup I've seen today and that's
it.
Nvidia now red to green.
Give you a read out of the market. Tesla
now 0.81% down. Nvidia half% up.
Microsoft 1% down. Meta 1 and a third of
percent down. Google 1 and a half% down.
Amazon half% up. Amazon just under 1%
and Apple just under 1% down.
Market needs to make up its mind. It's
going to take some time here by the
looks of it.
Sorry, I keep smashing that mic.
Back up to that previous week value
high. And are they going to squeeze
through this back to higher day?
I'm not too interested in this right
now. edge to edge without taking any
liquidity.
So if they want to complete this
rotation, they should come up to 350s.
Same as here. They didn't complete the
rotation to 190s.
They got stuck
this liquidity building phase right now.
Can this market find a bid?
Here we go. New high day then. All
right. Can it complete rotation now into
here? 350. If it takes out 350 and
squeezes, I will watch previous day
value area low.
to see if we reject that from Friday.
Not going to give it too much credit
given that there was above all volume
traded, but I will respect it.
So, there's your higher day.
Still not taking GloEx out. I would like
us to take that sort of London pivot
high out from GlobeEx at 240 250 and
then see how we react. They fall short
again. The same trade as earlier, but
it's not not looking very nice.
Just rotation here from one side to the
other. You can see the box. It's all
we're doing. We're trading box to box.
All right. Well, while this market fats
around, I'm going to grab my bottle of
water from next door. Be right back.
It should try and complete a rotation
there.
Can't say I'm surprised about the action
this morning. This was uh
always likely to be the case.
Can they get up here? They're trying to
hold previous week value high to come
and clean out GlobeEx 44s and then
previous day value area high. And you
have another 10 minutes till the next
news piece. Come on. Put that
25 230 previous week area high. Oh,
really?
330. Do you mean 25,000?
230. Oh, you have it lower. Well, I
don't know. I've got it. It It is where
where it is for me. I'm not going to
change it. But yeah, there is always
discrepancies between the two for sure,
which is stupid really when it's based
off volume traded off a centralized
exchange like the CME. There should
never be a difference, but there we go.
All right, they should complete this
rotation now and take out this 44s here,
basically the 50s. And then I'll be
watching to see if they fade these
levels from Friday.
cumulative delta. Um, yeah, you can use
it. I don't really use it too much.
It's good for trending environments, but
I'm not too interested outside of that.
I'm more interested in delta getting
stuck in between each candles, but you
can use it. Sometimes it will give you
divergence, like if we're making higher
highs here and delta isn't, which is
what I am seeing on a fiveminute chart
for now. Shows a bit of weakness in the
tape.
Unbelievable that they still have not
taken out.
Come on people.
They're going to wait for 10, aren't
they? at the moment. Wait for that new
hourly and 4hour bar.
Uh if we find a squeeze above Gloex,
then yeah, I'd be looking at 76s, 400s,
what's the top level up here? And 40s.
If you get a squeeze, if there's
acceptance above here, you'd be looking
for a drive into these. If they want to
close the gap, the gap fill will be
480s. It's quite a big ask, but
it's not out the question. And uh we can
still sell that based on an hourly
possible that bears still come in versus
440. So, anything possible right now in
this market. Quite a intricate part. TPT
code is flow zone. The links are down
below. Flowzone for TPT, not FCT. If you
use code flow zone, it will get you 30%
off right now.
Come on, market. You got to go and take
Globeex out. We can't do anything
otherwise.
Vick's coming into these uh 1740s like
we talked about.
Let's see if it finds a bid here on the
VIX or not. If not and it goes for gap
fill, this market can start squeezing.
Like we said, the red box is key. Look
above and fail or, you know, base above
for a squeeze. Yeah, sorry about that.
Yeah, code flow zone.
It won't change it. I might ask for the
fifth millionth time this week.
Okay, Globe's coming up. So, if you did
take the long, hopefully it gets there
for you. If you got long off VWAP, this
higher low, your location's not ideal,
but if you took this, you're looking for
this and a squeeze out into here. So, if
you get this, that would be TP1, TP2,
TP3, TP4, TB5 would be gap fill. If you
got all the way up there, which would be
the yellow line above you, all the way
up here, I'd be very cautious as we get
into here that it doesn't do a look
above and fail.
Still not taking out. Incredible.
Are they actually going to wait for the
new 4hour candle? 5 minutes left. Surely
they just take that out.
Would I recommend Lucid? Yeah, their new
their new one looks good. Lucid Flex. I
did actually buy one to test it out.
very much like funded next code FCT will
work there for you as well. Okay, GloEx
now taken. All right, so if you're in
this long, you're just runners all these
squeeze out. So these blue and red lines
and yellow and yellow line is your
ultimate target if it really wanted to
get going. If we base above here, we can
think about that long. But I've been
very very cautious about something that
shoves up, right, and then fails back in
this range here. So ba basically 320s,
right? Balls need to defend 320s.
Anything that's a look above fails under
320, rejects it, it's going to come
right back down to the other side again.
Why is energy pumping? Well, energy
always pumps this time of year anyway.
So, you've got uh rotations
plus what's what's energy going to be
used for?
Think about all the data centers.
everything we're doing with AI, it all
is going to require energy.
It's probably a bit of a safer bet than
a lot of other stuff right now because
guarantee the grid is not ready and they
are going to require a lot of energy.
Whether that be traditional types,
nuclear based, especially for all these
data centers that they're building out,
they all going to require energy. So if
you don't want to put money in the
builder, don't want to put money in the
chips and you can put money money in the
energy sector. And plus, as we get as it
gets colder into winter, we use more
energy anyway, which means historically
Q4 and Q1 are better better times to buy
energy, to trade energy.
Okay, Victor still failing. 1722s now
needs to find a bid here. If it doesn't,
gap fill is possible all the way down to
1650s and below.
Okay. into or testing previous day value
area lows. This is the previous this is
Friday's value area. All right. So, so
far this is Friday's value area. If we
reject this and we reject 320s, we will
move lower. Balls will need to hold 320.
Now
there or thereabouts. They will want to
hold 320s.
Advertising above right now. There's
there's a spoofer on the tape today,
folks.
There is a spoofer on the tape again.
They're walking this up right now.
Can we get acceptance into the previous
day's value? At the moment, the answer
is no. There's no acceptance inside
Friday's value area. Dips this morning
have been bought, but we didn't take out
GlobeEx, but there was a higher low
there. Dips have been bought. We are now
drifting higher. I would expect bears to
come in soon somewhere in here if they
don't already. And uh then we have to
see how we
will then be the battle. The wherever
the bear is coming down to 320 will be
the battle.
We're going to test these 320s. It seems
sample back towards it. How long? For 90
seconds. I'm just going to let this hour
and 4 hour play out.
And that kill candle that we had at 8:00
p.m. last night. All right. The
transition of that will be that previous
day value area high. I am interested
what happens when we come up here.
Range still good. Even with the VIX
dropping down, the range is still good.
170 points so far in the first 30
minutes this morning. It's not bad at
all. Still money to be made both sides
here. Right. They are trying to hold
these sort of 320s, 340s.
Does Fridays hold much weight after
being a half day? I think it was a whole
day. Um, but it was very, very light in
volume. I mean, I'd say none of last
week holds as much weight as normal
because the volume was so light, which
is why there's some caution trading this
morning. Everyone's just waiting to see
how we test out each levels and do we
cut through like a hot knife through
butter or do we find bids, right? So,
here's the push
on that news. Previous day, no
acceptance inside previous day's value
yet. No acceptance inside previous days
value yet. remember. I think shorts will
come in somewhere here. If they're going
to come in at all, if they're going to
come in, that's where they're going to
look to come in.
The range isn't bad, but it feels slow.
Tape feels slow today.
It definitely feels slow today. At least
in my mind it does.
Tesla is trying to go back red to green
again. Nvidia is and is holding,
but we are stuck at previous day value
area low. We're not finding acceptance
inside of uh
previous day's value, inside of Friday's
value so far. No acceptance inside of
Friday's value so far.
We are holding bids now above this. So
technically
this might want to hold um
actually want to redraw that 320. 340 to
320.
This here is going to be key over under
450. There is 400. There is
a battle here at these highs.
Let's get some volume on. We've been
here for long enough now.
Not you.
You can see this volume being created up
here.
Definite battle up here. Here's the sell
back down to these 40s to 20s. Now, if
they fail this, you can see the edge
like they've got thin volume node here.
Buyers will want to protect this. If we
fail this, we just go back into balance,
which will be very ugly and choppy.
Haven't
really extended enough.
Oh go. Yeah, I literally just put it on
now. I was just waiting for it to
develop a bit for the first 30 minutes.
So, still holding that low volume node.
Bulls still in control intraday but like
I said I think if bears are going to
come in it will be somewhere up here
there so far there's no acceptance into
Friday's value
tape feels very slow very very slow tape
this morning
everyone waiting for Jerome Pal tonight
at 8:00 Maybe
definitely trap some buyers above 67s
for now.
Let's just call it 70s. I'd say 70s is
key.
Some buyers got caught up there buying
the market at the highs. Not seeing
follow through since then. Just seen
that rotation sort of back test that 40
to 20 level we've talked about. Still
can't get even back up to 70s. These
buyers are not getting their way so far
that got caught up there.
Selling coming in here. This is the key
level. This blue box. If we go under
that, we're going to go back into this
sort of bellshaped
profile down here. Not ideal, just
standard distribution. And we didn't
take out the lows, though. It's worth
being aware of. So, here's the flush
back down towards the 20's. Low side of
this box. It's a low volume node. Buyers
will want to defend this low volume
node. Failing to do that, failing to
hold the edge will cause problems for
them.
The OC shifted up high now.
buyers really need to reclaim 70. If
they can't reclaim 70, they will get
caught at those highs, but probably got
a little bit of unfinished business.
Not seeing um any violent moves really.
Just feels
a little bit slow this morning.
They're going to retest these 70s here.
Been sold into again in front of 70s as
twice now.
And again, not getting their way through
70s.
Buy is trying again here. Nvidia
starting to go now 1% up.
70s is the level though. Buyers are
stuck above 70s for now. They will need
to get back above 70s. These buyers to
get a bigger move here.
Failing 70s in front of 70s again.
Definitely a passive seller up there
every time we've got up there and buyers
are stuck above it. If they reclaim it,
they can be squeezed potential higher,
but that's just what I'm watching it or
observing. So far, not much else to do.
Lots of volume being built out here.
We've been here a while now. This range
30 to
50 odd points. Not bad.
Tesla now flat. Gone red to green.
Invidia 1% up. Amazon half a% up. And
the rest of the market join in.
Still not getting through that 70s.
previous date value area low.
They're attempting now. They are really
really trying to shove this up now.
What a battle. Wow. Big buyer came in
there. Someone's someone keeps coming in
trying to force it up. He's not getting
his way. He is not getting his way. He's
being met at 70s every time. Massive
sellout up there at 70s. Someone's going
to lose here soon. This can't last too
much longer.
Rotating in 50 point range. Very, very
tight. Over and over and over and over
and over again.
Are they going to get all the way up the
gap? Phil, you just wonder.
The volume doesn't feel very big today.
Feels like an extension of the holiday
right now.
Just a slow drift.
Still at least 70s.
Literally nothing happening.
Come on, market. All right, they're
rejecting 70s again.
Back down towards these 40s to 20s
again.
If they lose these, we'll start
flushing. If they hold these, we're just
developing a new range up here again for
rotations.
But bid here at 50 and see if he
actually holds or they get sliced
through.
Yeah, they just bid off 50 again in
front of it. They front run it.
Vick's trying to find a bid
14 sorry 1720s needs to reclaim in 1740s
really come on market just do something
we can't trade in this tiny little range
forever
back to these 50s do they flush these
50s
if they do they'll be looking at the 20s
again we're just literally doing nothing
here.
No one wants to trade it seems today. No
one's interested in trading.
This is so slow.
The tape's literally like
it's so slow without any meaningful
moves in it.
Normally when you see this you think
drift higher. Just feels like last week.
Feels just like an extension of holiday.
Nothing's changed right now. P now up
here.
Back to the 70s.
So, we're trading 50s to 70s now. A
whole 20 points. I mean, what are you
going to do with that?
[cough]
Back to the 50s again. P again.
Oh my gosh, so slow.
Honestly, I'm getting ready to leave. If
we're going to do this for much longer,
I will leave. I'm not going to watch us
barcode like this, guys.
We need to move outside of this and we
need to do it soon for me to be
even think about staying here longer
because this feels like this market's
just gone to sleep at this point. It's
just stopped. It's completely stopped
doing anything.
Jesus Christ.
What am I watching?
Come on, do something. [\h__\h] hell,
mate.
>> [sighs]
>> Really? Did I get up for this? Are you
kidding me?
Come on. Don't care what you do. Just do
something.
All right, it's starting to break out.
Thank goodness for that. It's starting
to do something, right? Let's watch. See
how we act. Previous day point in
control. Previous day value area high.
All still in control here. We've
developed a new area here. Here's your
consolidation. Here's your edge.
Did just clear out the highs there. Not
too many buyers got stuck up there. A
few, but not really many.
Back down towards the 50s again. Is
there going to be follow through this
sign down towards the 20s? Do we snap
20s? At the moment, nothing's happening.
There we go. 30s.
Is there any continuation through the
20s or we just going to stop short and
go 50s all the way back up again?
Someone's been in 50s over and over and
over again. Right, there we go. There's
the 20s or 40s, I should say. Can we go
20s? No.
still bit in this low volume range right
now. If we leave this though and see
follow through, we'll probably come back
down into here.
Yeah, thanks Adam. Great to see that. I
was very happy with that
10k subs.
Still protecting this low volume node so
far. Volume now created up here.
Still no trade.
Not in the New York session anyway.
I did take a trade last night, folks.
So,
wasn't wasn't the biggest, but I did
trade last night.
They're trying to get to these 20s at
the moment. They want to test these 20s
out. They're into this low volume node.
They want to just do a little flush at
the moment is what they're trying. But
really how we act in here is going to be
key now. 60 now and say 60 to 70 we
check the delta.
No buyers trapped above. Yeah, above 70.
70 is still the level. Buyers are
trapped over 70s have been all morning.
Every push over there
50s again. Do they come and do retest
70s?
This is where the sellers came in.
They're going to come back up towards
E70s and test it again back inside this
volume node. Now sellers will want to
reject this. If they don't reject in
front of 70s, then buyers can take
control and we can just start creating
volume inside of yesterday's profile.
So, this is the chance. If they're going
to defend, they need to defend now.
Otherwise, they're going to get
themselves caught.
Right towards the 70s we go.
Alco still digesting excess from food
from Friday. Yes, probably.
Traders too sluggish this morning for
sure.
We're just not leaving an area, you
know. It's big move up, tapped into
blue, didn't wash wash Asia, straight up
and then just sideways.
Just is what it is. Like I said, I
didn't expect much today. I expect the
moves to come back end of the week.
Today, we'll just be feeling out each
edge.
And if we want to come all the way up
for previous day value area higher, we
can. That will fill the H1 imbalance. We
very might well sell from that point.
We're into sort of thin structure as we
get up up and over here. Anything above
yeah 350s anything above 350s gets much
thinner from Friday's profile and from
the weekly profile.
[cough]
Dreadful. [snorts]
Absolutely dreadful.
Uh, do me a favor. Smash that like
button. We will do some giveaways this
week. I will get some more Apex codes
for you all.
[snorts]
Yeah, just building liquidity.
Just building liquidity. I'm somewhat
surprised we didn't wash this first, but
uh I mean to come that close and not
take it.
Buggers. Did we do it on Yes.
Yes.
We did not. We tapped it, but we didn't
actually wash below. That's nasty.
[snorts]
[cough and clears throat]
Still stuck at these 70s.
Oh man,
this is going to drag on. This uh day is
going to be very, very slow. This is all
we're going to do, folks.
Very, very slow.
Thank you.
Oh, don't even get me started.
What a joke.
What a joke. I'm so pissed off with Zack
Brown. It's unbelievable.
[snorts] F1 was an absolute joke. never
seen such complete
stupid stupid decisions or lack of
like I've never seen it. Complete
incompetence. Like I said on my socials,
you know, it's like they're trying to
get jobs at Ferrari. That's how bad they
were at the weekend. I cannot believe
it. Every decision was terrible.
You didn't bring them in. You left them
both out. [\h__\h] stupid. So stupid to
do that. Number one. Number two, once
you realize you made the wrong decision,
you didn't rectify it.
You left them out far too long on both
stints, especially the second stint. And
then you put them on the [\h__\h] hards.
Like, put them on the softs.
So dumb. So dumb. And after they've
screwed Lando's race last weekend, well,
both of their races, but Lando is the
one that suffered. You know, if they if
he doesn't win,
then all they can only blame you could
like you got to take his head, Zack
Brown. You got to take his head. Like
it's it's on you, mate. It's on you.
Ultimately, the buck stops with you.
Okay, here you go. So, failing 70s
again. They're going to come back down
to test these 20s like we talked about.
So, no acceptance over 70s. That's the
key thing up here. Now, we haven't built
a whole lot of profile down here, a
whole lot of volume. So, you'll be
watching to see if they hold these 20s
for a rescoop and go or if there's
sustained follow through.
I saw someone say Max was stappen. I
mean, yeah, Max, he's doing pretty good
in a uh terrible car, but you know, that
was not about him. Um, McLaren have
literally gifted him the chance to have
to have the chance to win. McLaren have
gifted it to him.
Terrible.
What did you all think?
That's what I thought.
Arsenal didn't look at the races
yesterday against Chelsea either, but we
were sluggish, but not surprising gi
given the amount of games that we played
and big games that we played recently as
well.
Missing uh
our center backs didn't help.
Oh, market.
Yeah, it probably would have like it
probably would have been over a long
time ago in fairness to him because also
he wouldn't listen to bad decisions. He
would do what he wants because he's got
the experience and confidence to do it.
Tesla back green to red. This market
literally does not know what to do with
itself. We're just dancing around
volume. It's We're not seeing follow
through under 20s. We're not seeing
follow through over 70s. It is stuck.
We are completely stuck right now.
Big buyer coming in here.
just absolutely slapped it.
We actually move up off that though.
Big buyer came in right where we are now
and we've not moved higher. Worth noting
for now. It will need to accumulate here
at 40 or around there because he came in
with size hit the market and we haven't
moved higher.
Maybe we come back down to VWAP just to
punish him for doing that. I don't know.
God, I don't remember it being this slow
for a while.
Starting to see these lower highs form.
Maybe they come back down to be what
now.
I don't have a whole lot of confidence
with how we've moved this morning. I'm
going to be honest with you.
Not seeing follow through. Just seeing
uh
little ranges be created. If we start
leaving this range violently from above,
then we're going to see some downside
action. But we're not doing that yet.
VIX has found a bid at those 1720s to
1740s though.
Just like that, we're at VWAP. Will that
happen quick?
Did they bid off this or are we going to
see downside pressure now?
That buyer who marketed in, he got
himself caught there. He came in at 40s.
They're
bidding off you up buy came in at 40. So
I'm watching that level. That's his pain
point. That's where he came in.
Are they going to reclaim this range
that we've created up here?
Or are they going to reject it and
actually rotate all the way back down to
lower day?
Amazon just gone green to red or at
least green to flat. All right, Amazon's
gone green to flat at least.
Now it's gone red. So Nvidia now the
only mag green. Everything else has gone
into a cell
or at least closed its gap
back towards his 40s where that
participant got stuck.
Sorry folks, not a whole lot to do here.
If we reject this volume above, maybe
just maybe there's a rotation. But if
you look at VWAP and everything,
everything's flat right now. But if we
reject this above,
right, if we reject this, maybe there's
a rotation you need to get through TP1,
TP2, TP3, and then maybe we get that.
Otherwise, they can just fill this in,
do a dance like this for ages, create a
new volume node here, and they can do
this for a bit, this for a bit. I don't
really want to trade if we're not, we've
got no appetite to do a bigger move. I'm
not really too interested.
No, I mean I can Jack.
It's not a lot happening here either,
Jack. Really
double bottom this morning. Drive up
trap buyers at the highs above 840.
Sell back down. That's it.
Not a lot happening. The markets are are
pretty quiet.
Back to VWAP again.
We are starting to see that 840 become a
uh key level here where that buyer got
stuck.
Uh, I would say sellers just came in
here and didn't get their way. Really
lots of stops just got popped on that
last wash.
[cough]
It's just it's just SL like it's just
you remember it's end of the end of or
first day of the new month after a
holiday week on low volume. Everyone's
just feeling out what they want to do.
Like I wouldn't really want to be a
long-term buyer here, but
you know, if we are going to build out
enough liquidity, you can argue
for that buy,
right? If they can build this, I'd feel
much more comfortable. If we're going to
do complete a Santa Claus rally, I'd
want to see a wash and a go. Um, and
that's why I think you're building this
out. It's going to, if it offers one of
these later in the week, might be good.
Um, but you have to be careful that they
don't just roll it.
It's just these are really the legs,
right? So, it's just a question of can
it hold over that or not. It's we're
we're kind of in no man's land. That's
kind of the whole problem at the moment
where we're opening up. I mean, the
obvious sell straight out the newsletter
was here, wasn't it? These levels
haven't changed. These are out the
newsletter. That was the cell. There's
your look into supply fail back on the
previous day closed. There's your sell
that happened last night, right? So 500
failed last night. That's that's the
level you want to be selling at. Now
we're uh sort of 50/50 between the two
Totally
nice, Troy. Yeah, I didn't see it until
we absolutely dumped a load already. So,
I caught a small amount of it. Um, up
about 4 450 bucks per account. That's
all I got with micros.
We know that there's a buyer stuck at
40s right now. That's one thing I would
say.
It's just so slow to do anything.
Right. Sellers have the chance here to
take control of this session versus 50s
and really start dumping it. And you
just you're not seeing like the
aggression from them. Like maybe it
comes but at the moment we're not seeing
it.
I see some stronger selling there.
They're trying into this 300. There's a
bid at 300.
I'd say all the time now it stays heavy
versus that gray box above.
you know, potential shorts back down,
but
midpoint of the range on a session. It's
kind of ugly. Look how we've developed
current profile.
Like, is that 90 odd points or
something? 80 odd points.
The way it's left it is so slow. They
might just bid back up and test this.
It's It's just not a great looking kind
of thing.
Think about this. VWOPS, flow zones,
deep pullback,
previous week value area high, previous
day value area low, New York.
Everything's fairly condensed here. We
haven't left it. We haven't left it and
trapped enough for me. Like this. I like
these when we're violent, when we, you
know, aggressive. Leave a nice wick.
Trap lots of buyers. Give me something
to fade for that move back down. I'm
just not seeing that. This just feels
very controlled both ways at the moment.
The tape just feels slow. Like if we
look at map, it's not like an aggressive
tape. I can show you that can change.
It's just very slow. Like look how
controlled this is both sides. very
controlled like we saw some sellers get
stuck down here. Where's the guy at 40?
Was this him? Feel like it was before
that. Maybe it was here.
Yeah, 47. So, this is the this is the
buy the buyers that got stuck here. But
like we flushed down and we instantly
reclaimed and we're still going sideways
at those same kind of levels. Slowly
walking it down. But
I don't like this down here. This looks
like an end of auction down here.
just it's just not A+ folks. It's just
not A+ here. It's just a range. It's a C
money take money kind of day.
Did any of you get anything good in
Black Friday?
I did buy this chair. I'm very happy
with this chair. Very comfortable.
It was like I don't know 100 bucks off
or something. Maybe a bit more.
Move down to point of control. What?
PC's up here, mate.
You got some monitors. Nice, nice, nice,
nice. [snorts]
There's a 300 test
now. Starting to see more aggression
from these sellers. Might complete this
move now if they can get going.
I said it's possible they want to come
back down the lower day because we have
unfinished business down there. It's
taking so long that they put me off
taking it
value low of the session so far. Doesn't
mean we can't expand it. That's just
where we're trading at so far.
Starting to see some aggression here.
Probably going to try and complete
towards here. It's where buyers came in
earlier towards 50s. This New York open
has taken out that low. Not yet.
Went to his New York open as well.
I don't know what they want to do, Troy.
It doesn't seem like they're going to
have the power to do that right now.
All we've done really is wash uh the
London level and turn back inside. So,
we're coming back down to test this
lower lower band now. I just hate how we
formed that there was so slow. This was
probably the cell here,
but the tape was so slow at that point.
It's not bad. If any of you took that,
it's pretty decent. Even the flow zones
pretty decent.
So, let's see if they squeeze this back
up and then resell it.
And this is where we found a bid this
morning. So, they've almost done the
rotation already.
They're not going to make this easy.
[snorts]
Back towards the 300. I would say that
sort of 350 becomes key again. 320 and
350.
So, buyers who didn't get filled in the
morning's shove up. They just got filled
there in this imbalance right here.
That's 340s. 350s look big overunders
right now.
Straight up then.
This is fun.
All
right, let's see what happens when we
get up here. There's good power in this
move. This is back to that level again.
This sort of 340, 350.
Not too far away from it. What do we hit
there? 32s.
Back to the view up again. Are they
going to go up to 40s and 50s and test
it? If they get through that, they're
going to test the 70s. And if they get
through that, they can start squeezing.
Yeah, I just don't think it's very
pretty out here.
If you chased a short, you got hurt. If
you bought above 70 today, you got hurt.
That's kind of the story. There's
nothing else really going on.
All they did was fill that old
imbalance. That was it.
Are they going to come all the way back
down now?
Just feels a bit thin. The book
a little bit thin.
Sorry.
So, this imbalance from here
got filled. We found a bid. We pull
back. We're going to try and do this
now. That's what he's trying to do. I
just don't I don't love Look where we're
trading. It's just there's no edge here
at the moment.
I'm happy sitting still honestly
especially on first day of the month on
a Monday and like recovering from COVID.
I'm h happy sitting still.
What strategy do I use? Um well depends
on the setup. People get so focused on
that. It all depends on the setup.
Basically, I look to find a participants
who are offside where I can trade
ideally in a protrend direction, which I
don't think we're in at all right now. I
think the market needs to make up its
mind. So, if we're going to be tra
protrend bullish, we need to set a daily
higher low, which we haven't done yet.
Could be that today does that. Then we
look for
that kind of trade upside. If we are
going to fail, then I'm looking for fail
breakouts. So all I'm ever looking for
is trap traders for rotations from one
level to the next to go and search for
liquidity. So create liquidity, search
for liquidity. Today is a creation of
liquidity day by the looks of it, which
is why I'm kind of sat here waiting. So
here's the move back to 40s and then
50s. Squeeze will happen above 70s. If
they let the bulls out above 70s, that's
where a squeeze can happen. Nvidia has
caught a bid here. None of the rest of
the market still caught a bid.
So this is the shelf where we failed
from. All right, this is the volume
where we failed from. If we get back
through this shelf, all right, then this
will be a look below that fails and we
can use this liquidity at this point to
go higher. Very, very nasty how they've
done that. It's very, very quick.
Number 70 is the level that buyers were
stuck above. There's the look back to
PC. So, I'd say buyers now will want to
hold 20s. This shelf here, buyers will
not want it below that. They will want
to do this to complete the rotation. If
sellers start getting their way, they
can still complete. We still have
unfinished business down here. We did
not take out GlobeEx lows on any market
yet.
This is just ranging. This is why the
flow zones are kind of stuck here.
Everything's Look at the middle point of
your screen right now. both VWOPS, both
both flow zones underneath that PDL
and your lower time frame algo and your
previous week value area low very value
very very high
finding a bid off his New open. We're
just literally in no man's land.
I think this is also an old gap on the
spy, not just a new gap. We're actually
trading into into an old gap again as
well.
[cough and laughter]
Yeah, Nvidia higher day right now. I
reckon that 180 is probably quite a big
level on Nvidia. Probably on the options
which we've just traded into. I reckon
it's a big old level.
We got above that
80.27 liquidity at 81's
on the video.
London Asia suite.
Uh
well, [sighs and gasps] depends on your
timings, but I wouldn't consider it
because that I don't like that.
Uh
what was that? 0030 low.
And we haven't done it. Have we done it
in We haven't done it in New York hours
to the downside.
This low down here.
This low. We've protected this low
twice. One, two, protection.
We've left lots of liquidity down here.
Now, if you think about this
and this,
I'm not convinced by that in a range
leaving liquidity like that. Not
convinced by it.
Okay, here's the test of these 20s. Like
we just talked about, bulls will need to
hold this. If they fail to hold this,
there is more rotation downside
possible.
I' say 20s down to 05s need to hold for
bulls.
Everything's flat though.
Every single sort of indicator is flat
on the screen right now. No trend
develops.
For me, this is just creation of
liquidity. That's all we're doing right
now.
Best prop firm for beginners. Um
probably say go for something without
trailing draw down
funded next pretty good. Um
probably the new Lucid accounts pretty
good. They're on sale right now.
Um, if you just want cheaper accounts
because it's your first time trying, you
can look at Apex, but you just need to
be aware of the rules
and size down if you're going to trade
with them.
We're just totally stuck. Can't reclaim
this gray box. Right, this is where
volume's stuck and we're holding 20s.
So, the rotation now happening between
here.
Bulls take control above this. Bears can
take potentially control below this. We
do have excess down here.
Sellers were caught down there
and buyers were caught on this high as
well. So that's what I mean. We're just
in a range rotation. You might be like,
why is he sitting still? He's not
calling anything. So there's just
nothing. I really am seeing that. I'm
like, yeah, this feels like a shift in
momentum. This feels like someone wants
to take control. I'm just not seeing
that right now. Doesn't mean things
can't develop for you, but right now
what I'm seeing is not making me think
there's a big move coming.
Yeah, Tradeify Growth or as well. I
think they're I don't know if it's today
or later this week, they're going to
announce same day payouts as well.
So, Traify Growth as well. Another good
account.
One thing I'd say with funding next
though, uh, Fed what at 8:00 maybe Jay
might be right uh for pal. See if he's
uh particularly hawkish again or if he's
going to continue this doubbish pit that
we've had the last two weeks that I
talked about in uh in the newsletter.
Uh, one thing I'd say about Funded Next
and maybe the new
Lucid accounts, although I'd need to
check, is they don't have consistency
rules, whereas uh, Tradeify does. One
thing to be aware of,
always think not having consistency
rules can be very, very useful.
Shifting tape here. They're trying to
sell this back down to the 20s. Do they
get acceptance through it? This is where
they keep or they will need to keep
absorbing here. The bulls
just nothing. I'm just I'm watching the
book. You remember I'm also watching the
tape in the book. I'm trying to see if
someone wants to take control. We're not
seeing it.
Not seeing it right now in the market.
Like I said, that's I took that trade
overnight, so I'm not too fast either.
It's okay.
Probably a good day for me to um do my
course with a section on bookmap is
moving so slow it's very easy to explain
what's happening.
Yeah, nice for Black Friday sale. Nice.
All right, I'm going to use the bathroom
here while it makes its mind up. So,
remember 320s.
Bulls are trying to hold the 320s.
Acceptance over 360. I'd say 370 is the
big one. But any acceptance over here,
right, bulls can maybe take control.
Remember, every look so far this
morning, every look above has been
failed. But we have unfinished business
if they want to rotate. And bulls have
got to hold that 320 level. All right.
If you hold that 320 level, they'll be
looking to complete the rotation. I'll
be back shortly.
>> [sighs]
>> All right. It's trying. It's trying. If
you're bullish, you held the 320s.
There's your flag or inverse head and
shoulders kind of look. And it's trying.
All right. So, we're going to try and
squeeze now. Your targets are here. So
higher day, previous day PC 403,
previous day value area high and then up
here. All right. So there's your higher
low. There's the hold of 320 that we
talked about.
All right. And it's going to try and
complete this squeeze now. So you got
your TPS above. All those horizontal
lines are your TPS if you took it.
Do I like cricket? Yeah, I absolutely
love cricket. Harish. I love cricket.
Here you go. a TP1 coming up into high
day. Don't be a dick for a tick. Take
some here and then look for that squeeze
out
or your next levels. So 405s, 436es, gap
fill here, 482 if you get lucky.
There's your TP1.
Now just hold on and see if they can
squeeze it for you. If you took that
long from 320 or if you joined for this
flag
all the time bulls held this like we
talked about that's possible. They're
going to use this liquidity now to fire
this up. But you must not be joining
late. You should be joining here and
selling into these drives because we're
still in rotation. You don't know that
they don't do a look above and fail
here. So just move your stop up with it.
Take profits on the way.
Favorite cricket player? What? Current?
Probably Stokesy
given that I'm English.
Probably Stokes.
But growing up, um I used to love Jack
Callis.
I love watching him play.
obviously from the England teams like
Freddy and KP and guys like that.
Yeah, obviously watching the ashes, but
there hasn't been much to watch watch
has there because England have been so
pathetically shite in that first test
that it was all done in two days. Crazy
current. Uh I don't I did wash watch the
last test with India. Um
I like your uh fast bowler uh with the
weird action.
Trying to remember his name.
Can't remember. Alex, is the 20our
course still on Black Friday sale? If
not, could you please walk through
everything it includes? Uh, I don't
think I think the sale will have
finished now. Let me check.
I think it will have finished. I can
extend a Cyber Monday for you if you
want. Let me have a little look.
All right. Make sure you're locking in
some profits here. You just hit TP2. So
your last one, well, you got two more.
Previous day value area high and then
there's a yellow line above you which
will be gap fill, right? So this is TP3,
TP4. [snorts]
Do not get long up here. Do not start a
new money long up here. You're asking
for it if you do that.
You're absolutely asking for it.
It's still active until tonight.
So, code BF on all products. All right.
So, it's still active until midnight
tonight.
So, anything on my website, code BF,
will get you 25% off.
It's the last day though. This would be
the last sale. Prices will be going up
next year, folks.
[snorts]
Okay, a big seller came in there and
he's not getting his way. I would like
to see this continue to squeeze up for
you at this point,
but you have to observe initial balance,
initial balance rules. You've got value
area higher here now at 77. All the time
we're holding that potential squeeze
potential for higher Burma. That's it. I
love watching him. I love how aggressive
he is. I think he's really fun to watch.
I haven't watched uh I will be able to
watch it this this year, but I haven't
watched the uh IPL the last few years
because I just haven't been able to get
it here in um America. Plus the timing
for me is bit night bit of a nightmare.
Should you enter long if it comes back
to point control? What current point of
control down here? Um it really depends
how it acts when it gets there. All
right. Is it a good level? Yes. The
these are levels of interest. But you
know if you're just going to enter long
there, what's to say it doesn't wash
down. So what you want to see, you don't
want too many buyers caught here. And
ideally you want something like this too
long off if you're going to look for a
continuation. But just remember
lowhanging fruit TP1 TP2 low hanging
fruit have been taken. These are the
only things left now.
Market isn't particular particularly
Gosh, can he talk? The market is not
particularly
particular
uh it's not that strong today. I'll give
you a readout on the mag. Tesla 0.14%
down. Microsoft 0.71% down. Meta about
1% down. Google half a percent down.
Apple quarter of a percent down. The
thing driving this is Nvidia, which is 1
point or one and a half% up, but it did
just fail that look into the 180s I
talked about. I would imagine that's a
big options level there. We have an old
PC at sort of 18060, 18050. So, I'd be
watching that. So, we've just filled
well almost filled the gap there on
Nvidia. So, I'd be I'd be very aware of
that
once Nvidia fails. if Nvidia fails and
you might see a bit of air come out of
this market.
But so far it's it's just hold on to
your runners and how far can it go. All
right, but you know you don't want to be
buying up here. You know that this can
easily be collapsed on how they lack of
liquidity built here. This is just a
squeeze. This is this is shorts trying
to guess the top right now and they're
probably likely to get hurt and when
it's done it will wash them out and then
how we app becomes important.
>> [snorts]
>> Vicks failed that 1720 1740s now back
sub 17. It has potential for a gap fill
down to the low 16s here. Can't rule it
out. It's
somewhat unusual how VIX is uh acting.
Not so much today, but more how we acted
last week. To move from 30s back down to
the teens
without a pop on a VIX is uh quite
unusual.
Want to wash these guys at some point.
previous day point of control here. Now
book starting to dry up a bit here. Not
liking what I'm seeing on bookm feels
very very low
years I would say harish but I moved
around quite a lot.
So I started on swings and then I moved
from swings to small caps. Then I moved
back from small caps to large caps and
from large caps eventually to futures.
There's a battle here going on now.
These 420s.
Where is Nvidia? Is it at that 180? It's
underneath that 180.
They're trying to sell this. They're
attempting to. I'm not convinced they're
going to have the juice to wash all
these guys out yet. I don't think we've
squeezed out enough. But we will see in
good time, won't we?
As previous day point control holding up
for that.
There are definitely buyers caught over
415 on this last candle,
but it just feels very very very slow
today.
So slow. The way the tape's moving, it's
insane.
back to the level these buyers just got
caught at.
Not convinced we finished the auction
like I talked about. I'm not not
convinced it can't get up into this
previous day level and maybe even a gap
fill. You just don't know.
See weirder things from these markets.
We just feel like we're in holiday drift
higher. That's all we feel like we're in
right now. Just feels exactly the same
as last week. Just like very slow move
higher. I know we gapped down, but
that's what it feels like.
Yeah, it just Yeah, I'm I'm considering
it. I'm looking at other options as
well. Same as like Cheddar Flow and a
few others
uh which is on sale today. I just want
need to do some research. Make sure I'm
going to spend that money for the room.
Make sure I get one which is actually
producing good data and is useful.
I only really want the ETS. I don't
really care about everything else.
They're trying to squeeze this up. They
are attempting to squeeze this up.
Creating like a new range up here just
like we did earlier.
That last look above failed again into
those 420s.
Just there's no downside follow through
underneath point of control yet. So just
a new range being created again here.
previous day point control holding up
right now.
We are starting to potentially develop a
trend if it can hold pullbacks above
initial initial balance. But uh you see
now finally the flow zones have started
opening up. I' still given the lack of
volume we've had today. I'm still not
convinced by anything I am seeing right
now. I don't think it would take a lot
to move this market in either direction.
No, I think it was probably just
technical problems, Rosco.
But who knows? We'll never find out
anyway.
That will never be released because if
it was true that it was manipulation,
the amount of people would go to jail
would be insane.
They'd all start snitching on each
other.
It was down for quite a while, wasn't
it?
So, if you're still long from these uh
down here, you should have taken
partials into this and this. Your next
level is previous day value area high
and then uh previous day close. But make
sure you paid yourself because it will
not take much to wash this out. And I'd
say stops here at a 94s will probably
get popped at some point.
[cough]
Here they come. They're probably going
to company stops now. Like we talked
about, it won't take lots to move this
market. Honestly, it's not trading with
a lot of volume. All depends what they
want to do, what their intentions are.
They still haven't taken these stops
out.
Can't imagine that they defend these
stops. Honestly, I think we probably
take them.
Here we come. So, we're coming for these
stops now. And then how we act here
becomes important. Do they sweep and
want to move higher or are we just going
to give back this whole low volume move?
So, same as we had here, this shelf
here, we can draw a new one up here.
very exactly the same play. They're
doing the same [\h__\h] and they might
want to come back and back test this
now. And if they don't, then this will
be your support. They'll wick into here
and try and reclaim to go higher. But
remember, we are in a range rotation.
I'd be very, very cautious about
thinking longs up here. Your long
trigger was down here for this move. And
I'm not convinced about anything that
I'm seeing on the tape.
I don't think it would take much to move
this. Like I said, one big player can
come in and change everything. You can
change absolutely everything very very
quickly.
[snorts]
Did we make it there? Almost made it to
the 80s.
[snorts]
So if you want the short here, you will
need to see it reject 400s and you'll
really want this to start collapsing and
rolling over, right? But really
all the time we're holding this
we can complete more bullish moves. But
obviously if we come down here and get
stuck that's your IB rotation back to
VWAP.
We have just taken these stops now.
Right. So if we reject this I think we
should move lower.
See how it just does it in one straight
move.
So you got those levels above for the
reaction. Now, how we act into that gray
box above becomes key. How we act into
this gray box below becomes key.
Hopefully, it retests instead of just
doing straight moves. Like I said, I
don't trust the tape today. It's very,
very low on volume. It does not take a
lot to move this. [snorts] Really does
not take a lot to move it.
Just left this volume without retesting
it to get shorters.
My French
Okay. So, box to box again. [sighs]
Box to box again. Ideally, they retest
this and we see if that stays heavy.
It's a fade back in. If they reclaim it,
I'm not going to touch it, but it's a
new squeeze out.
Please retest. Come on. You can't just
do this single direction moves. Come on.
Yeah, video failed that 180 like I
talked about.
Please get up for a retest. Come on,
market.
They're trying to bid these lows at the
moment.
It's literally single direction back
down to point control.
Mother cluckers.
Well, still unfinished business down
here. If they do want to let this go,
you need a retest though, so that you've
got a nice price to fail.
This can still be a pullback that holds.
So, I'd be interested how we act once we
get up here.
How we act when we get up there becomes
important.
Audi still looks good. So feel part of
that imbalance from 8:00 p.m. last night
like we talked about.
This is the problem at the moment. This
is what I mean. This is the problem.
Here's your imbalance. Here's we expect
shorts to come in. Here's the structure
that bulls want to hold. This in here
can build liquidity out. All right?
Because bulls want to defend this.
shorts want to defend this. This is the
rotation. This is the issue right now.
It's not protrend because we haven't got
everyone on this side and we don't have
everyone on this side yet. It's
developing liquidity in these areas.
It might just be that we have to wait
for tomorrow to get a protrend move.
Very, very possible.
Yeah. And under 80s. Those buyers are
stuck on that big imbalance candle.
Definitely stuck. They're under 80s. Is
there going to be follow through is the
question.
Yeah, it's just not protrend yet on the
H1. It's just going to need time to
develop. And you know, H1 can start
bidding from 44 down to 14s. And like
really until we take out today's low, we
don't see weakness.
It's just one of those days like we're
not going to get protren every day. Like
we talked about,
shorts are likely to come in up here.
That's what we're now starting to see up
here.
The problem is
you would have had to grab that on the
breakout trade.
I don't think I'm fully engaged in this
market yet either. like mentally
way developing is kind of
a shelf here. So, let's see.
These are really the levels right now.
Does scalping with copy tra? Does
scalping work with copy trading? I've
tried a couple times, but my followers
seem to not pick it up. Yeah, it works.
Maybe you've got a slow connection or
not a good copy trader, but it
definitely works.
I trade on Ninja Trader, but it's just
me personally. I use the trade of eight
connection. I trade on Ninja Trader.
What a slow day.
failing to reclaim previous day value
area low there.
Bears will want to defend 80 to let's
call it 400 80 to 95. If bears defend 80
to 95, there's possible rotation back
down here. That's the level that bears
want to defend 80 to well basically
here. bears want to defend this or this
move down here to come and clean out
some of these liquidity. These would be
the areas where buyers will want to step
in where the volume is.
There's just nothing really going on
here, folks.
So, possible short here if they fail
that this push up. And now bears will
want to see a breakdown. So, we're
defending 80
and they want a new low and they'll want
to wash out the VWAPs here. And you
know, if they get very very heavy, you
can't rule out low of day because I
think there's lots of liquidity left
down there.
Amazon's not really doing much right
now. The rest of the market's still red
other than Nvidia
starting to try and see some aggression
here. Are they going to get the
breakdown to be up?
Here we go
into this gray box. If they fail this
gray box, we've got view up here and the
next gray box. So, the next move will be
into like the 30s down to 20s. These
were the key levels earlier. We can get
down to 30s to 20s. That'll be a cover
point. Here we go. Finally,
and then hold some for low of day just
in case it's 40s. Watching this cover
into 30s here. Just want one more flush
here.
And then hold one below day if I can
just in case. Just in case. Here we go.
Tag tag tag. Tag me. Tag me. Tag me. Tag
me. One out here. [sighs]
And just one left. And we just let it
ride now.
So here's your next TP. These gray boxes
we talked about. If we bail this into
here and then holding one for load day
just in case. I don't expect it to get
there, but just in case
using bookmap. You can see it above you.
I'm also using footprints.
Nice.
Want to see us take out this next view
up here. If we take this out then I feel
better about potentially getting down
towards low of day. But right now just
got one left now.
Don't want to see a rebid. Don't want to
see this hold anything.
Just want to see weakness come into the
tape here and start washing.
Nice. Thank you. Come on. Get this 20
out the way, please.
got an imbalance down into sort of 308
309 that they can fill.
Come on.
Not seeing follow through there. Don't
like that.
Taking this out.
Always add back in.
That gray box holding that shelf holding
there is the reaction of it. Didn't like
what I saw on the tape there. They had
the chance to take over there. So, still
the same thing applies. Uh bears are in
control all the time. They are
protecting these levels up here. All
right. All the time this is protected.
This is possible. This shelf here, if
this is protected, this is possible
today. Not probable, it's possible. So,
any pop up here which gets sold into can
allow this rotation. But I don't like
what I saw down here. Right, we saw
aggressive selling and it didn't move
lower. There's a passive buyer trying to
absorb this level here for now. So, I
cut the trade. I'm now flat on the
trade.
Starting to see them try and squeeze
this back up at this point. There we go.
So, yeah, they had two attempts there.
They tried to aggressive sell it
at sort of the 30s, the 30 breaks, and
then they tried again. They stepped in
at the 20s and they got absorbed, which
is why I cut it. There we go. So,
there's the squeeze back out. So they
got absorbed right into this gray box.
This why these are points to cover. And
then how we act up here will be key. All
right. Because if they reclaim all of
this, this node here needs to be
protected by the sellers. All right.
Definitely this volume up here. If this
gets sliced through, then this is
bullish again, right? Sellers will want
to protect this to complete the
rotation. I'm not convinced we get a
full rotation today because it just
doesn't feel like one of those days at
the moment. It feels like see money take
money.
Don't mind jumping back in if it sets
up. I see it squeeze higher, not higher
day, but back up here at this point and
see if there's a passive seller just sat
there waiting
and we'll see.
So 70s again same as same as earlier
today. Remember these 70s there was
passive seller here eventually we got
through it squeezed out and then they've
sold back through it. It's the same kind
of level.
[cough and clears throat]
Maybe Jack, I'm just not like I don't
have too much bias because we're trading
inside range, right?
Look at your daily. We're just we're
trading inside of the previous day's
range, right? So, we look below it
overnight, found a bid. We're trading
inside of Friday's range now. So, I
don't I'm not trying to carry too much
bias right now
because if they're going to put a daily
higher low in this market, they've done
it today. So, any breakout above current
day's high tomorrow, I don't want to
include it today. Tomorrow and onwards,
potential squeeze, right? Because then
we put the daily high low in, then we go
into a higher high and we can squeeze
back out. So I'm not carrying too much
bias on the Monday while we set up the
liquidity for the rest of the week.
Okay. So how we act up here now becomes
key like we talked about. So I want to
see strong sellers come in and defend
these levels. All right. If they don't
do that then obviously I'm not going to
sell it back down because we can
resqueeze higher.
Yeah. Exactly. That's all we've got so
far.
But we're back inside of the initial
balance. We're starting to like look
into these areas. If sellers get met
here, if we meet sellers here, then
we're going to look for that rotation.
But again, we've got a big node here.
And this is now point of control, which
is a pain that they've moved it down. It
would have been nice to have PC up here
and move away from it. So, we have to
respect this here. Now,
this node here,
if they sell into this and sell through
this, then we can move lower. But really
it's just think about the structure.
This is all we're doing right now,
right? How we acting here becomes key.
You want this little squeeze up to be
met with sellers. That's what you want
to see if you're looking for downside
action. And then you're going to have to
respect the volume below you. I'm
starting to see that move now.
Starting to see it.
Really nice that move into back into the
70s and 80s just got sold into for now.
Still very early.
Watching the tape there.
Don't have a lot of conviction either
way today.
Definitely sellers up there. Not
convinced we've swiped up enough to see
how big they are yet. Is there any delta
outside?
Any big outlier prints? Not really
seeing any.
Yeah, no big outlier prints.
>> [snorts]
>> They're
reselling again here through the 70s.
This 70 is big big level like we talked
about is big this morning. It's big now.
They're trying to be aggressive here to
get this close lower. They want to force
this down. These sellers this is this is
their chance. Their chances. Now, if it
can't do it, then you have to just
understand it means there's buyers on
the tape saying, "Hey, we're not moving
lower. We're going to move sideways."
There's a buying balance from uh 50 to
40 here as well. If it wants to trade
down there, it can. And let's see if
there's a buyer down there or not.
Um, yeah, I can see what you're looking
at, Raph. I mean, it is the same area,
but you know, it means that we're not,
it's more like a quasi. We don't get a
break until we trade under here, right?
So, I mean, there's nothing to say that
this doesn't do this still as well,
right? So, we have to just observe
because if we're thinking about swings,
this can still be a higher low, right?
There's your low, higher low, higher low
until we get a breakdown under here. But
if sellers are going to come in, this is
the area that they're going to need to
come in. This is the look above and fail
above initial balance failing to
reclaim. The hard thing is is how much
volume we've built out. Right? Look how
thick we are. If we get under this, we
get thinner and there can be a bigger
drop and that will time out well with
that. But until that point, I'd be see
money take money.
[snorts]
He's
70s again.
>> [snorts]
>> Massive seller there. Same level. Expect
to chew him up
to 8085.
So slow. So so slow.
The range isn't bad. You know, we've
probably had over 200 points, but it's
just it feels so slow on the tape.
Maybe just Okay.
into that low volume. See what happens.
VIX trading at low of day.
Interestingly,
there's your initial balance. These are
your key overunders now for sentiment on
the day. Sellers need to defend this
level if they're actually going to look
to complete a rotation. If they can't
defend this level, you cannot rule out a
squeeze for a gap fill. This is the
level sellers need to defend here or
hereabouts.
So far, they're coming in and selling
it.
Right.
Bing sold into so far. Still early.
This is the This is the area.
Definitely caught buyers up there.
Starting to see some selling here. They
need to take control now
because they've got the opportunity to
do it. I'd say a good close under 60s
would be good for for sellers at this
point. They've just sold really really
well up there. Caught the buyers up into
that push into 90s. They need a strong
clos under 60s and then you see might
see some more continuation.
It's there for them if they want to do
it. The opportunity is now here for
them.
Back to the 70s. Here you go. They're
going to come for these 60s like we just
talked about. Now, can they get strong
clothes underneath?
They need a strong clothes under 60s.
And really, if they can get under 50s
and then you might get a bit more of a a
violent wash.
Not doing a very good job of it so far.
My gosh, this is slow.
Jeez Louise.
Does anyone want to do anything today of
any meaning?
Have you got any intent to do something
today? Buyers or sellers? I don't really
care which, but can we just do more than
20 point mini rotations for hours and
hours and hours and end?
Feels like the same market as we had
maybe a month ago where we do this
nonsense for ages and then we go
straight up and then we do this nonsense
for ages and then we go straight down.
This feels like this terrible market
that we've had for a little while now.
I'd really like to see us move out of
these horrible market conditions and
into a protrend condition. I don't care
if we move higher or lower, but these
whole things where we go straight one
way, sideways, straight the other way,
sideways, they've got to stop, man. They
are not fun to trade. They need to stop
this. [snorts]
So maybe after the next few days, maybe
we can move into something with a bit
more smooth action. Let's say something
which is a bit more technicalbased
rather than just stupidity
on low volume. I'm not going to trade
low volume stupidity.
Still rejecting initial balance there.
still like the amount of tiny size being
offered on this market up and down and
up and down is [\h__\h] stupid. There's
no one in control here. It's uh it's
actually pretty weird to look at on the
book.
It doesn't really matter to me what it
looks like on 5 minutes. More about
what's participating. Like the actual
volume in it is non-existent. We're just
in no man's land. We're going to retest
this
[snorts]
I don't really care about the candles at
the moment. I care about how they're
participating.
What is this guy doing? Reoffer. Real
offer. Pull. Pull. Pull. Really offer.
Reoffer. Pull. Pull. Pull. What are you
doing, mate?
What are you doing?
This guy at 405 is being very odd. What
are you doing?
Back to test this high volume node above
then.
Fire successfully defended. Bear's doing
a uh god awful job for now.
This guy at 405 is being real weird. Why
would you keep spoofing such tiny size?
What are you doing?
[snorts]
Let's see. Sellers coming back in again.
They've got their chance here. They have
the chance to do it.
If they're going to defend this, this is
the first time we've I guess we've
tested this high volume node. But the
problem with how they're doing it, all
right, because they're not being
aggressive, we've now built out a ton of
structure here. So really, what are they
going to do? They're going to cover this
and cover this. They need to get a crack
for them to have anything of note today.
And I just can't see that happening.
Look how we built volume out. Look how
thick this is up here now. It's going to
take an awful lot to trade through it
now for sellers.
They got they really have to step on the
gas here if they're going to do it. I'd
be watching these 70s again. That's kind
of your key over under at this point
today.
I just can't see anything happening in
this market.
What's here? Let me check the daily
mainly say sell volume and still very
very low.
Yeah, I'm not convinced.
Well, everyone talks about a Santa rally
before Christmas, but reality is most
times Santa rallies happen in January to
be honest. But this is not a normal year
though. Everyone keeps talking about
they're referencing previous years.
[\h__\h] tell. show me a previous year
which has traded straight upside since
April of the amount of size and percent
that we have. So I'm very like inclined
to be very cautious thinking about oh
this is what we've done on previous
years. All right. Well this isn't
previous years is it? This is tariff
year. So
I don't know. All I know is hedge funds
I don't think have made the money that
they need to make. So it really depends
what their intents are.
Are are the Fed going to pivot and
probably do a cut next month? Probably
by the looks of it. And power will be
gone next year anyway. And then uh
Republicans will take full control and
no doubt Trump will have a puppet in
there and they just do cut cut cut. And
it all depends if we're going to pump
that cut. And also you need to watch the
[\h__\h] the Japanese uh trade carry trade
because their bonds are breaking out.
They're being forced to sell US indices
right now. that will cause a liquidity
issue on the market.
No, I do not swing options really.
Swing Commons.
Well, I would say bears right now failed
miserably.
Uh they can we can still move lower from
here for a failed rotation, but there is
no volume coming in here. They have not
come in aggressively and slapped this
down.
I don't know what they are. I don't know
pro probably alos, but I I couldn't tell
you with absolute certainty
because [snorts] I'm not them. And
anyone who says this is what it is is a
liar. Unless you're that person, you
don't actually know.
Okay. Failing previous day point of
control again. But you know, this is
just slowly just grinding all the way
back up to where we just failed from.
And if they want to complete the
rotation today and fill this gap, they
absolutely can. Bears will need to
defend this. They really should have
defended this low volume node. They
didn't. I'd say buyers are in way more
control here than bears in this market.
And it just feels like a low volume
grind. I would not be buying up here.
Yeah.
Jeez.
Look at that. This is what I've been
worried about the whole time. I think
this is going to break out and cause
issues in this market.
I've said it. I've said it for months
and months and months. This this
is the big issue and question mark for
me.
I think it underneath the hood of this
market, it does not look very good. But
it's been that way for a long time and
uh
doesn't mean it has to do anything.
It's just like 08.08 should have
happened in 07 and 06. It didn't.
Tops take an awful long time to develop
in markets if there's going to be a top
at all. It doesn't have to happen when
people are calling for it. It can keep
going and going and going. We might see
another two years of squeeze out. And
I'm not joking. I'm being deadly
serious.
[snorts]
We just got to trade what's in front of
us.
Balls are in control here.
Balls are in control here, folks. These
bears have done
an awful job
of defending any key level here.
Awful.
How long till lunch? I don't think
anything's going to change. This is a
slow drift range rotating market.
There's nothing to do in here.
There's literally nothing to do in this
market.
I just got to wait for it to come to a
level of actual interest.
Have a look at the bread.
Yeah, energy is the only green sector.
Some consumers aren't too bad to be
fair.
Walmart. Okay, we talked about that,
didn't we? See a rotation into cheap
cheap goods in preparation for uh
recessionary pressure.
Hold up. Yeah.
Okay, so tested that supply.
That gray box
probably comes for a rotation back down
to this edge here. And for me, bears
don't take control now until we move
under 50. All right. So, this is the
edge that they're trying to defend.
They've done a woeful job that if I was
them, I wouldn't have let it get that
high, but uh I'm not them. They're
trying to defend this. If bulls step in
here and hold 70s, they can complete a
rotation higher.
Yeah, big wick. But this is what we
talked about on the hourly, isn't it?
It's exactly what we talked about. We're
not in a prot. So, you're seeing that
big wick on the hourly, but all the time
we were under 440, we're in a range.
We're just in a range.
[snorts]
It is so slow on the tape.
There you go. So, they just supported in
front. They didn't even get there. Bears
didn't even get the rotation to 770.
Ball still defending. Just held at IB.
They just held IB.
It's just I'm not trading this. There's
just no way folks off this tiny tiny
walk up walk down volume. I'm
participating in this. I'd let rather
let Monday close out. See where we
close. This is just an inside bar after
drifting into Wednesday's session. And
that was done overnight. We haven't come
and retested any of that. There's just
nothing to to do here. We've looked
above and we've looked below um Friday
and failed both sides. That says
everything you need to say. Market
doesn't know what it wants to do. It's
just going to build liquidity. That's
it. There's nothing more to say about
this right now.
I certainly have no intent in uh
pushing anything.
Couple scalps and that was it. Or one
one singular scalp actually I should
say.
I can't really see like we're moving up.
What the [\h__\h] are we moving up on? This
market's doing nothing in the mag.
Absolutely stuck. But uh
we've just moved up again.
[laughter]
Maybe previous day value area high.
Maybe they at the moment. I just feel
like they're going to close this gap.
that just feels like they want to close
this gap. It's just a slow drift, drift,
drift, drift, drift higher. [snorts]
You can't think about anything else
other than closing this gap right now
for me,
which is amazing. We're just going to
ignore everything that happened
overnight. I mean, it's actually Pretty
insane
for a low volume drift.
Shows how thin the market is when we can
do 300 points either way and it not
really matter right into
so ugly
story of this market really isn't it
since April just bears are absolutely
pathetic. Think about how much control
they had uh prior to last week and they
just fluffed it. They completely fluffed
it. On a holiday week when there was no
one present, they fluffed it. And on
today where they had a gap down on low
volume, they fluffed it. There's no
there's no selling. There's no selling
in the market anymore. We had a week.
Was it a week? Was it even a week?
Couple weeks. We had a couple weeks of
selling. That's it. That that was it.
Sweep a bit of liquidity in markets now.
Okay, we're slowly grind all the way
back up. [snorts]
Yeah, I mean ES is same story. It wants
to go for gap fill. It wants to fill the
gap into 60
and VIX the same story. It's just
breaking down. This is just a slow grind
higher. You can't fight this tape. It's
just a very slow grind higher. And when
they're done with it, you're going to
see a cell back down probably inside the
range.
[snorts]
Tagging previous day value high there or
near enough.
So no acceptance above it yet. Once they
get acceptance above it, they will
probably go for gap fill and glowbacks.
Once they get acceptance above there
[snorts]
is amazing when you think
this strong selling that stepped in
here.
It lasted three minutes and then it was
not present again.
That is uh that is
times that by what we've seen since
April. That's it right there. That's
that's it.
400s now. I'd say you're overunders all
the time. They're protected.
Order in control.
I cannot believe
on a new Monday and a new month, we're
just trading inside
of the least volume we've ever seen on a
Friday. We're just trading inside of
that tiny amount of volume for a Friday.
Absolutely
pathetic.
We just need to get PAL tonight and see
see what we do.
Okay, they're going to try and get to
these 450s.
There's a 300 lot up here advertising.
What's the bet he pulls once we get
there? Probably quite strong, I'd say.
Probably just pulls his order.
That's where they're trying to get up to
at the moment. 450s, but I'd say really
470s
and 480s are the job.
I cannot tell you how low this volume is
that we're moving in.
It's so slow.
Like we're trading these tiny little
like 10 lots, two lots, two lots on the
market. Like seriously, guys,
just squeeze it out for [\h__\h] sake.
[snorts] Finish the rotation for once
today. Maybe set something up for
tomorrow because if you don't finish
this today, there's going to be nothing
to do tomorrow either.
You're a permable. I mean,
I'm not permable yet.
If we can set a daily higher low and we
start breaking out later in the week,
then yes, I think alltime highs can
definitely be taken. No doubt about it.
I'm not saying that on a Monday of a new
month after a low volume week. I think
that would be idiotic to be quite honest
to say something like that because we've
traded for
2 and 1/2 hours with some of the lowest
volume I've ever seen.
So, I think trying to be that biased
will probably get you in trouble.
And it's fine to say permable, but
permable versus what? Because you're a
day trader, so it really doesn't mean
[\h__\h] does it?
Because what actually matters is where
you're buying and where you're selling.
Saying things other than that, it
doesn't really matter. I'm bullish to
alltime highs. So that's great. Where
are you buying it? How big's your stop?
How big are your bollocks?
Since 350.
Yeah, on that reclaim. Yeah, not bad. I
think these are the targets at the
moment. I can't see beyond that. But
guess what? That guy pulled his order,
the 300 lot that I told you about. I
told you he'd pull it. It's too much
spoofing on the tape today. Way, way,
way too much spoofing on the tape today
for me.
Low volume and we're spoofing. Like,
what are you doing?
Why? Why bother?
So slow. My gosh.
Video's coming back to test that 180.
That's definitely an options level up
there. They failed every time they've
attempted it.
How long to lunch? 10 minutes. What a
boring session.
Man, there's so much spoofing.
I don't get it. Why would you Why would
you put a bid out for
two seconds?
It's not like we're even close to it.
You put it like 10 points below for a
whole two seconds. It's some weird [\h__\h]
going on, man.
we can get some nice retrace. I mean, it
doesn't look like that to me.
Everything's been absorbed.
Um, there's no aggressive participants
at the moment.
It just seems like a very slow drift and
grind higher trying to get gap fill, but
they're so slow. That's all it feels
like. They're just there's nothing
here to do for me.
Big buyer just tried there. They just
filled those guys at 450.
I mean, why are you going to fill that
and not come up here?
It looks like that's what they're going
to do. We're going to slam back down to
30s now, are we?
Jesus Christ. Go in a 20 point rotation
again for another 20 minutes.
Are we going to do this again?
So done.
Oh my gosh.
[snorts]
All right. Well, Bulls have got to
defend this level that they've made up
here now. 420 to 400. That's your
overunder. Balls need to defend this.
The rotation completion is up here. They
don't do that. I don't see what the
point in today was. If you're going to
drift higher, get this close to a gap
fill and not do it. I don't really
understand what the point in any of this
is at that point. We need them to fill
it. So, that allows us to have a better
trade tomorrow because I'm not
interested in trading this shite
tomorrow.
They're going to come back 420 now. Are
they come and test these 420s?
Yeah, I'm going to come back 420. That's
what I want to do at the moment.
Bidding down there.
and we said Tesla that 180 is definitely
the level they can't get through it.
They front run it again.
There you go. Here's that move to 425
420 that we just talked about.
And this is the decision point. Balls
need to defend this. Failing to defend
this will open up a bit bigger wash.
This is the level that they must defend
at this point. They got to defend this.
I just don't understand
why you would do all this work to not
fill the gap. Surely you're going to
fill the gap. You've done all this work
of absorbing it all day long.
Surely you're going to go for gap fill.
Doesn't look like the auction's finished
to me at the high either.
Don't think there's a buyer stuck at
higher day. There was some big buying up
there, but it doesn't seem like he's
stuck yet.
[sighs] Apple now green, Amazon green,
Nvidia green, but still not through that
180. That's the level I'd say. 180.
That's the level.
Yeah, I'm all right. I'm just low on
energy. I would have liked another trade
today really, but
The tape just looks very slow.
What you're saying doesn't actually make
sense. You just said you're a permable.
Then you said I didn't say I'm long now.
I don't short markets. I'm only longs.
So what? You day trade and you're only
long. It's going to make your life quite
hard.
Or are you swing trading and you're only
long? That makes sense to me. That
definitely makes sense.
Yes. Of course. Of course. The market's
moved by a [\h__\h] grayhaired old man
who has the time to sit on YouTube
talking [\h__\h] every day.
Oh my god. What are these guys doing?
We're doing it again.
2 minutes to lunch.
[snorts]
Back testing 420s. That's what I do.
420s and 400s. Failing that bit bigger
wash, but that's what they're doing at
the moment. Just going to come back test
it. [snorts]
Imbalance down here into the 10ens.
They're bidding at 25. I expect they get
sold through to be honest. And he's just
pulled his bid.
I cannot actually believe the amount of
spoofing for a low volume day I've seen.
Normally you see spoofing with like, you
know, the big lot like we saw earlier,
the 300 lot, but we're seeing spoofing
with like five and 10 lots. Like,
what are you doing?
Oh, I'm really scared of your five lot.
Like, what what is going on? [snorts]
Yeah, I think that's it. I think that's
literally it, Adam. They're just like,
"Oh my god,
we've got to do something to fill our
day. Let's just uh put limits out and
then pull them instantly.
block here on ES. You can see that
48 and 50s on ES. Big blocks set up
there.
Look at this guy. Spoof. Spoof. Spoof.
Move down.
>> [snorts]
>> video. Still can't get through that 180.
It's definitely a level.
It's definitely a level. That 180.
Okay, they had a finally gap fill.
Like I said, I don't think there's any
reason to be up here if you're not going
to go for the gap fill. What's the point
in doing all that work if you're not
going to fill the gap?
Wouldn't make any sense to me.
Into lunch now. Okay, job done. Thank
God for that. Right. My hope for the day
is that they at least fill this gap.
Please fill the gap. All right? Because
I don't want to leave an imbalance there
for tomorrow because I'd like to trade
properly tomorrow.
And all we're seeing today is just a
slow grind back up to where we came from
overnight. That's literally all we're
seeing. And we know there are sellers
hanging out at 500s. We know that
because of the reaction there that we
got last night. All right. And it's a
big level. We talked about it in the
newsletter. It's got all the volume from
it's like three days worth of volume. So
Monday the 10th, Tuesday the 11th,
Wednesday the 12th, and some volume from
Thursday the 13th. All right. So we
basically got three, let's just call it
three and a bit days of volume are
hanging out from 500 to 800. That's
where the sellers are. I'm not uber
bullish like some of you until we
reclaim that level because every time
we've come into there we have a two
weeks worth of balance range where we're
very very thick up there and everyone
above 900 is still stuck. So all the
bulls are still stuck over 900. So I'm
not uber bullish until we get back
through these levels above back through
here. All right. Every time we've come
up here we have got stuck. So that's
what I'm watching. I think they're going
to sell these again. I think we need a
deeper pullback probably back down to
24,900s
and a hold of that. And if we hold that,
that looks a bit better. So, that's
where my thoughts are for the week. Um,
I don't make anything of it, TJ, because
I think the volume's so low. I think
it's kind of inconsequential, but uh
yeah, we haven't made
higher highs on the cumulative delta all
morning really since, you know, that
10:30 push. So I I don't like I said I
think with such a low volume day I think
it's easy to just move stuff around. I'm
more interested how we operate
the rest of the week. All right. So
hopefully we fill this gap. Really don't
want to leave that open. That makes
tomorrow a pain in the butt if we leave
that open. If we can leave that open
what I'd be looking at this week. Very
simple.
Right. Here's your two weeks balance
range. You can see right buyers are
trapped up here. No doubt about it. This
is the range. All right. If sellers
defend this, then we're looking for that
rotation down to here. If we come down
here first, then we're looking for that
rotation up. So, there's a move here and
here. There's a move here and here. If
we lose this level, it's good night,
sweetheart. All right. So, that's what
I'm thinking about this week. I think
we're going to do some rotation from
here to where was it? Here. I think this
is the game plan for the week. Build
liquidity in here. If we hold this is
very bullish because we're probably
letting them out. But if we look and
fail down to here is bullish from here
back up. That's what I'm looking at for
the week. I'm not thinking beyond that.
I'm not thinking about anything else
beyond that. Um volume's telling the
tape.
That is very very thick but it's not
fresh right because we've come into it
once, twice, three times, third visit
into it. So this this is the area how we
react there probably dictates what
happens for the rest of the year to be
honest into January. Reclaim that. Yeah,
we're going to make new highs. No doubt
about it. We reclaim that we're making
new highs.
All right. Uh that'll be that then.
Let's see what we get for tomorrow.
Hopefully they fill this gap because I
don't want to leave an imbalance to go
into tomorrow. If they can fill this
after doing all that work today, at
least we've been efficient and we can
see what we get tomorrow. Um, that's it.
I'm not going to touch this this
afternoon. I don't think there's any
volume here being traded. I think one of
you said it rightly. I think everyone's
waiting for Powell, and that's at 8:00
p.m. tonight. So, let's see what he
says, if he spooks the market or if he
actually pivots to being dovish like the
rest of his uh friends did last week,
which is why we got that squeeze up.
Let's see. All right, folks. See you
tomorrow morning. Hopefully, we have a
better day, a few more setups, and we
can go from there. All right. Peace and
love.