How's it going, team? Move this down.
All right, it's going to be a shorter
stream again today. Um, still, as you
can hear, feeling absolutely dreadful.
So, this uh whatever this virus or flu
is, it's uh it's not going away.
It's only getting worse, unfortunately.
But let's uh make sure you are set up
for today. All right, I'm going to start
on the daily chart as always. And you
can see in the daily we are still
technically making from pivot high,
lower lows, lower highs, lower lows,
lower highs. Right. What we're going to
do today at the moment is start with an
inside bar. So yesterday was a big very
very low volume drift higher. All right,
there was absolutely no volume
yesterday. If you look at yesterday's
volume compared to the last three days
of sell volume that there was just
nothing. No one's at the charts this
week. All right, because it's holiday
week. So you need to be careful.
Um but we are now building an inside
bar. Did we look above and fail
overnight? No. Right. So we're watching
I would be watching for two well three
potential plays today.
One would be a look above and a fail
back inside the range. That would be
probably the most common thing I would
see highly likely to happen today. All
right, a look above previous day's high.
I don't know how high it wants to get. I
wouldn't imagine if bears have got any
sense that they let it get anywhere near
the 300s, but some kind of look above
and fail back inside previous days
range. I would say it's fairly probable.
If we get above and we hold previous
days high and we start to build out,
that's a very bullish move to come back
up maybe to this low volume node, 300,
400. Wouldn't have to be doing that
today, but it's something I'd be aware
of if we're going to base it above
previous days high. The last thing we
can think about is a pullback probably
somewhere into where we can find some
structure for that move higher. All
right, so those are the three things I
would consider. Most of the action is
going to take place in here today. I
don't think we're going to be either
side of that range unless some news uh
driver like the 10 10 a.m. news changes
something.
Okay, let's get into the hourlys.
You can see here we are still sat inside
previous week's value and previous days
value now as well. In fact, I'm just
going to mark out make sure that
previous state level was accurate. Give
me just a moment here. It's 9:30.
All right, there we go.
Okay, so we're trading inside. Oh, don't
do that. We're trading trading inside of
the previous week value area towards the
upper side of it. We've rejected
previous week value area high up here.
We've created a previous day value area
high up here. We have previous day value
area low and previous week point of
control below us. So if bulls are going
to defend, all right, then we're going
to think about a rotation down into here
and then looking to defend that. If they
fail to defend that, what we thinking
about? We'll probably look below and
fail. All right, probably a little look
underneath into some RBS structure back
inside and fail. I expect the rotation
to happen in here today. That would be
my expectation for today.
So, I'd be thinking about buying um sort
of 740 down to let's call it 600
somewhere down there once we get down
there if structure forms for that kind
of move. And I would think about selling
um sort of above previous day value area
high if it has the strength to get above
somewhere into like these 100s where we
get a bit thicker and then reselling
this for that rotation back down. I
don't really want to trade in the
midpoint which is where we're opening
up. Of course it is in no man's land,
right? Don't really want to execute in
no man's land right now, right? Because
this is your range.
We don't really want to be executing
here, right? We want to be fading tops
and buying dips down here. If the market
gets very heavy for some reason, if this
is a twolegg and they're ready to sell
it again, right, you need to be aware of
getting stuck under here because that is
going to really open the door to use all
this liquidity. So, you cannot just
willingly buy this on dips down here. We
need to show you some form of structure
to get involved in.
[clears throat]
All right.
Zoom this out a bit. As you can see,
overnight very clearly, we projected up
here twice and uh trying to create some
form of range up here at the moment. All
right.
If they can hold this, they're probably
going to look for that squeeze and then
a fail up. There would be what I'd be
thinking about off the morning drive. If
they squeeze up at the morning drive and
they sell into here, I'd be interested
in that count. Well, potentially trying
to trying to time the protren short.
Um, let's have a quick look at ES. I'd
imagine it's exactly the same. Yeah,
surprise surprise. No difference there.
Let's go to In fact, that's actually
come right into it supply and that 720
level.
So, even better area of resistance up
there. Let's go to the spiders. Right,
spiders have a call uh or they did
yesterday. I haven't checked this
morning. Set 670 was a call wall. All
right, it's a big options level. All the
time we're under that. We're probably
looking for a rotation back down to
somewhere sensible after such a giant
move. So, I'd be watching that 670 on
the spy. We can we can set a little
price alert there just in front of it.
>> [snorts]
>> All right, QQQ. Same kind of story.
Not quite as uh frothy up here, but you
can see we've come into this kind of
level where we failed from. All right,
so you'd imagine this is going to be
where we're going to fail from. And it's
just where the bulls catch that rotation
or we do this move down. That would be
my expectation.
Let's have a look at the mag.
Some video has been weak today. All
right. So, straight away you can see
Apple gapping down. The big drive
yesterday was approaching alltime highs
and uh
little bit of a gap down here is whether
it can find a bid into sort of 73s.
Amazon, same kind of story.
Came in and tested this R level. Can it
catch a bid to complete that move? It's
got a long way to go to get back up to
the highs. So, Amazon, that's the big
difference between that and Apple.
Amazon been being absolutely destroyed.
It's probably a good buy soon if not
already. Let's have a little zoom out.
Yeah, it's pretty good. This is where
the start of the origin of the move is.
So, be interested how we get when we get
down to sort of the low 200s if we can.
Another gap down there on Amazon.
Google, remember that's been
ridiculously strong on a squeeze.
Big gap up again on Google. I mean, this
is this is getting ridiculous. Um, we're
probably about three standard deviation
now on the daily. This is very, very
dangerous at this point. It needs to
come back to here to retest it. Um, we
can have a look on the daily very
quickly before uh we do anything else.
But yeah, that's frothy meta. Very
strong. Remember, I'm long meta. All
right, I bought the 80s down here. Only
a feeler, not big size. I did call it
out in Discord. Told you I'd got long
meta for a feler. So, already up. 40
bucks a share, but it is only a feeler.
I need it to come and base out and prove
to me. I'm not sure it's done selling,
but I wanted to get something on. The
reason that being it had been absolutely
decimated back into a point of interest
for me. So, I wanted to get something on
here. If it fails deeper down here,
obviously I'll cut it and then re get
involved.
Uh Microsoft. So, we got mixed bag so
far. Microsoft gapping down, weakness
there. Uh Nvidia, they're really weak
one right now. All right, that got
absolutely destroyed. All
right, had the chance to try and base
above this level here that we talked
about yesterday pre-market. It had to
get back above this zone here. It
couldn't, right? Kept squeezing up,
failing, squeezing up, failing,
squeezing up, failing back down to the
bottom side of the range. If they sell
72s and 70 break, it's probably going to
be a bit nasty because we've got
liquidity 68s and 64s to go and clear
up. So, a mixed bag. You got what, three
green, four red right now. We can have a
look just slightly outside. Imagine
there's going to be weakness in the
other chip names. Yeah, AMD gapping
down, Oracle probably doing the same.
Yeah, Oracle gapping down. So, a little
bit of weakness um across the board here
on some other names. Um let's just go to
Google quickly so you can see what I'm
talking about.
All right, that's not healthy.
Look where we are premarket. I would
imagine
that is at a third standard deviation.
Yeah, it's a it's a third standard.
Remember, Ballinger bands are two
standard deviation from the 20-day. We
are now above a 100% move from that
Ballinger band. We're above a third
standard deviation. This is not healthy.
It is not It cannot sustain a rally like
this. So, do not be surprised. Maybe
they do a rally for a few more days, but
this is going to crash and crash hard
when it's ready. I know it's a mega cap,
but you cannot go gap up,
squeeze, gap up, squeeze without coming
back. This is looking like a small cap.
And for me, that really sums up this
market right now. It really does, right?
It's uh,
for one of a better word, stupid and
irrational.
All right, it's not sustainable to do
that. It's just not, really isn't
sustainable. Three standard deviations
on a mega cap will not end very well for
those buying the highs.
Okay, we have got news at 10.
What's going on here with the camera?
Give me a second. What's going on here?
You can actually see me. There we go.
[snorts] Okay. So, looking for rotations
today. That's my expectation. I'm not
convinced I'm going to take a trade. All
right. Because I'm really not feeling up
to it. Uh book. Let's just have a quick
look at the book. Not much going on. No
big numbers on the book. I wouldn't be
surprised to see light volume today as
well.
Let's do these good mornings. Morning
everyone. Uh can't see who's at the very
top, so sorry about that. I'm not sure
who it is, but good morning JMM. Good
morning. The Richardsons, Chad,
Inferris, Toby, Cold Strike, Sergio,
Ahmed, Exploit the Vibe, Tartan,
Jeff, Andrew, John, Dennis, Calypso,
Christy, Jappie, Naz, Fall Forward, The
Law, Mark, Arrow, King, Troy, Brandon,
[clears throat] Miguel, Larry,
Lochina,
Lauren, TC Raphael one-on-one green
otter Eva Dimum Derby what a great name
but Leon
Azade Abbott Ronald Ejecto John B abit
Tonio Aaron Chad Richard Gerald Marrick
Mr. Slim Prrisca three bar reversal
Charles John Frank Peter Ilas Kingdom
Monty Peek King Jeff Lauron espider
gangster garbar ready Rosco is such a
great name all of these names uh broken
candles
zapper croco and as trade right good
morning everyone morning
3 minutes to the open right so I'm
looking for look above and fail look
below and fail that's really what I'm
looking for or Look below and stay heavy
with weakness. But I'm just going to let
this do whatever it is it wants to do to
start.
Sip of my meds.
I guess one thing we didn't talk about
is the VIX, right? The VIX gapping down,
opening up around these 20s.
If we start, you know, getting back
below what's this low here? 1925. Then
maybe we have a continuation of a
bullish day or even just a rotation day,
slower rotation day.
Ukraine peace deal with Russia
announced. Has it actually been agreed
though? Because Trump tried to announce
it and Europe and everyone said no. Let
me check that.
Where are you saying that?
Not saying that
Ukraine supports the essence of the
framework. It's not a done deal.
Yeah. Exactly. This is what keeps
happening. You got to understand America
keeps floating ideas which are not
acceptable by Europe um or by anyone
other than Russia. So it's not going to
get done until everyone agrees. So just
be careful saying things like that. Make
sure you understand the actual
statement. [snorts]
Peace deals are getting announced every
other day. Whether they're done or not
is a whole different ball game. Until a
peace deal is done, we're not going to
really see it move the market, I don't
think.
>> Yeah. [snorts] Well,
headlines can say what they want, can't
they? You know, if you believe the media
headlines, then um I don't know what to
tell you, my friend.
Headlines and reality are never quite
the same thing.
Okay, let's see.
[snorts]
Oh, no. I'm not having a go at you,
mate. I'm just saying, you know, it's
it's not me digging you out. I'm just
saying the headline and the truth is
always different. It's like the headline
right now from Trump saying inflation's
down. Go and actually have a look at the
prices. Look at competitive prices.
There was a dock on it last night if you
want to see where they're saying uh
Thanksgiving's cheaper this year. The
cost of the turkeys is cheaper. Well,
actually the cost to wholesale is 35%
higher currently. So they're just taking
the hit and that's just on the turkey.
The cost of every every other thing that
you will eat or drink has gone up
between 16 and 35%. But the headline
will say cost of living uh cost of
Thanksgiving has gone down under Trump.
All right. So, so important to always
understand the detail what's really
going on under the hood,
especially [snorts] when you're trading.
Can't trade a headline. Cannot trade a
headline. Easiest way to get killed.
[snorts]
[snorts] All right. So, opening up
inside here. Nothing to do here. Did we
just take Asia low? London low.
I'll give you read out on the mag.
Tesla 1% down. Here's the big loser.
Nvidia 4.68% down. What What a surprise.
It couldn't hold that ridiculous
turnaround it made yesterday. What a
surprise. Just this market trapping
everyone right now. Microsoft 0.09%
down. Meta the leader today 1.30% up.
Google just under 1% up. Amazon pretty
much flat but red. And Apple 0.65% up. I
think we're going to get an inside bar
today and rotation.
If we want to dig lower first, then I'm
going to have to think about buying off
a rotational low. If we can do a look
above and fail, which would be my
preferred move, we can fade nearer a
supply block, which would be much, much
better than trying to buy the dip in
this market. But let's see.
And I'll probably only be here an hour
or so, folks. Probably
really not doing too good right now.
[snorts]
Uh I did post in chat. All right. Uh a
link in chat. I have just done a
partnership deal with funded next after
taking my first payout. That video will
go live today. As with all prop firms, I
want to make sure I get paid and that
they do all the things that they say
they do, which they do. So we will now
be working with funded next. They have
just launched a deal.
I'll read it out to you.
For new users, you will get 30% off the
50k and 100k legacy accounts and 20% off
the 25k legacy account. My advice would
be do the 50k. It's the best account by
far. All right, so 30% off that. There
is now no 40% consistency rule once
funded, which is amazing, which means
you can hit big winners and scale. For
existing users, you will get 15% off
your current uh accounts on there, which
are resets, and you'll have to use the
link in chat to get it. All right, it's
pinned to chat and use code FCT30, but
the link is pinned to chat. If you want
to get that deal, that's what you need
to do. Which means a 50k account is
currently 111
bucks. All right, 111 bucks. And that's
not a monthly fee. There's no activation
fee. It's a onetime fee. So, it takes
you three months to pass a 50k account.
So be it. Um, it's a 1:1 riskreward
ratio on those 50k accounts.
So you need to make 2500 and as long as
you want and you've got 2500 end of day
draw down to risk. I don't think there's
a better account out there right now.
It's very very easy to pass. Very very
easy to get paid. Get paid every 5 days.
What was the TPT deal? Uh they've got
30% off on TPT and if you pass your eval
without taking a reset and get to pay
out, they will give you your money back.
So if you spend 110 bucks whatever it is
[snorts]
and you pass it and then uh you know a
week or a month later however long it
takes you get to pay out you will get
that hundred plus bucks back. So it cost
you nothing. So you can get paid for
free. You can literally turn zero in
investment into tens of thousands of
dollars on TPT.
Go over the deal again.
New users 30% off. I would advise you go
for the legacy 50k account. I'm only
talking about this because the market's
not really Has this just gone to sleep?
What's going on here? There we go. Um,
back towards this New York open. Nothing
happening here, folks. We're just stuck
in a very tight range. Just flat at VW
up and flow zones. Bears have control
right now. I don't want to be short
here. If I'm going to be short, I want
to be short up here or up here. That's
why I'm not really touching this. Okay,
so funded next 30% off for new users on
the legacy account. Look at the 50k.
It's the easiest one to pass. All right.
It's a onetime fee. 111 bucks right now.
Onetime fee. Not a monthly fee. No
activation fee. Onetime fee. That will
get you $2,500
in draw down. All right. It's not a
trailing draw down. It's end of day. And
all you need to make is $2,500. You can
take as long as you want to make that.
There's no monthly renewal. It's a
onetime fee. You can have six of those
accounts. You can get paid out every
five days, right? You just need 5 days
of $200 or more. And uh you can take up
to $6,000 per account every 5 days. And
once you get to 30 days, you can take
all of it out. And uh the split is an
80/20 split. So like TPT,
but if you hit a big winner,
you can take a big old fat payout on day
30.
Uh I'll have to check on the live stuff.
They probably just roll most of your
account over. But I mean, at 30 days,
you can take 100% of it. So why would
why would you even want to go live? Just
take it all out.
Just go live in your own account. Yes,
includes trade ninja. I will never
promote a platform that doesn't include
trade or ninja.
Well, I've got a video going live uh
later today, but it it has the old
prices, so it's cheaper now. But the the
link, if you look at the top of your
screen, there is a link up there in the
code. You've got to use that link and
that code to get the price.
It's like an affiliate only link or
something. And well, that's what they
told me anyway.
Hit your goal. $50 trade on Apex. There
you go. Nice.
on top step is that they've changed
their payout rule, their payout rule
policy once you take that payout.
They've actually gone and back and
changed it again because there was such
a kick up. They're basically saying you
had to make the same amount of money
again in your second and third cycle.
They've changed it now just saying, "Oh,
you need to have positive P&L." What
annoyed me was that they left that rule
out on all advertising and of course
their coaches also who want to talk [\h__\h]
about every other firm and every other
trader who are just woeful also left it
out. So they want to take the high
ground but leave the most important part
out which is a change in payout policy
on the PAS but they've gone and changed
it again and now they're saying oh it's
not confirmed yet. So, we will see. But,
yeah, not a company that I think has
good business ethics as I've talked
about before.
Okay, so just in the middle of this
range. We're just we're literally in no
man's land at the moment, folks.
If you're [snorts] wondering why I'm not
like actively trading other than being
ill, there's actually no no area here
I'm interested in trading in. You would
have heard me talk about this before,
like when we open up in no man's land.
I'm not really interested if I'm going
to be a buyer today. All right, I want
to be a buyer
at least at value area low 750, 700s,
maybe a look below even into 600s and a
reclaim. If I'm going to be a buyer, I'm
going to be a buyer down there. I'm not
going to buy the top of this range up
here. I'm not really interested buying
the top of this range up here when we're
in a major sell and supply is up here,
higher time frame supply and here. So
any look up into here, I'm interested in
shorting. If they just puke this today,
it is what it is. The the sell
opportunity, right, was on this failure
to move higher here. Pre-market is this
8:30. There's your high. There's your
failure to move higher. There are the
key levels. There's the lower high, but
selling the bottom of this range. Yes,
it could come down to here, but could
also come up to here. So, our risk,
right, is one one. It's not a great
location. Remember, we're always talking
about location and momentum before any
trade.
[snorts]
[cough]
Oh, I'm glad you're happy, Rosco.
Uh yeah, I made more than that. I took
uh $25,000 out on that on that first
payout.
Left a good chunk in. And um I'm going
to get I actually did it on a 100k
account because I didn't realize how
good the 50ks were. So, I'm got some
50ks in the works now. Get those passed.
Link them all together. I'll try and get
six 50ks and just go 6K every 5 days is
probably a bit tough to start with. But
if I can get to day 30, I think there's
a good chance of getting 50 plus,000 out
of those 6Ks fairly easily,
especially if uh the market's moving.
Okay, back down towards these lows.
Remember, we're thinking about if you're
short this, I don't like I can
understand being short this. It's just
the location's not ideal, but the
momentum is there at the moment. You are
seeing that bare flag. There is a fail
at New York open. There is a reason to
come lower right now, which is what
you're seeing.
What size do I trade? I actually trade a
a mini on those 50ks because it's not a
trading draw down. [snorts]
So, if we can get a good setup and get a
mini in.
Lots of sellers here on the tape. I'm
really sorry, guys. I'm going to have to
use a bathroom already. That's how sick
I am right now. I'll be right back.
Okay.
Oh wow, what a breakdown. All right,
coming into level of interest
coming [snorts] into these level of
interest. Then previous week point of
control, previous day value area low.
Market's heavy here this morning. That's
big selling this morning.
Back to uh
back to where you came from market. All
right. It can go all the way down to 600
if it wants here. It's very very
possible if they move lower and reclaim
and obviously there's that move uh back
upside which is very possible back
through previous day value area low. At
the moment, you're just seeing strong
selling if they want to go 600s and they
will absolutely go to 600s.
So, I'll be watching to see if they
reclaim value otherwise. And probably a
move all the way back down to where we
once came from.
That ATR picked up, didn't it?
Oh, yeah. It did. 50 plus points while I
was away.
I'd watch previous day value area low
here they reclaim that they are so far
defending it on the tape
and if they fail previous week point
control sorry I got to zoom this out of
my down here we it's very very possible
we came back come back down to where we
came from like I talked about it's
wouldn't be unheard of at all yesterday
was straight up no structure
There you'll see more of a bleed out.
Not surprise me in the slightest.
Is that point control? Yeah, point
control now hit.
Still selling this. Not seeing any uh
action here on the tape. This is very
heavy selling. 600s. I'd say it's very
possible right now. Uh, one thing I did
just get noticed of or notified of, I
should say. Can't talk again. Sweating
my buckets here, is that Apex have just
done another sale. They've extended the
80% sale, but they've added on 100ks.
Now, uh, if you pass the 100k on a 80%
sale, you also get a $10 activation fee,
which is bonkers.
Okay, seeing someone try and bid here,
but I still don't think they're done
with it. I'm sweating buckets. I'm
struggling here.
Sweating buckets here, folks.
600s looks possible at the moment. This
next block all the way down here. We'll
have to see though.
It's very heavy angry market right now.
Very angry market.
[snorts]
No bid yet. Not at all. There was
someone down there at 70, but they don't
look very strong.
Big old sell.
I'd watch 700s and then previous week
point control and see how they at there.
But
is there any response here from anyone?
There's previous week point control sort
of test through here. Their test
previous day value area low if they can
get acceptance through it.
This looks really nasty on the tape. Big
big players coming in both sides here in
this last 30 seconds.
Huge buying at the bottom. Huge market
selling on that last pop up. Someone uh
they're being horrible to each other. I
don't think they I don't think they like
each other today. these players. There's
some big big players jumping around
here, shoving some pretty big lots down
each other's throats.
Sellers want to get to 600 by the looks
of it. They're defending that previous
week point of control.
That's what I'm seeing anyway.
Interested if we can get down into here.
looks like it at the moment. Maybe if I
wasn't feeling so sick that would have
been a trade that I would have taken. I
don't know. But uh right now I'm just
can't imagine doing anything right now.
I feel so sick.
It's probably because I'm talking low.
Just turn it up your end. I'm not
changing anything by end.
>> [snorts]
>> When is
you miss?
Still not done selling this. They're
being very very aggressive here this
morning. Tesla um Nvidia now 6.34% down.
There's a massive market seller just
come and slapped it here. Huge. There
you go. So, they're reacting afterwards.
Someone's pissed off for sure. Probably
got squeezed out yesterday.
Someone is not a happy bunny.
>> [snorts]
>> Uh, I don't track current week value
area low if that's what you're looking
at. I'm more interested in the previous
week. It's only Tuesday on light volume.
So for me, you know what does that
really mean? We've traded light volume
here for a day. Doesn't really mean
much.
Still, we trade lower. 600s. I'm telling
you, they're going for it. There we go.
Straight dump. Straight dump out of that
range. [snorts]
Oh, a reaction of 600 we did talk about
is probably where it's going to go.
Let's see if I'm interested in doing
anything. I don't think I'm honestly
well enough to do anything. It's the
bigger problem right now.
Will they trade back up to previous week
PC and sort of gut check that
That's what they're trying to do.
Comes the relief.
Sweet point of control. Maybe value
95ish.
>> [snorts]
>> into here.
If they get through that, remember this
is a straight
puke out. We can go straight back up
because this is very thin. So, if they
reclaim this area, they're going to come
straight back up here. This is what I
mean. It just feels like a rotational
market to me. So, think about what we
talked about this morning. This is what
we're seeing. We've come from one side
of the rotation
to the other side of the rotation.
I wanted to be a buyer down here and I
want to be a seller up here. I don't
really want to sell there. It's just
unfortunate that's where we opened. And
here comes the squeeze. So, right back
through.
[snorts]
They can really rip this now if they uh
can base over
80s.
Strong bar coming in here. You'd want to
see a seller come back in and see if
they can actually produce a higher low
these buyers because right now it's just
one way down, one way up. There isn't we
haven't formed any form of structure. So
imagine some sellers will come back in
at some point. At some point
[snorts]
So, see if this pullback holds. If not,
are they going to resell it to new
loads? Sorry, folks. I'm doing my best
here.
[sighs]
still squeezing. [snorts] This might
come all the way. Honestly, it might
come all the way back up to here now.
So, VW up now and it might come all the
way back up to here because you've got
no structure in here. That was straight
move down, straight slingshot back
upside at this point. This is the market
that we've got right now.
You just have to deal with what you've
got.
That was That was your pullback to hold
this little shelf, this little thing
here. That's your TP1 and that's your
TP2. If you're long, if they resell
this, they're going to look to retest
this low. All right, just be be very
very smart with uh how you're playing
today.
[snorts]
>> [cough]
>> and the squeeze is on all the way back.
There you go. [clears throat]
So, if you took this long from here or
maybe played that little pull back, make
sure you're paying yourself any weight.
Again, I'm not trading today, guys.
isn't far too sick to do anything.
Fortunately,
the squeeze is on so far. Just move your
stop out on the way because you're very
thin back upside as well. So, you've
been thinned down, thin up. There's no
structure here. You're going to have to
be careful [snorts]
and protect yourself because you don't
know when this squeeze ends. You have
targets to aim for above, but it doesn't
mean it gets there.
[clears throat]
>> [snorts]
>> I'm going to turn this light down a bit
though. My eyes
catch up. [snorts]
All right. So, you'd want pull back to
hold if you're going to play long.
700ish 680 700. That's what you're going
to need. That's going to need to hold
that.
[snorts]
Didn't even get down there yet. very
very squeezy at the moment. You need to
wait for a pullback here if you're not
already long. You do not want to chase
this here. You're in no man's land
again. They're doing this for a reason.
They opened up in no man's land. They
puked it. They bid it straight back up
and we're back into no man's land with
no structure again. This is not by uh by
accident. Let's say [snorts]
they're going to make this hard because
this is how they build liquidity. Yeah.
And 10 a.m. news. You're right. 2 and a
half minutes. Well, thank you for the
reminder. Absolutely right.
>> [snorts]
[cough]
[clears throat]
[snorts]
[sighs]
[cough]
>> Oh my gosh.
What a nasty virus or flu this is.
Honestly,
Bloody awful. [clears throat]
Bloody awful. [snorts]
[snorts]
>> [clears throat and cough]
>> Yeah, really not good. Peter, I just
didn't want to not turn up for you guys.
I said I'd be here, but definitely not
in any fit state to actively trade. Here
you go. So, squeeze all the way up.
So, literally from one side to the
other.
Oh, they're so horrible.
We lack structure. So, all we did was a
rotation. And if you go back to the
start of the stream,
we talked about the rotations in this
market being probably this RBS
or if they wanted to drift through. So
fail here, back down to here. Now, if
they reclaim this, actually gets pretty
bullish at that point.
But there's your rotation. This is uh
so horrible how they've just done that,
but also not surprising.
>> [snorts]
>> Why is that not following right now?
[snorts]
I think it's got just got crushed as
well after that opening drive straight
back down to it New York open.
Oh, the SO was so good. But I mean, it's
horrible when it does this. Like, you
tap it and then it's gone. So, really,
what have you got to do? You're going to
have to risk 70 odd points here because
of the lack of structure. It's
It's really hard. You're going to have
to size down at the moment.
[clears throat]
You want me to look at GC? Is it being
really good? [snorts]
It's kind of similar.
I don't like that. That's looks pretty
bearish to me.
Looks pretty bearish to me. They'll
probably come and sweep those loads at
some point.
Are you enjoying trading GC still, JD?
Is that your go-to?
[snorts]
So, straight back down now. I need to
see if defending this or not down here.
Is there any structure for these guys to
uh build out?
What are they? Uh
well, not weird because it's fairly
obvious what they're going to do, but
not very nice.
Not playing nice. There's definitely two
guys on the tape who were not happy with
each other. Both had huge size. Seems
like the buyer won at those lows. Yeah,
they were they were very upset with each
other.
bids here at 50s. I still wouldn't
necessarily bid this. I'd wait to see if
it comes down here. This can this can
just be a lower high that fails again.
That's the thing. And they know they
know that. That's why they've done it.
They are very very aware of what they're
doing at the moment.
Give you a readout on the mag. Sorry, my
throat. Um Tesla 2% down. Nvidia 650%
down. Microsoft 1.51% down. You have a
split then. Microsoft Meta sorry 1.81%
up. Google 1.80% up. Amazon 0.14% up.
Apple
uh 0.80%
up. So they are doing completely
opposite things right now. You have
strength in the names which are not chip
related basically. So anything chip
related is getting absolutely hammered.
Anything non-chip related looks all
right. Looks all right. [snorts]
It's holding on.
Why are you doing this?
The energy today. Okay. Right down to
where we came from then. And if bulls
don't defend this level that you're at
now, then you're probably going to see
new lows.
>> [clears throat]
>> Looks angry. Someone's angry again. This
is where bulls stepped in. I'd say this
level you're at now, 80s. It has to
hold. If they don't hold 80s, I would
imagine you're going to get new lows.
At least that's what I'm looking at.
That's what I'm seeing.
[snorts]
Still they're selling it very aggressive
here. Let's see if
These levels are matching up. Where have
you gone?
How do I interpret that or consumer
confidence is is lower than expected? I
mean, I think that's probably everyone
already knows consumer's confidence is
going to be low because it doesn't
matter what they say in the media.
[snorts]
People are having a hard time right now.
That's how I interpret it.
I think it' be anything like that's
probably priced in is the best way of
saying that.
Like you have to think think when you
look at stuff like that even with that
that fear and greed index it doesn't
mean
anything. Do you know what I mean? Like
it doesn't mean anything.
We all know people are having a hard
time. That's that. We all know that,
right? It's like the most obvious thing.
People are having a hard time right now.
It's tough out there. People are
struggling to pay bills, [clears throat]
regardless of what the uh media want to
put out, things are expensive and people
people are feeling it. So, consumer
confidence is going to be down.
Um, where are you seeing like safety in
in those kind of stocks is your discount
stores. So, you're seeing like premium
stores. No one's buying anything from
premium stores, but your discount
stores, Walmarts, your Costco's, come
on, but please are still making money.
So, it's always a good sign of a
tightening economy.
And the range rotation continues then.
That's all you're in. It's all you're
in, folks.
So buyers defending
defending your current point of control.
Exactly, JD. There's no breadth.
Exactly. It's strong on not even seven
stocks really. It's strong on like five
stocks or something.
That's exactly it.
If you look at like uh QQQ,
is it NQE? QQQ.
We're still not reclaiming.
This is equally weighted. If everything
was equally weighted, right? So, I think
there's more room downside. It's just
when are they ready to do it? Maybe not
over the holidays.
[cough]
Alex can't breathe. [clears throat]
Cannot breathe right here.
Okay, back two value area high on the
day by the looks of it. Come and test
these 800 VW up there. Bulls really, I
mean, if they want to do something,
they've got to reclaim these areas up
here and get up here. I mean, I just
think you're nothing more than a range
rotation right now, right? Failed the
highs. Like we said, we would want to be
short up here this morning. Didn't get
that. The cover point was down here,
right? Was your RBS zone and your value
area low. They've bid back off that. You
don't want to be buying the highs here
and you can't fade a move which is uh
this aggressive and it's liable to
squeeze. Market's done well I had to get
this open 277 points this morning. Both
up and down by the way has done it down
and basically pretty much back up. So
your range is violent.
[snorts]
[clears throat]
No activation fee on the deal. Yeah, no
activation fee. So I I'll go through
those deals again because it seems like
a lot of you interested. TPT is 30%
discount. There is no activation fee and
if you pass without doing a reset and
get to pay out, they will give you your
money back for whatever you paid for
that eval. Probably like 120 bucks or
whatever it is. Apex just announced an
80% discount.
Okay, with [clears throat] still with
the $40 activation fee, but they've
thrown in an added bonus. If you do the
100k accounts, the activation fee is
only 10 bucks. All right, so that's
probably the cheapest all-in-one you can
get right now. It's super cheap if you
want to do 100k. And then funded next
[clears throat and cough] I posted this
morning. It's linked up uh above. That's
probably
one of the better ones right now. Um it
will currently cost you 111 bucks for a
50k account if you use my code and link
above. It will only work with that link
above.
Oh, it shouldn't be.
It shouldn't do that, Jade. Um, I will
message them.
So, you've gone all the way through to
payment. You've selected the right
account
and it's still doing that.
These are the Black Friday sales that
I'm talking about, Market Stalker. These
are their Black Friday sales. This is
exactly what it is that I'm telling you
about.
See, good of Apex to extend and that
100k offer is well, it's pretty
interesting. I would say $10 for
activation is pretty good. We get a news
catalyst event. It might be worth having
a shot.
Code didn't work. Let me message them.
So FCT30 doesn't work.
What about FCT?
Correct. No, you you can't take more
than a month. You shouldn't need more
than a month. the current price action,
but
it's [clears throat] an it should be an
additional additional try FCT30
and it's an additional on top of the the
code already. So, it's an additional
one. So, if you click the link in chat
above,
I can put it in and then then use SCT30,
it will give you an additional
amount of it.
that link there. Don't know why it does
it like that.
Let me message them.
I've texted now, so I'll let you know.
Oh, it's not live yet.
Okay, you got to wait until the end of
day. 8 hours.
There you go. Well, you know, before
everyone else.
Just wait eight hours.
>> [snorts]
>> Yeah, it's in Discord already, mate.
[clears throat]
Yeah, exactly, Adam. Oh my god, I'm
tripping with sweat. This is awful, man.
All right, so you've got lower highs and
higher lows. Oh, don't do that. All
right,
this is a nasty formation here.
Seriously, Trading View, I haven't got
the energy today. There you go. All
right. And it's going to probably get
tight in here and then maybe comes up
here. Maybe it comes down here. Maybe it
looks above fails. Maybe it looks below
fails. This is all about building
liquidity. That's all today's session
is. Remember, we're just an inside bar.
Look at your daily. All you are is an
inside bar. [snorts]
[snorts]
>> [snorts]
>> I think it might be new users only. Um,
might be just be new accounts.
New users. Yeah, new users.
My link will still get you a discount,
but I don't know if you'll get
everything off.
Have to try it tomorrow. I can't imagine
that's right. I think their language is
just off.
It goes live tonight.
Market's doing nothing. nothing other
than trap him. [snorts]
Down at that 170 doesn't look too good.
Big spacing out.
That looks awful. I don't think the
market's going to change from what we've
seen here. I don't think it's got a
reason to today. I think this is it. It
was just going to do a rotation and that
be it.
Can't believe that lower day was 602 and
we said 600.
Crazy.
back through previous days value. Can
they get acceptance above though back
into value? At the moment doesn't look
like it. This would be the move back
into yesterday's value. At the moment it
really doesn't look like it.
And just zoom out like look at the five
minute.
Nothing's going on here folks. that is
uh leave me alone if I've ever seen it
kind of move.
All right, if you caught the short this
morning,
great. If you caught the long back up,
great. But in here now, this is going to
just rotate and chop people up.
It's done its move. They've probably
made their money for the day. [snorts]
Yeah, don't blame me.
Don't blame me, Peter.
There's just no follow through either
side.
And the range is actually pretty big.
The ATR is still pretty big.
No acceptance over previous days value.
No acceptance underneath previous week
point control.
This looks nah.
Just nah.
back to value. Can't get through value.
It's current point of control on the day
here now as well. Just a thick traded
level. Until we move away from that,
there's uh there's literally nothing you
can do with this.
Uh yeah, it's going live. The funded
next one going live today.
Just waiting for the artwork.
Oh, come on, market.
Probably going to get out of here in the
next 10 minutes, folks. Market's not
doing anything, and I feel dreadfully
ill.
Thought they'd come back up to test this
side of value, but at the moment,
there's just no, not even able to do
that on the rotation. They're just stuck
doing nothing.
made money on the short and then long
and then retest weekly pivot created a
higher low and rotation from there. This
one,
yes, that made sense. We said 80s,
didn't we? Drifted just below, but
there's no close below 80s.
But now I don't know. [clears throat]
Don't know what they want to do. I guess
it depends if they're done selling the
chips or not.
[cough and clears throat]
[snorts]
maybe up to test value like we talked
about in VWAP.
It's not a shorted one up here. That's
the problem. The shorts much higher
right now.
And you're starting to get multi-time
frames spike,
which is going to be a problem as well
because that last pullback into 680 or
that low 600 which held could
technically be a higher low or is
technically a higher low on an H1.
So shorts don't have control until
that's taken out.
If we go back to what we talked about at
the beginning of the day.
Oh, wrong one. If we go back to the very
beginning of the day, we talked about
this move here probably being the
rotation between these. All right. So,
first leg, second leg, right? What
happens now is important. Does it do
this or does it reclaim for the squeeze?
And I doubt it makes the decision today
to be honest. I think we just build the
liquidity today and it makes that
decision
maybe not even tomorrow, maybe uh after
the holidays. We'll see. It's kind of
how they set it up into the holidays is
pretty tough I would say
to make that decision.
Is there a downside to getting two or
three accounts that refund on passing?
Well, the downside is if you're spending
money
and uh you're a newbie, you're saying,
and and you don't pass them, it's going
to cost you money. That would be the
downside. That's that's the risk, right?
because I don't play options. There we
go. Simple as that. Because I don't I
make my money trading trading uh
futures and I roll it into ETFs and
stocks. I don't trade options. Just not
my thing. I don't want to deal with
theta and gamma exposure and time decay
and no more right things.
I don't mind taking leaps.
Okay, back towards previous week point
control again. Market's still not
moving.
Range starting to tighten a little bit
here, but it's still pretty decent.
Still looking at 50 point M1 candles.
Do they soak here again? [snorts]
I'd say Nvidia 170 is going to be key.
Bouncing around there at the moment.
Look somewhat key at the moment. I would
say
protect the edge of this range and trade
back upside.
Yes, they do. And it's that 170.
You're going to go into chop between
these levels. Now,
what do I think of the 100k deal? You
get $3,000. you need to make six, but
it's relatively cheap.
Um, [sighs] I mean, yeah, look, the 50k
and the 25k are the easiest to pass. If
you want the extra little bit of wiggle
room, it's worth it. Is it a harder
pass? Definitely. It's very cheap,
though, but
it's basically the same price as the
50ks if you pass it, but you get an
extra what, $500 of draw. It's not that
much. Um,
just personal preference.
It probably comes in about the same
price, does it? Depends how depends how
much you want that extra $500 to draw
down.
First shot made sense, but do you think
taking the retest of globe XV up and 5
minute 20 was good idea? Alex felt a bit
risky after the squeeze up. You took
this one. Yeah, I think that's fine.
There's your shelf. That's where That's
your structure where we broke down from.
That's the retest of it. As long as you
I mean, as long as you had a risk, a
reason to something to risk off. That
made sense. Definitely. That made sense.
Now, nothing makes sense to me. This
short made sense, but the location
wasn't ideal. This long from here was
great long, but again didn't offer great
structure. And this short makes sense.
Now, I don't think anything makes sense.
Remember, we talked about coming back up
to this shelf.
All it's done is test structure.
Remember, like we built liquidity,
we failed. All right, Alex is in the
bathroom, but you get the big failure.
600 was the level, right? The RBS zone.
They bid, they go back to where we've
got no structure. So, we bid back to
structure bid structure fail. It's where
sellers took control. Back down to where
we bid off. Okay. Now, we're doing the
same thing over and over again. If you
think about this line and this line,
test that. Okay. Test this. Okay. Test
this. Okay. Test this. Something is
going to give as they keep playing SNR.
At some point, someone is going to get
hurt outside of this. We don't know
which way because it's a total gamble
right now.
>> [snorts]
>> Have a look at Google.
I mean, that's a good hold.
See how it tested structure? There's
your structure.
No structure here. Test structure and
held. If if Google fails this, that's
your first lower high. Really, the
weakness comes when it starts letting go
of this.
I wouldn't say it has to do it.
I would say the move is stupid.
Like
I don't think this is sustainable
for a mega cap.
I know it's playing catchup, but that's
like I showed you on the daily. It's
past three standard
past three standard deviation.
Just think, just put it this way from
what's this day here? Friday.
From Friday a couple weeks ago. Or
actually, I have to go a bit lower.
from yeah from the beginning of this
month it's added a third an extra 33% in
in value in market cap
in like four weeks.
In four weeks it's added
33% extra market cap in four weeks.
It's too much. It's not sustainable. Not
for a mega cap. A small cap can do that.
No problem.
On Google now.
50 is a big levels. Probably one of the
most traded levels up there. 564 lots.
But I'm not seeing like anyone offside
really. I'm just seeing it build out.
Vid is still holding that 170. And
that's the key level bidding off 170.
to previous day value area low. Can they
complete this squeeze up now? It's the
question. Can they run all these stops
through here and retest this? If they
reclaim this can get nasty, but again,
it's just a range. I wouldn't want to be
bullish up here. I want to I want to buy
down here like I talked about, but I'm
just not well enough. That was probably
a decent risk buy here because you don't
have to risk a lot.
That's being annoying. It's not catching
up with the price action.
All right, I'm going to have to go to
bed soon, folks. I'm really struggling
here.
Five minute or was pretty good this
morning. Really good actually. That sat.
Yeah. Failed look above really good the
five minute this morning.
So just remember I think you're in a
range rotation. So, you know, even this
move up, maybe they come up to here if
they get really lucky, but you probably
get sold. Maybe they clear out some
stops if you get very lucky and then
they get sold into. I don't think we're
going to see a sustained move outside
today. It makes sense for this to be an
inside day with look above and look
belows which fail because that's how
they're going to build liquidity for
whatever they want to do next. In my
mind anyway. That's that's how I'm kind
of viewing it. retest of this high up
here.
New York open.
Google's trying to catch a bit of a bid.
It's coming downside
back to value on the current day.
You're still inside your IB high. IB now
set. You're just no man's land.
As you get into the top of the range,
I'd be looking for looks above and
fails. If you get to the bottom of the
range, I'd be looking for look below and
fail. That's what I'd be looking at you
guys. Just a couple more minutes out
there.
almost there. It's a complete rotation.
[cough]
Video now well off that 170 level that I
talked about. So they saved it there.
Now trading at 171.75.
So, they did save it there on Nvidia. Do
they want to come back up for these
highs and clean these out?
What we got on GloEx? It wants to do
that.
That
would be a very big move.
Yeah, I will I will get some rest
shortly. Don't worry.
I'll probably take Friday off though to
be honest if I'm feeling like this
because it means I won't get to
celebrate Thanksgiving. So, I'll
probably take Thursday, Friday off. This
has put me behind schedule on making the
course for you guys as well.
Unfortunately, I wanted to finish that
this week.
I just haven't been able to.
Okay, so they're trying to break out.
There's your squeeze.
I would say there sell up here probably
maybe run these stops and a sell up here
if they get through this. Maybe a big
squeeze and then a sell up high. You
have to see. Have to keep your eye on a
mag
and just expect the rotation today. It's
what you have to do. You have to expect
rotations on days like this. Today
meta looking really good. I'm kind of
gutted I didn't size more into that. Got
a feeler on it and that's it.
I'm already up 5% on it on a swing.
Kind of annoying.
Battle eights here. Failing eights here.
Do they hold this pullback where they
just broke out from? I guess is is the
question or not? At the moment, it's
looking like a failed breakout like we
talked about.
Big failed breakout.
back to run point of control. This is
why I saying the edge of rotation. I'm
surprised they didn't run the stops
first. They might come back for it
later. Now,
here's your value
for the session.
I'm going to draw this out for you and
then I'm going to get off. All right,
that's the deal. That'll be the deal.
All right, let's just make this make
sense for you all
so you can see what we're dealing with.
to zoom this out. All right, here is
this is the previous week's value,
right? That's your previous week's
rotation.
Where's previous day? This is your
previous day's rotation.
This is your current day rotation, your
developing rotation.
Right? You can see how we've built
liquidity. We're not finding bears are
not finding acceptance underneath here.
All right? So bears are not finding
acceptance underneath here. Bulls are
not finding acceptance over here. So
your rotation is going to keep taking
place in this zone. If we get under here
and hold that, bears will take control
for a rotation lower. If we get above
here and hold this, bulls will take
control for rotation higher. But what
normally happens in these plays will be
bulls will get trapped looking for a
rotation and get dumped on or bears will
get trapped looking for that rotation
and get dumped on. What I would say is
momentum is with bears. So I'd be more
inclined to look for that than I would
for that today. And I'd be more inclined
to look for this than I would for this.
But we'll just see. Hopefully that makes
sense to you all. All right. Like we
talked about the very start of the day,
the levels I've given you have played
out. 600 rotation down, probably bid
off, probably build an inside bar. That
all comes from looking at the daily,
right? This all comes from understanding
we're probably just going to rebalance,
right? We have not got above, right?
We're not in breakout, right? There's
your swing. We're not in breakout.
There's your previous day. What have we
just done? We've all we've done is come
to Friday's high. That's all we've done.
We've just repriced. We are probably
going to build in here because what that
allows
if too many bulls get in here or if they
do this move next week or Friday maybe
it allows downside pressure. If too many
bears sold the lows and they do want to
print this higher, right? Then this
breakout here will be amazing because
you're going to have bears stuck here
and bears stuck here and then they can
get a squeeze and this can still be sold
into and you cannot rule this out and
that's still being sold into. It's very
very possible on a higher time frame.
Look at the balance that we've created
here now. We've spent so much time here
and especially
who remembers this level 25,000s to
700s. Well, that's basically all we're
doing. Hello. Hello. Hello. All right.
It's the same level over and over and
over again. They're going to keep
rotating because they know how key this
is for dependence on what happens next.
this. Remember how we built liquidity
here in September, October to get to
alltime highs. We can do the same here
for Santa Claus or we can do the same
for saying, "Hey, good night retail.
We're out here." Right? Hopefully that
makes sense to you all. I am now going
to leave here. Um I'm really sorry
folks. I I was really really hoping
I'd be well enough this week to trade uh
with you all.
I didn't think I was going to go as
downhill the last few days as I have.
Hopefully, it's not nothing too
sinister. Um, I do have some slight
concerns because it's gone quite a while
now. This is approaching a week and it's
getting worse, not better.
[snorts]
But hopefully you guys are prepared. Um,
what I would say is if if you are
someone that likes trading trend, today
is probably not the day to trade. All
right?
>> [snorts]
>> If you are not play, if you're not good
at playing rotations, be okay with
leaving it. What I'd also say, the one
thing we should probably talk about just
before I leave
is why holidays are hard.
Right, this is your daily. Just going to
stick some volume on here.
[snorts]
[cough]
Okay. Can you guys see that?
All right. This is saying to me sell
right downside pressure
increased volume once we get to the low.
Look at this big drift day yesterday.
Very, very low volume on that drift day.
Hopefully you guys can see that. All
right, that is a low volume drift day
up. Remember what we look for when we're
playing pullbacks. All right. So, if
we're in an uptrend, we want the up
cycle to be increased volume and we want
this cycle here, the pullback to be down
downcreased um in volume. Decrease in
volume. God, I can't talk. Right? So,
the trend is lower. This pullback leg
yesterday was decreased volume. If we
pin this in and then sellers come in,
that's where we get liquidation for new
lows. All right? So, just be aware of
that. This is holiday volume and
pullback volume. Do not get caught in
it. Um, especially those of you who like
trading GlobeEx, I'd be increasingly
careful trading GlobeEx this week
because the participation is uh going to
become less and less and less
as you get more and more New York
traders uh taking increased times off.
All right, folks. Um, big love everyone.
I pray the most high remove your
sickness speedy day, speedy road in the
mighty name of Yeshua. Thank you, man.
Yeah, I I'm I'm really hoping I feel
better. Um I will trade with you
tomorrow. Even if I feel like this, I'll
get on for an hour. Um
first day will be off for Thanksgiving.
I will probably take Friday off. I
cannot imagine there's any good volume
or any good trades on Friday. And if I'm
feeling like this, I think those extra
few days in bed might really help. And
then we can um
trade Sun uh Sunday. This is how ill I
am. I can't talk. Then we can trade
December really well and close the year
out with a good year. Um, all right
folks. Uh, I will pop in to uh Discord
after a little nap and stuff. Let me get
some more meds in me and we'll go from
there. Please trade safe this afternoon.
You can see it's a rotational market.
Please don't get stuck. Don't do
anything stupid. Don't fight. Remember,
your job in rotations is to see money,
take money, and survive for the next
day. Peace and love everyone and speak
to you soon.