Morning everyone.
Morning. Morning. Morning. As you can
probably hear, still not uh nowhere near
fully better. Actually felt possibly the
worst I've felt today, which is
surprising. So, I probably pushed it a
little bit too hard yesterday, but so be
it. We are where we are. So, I'll do my
best to stay with you for at least an
hour or two today. We'll see how we go.
But hopefully you had a good weekend.
Okay, starting off on the daily chart
then and we're opening up with a bit of
a gap up here.
Last week, we can have a look at last
week's levels
of
Monday's high into Friday low. We're
coming to back test 50% of it. All
right, that 50% level is basically 640.
All right. So, we're right in the middle
of the previous week range right now.
Might seem uh like we're fading hard,
but we're actually just stuck inside a
box. We're bearish overall, but we're
stuck inside last week's box at the 50%
mark. So, I'm interested how we react
there and also into the volume that
we've created here uh over a number of
weeks now. So, 50% 6 uh what's this? 640
and then into the 800s if we're going to
get into those fibs.
So aware of that. Structure- wise, we're
definitely making lower highs and lower
lows. All right, just a little bear trap
there and a slam down. So interested how
we act into this 640 to 800 level. Do we
reject that for a rollover or at least a
retest of that or are bulls going to
reclaim that shelf, this shelf here?
All right. To see if they can build
something like this to come and clean
out some of these levels. And then we'll
have to see. remember buyers are still
very much trapped up there but that's
what we're watching right so sort of 640
into the 800s and if we really get going
we we can talk about those 2523s
if and when that happens
let's move you over to uh the hourly
here
just focus on this chart here with me
for a moment
right previous week levels marked out
here if you want to take note of those
of you who haven't used volume profile
before. Those are your previous week
edges. Like we talked about, we're
coming into a very thick area up here
into the previous week point of control.
You can see this is where we built out
the most distribution, right? So we
distributed up here, huge distribution
here and then a little bit down here. A
bit more like accumulation to go and
back test. So this is starting to get
interesting how we act here. This is
this is your contested zone. All right.
sellers will want to remain having sell
pressure versus this zone, right? They
won't want bulls to reclaim these zones,
right? They just won't because that just
gives too much momentum back to bulls.
If you start reclaiming these pockets
here, bulls can start looking for these
drives higher to come and repric some of
the old imbalances.
So, we're watching these zones here. You
can see overnight all we've done gap up,
push, fail, double top, fill the gap
back to the same level. So we're trading
inside this edge right now. Basically
600 down to the bottom of that gap would
be 360 and the top of that gap is
basically 450s, right? Most of price has
held to 450 450 600 failed to the bottom
reclaim 450 600. There's your box. That
is your box. Um it's big box. All right.
Considering that was done in Globex, you
know, you're trading in
150 to 250 point ranges. It's not small.
All right. So, just you're gonna have to
watch your sizing. You would have seen
last week that uh
it was uh moving very fast, especially
on those days I wasn't here on Friday. I
was in insane volume traded on Friday
for OPEX. If you move up into the five
minute, you can see what we've done
overnight. All right, we're starting to
actually build out what's what's a bit
concerning is one of these. Right,
that's definitely what we're building
out at the moment, I would say. Um, so I
wouldn't be surprised to see a wash down
here and a price back up and a wash back
down and a price back up and that can
develop over a number of days. Remember,
we've got no news today. All the news is
coming Tuesday, Wednesday. Thursday's
off. Some people might come back Friday.
Unlikely there's too much volume there.
All right, so the the big contested days
are going to be Tuesday, Wednesday this
week. Um, and they probably want to get
off their desks early on Wednesday. All
right, so just be aware of that. No news
Monday, not uh high probability setups,
but that is definitely possible that we
go into rotation while we build
liquidity with a higher time frame to
make its decision if we're going to sell
down or hold the volume to print back
up. So, be watching those rotation
levels.
Um, let's get into the right one. Here
we go. Right, let's have a look what the
other indexes are doing.
Yeah. Yeah. Same kind of story. The
danger is like lower time frame bulls
have broken out of this. Is this just
like your leg that gets sold into for a
retest of this low would be my question.
All right. They're looking to repric
some of this. Same thing as ENQ. Not a
big difference. I do want to have a look
at the ETFs very quickly. Um,
this 650 down here was a huge,
huge, huge, huge, huge, huge option
level. Huge.
Biggest we've seen for a long time.
Probably remains thick. So, all the time
we're holding that. Uh, maybe we can
have a rotation back up. Not I'm not
talking about a huge move back up. I'm
talking about like the moves like we've
done here. If we start failing 650s,
then um I think the next level was
actually 642 on the options chart, but
I'll have to check in a bit. Q's, same
kind of story. That 580s was a big
level. All right, so worth marking those
out. 650s,
580s, those are huge, huge option levels
right now. Um Q's just looking to do the
same thing. It's trying to repric this
sort of swing midpoint at the moment and
we're there or thereabouts. You can see
after that we get into a golden zone.
Um, on the way down 600 was a massive
level. So, I'm assume it will be on the
way back up as well. Uh, Dixie starting
starting to really go now. This is what
I was talking about for a while.
Everyone was calling for Dixie lower and
I saying it was setting up for a
squeeze. Um, that is what we're starting
to see now.
And if we start breaking out, we can uh
really get going. Everyone, it was a it
was a down here. Everyone was too
shortsided and uh they they got
themselves a little bit caught in that
move. Let's have a look at the mag see
how we've recovered. Uh relative
strength in Apple which has been great
for me. That remains because they've not
heavily invested in the chips like all
the other companies. So as we've had a
rotation out of AI they're still being
seen as a bit of a safe haven and you
can see we're just still in a big old
range here on Apple. Right? That was off
the earnings move and this is still a
range. So, until we see a breakdown
under this range, I'm not going to be
forced to sell the remainder of my
position. We look pretty good. If we
start breaking down, then maybe I'll
start trimming some more profits, but
I'm trying to give it a chance. Uh,
Amazon
gapping up here on Amazon, and it looks
like it's tried to find a base there on
Friday.
And I'd say any pullback that holds 219s
can be a bullish rotation.
And they want to test this supply up
here. Very simple. So, very much like
the ENQ, balls in control down here.
Bears in control bank down here. This is
kind of your no man's land. You really
want to be trading an edge or an edge. I
don't really want to play the middle of
the range. Remember, we're opening up
that 50% of the previous week range
right now. Goo on an absolute tear at
the moment. Let me Wow.
Fair play, mate. Fair play. So, ever
since they uh won that law case, which
was like way down here somewhere here,
it was and it's just been risk on on
Google and that thing is pushing.
Impressive. Big old gap up on Google. I
imagine you will see some profit taking
soon
because that looks pretty extended to
me. I'd have to check on the daily for
the standards, but big gap up on Google.
So, gapping up on Amazon, gapping up on
Google,
gapping up on Meta. Um, I've got a
feeler on Meta at the moment. So, I
started a feeler down here. Just a small
size. I still think we can trade lower,
but I just wanted to get something small
on for a long position just to see how
it trades out, but I think there's still
a chance to move down into this uh
anywhere from 400s is where I'm really
interested in. 380s maybe midpoint of
this. If we can get a move like that,
I'd be absolutely delighted for a
capitulation bottom, but we will see.
Um,
yeah, another gap up there on Meta. So,
so far, tech looking strong. Microsoft
slight gap ups giving some of its gains
back from the pre-market. That's in a
range from Friday. So, just inside of
Friday's range. So, no gap up outside of
Friday's range. So, weaker compared to
the Q's.
Nvidia flat. Opening up flat. Remember
that's the one that's was heavily sold.
We saw some recovery of uh this is Trump
news saying, "Oh, maybe we will sell to
China." Not sure anyone believes that on
a Friday afternoon saving the market,
but we'll see. Um, by the way, lots of
inventory caught overhead on this one.
Right? Really important you understand
that. Lots and lots and lots of people
caught overhead on Nvidia. This is like
the breakdown level, right? If they can
hold 85s, they're looking to trade back
down to the 60s. Here is
basically over 90s. Everyone's caught.
Everyone is caught over 90s.
All the retail that bought the highs.
It's worth being aware of that. It's
flat on Nvidia and a slight gap up from
Tesla. That's been weak. There's no
doubt about it. That's been weak. It
lost the 420s. That was the big level,
right? So
push and fail.
Created a low here. Here's your main
pivot. Grinded back up. Double top.
Couldn't even take it out. Failed. Came
back down. Lost 420s. Sub 400. Back up.
Peaked above 430s and is failing. All
right. This is a rotation lower. That's
not a bullish chart right now. It would
have to reclaim everything up here for a
rotation. Um, so yeah, not uh not pretty
looking chart. If we look at equally
weighted mag,
look like they're going to be flat on
the open. No, slight gap up. Okay, so
equally weighted, slight gap up.
All right, let's see what you guys are
saying. How we doing for time? Few more
minutes left.
I'll do my best today, folks. I'm uh I
am struggling. I'm really really really
struggling.
All right, morning everyone that's here.
Uh, for some reason I can't see who is
above fall forward. Apologies for that,
but whoever's up there first. Good
morning. Uh, oh, there we go. Clint and
JMM. Good morning. Morning for Forward.
Inferrisk, the Richardsons, Jeff, Toby,
Christy,
Mark, Mr. ET, Alvaro, Miguel, Chris, DL
Smith, Thumper, Abby, Zade, Brandon,
Jonathan, Sergio, Oneonone, Larry, Bart,
Lou, Riley,
John, Dennis, Gerald, Danny Snipes,
Richard Johnson, Lindle,
John
Patrick, Red, Plasma, Noah, Marrick,
Tartan, Hold Strike, Ejector, Ready
Rosco. I love I love that change of
name. Looks good. Green otter.
Oh my gosh, it's just skipped down.
Uh, Leon, Raphael, Ronald, Troy, Lauron,
Prrisca, Three Bar, Jaddle, Gangster,
Gar
Real Estate, You Shot, Nobody, Steven,
Bert,
Troy, Aric King, Jappy,
Ariel. Who else we got in here? Big big
stream today. Mikey Dimome Derby, John
Dennis, Jacob, Steven Merch,
Aaron Cleveland, Exploit Vibes. Morning
everyone. Smash that like button nice
and early. Let's get these likes up. I
want to do some giveaways this week. I
really want to do some giveaways this
week. Remember, today's the last day of
the Apex sale, folks. Um 80% off Apex
$40 lifetime activation fee. Links are
down below. Code for that is FCT. Uh we
have had a new sale just been launched
today by uh take profit trader down to
30%.
But if you pass your test account, you
get all of that money back, right? So
it's probably about 110 120 bucks for 15
uh for a 50k account. And if you pass
it, you get that money back. So pretty
good. Basically free. So just take your
time. There's no time limit to pass it.
So a great time to do that. Code
Flowzone will get you 30% off there.
And I'm also running a sale on uh all of
the Flowzone courses right now. and all
the indicators. Head over to
flowzontrader.com.
Use code BF at checkout. That ends
December the 1st. You will get 25% off.
First come, first serve. There are a
limited number. There's been a lot of
you sign up in the last few weeks. So,
running out of the 20our courses at the
moment, but uh still some left and the
indicator's plenty left.
All right, so we know what we're looking
at.
What are you most of you looking at?
Look at that. It's pretty split today.
That says a lot, doesn't it? 36% of you
looking for rotations to build. 33% of
you looking for bullish moves to repric
higher. And 31% of you looking for
bearish moves to previous day low. Well,
that speaks volumes to me. That
basically says we don't know what we
want to do. And that doesn't surprise me
because we're opening up right in the
middle of the range.
So, here's the open. I don't know if I'm
going to trade today, folks. I'm going
to be honest with you. I'm feeling
absolutely dreadful.
Um, that first push this morning was
sold into in front of GlobeEx.
All of the mag opening green here. All
right, so Tesla just under 3% up. Nvidia
is flat, just about green. Microsoft uh
approaching half% up or a third of a
percent up. Meta 1% up. Google 3 and a
half% up.
Amazon 1.21% up. And Apple 0.69%
up. So everything green other than
Nvidia. Nvidia is a weak one. Surprise,
surprise. We talked about it's got a lot
of bulls trapped overhead. So I'm
watching how we act here and these two
levels above. Okay. Um I don't suspect
bulls take control above uh previous
week point control, but if they do,
their target will be previous week value
area high. But that would be a quite a
tall order to do on a no news Monday.
But you know, we've seen weirder things
in this market. It does love to move
higher when there's no news. this
market. It's been one of those markets
which grinds and grinds and grinds
higher when there's nothing.
Which eval is offering a refund upon
passing? Uh take profit trader code flow
zone take profit trader 30% off and once
you pass they give you your money back.
I did Raph. Raph, I've tried everything.
Um honestly it feels like co because
it's not going away. feel I'm the
unluckiest guy with this stuff, but my
head feels like it's going to explode. I
thought I was feeling better yesterday.
We drove back from Palm Springs. I was
on the mend. We got an early night and I
have barely slept. My head feels like
it's going to explode from the pressure
in my sinuses and my jaw and everything
else.
So, yeah, I don't know if I'm capable of
trading today. I'm very sweaty,
but I wanted to be here for you cuz I
promised you yesterday on YouTube I
showed up because I was feeling better
when I did that short video yesterday.
Today I'm feeling like uh
well, I'm not feeling the best. Let's
just not use any curse words. I'm just
not feeling the best. But let's see.
Okay, so through previous day high
target would be up here into previous
week point control right now. That's
where they're trying to squeeze to.
And uh if they get through that
uh we start basically we start getting
thick um from 660s like we talked about
all the way up into 700s. If they get
through 700s they can trade to 775. If
they get through that they can go all
the way up to 8 and 900s which will be
an impressive move. Um we're already
moving skipping and very fast out the
gate folks. All right we're skipping and
moving very fast out the gate again.
So, just be careful.
Yeah, I got my withdrawals from TPT and
and I took uh what did I take last night
from Apex? Took 18,000 out of two
accounts last night on Apex. Just wait
for that to come through. So, a payout
number sevens on Apex.
All of the market pushing here. GooG,
the one doing the alltime high breakout
here. 4.42% up. Tesla having a big day
or big morning as well. I'd watch Tesla
into the 420 if we can get there. That
was always the level. How does it there?
VIX sliding lower
as expected really after an elevated I
don't know five sessions from VIX. So I'
watch Rick Vicks into 21s and 20
pivot into around 2125 if it fails that
all the way down. Well, it can go down
to 1928 if it really wants to.
Thanks, Endo.
Still we trade higher. Straight up since
the open.
No chill. Squeezy squeeze. And that
previous week point of control looks
like a big area for them to trade into.
And then I'd say if we get through that
this next red box and if we get through
that all the way up here, which is
bonkers, but this market is bonkers.
big big thick area up here. This will be
contested as we get up here. I think be
interesting if they blow straight
through it. That's um well that's saying
something because this is the biggest
volume that we traded last week is into
here right now. Uh on Ninja Trader, I
have it just above into sort of 13s. So
I'll be watching up here to see if they
fail. All right, I'm watching up here to
see if they fail. They're
very close. Here's point of control on
Ninja. Sorry. So, I'm just watching
between the two different ones.
720s. Now, if they continue to squeeze
upside through the point of control, the
next area, what's this edge?
Yeah, 720s and then 760s. But I imagine
there will be some pressure up here.
Um, and if not, well, I think bears are
going to get themselves very, very
caught, but we will see. So, definitely
some profit taking up here. Watching
this to see if they fade it. Small
position in this now. Just small size
because I'm really not feeling too good.
Already locking in some money there.
Watching if they hold 700s, I'll cut the
rest. Cut the rest there. Can always get
back in again. and I'm not feeling too
good. So, I'm just going to take my
money when it's available today.
Failing that previous week point of
control and they can offer a rotation
all the way down to here. You can hold
this guys. So, I'm just really not
fitting up to it. So, any profit I see
today or will take it.
But yeah, if they fail this, I'll be
watching for this rotation down here. If
they reclaim, the next level will be
760. I'm already out of this. Like I
said, reclaim 700. Don't want to sit in
it. But if they fail a repush there,
sellers came in there into 690 680.
They're caught offside at the moment. So
maybe one more squeeze above. We trade
under 680s, then I think you'll see some
weakness based on order flow.
680s is the level I'd say at the moment.
Let's get um some volume on here.
No, that's the wrong one.
There you go. 680s. That's the shelf
being built.
I'd watch 700s and 680s. Sellers keep
trying to sell at the low of this
candle. You actually want failure under
this. That was what will confirm it.
It's the 80s. If you fail here, you can
snap. Potential to snap lower if you
fail here. Lots of sellers coming in
here trying to force this market lower.
That back down to 600 is their target at
the moment. Here's 80s. So if you if
you're in this, you need 700 to stay
heavy. Really, you want 80s to snap and
that trade down to 600 for you. You must
be taking profit. It's a squeeze up
today. You don't want to be caught the
wrong side of this.
You don't want them to reclaim
700 here. sellers got very very heavy
there at 695s under 700s. Here's the
flush for you guys. It's looking great.
Looking really great all the time I
hold. Remember, see money, take money in
this environment and then hold runners.
If you can get down to uh 600s, think it
looks good.
You don't want a reclaim of 700.
Needs to be an instant cut because they
can resqueeze it above that.
If you guys can hear that. My ears so
bad.
Uh Marrick, that's a very um good
question, but it honestly comes down to
personal traders. For me personally, I
would always buy Trader 8 because then
you can use it on Ninja Trader, you can
use it on Trading View, you can use it
on Trader 8 website. It gives you the
most opportunities to trade on web-
based and mobile and and link up to
other accounts. You look really good
here, folks. Look really good. Big TP
coming up here. Um, once we start
flushing under 650, it gets a bit weaker
down into 630. So, you can take a little
bit of a TP into 650. Got an imbalance
there. And if they fail that, you're
looking for 630 and VWAP. Looks really
good, though.
So, here you go. TP1 coming up here into
the 650. You've got a volume shelf here,
under that, into here, and then hold for
all the way down here. What a really
nice trade for you guys. Beautiful. Wish
I was feeling well because I'd still be
sat in it. Just cannot trust myself
today.
All right, failing 50 is looking good.
Watch this BW coming up here, folks. You
can take some off into this. Make sure
you've already paid yourself some. There
is a shelf here. They can support the
bid here if they want to. And then you
can hold runners. If they get really
weak, then you know where we're going.
All the way back down to the New York
Open.
Awesome. Full forward. Awesome. So, you
got in pre-market. Really nice.
Really nice, mate.
Okay, so they're trying to find a bid
here.
Vick's also finding a bid. The timing is
good. If Vic starts reclaiming New York
open,
we'll get some more weakness.
Looking good. Looking really good.
There's your VWAP and come down to these
600 retest like I talked about. That
would be a 100 point trade for you guys
basically. Or if you took the 80s break,
it would be 80 point trade. We have some
imbalances here into 620 to 600. So you
need to be taking the majority of your
position off there.
Really nice.
Why am I in a position? What?
I'm literally not in a position and it
says I'm in a position.
Uh
uh.
Well, that's weird.
Flattened that. But I'm not in anything.
Bizarre.
This is why I can't trade when I'm sick.
That exact reason. That is bizarre.
Where would that order have been out?
We got any resting orders?
Cancelled orders.
Cancel. Cancel. Cancel.
Bill. Oh, looks okay.
Who knows?
Okay. So, they're finding a bid in this
shelf. All right. Value for the day.
Like we said, there was an imbalance
there to hold. Now, they're going to
trade back up and try and test that sort
of 680 to 700. And if they squeeze
through that, they're going to go for
leg high because that's your first
pullback. So that was yourself from
previous week point control down to this
area. See money take money. If they fail
this, we'll make a lower low or attempt
to go lower low. If they hold this, then
there is a new squeeze available there.
Look to trade into 760s and then maybe
all the way up here if they really want.
But remember, this is a heavily
contested area like I said.
Yeah. And the weird thing is though, I I
have my um lead account open and there's
no orders on it. So there shouldn't be
can't see anything. But hey, it whatever
it's fine. I I caught it and I closed it
instantly. But it's just uh
always a bit of a worry.
It's a retesting the 80s and 700s like
we talked about. Sellers will need to
defend this. If they don't defend this,
then I think we can potentially squeeze.
If they successfully defend this, then
probably a rotation, look to retest this
previous day high. And if they fail
that, all the way back down to New York
open. So there you go. There's a retest
of those levels. That's why order flow
is important. Failing into 680 to 700.
That was the key level that we broke
down from. And you're seeing sell
pressure come in there. All right. And
they're going to battle it out here in
this rotation. This is value on the day.
Now failing this value would test
previous day high, GlobeEx, and New York
open. All right. So, this is where
sellers are in control right now. Right
here is where they came in heavy here,
right? And they're trying to defend
this. If they get successful, you're
going to get a retest of these levels,
right? If they're not successful and you
get one of these, you want to be very
careful that you don't get squeezed out.
So, it's why I'm saying see money, take
money, because also you're moving fast.
Like, we're at 206 points in the first
13 minutes already.
Nice, Richard. Nice. Yeah. Did any of
you get it with me?
Hopefully some of you got it. Some of
you might still be in it.
It's rejecting the key levels very very
well.
Yeah. W's in chat if you caught it.
Ah, here we go. Amazing.
Okay, you might have seen at the bottom
of the screen there is a funded next
sign which has been here you go
continuation of sale here. So lock, if
you haven't paid yourself some, lock
some in here now, please. All right,
because we have an imbalance here. And
if you can keep going, we can come down
to retest these previous highs from
GloEx, the New York Open, and VWAP. So
as long as you paid yourself, this is
your first lower high. This is now a
lower low. This is setting up really
nice for you guys who are short versus
680 to 700. This is the move blowoff,
pull back. We sold here. You could have
added here. your TP into here and you
hold for this wash down into here please
you do not fight 68700 on any reattempt
now um right like I was saying you might
seen underneath
there is a funded next logo um we have
now done a partnership with them at
flowzone you can use code FCT currently
they have 40% off and if you use FCT you
get an extra 10% off as well I will be
doing videos on them coming up. Um,
those in Discord will know I've already
taken a payout for them. Why do I really
like them? The legacy accounts you can
pass in 3 days.
Once you pass those, there is no
consistency rule and you can take 50%
off out of whatever you make in the
first 5 days and then 100% in 30 days.
Well, it's 90% I think.
So, a little bit like Topep, if you're
looking to scale and grow without having
a trading draw down, um they are
probably the easiest ones.
I don't know. I've never traded them
with them this this trust traded. So, I
only only talk about firms that I trade
with. I'm sure they're good, but I just
haven't traded with them. So, Funded
Next, they they go sort top five, top
three for me for next year.
them. Apex and TPT at the moment for me
are very very good.
I think it's both.
If you want to do the rapids, I think
it's both right now. Um, but if you use
code uh FCT gets you an extra 10%.
Funded next. Funding ticks are good.
Yeah, I've traded with them. But funding
next, I think for scaling are the ones
right now. Really, really good for
scaling.
size up and let your trades work for you
instead of having to scalp along.
Still trading in this sort of value area
range for the day. As long as you've
locked in, you're okay to hold.
You want to be careful if they keep
holding this in balance at 620 to 600.
Remember that was our target. That was
our 80 point target. If they keep
holding that, you want to be somewhat
careful.
You should have paid yourself a good
chunk of change already.
Yeah, lots of you getting it. I'm just
seeing this now. Antonio, Ejecto,
Steven, Troy, Miguel.
Lots of you getting it. Nice work. All
right. Be careful if they reclaim here.
I said 680s has to hold. Do do not bite
the tape. If they want to squeeze
through it, you just have to cut the
rest of your position out.
Cannot be fighting this up here. Sellers
do not get the breakdown, they will get
squeezed out. So 680 to 700 was the
level. If they reclaim it, cut the rest
of your position. You should have made
money already.
Nice, Chris. Nice work.
Th000 for the day. Done already. Nice
work. Yeah, thank you, mate. Hoping I
feel better soon. It's gone on quite a
while. Right. Sellers trying to defend
this level 680 to 700. You can see how
heavily contested it is up here.
It's a big level. If bear if bears can't
defend it, a bigger squeeze is on here.
[Music]
Blow zones are bullish, but uh it's not
in location I'd be really buying in
today. Not when we trade banging into a
big volume area like that,
which is why I wanted to play that trade
off previous week point control for the
fade and then the cover.
So bull's not reclaiming yet. This is
still holding up. All right, it's still
holding up. And if bulls get trapped
here and we let this go, we're going to
come straight down.
Big if, but if you're still holding
because it didn't reclaim 700, you look
okay. But this is the contested area,
isn't it? You can see we're rotating
between this. You want to be careful for
look below and fail. But if you get
follow through
all the way down into here, let's have a
look at the mag right now. Nvidia 1%
down. Microsoft half% down. Google
absolutely flying. Relative strength
there. 5.60%
up. Here comes the cell. Can they get
continuation underneath 620 600s for you
guys?
VIX back into uh New York open.
Now this 30 minute bar will be closes
will be interesting with left point
control high seeing weakness come in
here looking good now I think those
bulls might have gotten themselves
caught up above 680s and the ones that
caught 620s so you want to see
confirmation
for follow through need a rejection of
620s now you should have been paying
yourself on the way down please
really really good trade now you're you
should be uh
uh 100 points here.
You're coming into structure here. So,
make sure you're covering some. This red
box technically would be a blue box now
because remember it's top. So, R level,
which could potentially be
S level now, supply level, support
level, sorry.
Trading back down into GlobeEx
sort of highs. Uh, one thing I want to
remind you of what's possible that we
talked about this morning. Where is the
high time frames?
Did we or did we not talk about this
happening? Right. You want to be careful
here. If we fail this, we can come right
back down here. It doesn't have to be
today. It could be tomorrow. If they
hold this our level, we're going to try
and rotate again between these two.
You should have paid yourself into this
blue box. Really nice trade. Honestly,
that's all you need for the day. That's
100 pointer like done right.
Don't overtrade today when we're opening
up inside the previous week range with
no news.
I'm going to go and get some more
tissues and uh drugs here cuz I'm
suffering. I'll be right back.
Oh gosh.
So, continuing to rotate.
Nvidia looks like it might find a bit
found a bit of a bid there, folks. As
long as you paid yourself, you're okay.
It's looking a bit more bullish. It's
starting to reclaim. Testing current
point of control.
Holding those deep pullback flow zones,
isn't it? Holding that blue box, that
cover box as we rotate higher. Remember,
680 to 700 is the squeeze trigger.
All those balls.
I can tell you now, folks, I'm done for
the day. That was a one and done for me.
I'm really not feeling up to it.
Uh, I use a mix between um, Trading
View. I've thought about paying for uh,
sorry, my brain is struggling to think.
Uh, Tide from Unusual Wales.
It doesn't like and normally I don't
really care about it if I'm honest, but
the thing is we've moved so violently
and we were in uh OPEX that I knew the
GEX levels would actually matter. Um and
that's the only reason why like we're
now into new contracts now. Probably
won't matter so much in the next week or
two.
Okay, so they're trying to squeeze
through 68700s for that squeeze back up.
All right. And if they can complete this
squeeze back up after sort of a two-leg,
this is the question that they're
asking. Can they do this now or even
this if they really get going? But 680
to 700 is a huge level.
just did fail. New York Open
there's lots of places you can look at
it. I think Cheddar Flow is another one.
Um,
Tide,
uh,
I think of them all.
So still failing at 680700. Bears still
defending it. This rotation still
happening. Right. So you're just in a
100 point rotation right now. 680 keeps
failing and they keep finding bids at
580s. Right. So literally between these
blue and red boxes. Remember these have
been on your charts all day. This was
always red. This was red at one point.
We got through it. It becomes blue. This
is your rotation. They will have to make
a decision. If bulls win, they get this.
If bears win, they get this. And this is
the rotation. Edge to edge to edge to
edge. Edge to edge. Eventually something
will give. We got the first test. Oh,
that's it. Mental Q. Yeah, it's supposed
to be very good. Then that prints
automatically onto Trading View or
bookmap as well. I think
some big selling coming in there on that
last shove up.
Bulls can't get through that 680. It's
been very very very well defended so
far.
Just seems like a dangerous uh liquidity
build out at the moment.
Where is that buy side down to left? 55.
I think I just saw it.
Right into him.
Is there anyone above? Stop moving so
quick. Tape. Uh 650s. What's this block
up here? Slow down. Tape. Jesus Christ.
Can't move up. Level two.
650s. Yeah, lots of sellers coming in
there.
Side delta keeps getting smacked there.
Biggest level. Big big level traded up
there as well. Huge volume.
55. Big volume traded at 55s. Big volume
traded at
Yeah. 50s, 52s, and 55s.
Moving fast though. The tape right now.
A RTY breaking out. Yeah, it's not
surprising. Bit of a rotation back into
some small cap names.
Yeah, relative weakness YM red on the
day, but it's trying to go red to green
at the moment. Tried to play catch up.
Nothing's really happening here, folks.
She's just trading between the two
levels.
VIX is failing. This has got the ability
to squeeze here. If it can get through,
it's got to get through the 680s.
There's a chance they try and squeeze it
out for a high day push. It's not
something I would trade, but just making
you aware what is currently setting up.
2 minutes until a new H1 and H4.
I'd say sort of 780 785. This level up
here is interesting. That's like the
edge of the volume from last week. After
that, it gets very very thin up to 890.
Still rejecting that level. Still
defending getting tight here. Someone's
going to get hurt soon enough.
Someone's going to get hurt.
What's up, Tyson? Morning, buddy.
Everyone's names seem to have changed. I
think it's that YouTube thing where it
changes it, isn't it? To your handle
rather than your name.
Nice, Andrew. Great work. Yeah, that's
it. hit your goal in a market which is
not particularly pleasant. I would say I
think great work. We got 100 points very
early this morning. First I made 20
minutes made a 100 point trade.
Okay. UH1 here. Here comes the high. So
through the 680s and 700. This is the
squeeze I was talking about. They
probably come and take out these highs
at this point. This high here, right?
Because they've taken out this level
here, 680, 700. They should complete
this rotation. If they're lucky, they
get a squeeze up to here. And then you
have to see if they sell from there. But
that bulls defended this RBS zone really
well. Remember this was resistance
becomes support. That was the dip that
held. This is first higher low. And
there's your squeeze and break out now.
So if you took the bullish play here
with the flow zones or deep pullbacks,
don't blame you.
You must be TP1 into this now and then
hold uh for 760 to 780. And then if you
get really really lucky, you might get
940s or 950s.
That would be a hell of a move.
But just remember, yeah, we get very
thin
over 780s. So you can call it the whole
number 800s, but after 800s, it's very,
very thin because if we zoom out,
we were straight down and we were also
straight up. All right. So, this is
no structure up, no structure down
through here. Very thin to the next
point. All right. So, you want to be
cognizant of that.
Where is it? Lost it all.
always looking for a new leg higher
here. If you did, like I said, if you
took the bullish move off the RBS or
reclaimed here or even if you're taking
it set at the 680, 700, make sure you're
paying yourself into this high day and
then hold for this next block up here
and then if you get lucky all the way up
here. There you go. Here comes the
squeeze. So, squeeze through 68700s.
Like we said, that's your squeeze level
cuz that's where bears try to defend. So
once they fail to defend it, they are
forced to cover.
Looking good. Looking good here.
Get squeeze out.
video trying to go red to green as well,
which will help if it actually is able
to do that. Just be careful here. Lots
of buyers coming in this last candle. We
need to complete the rotation.
Some passive selling into 40s, 50s, and
70s here.
Like I said, over this red box. Okay,
we've got the whole number 800, but over
that there is basically 100 point
squeeze available if they do not defend
here. So if we think about this, if we
were going to do a profile on this,
we're basically thick like this and then
we're thin and then thicken out. All
right, so this is thin in here from two
sessions. So bears will want to defend
this. If they get through this, they can
repric very very very quickly. It's very
thin that move.
Doing my best to stay here with you
folks. Doing my best.
I have to get my the gun. Make sure
you're taking profit up there.
You've got a little bit more to go here.
defending this shelf here at the moment.
I think he probably get one more little
shove up, but we'll see.
Fix testing mode.
Nvidia gone red to green. Microsoft
trying to do the same. Everything looks
pretty bullish right now. So if you're
in this long from 780,
look good. Just make sure you pace
yourself here because it is a big shelf.
It's red blocking above you
and they will defend a level at some
point whether it's today or tomorrow.
And it can be very aggressive when
they're ready.
lots of balls came in at um
those 750s. That's going to be a massive
level now. And they just got caught on
that last little push a little bit. See
if they repric it above again. So very
aggressive buying up there. They might
have got themselves a little caught.
I'd say under 750s is the more
interesting level.
Balls came flying in at 750.
Here you go. Is the test of it. This is
where they came flying in.
Big transactions here. This is fast
moving tape now at this point. Big big
transactions.
in balance down to those 720s.
So, sort of holding that sort of 50ish.
Didn't feel the imbalance.
Haven't quite Well, we have made that
red box to be fair. We have made it to
it.
Psychological level would be 800. This
is the top of the shelf really. 780
psychological 800 um through that then a
uh 900 point squeeze can't be a squeeze
to 900 can't be ignored at the moment.
You're seeing bears trying to defend
this top of the shelf. So if we start
losing 50s here, there's a bigger sell,
which is what you're starting to see
now.
That's strong selling just came in.
starting to lose 50s imbalance here down
to the seven sort of tens. So remember
the squeeze happened from 680 to 700. We
squeeze right the way up to the top of
this red block which we know is the edge
of volume and supply based on the
previous week. We're starting to see
some selling up there. We're just
waiting now. If you're going to play the
reversal, you just need these bulls to
get stuck.
You have to know their imbalances on the
way up. has been a bit of a squeeze out
so far this morning, but they have been
supporting bids. We starting to see some
more aggressive bears trying to bend
here. This is the imbalance right here.
720 down to the teens previous week
point of control. Do they hold a bid
here or not?
Mag all bullish still pulling back to
flow zones right now. Big contested
level here.
This is the imbalance that we held. They
sell through this is a bigger wash
coming. So we have to see how we act
here.
Back to that previous week point
control. bulls uh defend that
and maybe they've got bigger ambitions
back to the uh sort of 900s the previous
week uh value area high.
See bears want to defend 50s now because
we traded under 50s. Bulls are stuck
over 50s
and if they can't defend 50s there is
probably a bigger squeeze going going to
come and happen.
trying to defend it. It's more
aggressive here.
Got a small little piece on this just to
see if we fail here
on that last push up to 50. Already
locking some in. We're holding flow
zones at the moment. I want to be
cognizant of this is previous week point
control and flow zones, but I think this
is the area that they wanted to defend.
That's the shelf. If they squeeze
through that, then they can come out all
the way up here. Again, you might say
I'm playing counter trend. I'm trying to
time when the multi-time frame alignment
goes into agreement here.
Nice.
Down towards these 700s. Blocking some
in here. Let's see if we trade 680s now.
Any reclaim of this last level up here?
42. I will cut.
I felt sorry for the McLarens, man.
Like, well, especially for Lando. It
doesn't really affect uh Astria at a
[\h__\h] race.
I mean, blows that title wide open,
doesn't it?
So, if they hold 700s, I'm not
interested.
I want to see a wash to 80s to get any
more size off. Want to be careful here
because they keep trying to sell the
lows. So, I'm going to trim a bit more
here just from what I'm seeing on the
tape. Keep trying to sell 700 and not
selling through it. I want to see a wash
down. Here we go. Come on. Can we wash
through it? They're trying to sell it
again. There we go. Fantastic. Right,
there's the 80s. It's locking some more
in here. I'm watching this shelf now
into 60s.
Beautiful. Cognizant of New York VW up
and point of control. And if we get
lucky, we come down here. But we're
locking some more in here. Again, just
playing the tape when it happens in
front of us at key levels when we see
participants get trapped. Trying to time
that higher time frame, lower time frame
alignment. Really nice. Beautiful.
Remember 68700 was the squeeze point. We
repriced that.
Don't want to see them hold bids here. I
just want straight flushes. If we're
going to see weakness now, it it's going
to have to happen here. Otherwise, it's
just a scout back down for them to bid
off,
which it might be. Going to watch
previous week point of control.
Basically, use that as my risk at the
moment. See if we get a big old wash
here.
nice. We can trade to 30s and the teens
if they're going to if they're going to
stay heavy. 30s and teens would be my
next cover point.
Nvidia starting to lose itself now. Half
a percent down. Microsoft starting to uh
sell as well. Previous weekly point
control of my risk here. I will take
this off. Basically tap me. Uh it's
slightly different on Ninja Trader. So
that's why. And I'm out. Out on a
runner. Still not a bad trade. Not a bad
trade. So that 50's rejection and we got
as low as we've almost got another 100
points there. It's not bad.
Scalping away.
No worries, Kevin. Yeah, it's just a see
money, take money environment at the
moment because we're trading inside
previous week's value.
Yes, I am taking technically counter
trend on the day, but I'm trying. I
don't want to really be long
when we're uh where we are based on the
previous week's value and trading
upside. Uh the long here was probably
good. Maybe I should have flipped and
took that long up and then resold that.
But don't really have the capacity this
morning to be uh taking too many trades.
So two for two now.
So reclaiming that point of control,
testing value on the day.
Do they want to go higher? Have they got
ambitions for 800? And if they break
800, 900.
As the rotation continues, they're still
bidding us up. Just a slow drift up
today. Really no follow through from
bears. Balls are in total control. You
can see they pinned V up again,
reclaiming key levels.
Like we said, above this red box, you've
got the 800 psychological, but then it's
very thin up into here. So, do not fight
this. If they want to squeeze it up into
here, they're going to squeeze it up
into there. That is what it is.
What copier am I using? I'm actually
using affordable indicators copier at
the moment. What copy are you using
that's doing that? Black widow.
I haven't had any problems. It's moving
over
can send you the link if you want.
You get discount with this. I know
they've got a Black Friday sale. I don't
know if it's launched yet or not. I'll
put it in chat for you.
that link there I just sent
their copies are very
Rosco, I just got your email. Have you
sent me your uh Ninja Trader machine ID?
That might be it. If not, I'm not sure.
Otherwise,
sounds like you've got a few tech issues
your end recently, unfortunately.
Buckets, man.
Spy day
[Music]
might you might need to a restart on
Ninja Trader or something then mate cuz
everything's set up fine. Let me just
check.
Oh yeah, I can see you set up. Yeah,
you've got access. Full access.
You might just need an NT restart or
something.
It won't be the indicator. it be uh
something to do with your end
cuz I have it running right now on my
screen as do I know 100 other people in
Discord. Sounds like you've had a few uh
tech issues on that computer from the
sounds of it which is very odd. I'm
really sorry that's happened. It's
a pain.
Everything in drift higher at the
moment.
H1 looking like is leaving a bit of a
pin high.
might be worth um are you in the
Discord, Rosco? It might be worth uh
posting it in the Discord. Some of the
guys in there are tech wizards. They
might be able to help
see if indicators duplicate accountable
risk manager
and then discord bundle 295 for the
bundle or just copy. I'm not sure. I
haven't I haven't looked. Um, give me a
minute and I'll have a look. I haven't
looked.
Okay, rejecting or like trading in and
around that previous week point of
control. You can see we're building out
volume up here. Gosh, I'm struggling
today at 730s. They're defending this
red box at the edge. They're now finding
bids in this which is currently
flip it. All right, as acting as some
kind of support at the moment and we're
going we've gone from this level to this
level, this level to this level. You can
see how we've traded from level to
level. Right. This is how the market
trades from here.
Right. This was red straight through it
up into here which is red. Pull back.
Hold blue. Convert blue. Trade up into
this. Now trying to hold this. Building
out liquidity here. It will make its
decision soon enough. Um you had a 250
plus point move this morning already.
Initial balance going to be set in 10
minutes. And this is an area bears will
want to defend. If we squeeze through
this area, can't rule out all the way
back up here.
You cannot rule that move out.
If you've done the course, Rosco, it be
the at the end of the course. You've
done the course. It's at the end of the
course.
Oh, still trying to hold.
Magle green other than Nvidia.
Vick slow day.
drift higher seems in full effect right
now.
If we get through this in the 800s then
obviously those 900s are the target. Let
me just check the book if anyone's up
there
at 875. Where does this actually come in
a bit higher?
What you're not seeing today is
aggressive selling like we've seen for
the last week. That's definitely not
happened yet. Not got to an area where
they're interested in selling yet. Not
aggressively.
What's in control right now? Lower time
frame.
video trying to go red to green again
for the second time today. Approaching
its closing price.
This is a big area up here, folks. All
right, it's a massive area
based on weeklies. All right, so if we
go down to here,
right,
it's this shelf here. We talked about
this area earlier. This is the contested
area. Bears will want to defend this to
force this rotation. And if they don't,
the squeezes up available to here. Bears
will want to defend that. If they don't,
oh my god, we're going to give back that
whole move from Thursday.
Right. I'm not convinced capitulation
low is in yet. I'm not. But uh
hey,
these market makers will do whatever
they need to do to make their money.
Okay, back down to the 700s again.
Nvidia sold into its close. All right.
So, tried to go red to green. Found a
bit of a wall there.
Starting to see a little bit of stronger
selling on the tape here. It's the first
time today I'd say there'd been a bit
more strong selling on the tape here. Be
aware of that.
Watching this to see how we now. Much
stronger selling coming in here under
700.
There's an imbalance here.
So, watching
much stronger selling. They're being way
more aggressive now on the tape. So,
let's see if there's a buyer trying to
soak or if this just gives back and
collapses. You'd be watching that VWAP
again.
Way stronger. They're coming in starting
to hammer this now with market orders.
Way stronger. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
I haven't got any add-ons running, but
Matt, what are you talking about?
What is an internal high or low? Like
this would be an internal high.
Yeah, because your swing points on the
day would be from here to here. So all
of this is liquidity created internally
between this and this.
Yeah, strong selling here. Strong
selling here.
They are trying to hold this up. There's
someone on the tape trying to soak this
in this level
around this 700.
There is a buyer trying to soak it.
Sorry folks. I'm trying to do my best
here that I can, but I'm uh very croaky.
I will get my words mixed up. My head's
very foggy right now, but I'm doing my
best to call it as I see it.
So, I'd say buyers have failed over 740
so far this morning. Every push over
that has been defended into this edge of
range, this red box. We're trying to
find a bid here at the moment. I'm like
I said, I wouldn't want to be a buyer up
here. I think it's way too risky. Your
buying opportunity were at the lows.
It's this market is favoring swing
positions at the moment. If you bought
that squeeze out from Friday,
right, you're laughing. If you bought
this squeeze out from Friday, I wouldn't
want to be a buyer all the way up here.
Like, what's that price down there?
900s. You We're 800 points higher. I
really want to be buy 800 points higher
at last around last week's point of
control.
So they will do whatever it is they want
to do. If they want to get up here, they
will get up there. If they want to sell
that, they will. If they want to repric
all the way up here, they will.
I don't want to buy uh top side of the
rotation though. Also, I'm not going to
fight momentum and had my two trades. I
don't feel well. So good.
What time frame do I use primarily for
executions like one or five minute?
I'm watching order flow um every like
every tick, every second, right? So,
what I care about is where we're coming
into key levels on like an hourly or a
daily or a weekly and then I'm focused
in once look like like look at these
levels. These have been up here all
morning. I'm focused in once we get up
there, how do we act? What happens to
the order flow? Right? Same as we took
this short here. Once we got up there
into previous week's point of control,
how do we act? Then I'll take a
position. Then I'm zoomed in into like a
one minute or watching tick by tick. But
in between, I just try and relax and
give my eyes a break and let it do
whatever it is it wants to do. When
we're not at a level, I don't really
care because then you're just trading no
man's land. When we're at a level, how
we act becomes important. Then I'm
zoomed in. But people get confused with
that. They watch the one minute all the
time. like you will get exhausted if
you're watching a one minute or 500 or
1,000 tick all the time. Just set price
alerts if you're not um good at waiting.
Set price alert for a key level, let it
get to the key level, come to your
computer, then dial in and watch it.
Oh my god, man. My right ear.
This is the one I'm partially deaf in
from DJing, but it really really hurts.
Every time I get an infection, it kills.
I just want all the stuff to come out.
It's just all stuck in here and
nothing's coming out. It's the worst
feeling.
So, you can see there's a battle up
here.
You see it on book map above you.
Move this in for you a little bit.
Sorry. So you can see zoom this in. So
you got passive sellers up here sat on
the book.
I was looking to complete a squeeze by
the looks of it to trade to the edge of
this volume. Remember after that 800
psychological and then there's a gap.
This is very very thin. I wouldn't want
to do anything in this. Right? You
that's no man's land. You could look
above and fail. Initial balance now set
as well folks. All right. IB now set as
well.
Big selling here. This is aggressive
back down to the 700. Remember, there's
been a buyer on the tape around this 700
so far this morning.
It's way more aggressive selling at
market there.
They are still holding it up. This guy
at 700 is soaking this tape so far this
morning. He might maybe he's got an
ambition of where he needs to get it to.
We We don't know, do we? We He can do
whatever he wants to do. I'd say once he
gets out the way it might get a little
bit nasty because he has been here all
day.
Sorry, I know I'm pulling weird faces,
but I cannot explain the pressure in my
ears right now. Should not be sat here
really.
Our trend is bullish. Uh, not for me.
Not for me. It's just a repric. I I
would say your swing, if you look at
your swing high for me, the hourly does
not change until we get above 25,300.
Yeah. So, we're in a repric level here.
Let me show you. Uh
if we think about legs, you got to think
about legs. Someone asked about
internals and externals earlier. This is
a good way to to look at it, right?
This was the liquidity built out and
then we fail. Okay. Swing low. Swing
high. Swing low. Swing high. Swing low.
Swing high. Swing low. Swing high. Swing
low. Okay. Where are we bullish above?
We're not bullish until we take out the
swing high.
Right. We're not technically bullish on
the hourly until we take out a swing
high. Yes, we've created liquidity here.
Yes, this is two leg moving higher, but
this is your counter trend leg which is
liable to be sold into to make a new
low. The hourly shifts bullish when we
print above this, right? When we take
that out and we shift to bullish
structure. That make sense?
And you make it really simple. There's
your downtrend. We're in a channel,
right? We're printing up for this
channel. We're probably going to get
sold into at some point.
So, you have to understand the swing
points.
Who was it that asked that? Peter, does
that make sense to you, Peter? I can
draw it out for you if you want like in
a simplified terms. It's really
important that you understand that
though. A lot of traders get that wrong.
They're
trying to squeeze this. They are
attempting to squeeze this. There's a
passive seller up here at 60s and then
800s. All clear. Yeah, no worries. Yeah.
Yeah. As long as as long as you as long
as you get it, mate. Really important
you understand that.
Guys, I'm going to be honest. I don't
know how much more I've got in me here.
I'm starting to um sort of sweat and
shiver a bit. So, I'll do my best to
stay here. I don't think I'm going to
make it to lunch. If the sooner I get
off, the sooner I'm going to get better.
I'm really sorry. I thought yesterday I
was going to be absolutely fine today. I
couldn't believe that slept like I did
and woke up feeling so crap. But I will
do my best to stay here as long as
possible.
Let's look at that fib as well from
wherever that was it Thursday cell
bull trap high down to the low
and we're coming right into 785 is the
start of the golden zone fib. So if you
go from that high on Thursday down to
the low on Friday we have traced
retraced now 61%. This is a golden zone
fib, right? So the fib starts here.
It's why I don't want to be bullish.
It's not a good location to be bullish,
unfortunately.
I know we're squeezing higher like not
going to fight it.
Location not great.
Doing my best here.
You're looking for a sale, Kevin. Yeah,
it's not a bad area, but there's still
bulls are still coming in here at the
moment. You need to wait for an exchange
and bulls to get trapped in some form of
displacement. It might come soon. That's
what I'd be waiting for if I was you.
Exactly. Wait. Exactly. Wait for the
direction confirmation. Wait for a buyer
to get trapped. like a little blowout
top or an exchange where we leave a key
level. Otherwise, you're just fighting
it so far today.
You know, bulls are in control, aren't
they? All right. So, if you bought that
RBS, you're in control. If you bought
this RBS, you're in control, right?
We're in higher prices here. So, if you
don't mind joining momentum longs, they
are playing for you. Flow zones are
holding. We haven't seen a blowoff and a
let go of volume. We might not see it.
Might might not come today. We're in a
no news day. No news days often just
drift higher. They often often drift
higher is uh very possible.
800 looks like a sort of target here.
But like we talked about, it's thin.
After this on a weekly, it's very thin.
Previous week value area is basically
930s,
940s, but actually we don't really get
thicker until we approach those 25,000.
So, you want to be careful if we get
through here that if they really want to
squeeze this, they'll squeeze straight
upside, which would be a nasty move.
Basically, repricing Thursday very
quickly.
Big transactions happening here.
Big market orders. So, it's probably
shorts getting stopped out here. So, I'd
say the top might come soon if this uh
gives that look above and fail. Okay.
Lots of guys got popped there. Lots and
lots and lots of guys. And see what they
do, how they react. We watching, you can
watch initial balance. It's still got
more juice in it potentially, but I'd
just be uh very cautious because we're
at that shelf that I've been talking
about all day. The top of that red box
is the edge of that shelf. And you saw a
lot of market buyers coming in trying to
buy outside of initial balance. If it is
a massive big if, if they fail here,
there's that rotation back down. if if
they do the look above and fail. So far,
they're holding bids and they've got 800
to aim for and then above that
925,000. But that would be um a hell of
an impressive move. I'll be honest.
So far, looks like a bit of a look above
and fail with buyers caught up there.
Definitely seeing some selling here.
Yep. Look above and fail so far by the
looks of it. Small short position is
what I'm looking to take here. If I can
see an entry model that I like.
Not seeing it yet.
So, big buying came in 760s
and 770s.
Do we displace away from that? Do we
leave them trapped and displace away
from it or do we just hold? If there's
still a buyer on the tape, you can't do
anything. But there's been a buy at tape
all morning at 700s.
There's the flush. I need an entry if
I'm going to get this. Don't want to
enter late.
Can't see an entry model here. Lots of
sellers coming in there and they're not
moving lower. So, there's a passive buy
there at 750.
Passive buy at 750. Still not in.
There's no entry model for me here.
Still soaking. Still absorbing.
And this level here is where they would
need to reject.
Not really liking what I'm seeing here
for a short. Nothing. Nothing yet. Maybe
next candle.
Maybe next candle. Still holding. These
buyers are still walking up.
Looks like they want that 800. Remember,
above this red box is very, very thin up
here. That's why I don't want to front
run it. If they're not done, they're not
done.
Can't rule them out going to 900 or 25k.
[\h__\h] mental, but can't rule it out.
It feels like it's going to explode.
Okay. A lot of buying coming in here. A
lot of buying coming in here.
Is there anyone looking to sell today or
are they just going to let this squeeze
out all day? Don't think the high is in
yet. There was some selling there, but I
don't think the high's in yet based on
what I'm seeing.
Looks like drift up to me at the moment.
eights coming up here and then through
that it can get very squeezy. It can get
very squeezy up into this box. It's
pretty amazing if they get to previous
week value area high on a Monday, but uh
you cannot rule it out. This market's
done weirder things.
Where is Google? Oh, still sitting
around 6% up. Dragging that market up
with it.
New highs here 800 that psychological
level.
So you can think about look above and
fail for the initial balance
potentially,
but you want to see displacement. You
want to see them be a bit more
aggressive. They still not filled all
these participants at 800 yet. They're
sat there on the book looking to get
built 200 lot.
There's a bit of excess. I don't like
that. That 200 lot's still set up there.
Feeling an imbalance here.
Remember, there's been a buyer on the
table all morning absorbing
and structure is bullish. We're above
initial balance. You don't want to fight
it. If you're going to take it, it's
really tough trade this. You're going to
look for it. And right now, we're just
in straight move upside. It's just a
straight grind. So, you can keep buying
flow zones. If they keep holding initial
balance, they keep holding this. This
will become blue. Remember,
right? And that's what we've done all
this all this morning. Test one level,
come back to the other, flip it. Test
one level, come to the next level, level
it, flip it. Test one level, come back,
maybe flip it. So, you cannot rule out
this squeeze all the way up here. You
You just can't You cannot rule that out.
It's why you do not want to front run
anything.
VIX low of day
grinding higher. No news grind higher
right now.
Still not filled this guy at 800. There
he goes. He's filled now. Right. So,
huge market order buyers coming in here.
And do they hold or is this the blowout?
So far, they're holding.
That was a huge huge lot came in there.
Big transactions.
Still a buyer on the tape soaking right
now. Still moving higher. Still no
reason to be short on this. Still
grinding higher, expanding higher.
Shorts caught in this at the moment. But
we are into that thin volume area that I
talked about. Bears need to defend this
and they need to defend it soon because
if they don't, we're going to go to
those 900s.
If we go to 900, we might as well go
25,000 might we at that point.
which is impressive. So you'll be
watching the initial balance trades
today. Now if you hold IB squeeze, if
you let go of IB, look above and fail.
Watching this 800 now. Coming back to
it, we've left buyers trapped above 800
for now. Not a huge amount of excess,
but there is some. Uh I'd say you need
to trade under 92s, and really you want
to trade under 77s for any conviction
for anything else. Otherwise, they just
keep soaking.
There's a buyer moved up to 760s now
trying to advertise that he's trying to
soak which is basically initial balance
just under
mag all green now everything green and
gone green markets in a squeeze or a
pump or whatever you want to call
800s. Watching this 800s are still
soaking 800s.
Still not seeing aggressive selling on
the tape yet.
Still buyers in control.
back to these 800s and if they fail this
maybe initial balance
and then you can think about that IV
trade if they do start failing initial
balance big if nowhere near there right
now still soaking 800s
700 coming up on ES
level, psychological level. It's the
same as us. 700's ES 800 ENQ.
Starting to see a bit of volume being
built out here.
Big transactions here right now.
Actually, over under right now.
Still they're soaking. Still a buyer on
this tape. Soaking every single little
dip. He's soaking everything.
He was at sevens and he's moved up. He's
trying to soak eights now. He's
advertising eights.
Still they're buying everything.
Absolutely everything. All of the mag
green. No reason to sell this. This
continues to squeeze
and you can't rule out the move to
nines. Honestly, you cannot rule out the
move to nines and previous week value
area high at this point, which is
bonkers given where we've opened and
stuff. But this is the market we're in.
800's the level right now.
Actually, a little bit under
really fir firms up under 780.
So, sellers are stuck so far.
There we go.
Let's move back to eight. Does this get
soaked again?
Big selling here. They need to get their
way here, the sellers, otherwise they're
going to get caught. Big selling here.
into the eights like we keep talking
about.
Someone's still holding the bid right
now.
This is the last four minutes sellers
have tried in this area and they haven't
got had any success under 800. So
they're looking to have success under
800 and they can't find it right now.
There is someone passively buying
everything.
It cannot move lower at this point. Not
yet.
Well, volume will be lower this week
because it's a holiday week, Kevin. I
mean,
most people probably with any sense
wouldn't really bother this week. I
think if the market hadn't done what it
done Thursday, this week would be even
lower volume.
Okay, back down to Tesla 800. You can
see there's some bids at 775 760 right
now, but uh they're just advertising.
There's still someone soaking. Sellers
are caught at the moment. There's no
doubt about it. Seller sellers have
front run this 800 up to 820s and
caught. We don't have buyers with an
excess up those tops. That is sell
excess up there. So, I'm not convinced
how that is in yet.
The shelf's got a little bit bigger now.
That's your shelf. And they're still
holding it. And delete this a little
bit. It's a bit ugly. You can just use
the edge of this blue box in RBS.
said, I'm not convinced high days in
yet. I don't think we've got much excess
up there, but we'll see. 800 still being
defended.
Still to 800. If they fail 800, you'll
get a snap, right? If they fail here,
you can maybe get a snap down to here.
50 point odd snap. But so far, it's
being defended.
trading into those 21s we talked about
at the beginning of the day
back flat or just about red
now gone green
markets come to a bit of Just stand
still.
Just wondering like are they really
going to come for these river sweet
valley today?
Feels like the answer is yes at the
moment which is
just insane. The size of moves in this
market at the moment. The swings are so
big um per session.
Really, really impressive.
Someone's going to get hurt here. You
can see this gray box, this volume shelf
being built out. We are into sort of a
thin volume area. There is a little node
at 8.90. All right, there is a node at
890. I'm just going to Let's just make
sure this is accurate. Let's do this to
That's the wrong one. Let's do this.
Sure it's down far enough there.
Okay. So, that's to complete the
rotation will be up here. If they fail
here, then it would be a move back down
into this blue box or at least to
initial balance, but maybe into the edge
of value. This is where we really found
a bit 7:30. So if they fail this, I'd be
watching the trade to IB and if they
fail that point of control. If they hold
this or hold any dip, then the
completion of the rotation's up here for
bulls. It's asking a lot. It's asking a
lot to do that. But uh
hey,
we're only at I don't know 300 points on
the day. I think on Friday you had four
500 point swings. Okay, testing the
bottom side of this gray box again.
Still bulls are defending that 800
sortish area.
They let go of this. It might be a wash
and a snap. I need to be careful there's
not a bear trap. But
only thing I don't like is I don't like
the excess at the high. Don't think
there's enough buyers caught at the
moment.
Definitely starting to stall out
or green.
holding flow zones. Everything's still
bullish. No move away from volume.
Sellers have not taken control.
Last push was sold into from the buyers,
but it not at highs, but definitely sold
into above 804
and buyers caught up there, but still
holding the key level. Here you go. So,
starting to move away from this. Now,
can they have follow through to IB and
back to uh value area high on the
session? So, I've got a small piece on
this now.
See money, take money, I would say.
Watch the 775s.
Come on, baby.
Leaving volume.
Come on. Let's get to IB at least and
then let's dive through IB. Really nice.
Moving my stock into the money now.
So TP1 would be IB. I don't want to see
this reclaim. I really don't want to see
this reclaim. If it reclaims, I'm just
going to cut it instantly. It needs to
retest and stay heavy. I do not want to
see this reclaim because we had a lot of
aggressive selling coming in there. It's
a good hold for now. I'm going to move
my stop down. I've paid myself a little
bit. I'm going to move my stop just
above 800
because I think if we reclaim that, we
squeeze high of day because I don't like
the excess at high of day or lack of it.
I know it's counter trend as well. I'm
trying to time when this peters out. So
far so good. Come on, baby. Come on,
baby. Be kind because I'm not well
enough to sit in this too long.
Looking for this gray box to reject. If
it doesn't reject, I'm out. Okay, if it
doesn't reject, I'm out.
Very close to taking my stop here.
Just missed me barely. Probably going to
take me this candle. I can always get
back in, so I don't care. Paid myself
already.
How's it not taking me yet? Insane.
Might get lucky here.
It's coming in here at 85s.
Flush through this 85 lot.
Nice. Get through him.
Get through him.
They're moving the bids down, which is
good to see.
Nice. Taking him out. Watching 770s
next. Don't want to see this. Uh, hold
up here now. We've just taken out the
actual volume. They should trade through
85s now. If they don't trade 385, it's
going to be a problem. It should trade
through 85s and go to 770s now. Stop
soaking here, you little you little so
and so. Here we go. Thank you. Down,
down, down, down, down, down. Beautiful.
Here we go, folks. So, TP1 coming up
into IB. Don't be a dick for a tick.
Okay, here we go. Into IB. You going to
fill me or I'm going to have to move
this down? You going to fill me?
You going to fill me? Okay, I'm going to
take one off here
and then see if we collapse initial
balance or not.
It's three for three today. Oh, it
almost took me out. Cannot believe. I
think it missed me by a tick. A nice
rejection of that gray box. You can see
how I play these. And initial balance
now becomes key. If we fail this initial
balance, then I my expectation is to
trade back to point control and volume
and VW up. All right, so I'll be
watching TP2, TP3, and if they collapse
this whole thing back down to here. I'm
not going to rule that out.
All right, nice winner here, guys.
Really nice. Three for three today.
Hear how I said like we're not going to
front run this. We need to wait for them
to leave volume for the shift of volume.
Once we left, came much easier. If you
were short in all of this trying to
guess it, you got caught. If you just
waited, it gave you at least some money
here. 30 40 points again. If they
reclaim this, I'm not interested because
then they'll have ambitions of of uh
trading higher.
Can't rule out previous week value area
high with how we're trading today.
Cannot. I don't think we want to do
that. I want to see this happen here.
But, uh, if they do this, we cannot rule
this move out here out, which is why
it's very much a C money, take money.
But, we definitely left buyers trapped
over here. I just don't like this
excess. What I mean is this this high of
day
does not have lots of market buying in.
Oh, and what I like to see is lots of
market buying up here and know that
there's a passive seller saying, "Nope,
we're not going any higher." We don't
actually have that. If we look at
bookmap,
it wants to move.
What's the higher day? 17s.
Yeah, this like look at that. It's like
a nine lot. These are small. I want I
want like these big orders here to be at
high of day. That's what I want. I want
this big order here to be at higher day.
That's what gives me more conviction um
that we're starting to like really
transition, but we're seeing stronger
selling come here. No doubt about it.
You see these passive lots here. Don't
know why it's saying that. I don't have
any add-ons going. Come on.
from last week. You mean Corey? The
single prints?
What do you mean from this session? Uh
can see a few into 800 which got
rebalanced, but not really anything
else. Maybe from last week,
which would make sense for that big dump
from Thursday. You mean do you mean
those repric those single prints?
It's kind of what we've started doing
now.
Think we fill these guys here. 770, 765,
760, 755. You got your initial balance
here. I think we're going to fill these
and move lower at this point. This looks
pretty good now. Rejecting this. See TP1
here, TP2, TP3, and then if you get
really lucky, we come back down to this
point, folks. You should have locked
some in into balance already. If we fail
this, this. If we fail this, this. If we
fail this, this
looks good.
Spirally filled one. QQQ still above.
Have a look.
I mean, yeah. I mean, you can even see
like even without a TPR, you can see
those f remember on the five minute
bars. We never we never turned around.
Never turned around.
Never built anything out. It was just
straight
straight downside move. Use a bathroom
here, folks. Be right back.
Oh, stop me out.
Oh god, never mind. Still a good trade.
Still might set up again.
I might be done though, folks. I'm
really struggling here. My head is
pounding.
We're banging into this volume and
they're not trading through it.
But look at the IB that held. That's uh
potentially signaling trend day.
Everything's bullish today. I probably
should have just been buying these dips
to be honest. I should have probably
flipped long here looking for that. But
it's so hard when we're into a huge
golden zone if we just think about where
we are. Like the location
is so so bad.
Right, there's the Thursday pivot.
That's your swing high pivot into swing
low. Move this down properly. And we're
banging into this golden zone now.
This is crazy. And this is the second
leg. So I don't want to long the high of
the second leg, right? I don't want to
long this because if this fails here or
anywhere up here then we get this retest
of this again and the best position
would be a short position here when in
the lower time frame this does something
like this. Okay. And then we can fade
that down to here. And it did it all in
one day all the way down to the lows.
But it's probably likely to do that over
a multiple session. And my expectation
is this week we probably
do something like this.
And we just build out a ton of liquidity
in here. I don't think we move above
this. Maybe below this, but I don't
think we do. If we do, it's a wild move.
Wild move.
Thanks, Jeff. Thanks, Jeff.
Big W. Nice, Jeff. Good work, man. Good
work. Yeah. Anyone who's taken winners
today, like so we've had to be see money
take money. I don't like being long
um up here for those reasons. Like maybe
at the beginning of the day if we drop
down to here, I definitely would have
been thinking about the longs, but I
think some of you took it pre-market. I
mean, this was a no-brain,
right? Holding previous day value area
high. Look at this. Filling the gap,
holding previous day value area high.
But, you know, I'm not up at this time,
but if you are, that's such a nice trade
of first, I don't know, 600 7 a.m. this
morning. That's 3:00 a.m. for me. That's
a really, really simple trade. Look at
how we built the liquidity.
There you go. Off to the races. That's
because of this and the gap. That's a
good long location. Perfect. I don't
want to be long up here now.
526 points higher. No, thank you.
No, thank you.
Why is this just whole thing just moved?
There we go.
Nice. Yeah, if you're just playing the
flow zone, I mean, they're playing if
even if you bought the IB. We didn't
fail IB, right? So, I short here,
covered into that. Stopped that while I
was using the bathroom. But, I mean,
flow zones and IB held. And there's your
flag. If they hold this, there's that.
If they fail this, that can still
happen. But
I think the target at this point's up
here. It's where they're trying to get
the wall up there. Where's ES trading
into? Above the 700s. Where's the
spiders? Trying to get back to 670s. Q's
back above the 600s.
It's impressive, man. It is impressive.
The range in these markets is
so big.
So so big.
It's a bit better. I still don't think
it's done.
I think they're just going to keep going
and going and going.
I mean, you're so close now. You're only
100 points away
from previous week value area high. You
might as well get there at this point.
I give you a read out on a mag. Oh my
gosh. Tesla not too far away from 420
now. 6.3% up on Tesla. Nvidia 0.45% up.
Microsoft 0.4. 42% up. Meta 3.17% up.
That's pulled back a lot. That was over.
Oh, no, it wasn't. It was Google. Google
4.93% up. Am Amazon 2.25% up. Apple
1.26% up.
The strength of Apple. Incredible.
I really hope that dip on Thursday and
Friday is not the end
of this rally because I didn't get any
positions in long term
or the start of this rally I should say.
I really hope we go much lower
selfishly.
850 here on the book for those of you
who are long. 850 on the book and then
880. I'm just giving you the reads on
the book. And then 900.
Uh that's where the liquidity is set.
And I'd say 880 890 gets thick. And then
a previous week value area high up
there. 945. This is a straight squeeze.
What is a measured move off IB right
now?
Where is it? 1.5.
basically 900.
It looks doable.
I mean, everything's held. It's
impressive.
That's your channel.
They do, Rosco. Yeah. Holidays
traditionally are very bullish.
Also, so are no news days. It's a drift
higher event.
Even so, it's impressive.
Like, it's cut through if you think
about Sorry. If you think about all the
levels that we were looking at today,
it's cut through this one. It's cut
through this one. It's cut through this
one. There was one up here I deleted.
It's cutting through every level. by
every level is turning into an RBS. So,
it's really impressive.
This might look not look like match, but
uh it's 300 point move in the New York
session now.
Pretty impressive. This is uh blowing
out shorts at this point. This is
getting uh
very squeezy.
It's definitely blowing out shorts. They
just got blown out there. That last bit.
Wait, I got pre.
Sorry.
Did we just trade into this? No, not
yet.
Not yet.
Yeah. I mean, if you're playing
patterns, yeah, you could say it's a
rising wedge coming into a level of
interest,
which would be a bearish pattern
technically.
Not really huge amount of a pattern
trader myself, not with things like
wedges and stuff.
Just trading what the volume's doing and
what the levels are telling me
to probably going to get out of here in
a minute, folks.
The drugs have kicked in, which is good.
Head pain starting to dissipate a bit.
Yeah, I think uh another day in bed and
some chicken soup would do me some do me
some good
Funded next did just uh
send me a text saying there's a big sale
coming Friday everyone. So be able to
use my code Friday. I think there's a
good sale coming
for uh Black Friday sales on the legacy
accounts.
Something exciting. So, we'll go over
that on Friday.
Oh, actually
It might be tomorrow. I'm just reading
what you just said.
Tomorrow we'll talk about it tomorrow.
So big sales coming
tomorrow on Funded Next. We'll do that
live on stream tomorrow.
Uh
Tuesday, Wednesday, maybe Friday. I'm
not going to guarantee Friday, but
Tuesday, Wednesday, assuming I'll feel
better than this tomorrow. Tuesday,
Wednesday for sure.
Some passive selling up there and
a little bit of excess on that last
move. I still think they just want to
continue to move higher.
Don't see
anything else yet, but uh it's a weird
one.
Certainly a weird one.
This
50s sellers could try take char 50s, but
you might as well just finish the
rotation to 900. So, it doesn't really
make sense what you're doing here, guys.
What these guys are playing at.
They should just go to higher at this
point, but it doesn't look like they've
got the juice right now. They should
just go higher.
They need a pullback first. Maybe they
should go higher, but uh
tape slowed right down. Looks like they
struggled on that last push.
What's the big red zone on my chart?
It's a potential supply block based on
volume.
It's where I think they want to target
up into and probably up here. It's that
ultimate target.
And then if they get out there, I might
as well go 25,000.
And these buyers are struggling to move
higher at this point. They've had a
couple attempts up here and they are
struggling. They should be moving
higher. They're struggling. I wonder if
there's deeper pullback needed in this
market at this point. These guys are
struggling up here. Here you go. So,
starting to see that flush now. I was
just talking about this. You could see
it on the tape. They had a few attempts
and they just they had no juice left.
There is nothing left. I would say now
if sellers take control of 60s, they can
move lower. is it's a horrible area to
think about shorting against because
they've got low hanging fruits higher
right now to go and take I'm certainly
not doing anything but was just
observing the tape there and you could
just see the buyers were really
struggling. There was no one interested
in auctioning this higher above 60.
Yeah. So the the red zone is based on
volume. So
you guys time.
Okay, here
previous week. You see this? Oh,
where's my arrow? This here. All right,
this is where we built out liquidity
here represented by this volume
represented by a resistance level that
we then bid through and we flushed
straight back down through it. And it's
also previous week value area high. If
they trade through this level, then my
expectation is that we come and trade
into these lows 25,000. We trade through
that, like I said, above 25 350, which
is where that last bull trap happened,
above there, bulls, if they can trade
above and base above. There's a big
difference between just getting up to
there and potentially hold um for a big
old squeeze out, but uh we're nowhere
near that yet. So, we judge that if and
when we get there.
responded next use end of day in all
stages for the tests. Uh, yes, I believe
so. I've only traded the um legacy, but
I believe so. Yes,
I'll check now. Hang on.
Well, everything works saying does
Fibonacci work. It's it definitely works
as a point of interest, but you you
can't just trade off a level.
You have to trade off how do we react
when we get to a level?
Yeah. End of day. Who asked for that?
Um,
Naveen. Yes, end of day. I've just
checked. So, Legacy and Rapids are both
end of day.
Still auctioning high. Like I said, it
shouldn't have stopped there, but maybe
they just needed a little pullback to
trap some bears in. Reason to go higher
right now is to come into previous week
value area high. You might as well
Some of you were long from previous week
value area low. Are you still Are you
still long, folks? Or previous day,
sorry.
We're about to complete a rotation from
previous day value area high to previous
week value area high. That is
impressive. From a daily to a weekly
level in one go.
What a market. What a market. It's not
normal to be able to do that in one go.
Not when the range is
Five, six, seven, eight, nine, 500 plus
points.
Do I manually draw my VP or do I use
PVP? Uh, I'm so I manually draw uh
previous week levels.
Um, PVP I do use on the 30 minute bars
on a side monitor,
but I'm just interested in where the
volume is on each 30 minute bar. See,
today we've just all we've done today is
move value higher and point of control
higher. That's all we've done. We've
never traded uh and closed under a
previous 30 minute point of control or
value. We're just we're just walking
higher, just squeezing higher.
Oh, you got one M andQ. What from
previous day value area high up to this?
It's it's a great trade. 500 point say
one one MNQ, but one MQ for 500 points
is what a,000 bucks.
It's nothing to scoff at. That's really
good.
Yes. Tesa 7%. That 420 is important.
I mean,
I think it's too early, Peter. I mean,
I had two questions right in my mind.
Was that a forced flush? So that, and we
talked about it last week, so that hedge
funds could get long because they
haven't been long all year, so that they
make their bonus.
Time will tell. Um, I'm not convinced
the lows in yet, but uh,
we can only trade what's in front of us.
What I will be annoyed is is if we do
make new highs this year, um, I didn't
get any QQ position filled to go long.
That will piss me off. I'll be honest.
That will really annoy me. Okay, getting
very close to this uh edge of volume
here.
This red block. Make sure I've got it in
the right area.
Yeah, it is.
I'd argue that's got moved down.
Okay, so that's previous week value high
up there.
through that gets a bit thinner.
Make sure your settings are the same on
PvP. Might be because of that. It might
be reading tick or bars differently.
Maybe Kevin, maybe it doesn't come, you
know. Who knows?
Only play what's in front of us.
It's certainly not a level I'm
interested in longing up here.
It's just been squeeze up all day.
Relief all day. Tell you what though,
the VIX has found that bid at that low
of day that we talked about. It's right
at the bottom of my blue box into 21. It
has found a bid there
for now.
Delta was pretty big on that high last
day push
this candle. Delta there was pretty big.
Might as well get to 900 at this point,
which is one and a half IB.
We'll go there.
Yeah, we can do a giveaway. Have we got
the likes up? Sorry, I haven't looked.
We got to 150.
No, I get to 150 and I'll do an Apex
giveaway.
Way too late to be long up here, I I
would say. I mean, it might still work,
but
this is looking the same as earlier now.
They're building out one of these again
into the top of that channel.
The tough thing here is they have not
completed. They might as well complete
this move. Like you got 900 here in
previous week value area high.
Might as well complete that move.
Yeah. If you get me to 250 likes, we uh
we can do a giveaway, guys. We're an
Apex account.
And don't forget, guys, there's the uh
Black Friday sale for Flowzone Trader is
on. So everything on the site 25% off
that ends December 1st or midnight
before that.
There won't be a better sale than that.
It's off everything on the site. So if
you want to do the 20our course and join
the Discord, now's the time to do it.
Prices are going up next year. Models
changing slightly next year.
Battle here against this sort of gray
box area. Their ambition is to come and
complete this. that they struggle.
This will feel a bit like earlier. I'm
done for the day at this point.
How can you say, Kev, Kevin, I would say
you get very biased in chat. How can you
say we have a sell bias tomorrow when we
haven't closed today?
What happens if we close today at lower
day?
you you front run and get bias. I've
noticed it with you. I'm just being
honest. Like, I've noticed it. You'll
say things like looking for sales when
we're still drifting higher or or we've
got a sell by tomorrow when it's it's
half 11, mate. There a long day ahead.
Like,
look at what happened Friday.
I'm not pointless dig you out. I'm just
trying to help you.
Look what happened Friday. Big big big
push. Sell. You don't know what's coming
now. You don't know. They might dump
this. They might be like, "Hey, dumping
the inventory now. We might close down
here." Way too early to be thinking
about biased tomorrow
when we're only what, two hours into
today's session.
It's trying to add liquidity higher to
drive it up here. They're trying to
offer offer higher to drive it up. They
just filled that 880. They've now added
890 and 900. Yeah. Again, I'm not trying
to dig you out, mate. I'm trying I'm
trying to help you so that you can see
what you do because I worry for people
that carry so much bias before a setup
shows itself. It's how you could means
you could come to the charts tomorrow
and we might be actually in a bull setup
but you convinced yourself that we're
selling. You get stuck.
This volume area being built out again.
Okay, let's do an Apex giveaway then.
Uh,
I think you're probably right, Mo.
You're probably right. We need a news
driver. Probably right.
Okay, code FCT. Type it in chat. Only
need to type it once and we'll do a
giveaway.
Coming back and testing the edge of this
volume, folks. You can see this over and
over again. I'm not con convinced
they've completed the auction. We have
left buyers trapped at the highs now,
but not convinced that that is the end
of it today because we're so close. So,
I might as well come and finish all of
this. In my mind,
I might as well come and finish the
auction and complete it all. Or maybe
they save it for later.
Who knows?
Nvidia now 1.80% up. I haven't looked at
that for like 5 10 minutes. That is
incredible.
Absolutely incredible. back in the 80s
for Nvidia where it's stuck above 200.
So, it's got a long way to go. But oh my
word, this market's just gone uh buy
everything zone, has it? Give you a
readout. So, Tesla 6.84% up, Nvidia
1.80% up, Microsoft 0.70% up, Meta
2.93% up, Google just under 5% up,
Amazon 1.85% up, Apple 1.31% up.
Markets found a bid. We're in this great
box and I think they want to get up into
here at the moment. I think that is what
they would like to do.
Definitely to 900s where they're
offering right now. Give you guys a
couple more minutes. Might put a winner
here.
This volume gets built out.
pretty thin
that
long till lunch. 30 minutes.
All right, one more minute left, folks.
Just type it once in chat. We'll pull
the winner in a second.
Starting to see a bit more selling into
the edge of this range. Looks just like
earlier, but we've not left it yet. And
the thing is there's low hanging fruit
through or there's a rotation to
complete above, which makes me a bit
nervy about taking a short here. But
it's exactly the same setup as earlier.
Okay, small size in stopping the money
because I don't like that we're so close
to that level from earlier. Watching
here if we can snap 50s.
Come on.
You snap 50s and puke. So, we pull the
winner straight after this. Exactly the
same setup as earlier. We're leaving a
shelf.
Take a little piece off here. Watching
30s and 20s if they cover. Stopping at
60s now.
Is that a right start? That's probably
not the right start. Hang on. 64s.
Sorry. Measure this out. Okay. Let's
pull this winner while I've got this
hanging on. Okay. Stopping the money.
TJ
Reds. Is that the right way? Hopefully
I've said it right.
TJ Reds.
Are you here TJ? There you go. Nice.
Right, just shoot me an email, please,
buddy. Uh, info@flowzontrader.com.
Send me a screenshot of your uh YouTube
and I will send you a free Apex account,
any size.
Remember, today is the last day for
Apex, folks. All right, it runs out
tonight. Uh, that's the 80% sale with
$40 for activation fee. So today is the
last day to do that. Uh they haven't
told me that they're extending it.
Starting to see failures here. Still in
this
like I said stops at 64. Might move that
a bit tighter
volume up there slightly differently.
Where's that little spike? 58. I don't
really want it to trade 360. Okay. Stops
at 60.
The runner either goes or doesn't. Like
I said, I don't love it because I don't
think we've completed the rotation to
the high out on the runner at this
point.
Still think it's previous week value
area high it wants to get to, but I had
to take the legit setup when it was
there.
Uh
that's going to be me team. I need to
get out of here. Um
solid day. I'll take it
considering I feel like absolute crap.
Decent solid day in the books.
And uh yeah, that'll do. Three for
three, I think.
Hopefully all good. And um I'll be back
here tomorrow feeling a bit better,
hopefully. But I'm going to rest up
today. I'm not going to be on Discord,
guys. I'll um I'll check in on my phone.
I'm going to close these screens down so
I can actually rest.
Um, so please look after yourself those
over in Discord. Look after each other.
Call the setups out when you see it. We
are rejecting. This is getting
interesting here. That last push up
tested the top side of volume and
rejected
and trapped buyers.
Well, I'm out of it now. I'm not going
to get back in. That that is a strong uh
rejection on the footprint.
left buyers up at 70.
I'd say if you're in this short, if you
defend 66s now, this can get very nasty.
This can be a roll back down to here.
It's looking good. It's looking really
good for you. Oh, you mother
couldn't have just let me have it, could
you?
Couldn't have just let me have it all
the way down. You had to do a retest to
the top side of it.
Looks good. Anyway,
um don't be long up here, folks. All
right. Don't be long up here. Um I'd be
very careful today. I would say their
ambition is this and 25K.
Um if it offers fails, you need to focus
on volume. All right? So, it's just
trading level to level. If it offers a
fail there, even if it does this, it's
level to level. It's level to level.
You're above IB. You're in a trend
higher day, but your location up here is
awful for a buy. This is in a golden
zone. I'd be more looking to see if it
peters out. If it doesn't peter out
today, maybe if they close it high,
that's the important. Maybe if they
close it high, it peter out tomorrow.
Um, and when you're trading downside,
you know, just respect the cover points.
Don't join too late down here. All
right, you need something where we leave
a shelf. TP1, TP2, hold runners just in
case, but that's what I'd be looking
for. Um, don't fight it if it reclaims.
Like I said, this is possible. Can't
rule out 25K. Um, last day for Apex. And
again, my my sale on Flowzone will end
uh December 1st, folks. 25% off
everything on the site. Peace and love,
everyone. I will um do my best to be
here tomorrow. Hopefully you had a good
day with me. Trade safe. See you soon.