Morning
team.
Morning everyone. How you doing? You
might hear my voice today. I've got uh
caught my cold or flu off my wife. So I
got pounding headache and cold and flu.
So bear with me today team. It's uh not
the easiest to have bright lights to
point pointing at you first thing in the
morning when you're not feeling too
great. But let's uh let's see how we get
on here. Okay, as always we're going to
start in the daily chart. Yesterday
making new lows in breakout. Uh those
who have done the course notice the
Monday, Tuesday, notice where we are,
notice what we did yesterday and where
we at today. It is important. It will
set the tone for the week based on the
weekly model going into Thursday and
Friday. Okay, so those who have done the
course, I'm not going to give you any
more edge than that. Just think about
where we we are. All right, this little
chunk here became important yesterday
and they lost it. All right, so we're
now trading
underneath
uh these lows here from the yearly
profile. So, let me just get my screen
up here so I can see you on the side
monitor.
All right, so we're trading underneath
this key level on the yearly profile.
You will notice this is sort of into
that 800 range. If you traded or watched
towards the close yesterday, we ranged
up here for a long time before they
liquidated late in the day. All right,
so bulls had numerous chances yesterday
into close. I was actually hoping we'd
get one of these. Um, but we didn't. All
right, they had numerous chances to get
back over sort of the 800 and look for
the drive up to sort of 850 because if
we closed up here, all right, that is a
much much more bullish close leading
into today to allow a squeeze. We didn't
close up there. We close right on the
lower Ballinger band which is pointing
down and you'll see it will take a bit
of time but eventually if we keep
trading lower this uh upper Ballinger
band is going to turn down with us and
we're going to start doing something
like this. Right, you've now got the
5day cross the 50. Everything's very
very bearish in the charts but our
location for the short as we talk about
is not ideal. Now, if you're in a swing
position or you're looking to add to
your positions, all right, you quite
clearly you have sort of uh relative
equal lows down here into this pocket.
All right, this is the area which bulls
will next want to try and defend. All
right, into here. If we get through
this, you've got a value area low down
here and this old pivot. All right, so
that's what I'd be looking at if you're
managing a position. I wouldn't be
putting a new short on at these lows. I
think it's very, very risky. The other
thing to note is we are opening up an
inside bar. We're inside previous days
value which we're going to get into now.
We have Nvidia earnings coming tonight
and FOMC minutes this afternoon.
Remember the last FOMC for anyone that
was here. Pal was pretty dovish. Uh
sorry, he was not dovish. He was pretty
hawkish on the December rate cut. All
right, we had priced in a December rate
cut and um well, he was kind of saying,
"Hey, we don't it's no guarantee we're
going to get that." the market did not
like it and that's kind of what signaled
the top in the market. So, we're going
to get the minutes from that to see what
what is said. So, into an hourly, this
is your value area from yesterday. Okay,
we're opening up slap bang in the middle
of it. Pretty close to a VWOP right now
as well. There's no edge in here, folks.
All right, what do I expect today? Churn
and burn, baby. Churn and burn. All
right, something like this. Why? Because
this will burn the theta. All right,
this will burn all the options who are
looking to trade Nvidia, looking for
this big move, right? That will burn it.
I wouldn't surprise me if Invidia ends
up doing absolutely nothing. But but we
will see. Everyone looking for it to be
the savior in the market. We will see.
Overall, right, we are bearish. There's
no doubt about it. Okay, we are bearish.
Here's the micro head and shoulder
inside the giant head and shoulder we're
looking at. There's the net line.
There's the sort of break. But we're
hanging on, aren't we? idea thread.
Could this be a bare flag to break down?
Yeah, it could also be a wedge. And this
is what I'm looking at. I'm I'm
wondering if this market needs a bit of
relief before going lower or if just the
trap in here is going to be enough
liquidity for a snap. Either way, we
know that this 800 level is a huge level
on the yearly profile. All right. If we
get over this 8850, I think there's a
squeeze back up to sort of 25,000
25,100. A look above here and fail.
There's a rotation back down. A look
below and fails. A rotation back inside.
And we expect chop and slop in here. I
don't expect it to come that far outside
of previous range. If it gets really
heavy, we'll just follow the tape. If
they want to dump this, we'll follow the
tape. But remember, your location, your
lower Ballinger band is down here. It's
not really ideal to be looking for
shorts down there. All right? It's very,
very risky beyond two sigas to be
looking for a short on a daily. So, I'll
just say that if we look at what
happened overnight, okay, opening or
closing, where do we close? Closed
pretty heavy, didn't we? All right,
closed back down here into this pivot
sideways in Asia. A little push up,
failed this little nugget here into 700.
Failed the 5200. Washed back down.
Washed these stops. Found a bid where we
had a bid earlier this day into this
edge. Bid back off it. London tried to
bid up right back into the old point of
control. failed that point of control
back down into the middle of the range.
Right? Nothing's changed. Absolutely is
nothing has changed here overnight. I
would not look at this overnight and
say, "Okay, sentiment shifted or bulls
are in control, right? No one's in
control here. This is a liquidity
building stage. The overall sentiment
remains bearish. Can buyers come in?
Yeah, they can defend the edge. Can they
get above 850? Maybe they can get above
850 for a squeeze. I would find it
unlikely for them to do that move today
unless uh someone knows something that
we don't which is possible. We can't
rule it out but I would expect more
liquidity to just be built out today.
Right into the lower time frames. Let's
look at some of the other markets.
Right. ES doing exactly the same thing.
Building out its range. Uh this is your
range built out yesterday. You can see
here are your pivots. Very very simple.
6 680s. as we can just call it down to
615s and PDC here 640. So just a big old
range but what becomes key is going to
become a spy doesn't accuse. What is
going on here? Let's get rid of that.
[sighs]
Okay, spy
660 was uh a put as was 670 and 672. All
right, you can see we traded under it,
we rejected it, we got back over it, we
had tried to hold it, we traded under
it, we got back over it, we closed at
it. is still going to remain a big
level. This is your under over right now
and they're just going to keep washing
it. It is a huge huge level. I'd say
under here we've got room back down to
the 40s I think it was when I looked
last night. Yeah, down here. All right.
Next w will be down here. It's got room.
If it wants to just roll over, it will.
But uh I would again be very cautious
looking for that move today.
Hugh, same story. 66 600 was your put
wall. All right. Yesterday they had the
chance to save it. All right. And they
failed into end of day and you can see
we've just rejected 600 this morning in
the pre-market. Right. So I would say
bears have the edge but we're in
rotation. We're inside of initial
balance from yesterday. But bears do
have the edge here overall in this
market.
Warned you. I warned you about this one.
All right. I warned you for the last few
weeks about this finding a bid off here.
All right, this is not good for the
market, folks. It really is. This is not
what you want to see in this market.
Maybe the hedge back to gold starting
and let's have a look at this 30-year
quickly.
Still just basing out. All right, that
catches a bid. I'd be worried. I am now
watching the JPY carry trade into
December as well because the 30s on the
JP on the [snorts] Japanese treasuries
have started breaking out aggressively
which is going to increase risk off. All
right, let's have a look at the mag.
[snorts]
All right, Apple remains holding on.
It's uh remains very very impressive but
it's got room here. If it starts failing
this shelf, we might see Apple coming
back down into it 50s. But it's still
holding on. Still not doing too bad, but
there's a little gap down there, but
it's trading inside of yesterday's
range. Actually, a 3-day balance range
here on Apple Amazon.
Same kind of story. All right, here's
your break at these lows. Here's
yesterday's range. We're trading at
these lows right now. I'd be careful
about a look below and fail. That would
be your typical sort of move back inside
for a chop day up to here, possibly just
to the midpoint.
But opening near the lows, not a bullish
sign. GooG
strong
strong found a bid
Friday last week pull back Monday little
wash below Tuesday holding this bid and
obviously that Bergkshire and Haway
holding this up and people are very uh
happy about what they're seeing there
clearly because it's doing a good job.
Meta. Another inside bar here. Here's
yesterday's action.
Trading towards the upper point. So,
maybe a bit more of a P-shaped profile
there on Meta. A bit more bullish than
some of the other ones we've looked at
so far.
Microsoft. That looks dreadful.
[laughter]
That looks absolutely dreadful. All
right. If it if it can't reclaim sort of
97 98, that is an awful look on
Microsoft. Nvidia. Obviously, this is
the big one. All right. This has got
earnings tonight 420 20 minutes after
the bell. I'd be very careful trading
into the close. You can see here's your
big old downtrend on Nvidia. All right,
here's your big downtrend. Here's your
wedge. Here's your pivot. All right,
that's the magic number. Sort of 79.
Just call it 180. That's your overunder
right now. If they start losing that,
there's moves into 76s and 73. I think
it's about a $12 move we're expecting on
Nvidia. I think at least. So
yeah, just be aware of that. At least
$12. 121 12 to $15 probably is normal,
but you know, in this market it could be
anything. Just be careful, folks. Just
be careful. It's trying to hold on.
And Tesla, the last one, another inside
bar and inside range. Right, there's
your big range. Saved 400, right?
Drifted to 380s, but reclaimed 400
somewhere in here.
More of a range. Not a lot to do folks
today. I would say if you want to know a
day that I become not interested in
trading, this has got the looks of it.
All right. This is absolutely got the
looks of a day which I lack interest in
trading. No doubt about it.
So just be smart today. Manage
expectations. Expect chop. All right?
Expect traps. Expect choppiness. Do not
be expecting a trend. The last thing I'm
expecting today is a trend. Given the
news events, given where we're opening
up, right, right at the midpoint of
yesterday's initial balance, pretty much
in the midpoint of yesterday's value.
It doesn't look pretty, guys. Right, so
manage your expectations, please. Right,
let's see who's in here. Do some shout
outs if we've got time. We have got a
few minutes. [snorts]
All right, morning everyone. I'm not
sure who's at the top. I'm going to have
a guess. It's Clint. I can't see it on
my screen for some reason. Morning
Clint, JD, Jesse, Noah, Inferris,
Raphael,
John, [snorts] Dennis, Toby, Ken,
Thumper,
ET, Jeff, Larry, Peter, Marrick, Cat,
Gar, the Richardsons, Lou Riley, Chris,
Sergio, Daniela, Jonathan, Otus,
uh, Daniel, Marrick, Eti, Awani, Eva,
Green, Kevin,
Chad, oneonone, Owen, Idris, Bart, Tony,
IO Toby,
I've lost you all now. Come on, OBS.
Prrisca, Eva, Jonathan, Crocco, Lindle,
Brandon, Troy, Mo, Abby, David, Full
Forward, You Shot, and Nobody, Myron,
Lauren,
Christy, Greg, Richard, Ejectto, Idris,
Omal, Abby, Patrick, Firewwater, John,
Bradley, Frank, Kingdom, Love, and Navy.
Good morning everyone. Hope you're doing
good.
Hope you're doing good. Oh god, I feel
dreadful. [snorts] Absolutely dreadful.
Hey Andrew, Mr. Slim L, morning.
Okay, so you're prepared. I'm just
expecting rotations today, which means
you probably want to be playing the
edges. Um, bears have the most control
right now overall in this market, but uh
just be cautious is all I'm saying
today. Uh, the one thing I guess we
didn't go over was the VIX. Actually,
let's just quickly look at that because
it rem does remain elevated.
[snorts]
Remains very very elevated in here.
Get rid of this some old levels here.
All right. These are the levels I'll be
watching. [sighs]
This is where we were for the April low.
All right. You can see [snorts] this
build out here
is very much looking like this right
now.
All right, these are all breaking out if
we do another one of these and break out
and the market's in big big trouble. So,
normally you would expect a down day
[snorts] after such a big day like this
on the VIX for the last few days, but uh
given where we're at, I just think we're
going to hold increased volatility into
uh earnings and then maybe post Nvidia,
we either get that one big push or that
pull back into here and have a little
bit of a cool off. But, you know, let's
just see. I don't want to uh I'm not
here to guess the market. I'm here to
trade what's in front of me right now.
So, we will just see. Whatever the
market brings is what we will be able to
trade. like yesterday didn't bring me
what I wanted. So, I was limited on
trading opportunity. Today, I think
we're going to be very limited on
trading opportunities, but uh you know,
who knows? Maybe something changes.
The downside pressure here at the moment
[snorts] back into that VWAP. We got
just over 20 seconds here until the
open, folks.
not in the rush because we're opening at
mid point of the range right at VWAP
right at PDC means nothing's changed
from where we closed yesterday in the
cash market to where we're opening today
is exactly the same point pretty much
means anything that happened overnight
was a whole lot of fluff was a whole lot
of fluff because we haven't done
anything different
that light down my head is pounding I'm
sorry team if it makes it dark just got
to take the edge off my head right now
all right here's the open. So, I'll be
watching this previous day value area
low. They probably may very well come
down and test this. And if they get
through that, maybe they test overnight
lows. We will have to see. And then if
we're going to play a range, we have to
really see if buyers come in and defend
it or not.
[snorts]
Gosh. Thanks. Thanks to my wife for
giving me this uh beautiful cold.
Okay, I give you a read out. The mag is
a mixed bag, right? Tesla 0.91% up.
Nvidia 1.55% up. Uh Microsoft 0.90%
down. Meta 1% down. Google 1.80%
up. Amazon 0.15% up. Apple 0.17% down.
Complete mixed bag. All right.
A complete mixed bag.
[clears throat]
>> [snorts]
>> And as you can see already this morning,
just chopped. We've not done anything.
Look at that opening print.
We went up, we went down, we went back
to the middle. Market does not know what
it wants to do.
[snorts]
Let it let it do whatever it is it's
going to do. Just let it do it. Don't be
uh trying to guess. You put something on
here, you're 50/50. Nothing more than
that. [snorts]
Yeah, quite right, Peter. Well, we're
going on we're supposed to be going to
Palm Springs this weekend. At the
moment, it looks like we're both going
to go and
sit in the house and drink tea and watch
films cuz don't think we're going to
have much more in us than that.
Okay, bear's trying to force us lower at
the moment. They want to come and check
that previous day value area low by the
looks of it. This level down here they
get through that you globeex down here.
Previous day low all the way down here
just uh under 400. So I'd expect bulls
will want to try and protect value.
We've literally gone nowhere. We've done
a 60 points in the opening three minutes
going nowhere.
Absolutely nowhere.
>> [sighs]
>> Let's see.
Can the bears get down to value area
low? Can they get below it for a drive
to test overnight levels?
Let's get an anchor on here if we get
that one.
Well, we expected chop and chop is what
we're getting
back to sort the opening print and VWOPS
and flow zones never got down to value.
bulls protecting value back to the
upside. We're going to go here and see
if the bears come and protect that
morning high and send us back into the
midpoint of the range and then maybe
they send us back down to value again.
And you're going to get the idea here
going the high.
So yeah, if you're doing anything here,
maybe you've got a system for this. I
certainly do not have a system for this
right now.
Here's a gamble.
There's the high of day. New high of day
in the New York session.
So maybe they come back up for this
previous day point of control. We're
thick in here. Like I said, I just think
this is going to be very back and forth.
If I was going to be a buyer, I'd want
to be a buyer down here today.
Don't really want to be a buyer up here.
uh because we're approaching this thick
gray level which we traded under over
numerous times yesterday which is why
it's marked.
You can see rejection of that volume. So
yeah, I'd be somewhat cautious trying to
do anything up here. If you're looking
to be a buyer,
I don't know what you can risk off up
here.
You can go for whatever you want, but uh
you are not you should if you zoom out,
you will see you're a slap bang in the
middle of a range right now.
So, don't think anyone's uh we're not at
the edge of a range and I don't like
trading ranges if we're not at the edge
because I don't know what you're risking
off. This is a thick area. If they want
to come and test previous day PC, they
can. It's what they tried to do in
Gloex. You can see globe it's just
peaked above there that P US PC.
[snorts]
Do they defend previous day point
controls the bears or do they let it
through? Remember 800 was the big big
level yesterday. If I want to be a
buyer, I've got to be a buyer down at
value. We haven't got down there yet
today. We've failed to rotate down that
far. We weren't too far away.
We haven't got down there.
This P is probably where they're trying
to get at the moment.
It's where we failed overnight. So, it
might well be where they're trying to
get up towards.
It's coming in the new course, Kevin. It
will be in the new course. I'm not
giving away any more edge for free on
YouTube when it gets into an advanced
training trading. I give away far too
much as it is.
So, defending 700 so far. Back inside
this thick gray box.
Guys, lots of you asking questions. Go
and watch the free videos. All right. Go
and watch the free videos on volume
profile that I put up. Everything's in
there.
Just a whole lot of nothing on the tape
right now.
Let's get one of these. Let me open up.
[clears throat]
Google having a day here over 4% up.
Big push from Google probably driving
this market at the moment.
VIX underneath its pre-market lows.
Question is, does it find a bid here
into sort of uh 2360 to 2340s where it
found a bid yesterday in the uh
afternoon and broke out from?
Yes, Nvidia earnings are tonight. Red
Dawn 420.
They're trying to get up to PC at the
moment. And you'll just see a lot of
back and forth here on the tape.
Just nothing for me. There's nothing to
do here. There's no edge here. Quite
happy to sit still. Look at lower time
frame algo. Look at the the VWAPS. Look
at your close. Look at the flow zones.
Look at everything sideways. It's
pointing sideways. No trend here.
There's no edge. We're not at a key
level. We're not up high enough at a key
level to fade. We're not low enough the
key level to buy. We're just at the edge
of the wedge.
There you go. So, protecting that edge.
[snorts]
Nice, Michael. Lovely work. Lovely work.
back to this gray box.
Same Peter. Yeah, I've got absolutely no
interest in this market. It's not at any
level that I'm interested in trading at
the moment.
If you're watching other traders who are
getting in and out of this market
and I don't know what they're playing
because there's nothing to do here other
than get yourself caught. [snorts]
And this market is in a liquidity
building phase. absolutely is. We've not
tested an edge.
[snorts]
Okay, back down towards VW up.
They're trying to bid off it right now.
They do want to if they're going to
complete a rotation off, they want to go
PC, but
who knows whether they have the strength
to do that. No F no guys, this is when I
get frustrated. FOMC is not coming. FOMC
is not today. FOMC minutes are going to
be released later. They are minutes
based on the last meeting which we
already know the result of. So we might
see how hawish they really were. But
FOMC is not coming today, guys. So let's
get that straight. All right. There's no
rate cut happening today. The next rate
cut, if they do it, is next month.
Let's make sure you're accurate and you
know what you're talking about.
Right. Nvidia earnings 420. FOMC minutes
this afternoon,
no rate cut.
Really important you know the
difference. Big difference between FOMC
minutes and rate cuts decisions.
No worries, Chad. Yeah, I don't know if
I'll make it to lunch to be honest. We
do like an hour. See how we feel.
[snorts]
You can hear like I'm so bunged up. Yes.
2:00 Raph. Yeah. 2:00 2:00 Eastern
minutes released.
Remember like we saw some comments even
early this morning. There was a few Fed
members in alignment with uh PAL saying
you know we cannot guarantee a cut in
December.
They're trying to do a breakout here to
get to the previous day point control.
They're trying to build this liquidity
of current point of control to get up
here. This is target one and this is
target two up into value. Like I said,
this is beyond what I would want to
trade right now. I don't mind buying
dips at the lows at value. We didn't see
that. Didn't even get down there. I'm
not going to buy a high today. That's
for sure. It would have to really get
above 800850 if it's going to be like a
trend join at highs and I just can't
imagine they're going to let that happen
in this market today. But you never
know.
So here's the move back towards previous
day point control. So, if you are
longing this for any reason, you want to
be locking in as we get into this red
line above this right here. That's what
they've been defending.
And through that, we're probably going
to go 800.
What was that high from? Yeah. To the
800s. If they get through this 800s is
where they want to go to. That was the
level they defended nonstop yesterday.
Okay. Nonstop yesterday. They defended
over and over and over again. um
yesterday afternoon.
Okay, that was defended nonstop
yesterday afternoon. Just be aware of
that.
Some selling on the tape here now as
they try and defend around these 700s
and that point control
desperate to complete the rotation which
they're unable to complete right now.
Haven't quite got there. I mean they're
not very shy of it are they? They're
pretty much there. They're pretty much
there in fairness to them. They're
pretty much there in fairness to them.
We should be fair to them.
Buyers trying to absorb here. But uh
like I said,
previous day point control is probably
the target and then through that 800 if
they are able to complete the rotation.
I don't know if they're going to be able
to complete through it all. That's what
they're attempting to do. I can only
tell you what they're attempting to do.
So there's previous day point control.
Now, I would hold on to see if you can
get up to 800. Now,
if you're in this long,
[snorts]
so through here, value area high up
here. Now, this is the area yesterday
which they defended over and over. I
will tell you if we get over this is the
thick area that we went over on the
weekly. If they if they get over this,
there is squeeze potential. I wouldn't I
would have quite happily been long for
this off here, but not off this move
here. is far too risky. And I'm okay.
Like I had a chat with uh one of you
last night is if I don't see what I want
in the tape or I don't see the setup I
want, I don't trade it. Not going to
chase in a range rotating market.
There's a squeeze. [snorts]
So next level value area high up here.
VIX coming back downside.
Google absolutely sending it 5% up.
Absolute madness. Madness from the goo.
Really strong.
[snorts]
Sweating. Not well, folks. Really not
well.
Oh, man.
>> [snorts]
>> There's your previous day point of
control being back tested now.
Okay. Current point of control on the
day all the way down here in this gray
box. [snorts] Main objective or first
objective was previous day. They've
tagged it. The next level would be this
move into value. They will probably want
to defend value. All right. If I was
them, I'd be looking to defend value
because if we get through 8850, a a
bigger squeeze is on in this market. I
will tell you that now. um because it
was defended so aggressively yesterday
afternoon. If they can't defend that
today, there will be a lot of stops up
there that will get popped. So, just be
aware of that.
[sighs]
Balls are trying to really get going
here. Impressive take to be honest. VIX
is really dying. We're coming up towards
the top side of this range. All right.
So, if we start getting through 800s,
800s, gap fill will be 880 from a couple
days ago. Uh, lots of stops up here.
Remember, this is like your resistance
zone. This up here, if we get through
that, there is a lot of stops up here
that will be popped. Bears will want to
defend this.
I see flow zone indicator is an add-on
with the course. Is it the same for
Trading View or does it come with the
course? add-on for Ninja. Uh there is a
version of it that comes with the
course. If you want the pro, you can
upgrade to the pro version. Uh Ninja is
a separate add-on. You're right. If you
buy it all at uh
in one go, you get a bigger discount.
So, if you're looking to buy the course,
if you add it on at the checkout, you'll
get a bigger discount than if you do it
separately later.
Okay. So, back down to previous day
point of control here. Current point of
control on the session down here. We're
building out more volume up here
currently.
This is we're come up into the area
where bears would want to defend. If you
just look left from yesterday and zoom
you out.
Where are you? All right. This is the
level yesterday afternoon. Bulls had a
good go at trying to do this move and
they failed. This is the level bears
will want to protect because if bulls
get above here, there is a bigger
squeeze.
So bears watching this level trying to
get this move here. This might open up
for later. I was happy to be a buyer
down here today for a rotation up to
this, but I don't want to be a buyer up
here particularly.
I'm actually not feeling good and I'm
happy to do absolutely nothing today
equally.
[snorts]
Alex, what are your current volume
sessions for this session and how does
it plot that on the right hand side?
It's a anchored It's a anchored volume
profile. I have it set just like this.
All right. You can do ticks or you can
do a thousand rows. It's up to you.
Thousand per row or two ticks. It
doesn't matter which. Same same.
It's an anchored volume profile set from
the New York open. We're always trying
to get this squeeze out to previous day
value area high here. [snorts]
I am sick, Kevin. Yes, it's the first
thing I said this morning when I came to
the chart.
[snorts]
Tapping into yesterday's supply.
bit still pulling down.
Google now 5% up. Apple relative
strength as well. 0.72% up. Looks good.
Tesla up as well. Nvidia 2 and a half%
up.
We're getting near that previous day
value area high. If you've been long in
any of this for any reason, you are
starting to see the flow zone start to
possibly offer a trend if we're going to
see expansion. But uh you know this is
an area where you want to be selling
into.
Don't you do not want to be a new money
long up here. It would need to get above
supply and base above.
Lots of stops from yesterday into sort
of 810
into 810ish
range. Actually not too bad. Very
actually very very good.
Very surprised. 207 points.
[snorts]
There's some selling up here into that
supply from yesterday. Previous day
value area high currently being
protected.
We're in nothing more than a range
rotation. So I said it wouldn't be a new
money long up here. You're asking for
it. Maybe if it pulls back and you know
offers a base out. We haven't completed
the rotation. Maybe there's something
there you might want to take.
>> [snorts]
[sighs]
>> So [snorts] protecting this shelf. You
can see this little shelf being
developed up here. Trying to get that
previous day value area high and 810.
That's what bulls are trying to complete
the rotation to. Bears are trying to
defend this area. Here is your shelf
currently being developed. Same area as
yesterday afternoon.
Then under here pretty thin all the way
down to 675. So balls are trying to
complete the rotation up here. Under
here pretty thin down to 675.
[snorts]
Still squeezing here. It is still
squeezing. It's very impressive to be
honest. Very very impressive. [snorts]
[snorts]
Up into 800. So your TP coming up here.
If you did take the long previous day
value area high, lots of stops are at
810 from yesterday and over that
well [sighs and gasps]
let's have a look. Over 850 there is a
squeeze available all the way up to 950.
I'll say that much.
I am somewhat surprised they want to do
this on the opening drive this morning,
but uh hey,
like we always talk about, they will do
whatever they want to do.
[snorts]
Some big buyers up there into 800.
Currently got themselves caught on that
last drive.
They're looking for those stops at 810
at the moment.
Lots of buying up here. Not much seeing
much continuation yet, but they're
looking for the stops at 810. And then
you're looking for 850 if you're still
if you're actually in this long. I'm not
in a position. I don't know if I'm well
enough to trade today, folks. I'm going
to be honest with you after this 850 if
they drive through. Here you go.
Squeezing through now. 10 and then
you're going to get 50s and then through
that you're probably going to get 960 is
possible. Gap fill would be 900 and uh
960 is possible for previous day high as
well. It's a big drive here.
It is impressive that they've turned the
boosters on out the gate. Somewhat
surprised they didn't at least come down
to here, but there we go.
[snorts]
>> [snorts]
>> VIX underneath previous day low. Now
you've just popped all those stops at
810. Next level is 815 then the 900s. It
is uh it is impressive that they've done
this on an opening drive. Really
impressive.
I thought they'd do this after Nvidia
tomorrow. Thought they'd just stick in
the range and do this tomorrow.
Nice green. Looking forward to working
with you.
So, still trying to pop these into 850s
and then you're looking at 900 960,
right? I think it's like 9. What's this
level here? 9:08 or something.
Be careful. If they build this out here,
you're thin in that move out. If you're
if you've been long in this, just be
make sure you're managing. So we can
come right back down 100 point down very
very quickly because these are big move
big big big moves. All right, watch your
ATRs. These are big old moves. You're
still elevated around 30 points ATR per
M1.
Right, we can shut this door when
they're ready for a big old pullback.
Remember, no bulls have been washed out
this market. This is a squeeze like we
talked about for most days on this
stream this week. Even in bare markets,
the bare market rallies are very, very
violent. When you get shorts cut caught
at a low or at a pivot and we squeeze
away from it is very violent
cup and handle on the 5m minute and not
not for me. I don't see that not for me.
Nice John. Yeah, anyone who got it, well
done.
I mean, flow zones offered it, but uh I
think it was it was kind of ugly to be
honest. It's kind of ugly. I I'll be
honest. This is how I see it. It's a
long trigger.
It was a long trigger
at midpoint of a range.
It's not even a C setup for me even
though it's panned out. This is what I
was saying to I can't remember who it
was last night I was talking to. This is
what happens with trading. Like just
because it does something doesn't mean
you should have been in it. Like for me
this is I'm following my rules.
Especially on a day when I don't feel
too good. I'm going to follow my rules.
I was happy to buy if we came down into
here this morning. If we did something
like this,
not going to let me draw. We did
something like this. Yeah, happy to buy
it here and here for that rotation. But
I don't want to buy the midpoint of a
range. Not really.
Okay, we've just popped uh London from
yesterday, I think. 60s. Yes, we've just
popped London from yesterday. Okay. So,
the next level really would be 960s. Uh
there's a previous date. I gapat will be
9:05
and uh Asia from yesterday would be 960s
or 958. So, you've just done a lot of
damage here. Be very careful. You're
frothy up here, folks. This is top level
of that supply. If they want to shut
this door on your face, they will.
Right. This is a new level been built
out here. We're very thin under 28.
Well, there's a 20 pointer, but there's
maybe a bit more like 50 60 pointer down
to here. So, be careful if they flush
this
I'll give you a readout of the mag.
Tesla now 1.18% up. Nvidia 3% up.
Microsoft just gone red to green 0.09%
up. Meta 1% down. Google approaching 6%
up. And absolutely insane 5.64% up.
Apple over a percent up. 1.13% up.
Amazon the weaker one today 1.40% down.
Here's the drive. So, what did I say?
Previous day were open was 9:05 or
something. Probably watching that level.
If you're into runners, 905s.
905s and then uh
at London High. Make this bigger. That's
how much her head's hurting. 905s and
then uh 956s I think it was.
Big old squeeze.
This is the next level. So 9005. So
you're almost there is the gap fill. Uh
and then 960s.
Yeah. Up in this is previous day high up
here. 960s.
There's 900s.
getting absolutely slammed.
All is in control of this at the moment.
Lower time frame.
This is the short squeeze. Remember,
you're now above those levels where the
short squeezes can start. This is what
you're starting to see. You're seeing a
rush to cover.
Big exchange up here.
You do not want to be adding long
positions up here. I tell you that much.
That five minute nasty straight upside
points straight upside on a five minute
in the opening 30 minutes basically.
It's big range folks. That is more than
we used to do in a day in the first 30
minutes.
Move that.
>> [yawns and sighs]
>> freezing. I'm trying I'm trying to stick
with you here, guys. I'm I'm not feeling
good at all. I'm trying to stick with
you for a bit.
New H1 coming.
You're right at previous day open
and the 5day moving average.
New loads on Vicks.
>> [snorts]
>> This is impressive that they're doing
this so early.
It's [snorts] impressive. You're very
steep up here, folks. This can offer a
nasty pullback when it's ready. Maybe
one more squeeze out into this if you
get lucky. If you're still managing a a
runner up, but just be careful.
Be careful. Please be careful.
Yeah, I will. I will duck out soon,
guys. Don't worry. Just sit with you for
a little bit longer.
Not going to stay here till lunch. Trust
me.
Okay, previous day open now like hit
that previous day open. Only thing left
now is previous day high
and then I guess I mean
can't rule it out. Previous week value
area low. I cannot rule it out up into
here. Very unlikely I would say on a day
which would normally be inside.
Technically, we're still inside until we
get above previous day high, but we're
outside of previous day value area high.
So, any bid that holds above previous
day value area high, all right, could be
supported now technically as an outside
to finish this rotation. Once they take
this, there's not that much left to aim
for.
Yeah, exactly. No. Yeah. See, previous
day open uh is here now 9:05 and
previous day high is up at uh like 5950
or somewhere somewhere around that. Just
call it 60.
Just call it 60.
[snorts]
previous day. I probably coming here by
the looks of it.
Google now 6.10%
up. It's mad, man. Absolutely crazy.
It's a crazy
[clears throat]
560. No, sorry. 560. That 800 to 850 was
the squeeze trigger like we talked
about. And uh now you're ripping off
that.
You want to see if they can hold bids
back down into that kind of level. Where
is that 800? Sort of this level here.
Here or here. If they hold bids without
completing this rotation, maybe they
come back for it. If they fail back
under here, that is a look above and
fail, right? If they fail back inside
value inside the 800s, it's a look above
and fail. Bulls need to basically hold
above 800. Bears want this to be a look
above and fail back inside the 800 and a
rotation down. That's that's the two
moves I'll be looking for the rest of
the day in case I get out of there soon.
[snorts]
You see now flipped higher
developing more volume here. You're very
close to that previous day high. You're
very close. Make sure you've paid
yourself on the way up here, please.
Make sure you paid yourself. Let's have
a look at ES.
Yeah, same move on ES. ES trying to get
up to 708 5day moving average previous
day high up there. Exactly the same move
on the S.
And same thing, there's been no
pullback. It's just straight up on five
minute bars this morning. So you just be
aware of that. It's a big big big
squeeze.
Trump speaking at 12. Oh my god. Really?
Does he really need to do that on a day
like today? What's he speaking about?
What is the volume profile? and good
volume profile.
>> [sighs]
>> might get a pullback coming soon. If
they don't take previous day high soon
and they keep going sideways, you might
get that pullback. So, just be aware.
It hasn't washed any bull out this
morning. Just think about what you're
witnessing at the moment. It is
literally straight up
without any stop being taken. Imagine
you're bullish anywhere this morning.
Your stop is absolutely fine. It has not
taken anyone out. Will not last forever.
At some point, it will want to take
people's stock.
>> [snorts]
>> go.
So, I'd be watching 800. I know it's a
long way. Sort of 840 to 800. If you're
trying to be bullish, need that level to
hold.
[snorts]
If it takes all the low hanging fruit
out above you, it's going to be quite
hard for you to be bullish on a
pullback, isn't it? Because it's got
less reason to go up then. means it's
run all the stops.
So just think about that as well. Only
real thing left here is this previous
day high that red line on your chart. Uh
let's have a look above that. Is there
much
line here that
previously
level would be 25,94ish?
Yeah, it's absolutely fine,
Ari. You can use it on any time frame,
any [snorts] time frame at all that you
want.
As long as you're playing that time
frame, as long as you understand what's
happening in that time frame, that's all
that matters,
right? You're starting to see volume be
built out up here. If bulls cannot
complete the rotation to previous day
high, do not be surprised if there's a
nasty wash as lots of volume has just
been built up here, right? They're
trying to complete this. Here's your
volume shelf. If they can't hold this,
you can see a dunk down to here and even
here very very quickly because this gone
straight up. This would just be a
pullback or a pullback to then try and
go higher to take this out, this low
hanging fruit. they take this first and
then do it. If I was you, I'd be less
interested in this market in general.
[snorts]
There are sellers trying to sell this
and they're not getting their way yet.
They're trying. They're trying to be
aggressive here to break 900s and come
down towards that 840 to 800.
And if we don't take out previous day
high, that's where bulls will want to
try and step in somewhere around that
840 to 800 mark. I would imagine
[snorts]
it's the edge of the first shelf here
that we just talked about. And if they
fail this, that next gray box is
possible. See, it's the edge of the
first shelf. I can this one up here.
Right. Here's your edge.
Ball's trying to defend this edge. You
let go of this. Here's your next one.
Here's your next one. All right.
We have not liquidated anyone yet today.
All right. You're only starting to see
only the top guys here who bought the
very highs currently are feeling pain.
No one here is in pain. All right. No
bull is truly in pain here right now.
They're [snorts]
still they are holding on very very very
well here. Looking for that previous day
high. It's what they're looking for.
There's no doubt about it.
Just flagged this again. It's really
good hold of this gray box. Top side of
the gray box. This is where they're
trying to get and then through here.
This is your next level up here.
Very, very strong. Very strong squeeze.
Shorts are are really struggling here.
Here
you go. Here's the move. So, PDH low
hanging fruit through that. Some old
weekly close up here if they're really
going to get motoring.
[snorts]
I think you get pretty do. You're so
close. You might as well go take.
So any hold of this gray box,
ball should defend it. underneath that
gray box, you just go rotation to next
level down and so forth.
But momentum has gone bullish on the
day. No doubt about it. Flow zone
started expanding right in here was
horrible. But once they started
expanding, that buy signal was literally
perfect. It's insane. Once they got that
and you saw that the it starting to fan
out, then uh it was impressive.
It was impressive. It's an impressive
move. [snorts]
>> [sighs]
[snorts]
>> Chicken noodle soup. Yeah. Well, it's uh
it's a bit early for that for me. It's
uh 7:13 in the morning.
Chicken noodle soup yet. Um a hot bath
and asleep sounds good. I barely slept.
I woke up 2:00 just my head pounding.
Top Ballinger. Get out of it, Jesse.
[laughter]
Where's that Top Ballinger?
They're going for alltime highs.
[laughter]
I'm from London. I live in Los Angeles.
[snorts]
I'm from from London, but I live in LA.
Top. Get out of it. Can you imagine?
inid inv video with a quadruple beat.
[snorts]
You're almost there. That red line, top
red line, that's your previous day high.
And that's why we've got a red box up
there. Supply up there.
That gray box is your first support
system. Each gray box is the volume
you've built on the way up. This is
nothing more than a big old squeeze. All
right, PDH taken. Only thing left now to
go for really is this gray area up here.
It's previous week close. I think
Thursday, Friday. Yeah, that's previous
week close. All right.
That would be like all the way back to
Friday's close basically from last week.
That'd be like nothing's happened.
Do I miss the UK?
What do you think?
Absolutely not. Miss my mates, miss the
banter, miss a good pub. I guess there
are parts I miss.
Miss going to the Premier League or the
rugby, but other than that, no.
[snorts]
Still squeezing.
This is a really impressive squeeze.
Next level is all the way up here.
That's your weekly close
and Google 6.66%
up. Pubs in LA. There's there's one
there's one decent pub in LA which is an
English pub. They don't know how to pour
a pint here. [\h__\h] getting a good pint
here is basically impossible. It's like
it's always it's always flat and it's
always got no head and it's never cold
enough.
It's that bad that like if if you got it
poured in an English pub, you'd be like,
"Pour that again, mate." But they don't.
They just don't know how to pour it
here.
It's a joke.
I'd only drink bottled beer here because
they can't pour a pint. How sad's that?
I order a bottled beer here because they
don't know how to pour a pint.
Unless you go to like there's good pubs
here like the Irish pubs like the old
fella um is good. Um
uh Queen's Head Santa Monica is good.
It's English pub, old English pub.
By a pint do I mean a kind of beer? A
pint is the size of the beer that you
would order in England. You wouldn't go
to a pub in England and say, "Can I have
a glass of beer?" Or or you wouldn't
even say a beer. You just be like, "Can
I get a pint of Stella, please?" Or,
"Can I get a pint of this, please?"
Uh, don't drink cider. Too sweet, maybe.
Maybe when I was a kid.
Yeah. And the bonds are all up today as
well. Got my eye on everything. Just a
bit of a relief day across across the
board right now.
Yeah, I'm sure New York does that. That
would make total sense to me. Sure New
York does it.
So, previous day high taken,
low hanging fruit taken. Only thing left
if they're going to drift it higher is
the previous week lows.
You're building out a decent amount of
liquidity up here.
Remember, you've hit your objectives.
So, I mean, even if they dip back down
now, it's hard to want to be long on
pullbacks now because this is a a giant
squeeze out which has now taken the
high. So, you know, there's less reason
for them to catch a bid to go back up
now because they've done the work.
Alex, do you know where the term mind
your pleases and Q's what where it comes
from? Please and thank yous. I I don't
know who invented it.
Whenever I hear that, I just think of
Ko.
Yeah, it means please and thank yous.
You tell me where does it come from? Do
you know the origin where it originated
from? It's just shortening for PE for
please and thank yous. [snorts]
points and corpse. Is it actually? No,
it's not. Is it actually?
Wow, I didn't know that.
I just think of Kano when I hit from his
song way back in the day.
Instead of going for small trades, why
don't you size up and go for the jo jug
that I've been watching you for a while.
You're pretty good at this. Um, I size
up when the conditions are good for me
to size up in and when I have my
accounts at positions that I'm happy to
size up in.
That's pretty cool. I never knew that.
Thanks for that, Rosco.
Nice fact.
Pints and quartz. Mind your pints and
quartz.
More coffee. Peter,
don't blame you, mate.
So, back towards this shelf that we've
built up. If they fail this shelf, then
we probably go 8 850s to 800s. But
they've built out a huge amount of
volume up here. Now, if they remember,
this is this has literally been straight
up. Can imagine us coming back down to
test some of this if they want. This is
the big level is your current point of
control on the day.
This is a big big squeeze out without
any pullback of any significance.
What a wild market. Just a casual 415
points straight up without pullback.
just uh
can have if I just said that 415
points straight up.
[laughter]
Look at an M5. No pullback. Just just
straight up on an M5. That is insane.
Welcome to the short squeezes in bare
markets. This is what happens. Bare
market rallies. We've talked about it
all week. It's It's exactly what
happens. If anyone's been here all week
with me, I've said the rallies in bare
markets are very violent.
There you go.
>> [snorts]
>> So, I'm selling up here. Building out
this volume. It's getting pretty thick
up here.
They let go of the shelf. Then I think
we uh do some washes into some of these
key levels down here
750. I mean previous day point of
control. It could, couldn't it? It could
it could come back to here. It could
come back to there.
We're starting to see some of these
bulls fil who have chased the highs
above previous day high. Remember anyone
who's been a breakout buyer above
previous day high. I don't know why we
do that but people do do that. They
might start to feel some pressure here
soon.
>> You won't get that rotation.
Trying to hold on here, folks.
See if we can get another 40 minutes.
Going to use a bathroom here. You have
to excuse me. I'm really not feeling
good. I'll be right back.
All right. Still building out in this
shelf.
Jack, you're short.
I mean, the area is good. I haven't seen
it let go of anything yet, but the area
is good. I'll be honest. I haven't been
watching the um tapers closely today.
I'm just not feeling well. But let me
have a quick look for you.
Um you want to defend 64 64 65. If bears
defend that, then I'd say there's a
little bit of excess left above that.
All right. But I' I'd be cautious on any
reclaim of 65 right now, just based on
the order flow.
Yeah, Tyson, they just emailed out
actually um saying that they know
they're still experiencing problems.
They're doing everything they can to fix
it.
So, who is it that just said they're
short? Uh Jack. So, just be careful
here. You they need to defend that area.
You're still building volume. I mean,
for me, there's no short trigger here.
You're still holding flow zones. You're
still basing out. Um, but if they defend
6465, you have had excess above that.
Um, but you would need to see that
defended. I think that last push, did
that come right into it? 63.75 was
pretty good, wasn't it? So, that's the
level. Whatever that last push was like
I talked about, bulls are stuck above
that. Reclaim that. I would be very
cautious to hold on to your short.
I would personally, I wouldn't be
shorting this yet. I haven't seen a move
away from anything yet.
[laughter]
Yeah, I think they get it fixed for
tomorrow. Tyson.
Oh, you're trading ES. Okay. Well, as
long as you doing what works for you,
mate. Like, I'm just telling you what
I'm seeing. But, uh, if you've got a
strategy that's working for you, it's
what it's how you should trade. You
stick to it.
Still defending that kind of level for
now.
wiggle here in the tape. There's a
battle here in the tape.
Starting to see some stronger sellers
try and come in. Being more aggressive
here.
Haven't got that move down yet, but they
are trying. They're trying to pile in
here.
[snorts]
Yeah, IB coming. IB is coming. 30
seconds or so. 45 seconds.
Just got absorbed there again. Bears
tried to sell on to 50 and it just got
absorbed there again. So, they're going
to retest this 64.
is trying to defend 64. So if they can't
defend it, they're in going to be in
trouble.
[snorts]
Uh, Francesca, go to the end of the
course, you'll see a module. Uh, in that
module, it tell you what to do. There's
like I think it's it's either called
Discord or it's called um members or
community or something like that. You
just got to shoot me an email from
there. It tells you what to what to say
and then I'll add you in.
Yes, we're well
we're definitely building up liquidity.
Your point of controls up here, right?
But we're defending 64 but not seeing a
breakdown at the unders underside of
this. I mean, we can tie this in smaller
now. There's your zone. This is your
zone which they're trading in. So, yes,
we're definitely building liquidity,
aren't we? We've traded the most volume
on the whole session has been traded up
here now.
Someone will get hurt. It's a matter of
time.
And if they fail this, then you know
they have room.
I'd watch the 900s and then sub 900s,
850s to 830s.
You'll be aware of bear traps today. If
their ambition is to get to that
previous week close,
you have to be aware of bear traps.
We're starting to see that move away
from that liquidity now. It's the first
time I'd say you're starting to see a
move away from liquidity, but be very,
very cautious. Balls have been in
control all morning.
PC is here for me on Ninja Trader. PC is
at 38 or 40s. Just be aware of that.
We're just trading around point of
control right now.
[sighs]
They caught it again. So that's the bear
trap underneath that shelf.
Back to the top side. And they're going
to keep going backwards and forwards.
This can take a while until they've got
enough caught one side that they want to
use.
>> [snorts]
>> Like I said, the trend today so far has
been up
>> [snorts]
>> That's interesting. Are they actually
going to print an outside day?
be so impressive.
It would be so impressive. [snorts]
[snorts]
Man, colds are the worst. I haven't had
one in so long.
Last time I was ill was CO. That was
like what June or July
[snorts]
is trying to defend this area. It's such
a big area, man.
Look at the lows from Monday
from uh yeah 10:00
into 2:00 and we traded away from it and
retested it and stay heavy. If they if
if Bulls reclaim this area,
it's really really impressive.
Over where? Over what area? The whole
over this whole area. I'm not going to
do the math on you. You can see it on
the session volume profile. It's right
here in front of you. Look, you can see
it right here. It's a thick area, right?
From 62
up to 87. That's where it's thick. And
then it thins out a bit and then we get
a bit thinner
until we get to this 900. It's right
here for you. You don't need me to tell
you. It's in front of you on the chart.
I have it in front of you for that
reason.
I think there's a wash coming soon. It's
just whether they trap bears in that
wash or not. Starting to build up lots
of volume here. Starting to see bearish
pressure try and force this wash down to
into some of these levels.
previous day high taken starting to
build volume up at those highs and now
we're starting to move away from those
highs.
Yeah, Kevin, you see that book map above
me? It's right there. It's there. There.
That's why I have it there for you to
use.
And even if you're not, you can use
volume profile. You can see where are we
thick? 37 to 50 is here. You don't need
to know the exact order number. You can
see where we're thick. This doesn't
matter if it's bitmap or whatever you're
using.
[snorts]
So if bears defend
basically 40 to 50 10point range, you
can see a rotation maybe for this wick
and down into here. If bulls reclaim
that, I'd be watching out for a big old
squeeze out.
Bear traps in this environment can be uh
pretty nasty.
I'm not playing this game anymore, guys.
Starting to see bears come in here. They
need to defend this level. This gray
box. This gray box right here. That is
what they must defend. If you're going
to see a wash down here, if they fail to
defend it, this can be a bullish move.
This can be a two-leg.
If they catch this, this is what you're
going to get.
And the target will be up here if they
do that. It's that's a very very bullish
move if they do it
up into this. Bears will try and defend
this gray box here.
That's an important level for them to
defend right now. [snorts]
That's what you're watching.
Overall momentum in this session has
been upside. There's no doubt about it.
You are 415 points higher. We built out
some volume going sideways.
You just can't rule anything out in this
market.
I'm going to start ignoring chat cuz
some of the stuff I'm seeing is
nonsensical at this point.
Starting to find a bid up towards that
previous day low. How it reacts there is
going to be important. I would say
they're successfully defending so far.
That box that is the area. It's been the
area the whole time.
There is room both sides here. It's just
going to be a battle of who's going to
win. Are higher time frame bears going
to protect this area or not? It's really
It's really that simple. Do higher time
frame bears want to protect this area
and force the rotation back down or not?
If the answer is no, or that the bulls
are saying, "Hey, we want it higher."
Then they will win. The levels are here.
I've put them there for you. Trade it as
you want. I'm not active today. Not well
enough to be trading today.
Starting to see some bears try and force
their way in here. 900 is a level. They
keep soaking off the 900 over and over
and over again these bulls. If you get a
break down here and you know that next
gray box is not out the question. It
isn't out the question. There you go. So
starting to trade into the 900s. Once
you snap this, there is potential room.
Just be careful of bear traps because
you're basically trying to play the
counter trend of the high, but we are
rejecting volume. So, this was the area
I told you so many times. If bears
defend this, which they did,
this move here is possible and this is
possible. Okay? Because we haven't
pulled back yet. They can bulls can set
a trap and do this. So, you do not want
to be bearish on any reclaim of that
level. That's all I'm saying. If you
want to be bearish at this level looking
for the wash, that makes sense. But do
not be bearish above this level. All
right? Because then you're going to try
and pick a top and you will get hurt. If
you want to be bullish, if you're
waiting, I'd say one big problem. You've
taken the lowhanging fruit today. But,
uh, I don't love this play. It's it's
probable that they will squeeze if they
do that play, but it means you're bet
buying very high. It's very risky. The
easier bullish move will be something
like this. You know, something like that
off off an area or even that same move
down here will be a nicer rotation
rotational move. Right now, bear
starting to take control after trapping
bulls at the highs after previous day
high was taken.
[snorts] Here's the 900s. Big
psychological level. This 900
bit. Still trying to get up to previous
day low here.
Okay. Tesla 1.8. 86% up, Nvidia 3.25%
up, Microsoft 0.13% down, Meta 1.10%
down, Amazon 1% down, Apple 1.37% up,
and Google 5.61%
up. Currently trading over 300s.
Amazing.
Amazing strength.
There's looking for that snap down to
that next area. That's what the bears
are looking for. They're looking to have
trapped bulls and defend this area.
Remember, this is the area from Monday.
If we zoom out,
right? This is the area under over under
over. Think about this.
We always talk about support, support,
breakdown, resistance, resistance,
breakdown. Currently, resistance. We get
over it, support, and squeeze as
possible. Which is why I'm saying if we
get over that, you do not want to be
bearish. But right now, they're doing a
good job of defending it. They've let
bulls chase above previous day high.
They've created a volume shelf here.
They're defending the volume shelf here.
They're liquidating this player here.
And now they're trying to get a flush
into these gray boxes. And then what
happens at that point? I don't know.
We're going to have to watch the
momentum as we get down there, right? Do
balls come back in or not?
I'm starting to sweat now. [\h__\h] I might
not be on tomorrow, folks. All right.
I'm I'm away Friday, but if I'm feeling
like this tomorrow, I'm going to have to
just try and rest. [snorts]
Otherwise, I'm just going to set myself
back.
So, a trap can live in this low volume
node. So, if you've been bearish, just
you don't want to see this snap back
from here. You don't want this to act as
a support mechanism. You want a straight
flush down to the next level. If you're
bearish on this move here into into 38s
or 40s, you want to see a straight swipe
down and then just trail it down and
hopefully it just pukes all the way out
for you. It' be very nice because think
about what we've done today. Have we
built any structure really on the way
up? Not really, have we? Right. So, the
deeper this goes, the better. But you do
not want to be bearish above this gray
box up here in red line. That is
absolutely asking for it. If they
reclaim that, it is asking for it.
Oh my head.
All right, here's the retest of it.
Again, if they reclaim this, I would not
hold on to your shorts. If they reclaim
this, I would not hold on. They defend
it, you're fine, right? They keep using
it as a level to sell into, you're fine.
Would not hold on to shorts above it. I
wouldn't be risking high day here.
Personally, for me, I think it's way too
risky.
Yeah, I don't blame you, Mike. I mean,
it's one of those days, right? Like
I was happy to be long, you know, if we
came down into here. Maybe that was
stingy of me, but you know, I'm not
going to play the opening drive when
all we did was this. We think about what
we did this morning. Up, down, up, down,
up, down. The first what, four minutes
didn't come into here. I was looking for
a lip below and fail if I'm going to be
a trigger long. And then we go and we
chop around here for a bit and then we
go and we just we just go. We don't
stop. We don't do anything other than
straight up. So you now, like you said,
we've taken previous day high, low
hanging fruit's gone. You're going to
see a move back down. We don't know if
bulls are going to come in and defend
that move because they've just got the
big squeeze out that they wanted. Who's
to say this doesn't come all the way
down to low of day.
We've seen weirder things happen in this
market, right? We've absolutely seen
weirder things happen right now.
It's a big squeeze out. Remember, it was
415 point squeeze out this morning.
Do I think they want to take 25,000? I
mean, they were pretty close. So, but
you know, it's not a level other than a
psychological level. The level really,
if they're going to they're going to get
above today's high, the level really is
up here, 25,000
and let's just call it 95.
That's the level. They're building more
volume out here. Walking this down.
Yeah. Yeah. Pretty much, Peter. Pretty
much.
I'd watch VIX into previous day low here
into a shelf. If it if it rejects it,
bulls might come in and try and find a
bid soon. But if we keep going straight
through it and it's going to go back up
to New York open now, well, this market
can get heavy pretty quick. Remember, we
were very, very thin on the way up. This
volume's been built on the way back
down. Wasn't really built on the way up.
This shelf here now you just call it
900. If they fail that, maybe we get
down into this gray box and VWAP
and maybe even test previous day value
area high, you know, because technically
if we bid above previous day value area
high, we can have an outside push.
Um, I mean, they stop started too low
today. They're
they're they're nasty. The way they did
it was pretty nasty, but it's just
because shorts started tripping over
themselves. That's that's all it was in
my mind.
My sinuses. My poor sinuses.
Thank god I don't work as a DJ anymore.
I used to have to play like this. I'd
feel like [\h__\h] Pardon my French.
[snorts] Money in the sweat jar again.
All right. Previous day low here for
VIX.
Big level it's trading into now.
Basically into 23s.
Heaviness coming into this market.
They're trying to sell it pretty hard
right now.
You can see the bumps in the road. I've
got them marked out. You if bulls are
going to step in, those are the areas
they can potentially step in. You cannot
rule this out just selling the whole
thing back. It's literally gone straight
up. You don't know if it's going to go
straight down. You just don't know. It's
completed its objective. I don't know
what their plan is with this today.
Where is spy? 64 Q's back above 600.
It's okay.
Right into sort of that next little bump
in the road down here. Maybe they get
VWAP.
So much pain. [snorts]
Almost do another one of these here. Now
this lower edge
will want to defend this.
>> [snorts]
>> Think it's getting close to that level
now. Very close into 23s now. Trading at
2298.
Very, very close through previous day
low already. Can it hold a bit above it
on the VIX? If so,
We're a bit congested in here. I'd say
23 to
2350 and then through that New York open
which I mean we'd give back the whole
move obviously if did that move New York
open
into these deep pullback flow zones. New
York view up underneath. We have
liquidity a little bit of liquidity
built out underneath. Not a whole lot
value on the day back down at 760.
You can see once they trapped those guys
at the top and they successfully
defended it, now we're starting to wash
down to search. What we searching for?
We're searching for new value, right?
We're searching for fair value. None was
deemed up there. We moved away from it
now. All the buyers got caught moving
aggressively away. We're going to search
for value. We don't know if and when
that value comes. It might not come. It
might be that they go all the way back
to the lows because we haven't built any
structure. I don't know. I can only tell
you what I'm seeing in front of me. I
have no idea what their intentions for
this are.
VWAP is currently trading at 34s
and I think it was 8 40 to 800s or 850
to 800s was the levels from yesterday.
Right. So here we go. Here's the 40s VW
coming up and under that previous day
value area high. Okay, so if you're in
the short, you look pretty good at the
moment. Under this, we get very, very
thin. Again, you can see the shelf
there. We get very thin under this.
Here's your VWAP bid. So, some bids at
VWAP here. A little bit of a reaction
here.
So, back down into that gray box and
shelf. That's your first reaction of the
day
or buyers.
And you need to see if they can sustain
anything here, really, don't you? You
need to see are they going to hold this
gray box. This is a cover point for you.
If you were short, you should be taking
a partial here. If they flush this
previous day value area high and then
all the way back down into 740s. All
right, so hopefully this makes sense for
you. My head is pounding, so I am not
actively trading this today, folks. But
hopefully me making sense of this is
helping you. Maybe I'm able to teach
even more than normal because I'm not
really trading it.
Oh, did it did it really mo? Yeah, for
me it was just a look. It was a look
above previous day high and fail. That's
all it was for me. Squeeze out, look
above, fail into key level here. Balls
either hold this level. If they fail to
hold this level, we drop down. So the
rotations, if bulls hold this level,
right, the rotation will be
between this box and this box, right?
Because that's when we get thick, they
reclaim this between this box and this
box. If bulls fail the rotation, we're
going to come down either here or here.
That's the battle, right? That's how we
build liquidity. We're searching to see
if this is deemed fair value. Do bulls
want to say, "Hey, no more. This is
good. We're happy to buy here. This is
too cheap now." Or do they go, "Hey, no,
no, no, no. We're we're in too much pain
here. It's got to come lower. We don't
like the price of this here. It's got to
come lower before we defend it." And who
knows? Maybe they don't defend it at
all. We don't know that, right? It's
searching. It's searching for prices
where bulls might want to buy it.
No worries, David.
So, next cover point for you if you're
in the short would be that previous day
value area high, which is 800 around
here. Somewhere around here, folks.
All right. You should have, if you've
been short, you should have paid
yourself something. I'm going to be
honest. You should have paid yourself
something. This is a big move. If you've
been short, you should have paid
yourself something
cuz we're into this sort of gray box
zone. If they fail this, then uh or you
get a bigger wash and you'd be very
happy. But you've got to pay yourself on
the way. You don't know if and when this
responds.
Fixes are really on a pump here, folks.
It looks like it's gunning for that uh
New York open. It really does look like
it's gunning for New York Open. We can't
rule out cannot rule out a low day here.
It's just mad that I'm even saying that.
But straight up, we can go straight back
down. Right.
415 points up. Can you imagine if we go
450 point 415 points down? Jeez Louise.
Jeez Louise.
Vick's still going.
2350 is now on a VIX. It is still going.
This thing is flying.
What a market. What a market.
Next point is previous day value low.
Sorry, previous day value very high. And
this box here, 24-hour view up. Those
are your next points. that you should
have paid yourself on the way down.
[snorts]
I mean, we're almost at value area low
on the session, right? If you're talking
about current session, but you have to
respect the previous s day session as
well. So, this is a big cover point if
you're playing value. That's a major
cover point here for for previous day
and current day. Remember, current day
isn't set and like maybe we want to
expand it. We don't know. We don't know.
Here
it is for me on Ninja. It's right here
right now.
Fix is still going, folks. Fix is still
going.
This is very bearish right now. All
those bulls who chased getting
absolutely annihilated.
Still seeing bears try and fly in here
at these lows. They're still selling.
I'm not seeing a bid on the tape yet.
This is all selling. Haven't seen anyone
come in and say enough. This is all
sellside pressure so far.
First time I've seen a cover bid here
right now. It's the first time since
this moved down I've really seen one
and I'm not ruling out there. You can't
rule it out right now. This is so heavy.
So next block here VW up here.
Straight up all morning. Are we going to
go straight down?
Straight up all morning. Are [laughter]
we going to go straight down?
VIX almost at New York Open. Man, oh
man.
Wild. What a wild market. I am
absolutely sweating buckets right now.
Sweaty, sweaty.
Bit of a shake out bid here. The bears
still in control here. Still not seeing
any bears get trapped here. Still
aggressive selling at the lows and we're
still moving lower. Bears are in control
here. No doubt about it.
What a market. It's just so directional.
Like it's just like we go one direction,
we stop, we go the other direction. Like
we just don't build out structure
anymore in these markets because it's
squeeze one way basically squeeze the
other way. effectively is what I'm
trying to say. That's all it does. Okay.
Previous day point of control down here.
VWAP down here.
Where's VIX is almost at that New York
open. Oh my gosh. This is so bearish
right now. The momentum in here is so
heavy. I'm still not seeing that much of
a bid. This is straight down. This is
not even tried to find a bid. Look.
Straight down. Straight up. Straight
down.
Let's see where we are in terms of a
fib.
Come on, Trading View. I have not got
the energy for you to [\h__\h] up today,
please.
So, coming into the 61. This is so
bearish.
Right, first bid. First bit of size been
put on the tape there. Uh 800 lot. And I
wouldn't trust him one bit if I was you.
That's such a big size. I think he's a
probably a spoofer, but it's the first
time I've seen some size been put on a
bid today.
I would not trust him.
They're going to come for him. He's
advertising and I guarantee you he
[\h__\h] pulls it.
This looks very bearish to me, folks.
Very, very, very bearish to me right
now.
I'm not sure I would trust that guy at
all down there. I reckon he pulls it the
moment you get anywhere near him.
I reckon he's a spoofer. I reckon he's a
seller. And I reckon he pulls it.
Vicks at New York Open now.
Fix at that New York open now.
NQ at VWOP.
ES under VWOP. Spy under VWOP. QQQ
underview.
NQ at VWOP.
Is there a response at all today from
these bulls or did we just trap everyone
at that high and it's time to go from
new lows again? I have no idea.
Genuinely, I have no idea what they want
to do with this market.
All I know is we're back inside
yesterday's value right now. We didn't
defend previous day value area high.
Some response here from bulls, but still
not big. You'd want to see Mr. 800 lot
move up if he's legit. And right now
he's not budged.
And I don't reckon he's legit.
It happens by both, Mo. By both.
So Vick's rejecting New York Open for
now.
Are we just going to go sideways now?
Seriously,
you guys not going to participate all of
a sudden? What are you doing? They've
just stopped.
Literally, they've just stopped while
they figure out what they're doing, I
guess.
Um, so if they do squeeze, they'd be
coming up here into 828, basically this
gray box. And if they got over that,
back up here, and this is the rotation.
And if they fail this, probably down. We
can move this a little bit. Probably
down to this little globeex level.
I've got to turn this light down, folks.
I'm really sorry. I'm getting such a bad
headache. I know it doesn't look as good
on stream, but my h head is pounding
right now. [snorts]
So, some buyers trying to wake up here.
It's probably as much covering as
anything else. Um, this can still be a
bare flag, which is sold into to move
lower right now because they haven't
built any structure out. I I would just
be very careful. It's a very one-way
take. We either going straight up or
we're going straight down. We haven't
seen much liquidity be built out other
than that. This is current value area
low on the day and they can expand it
because we are now inside previous day's
value. So they failed to hold previous
day value for now.
Yes, we are in a high volume node. This
gray box showing you the high volume
nodes. All right, I marked them out for
you. That's why they're there.
Few
shorts got stuck at 770 there. But uh I
would struggle to trust this. Honestly,
I would really struggle to trust this
right now.
I just think in in markets like this,
big players will do whatever big players
want to do. And as smaller fish,
it's very very hard when they just go,
okay, one side to the other. Who knows?
Maybe they come all the way down here,
this side to this side.
So it's a rotational market in 415
points of rotation.
Mind blown. But that's what it is.
That's the size of weekly moves back in
the day. We're doing those in 45
minutes.
Nice [snorts] David.
You're basically back into the midpoint
of the range today. I mean, what what
are you going to do with this? What are
you going to do with this? Probably not
a lot not a lot you can do with this
here.
Are they actually going to give this
whole move back?
You'd expect them to defend. If they're
going to defend this, they I would say
they need to defend this in this area.
Now, if they give this whole move back,
I mean,
if I
man, that is a big uh what should we
say? It's a big tell on the market,
isn't it? If they're going to give 420
plus points back, it's a pretty big tell
that this market is scared shitless
right now if they're not going to hold
any pull back.
That's how I read it anyway. I'd be
like, "Okay, the market's scared
shitless." So, they're going to hold it.
They need to hold here and they need to
reclaim all of this and try and get up
into there. If bulls have got any chance
today to do anything reasonable,
every pot now starting to be sold. Hey,
this is the story from the last few
days.
That last pop was just passively sold.
And I don't like that you have got an
800 lot advertising that he's a buyer
underneath 725. I don't like that one
bit.
Gonna come for him. I [\h__\h] guarantee
we come for him. And I guarantee he
leaves the tape. Here we come.
HOW LONG TILL WE OH, WHO' have guessed?
Who have [\h__\h] guessed he left the
tape? Told you.
Absolutely told you. It's so Their games
are so obvious, but it's so dirty.
[laughter]
It's so dirty, folks. When they do that,
he's non-existent. He's non-existent
because he's not a buyer. He's a seller
trying to make price go lower. That's
exactly what he is. So that you
understand, he wants price to go lower.
So, he's advertising a big old order
there and pulling it when it gets close
because he's got no ambition on actually
buying that.
And down we go.
Balls are [\h__\h] This is a big problem
now. And this this should be uh a big
warning sign to everyone of hey, we're
not respecting levels. We're not holding
above value. We're we're just selling.
Everything is being sold no matter what.
That's a bit of a warning sign. I would
say
if bulls can't defend after squeezing
400 points, it's a warning sign, isn't
it? If they can't defend, it's a big
warning sign.
It's the first covering we've seen right
here into previous day point control.
First bit of covering we've seen. Back
to VWAP we go.
[snorts]
And we now have this shelf above that
balls can get stuck in. We can move this
slightly. Right. This is the level.
Right. So balls will need to get above
this for a rotation. Failing to get
above that, they'll be caught.
Again, that was all from manipulation.
You get used to seeing these guys on the
tape. They're games. It's nasty. It's
not legal. But proving it's very, very
hard.
Vick's still not through that New York
open. They're still in control here.
[snorts]
Uh, yep. Very possible, Henrik. Yeah,
very possible. Which is down here? 600s.
Very possible.
Going to be a battle now.
I'm not sure they're done selling it.
The excess at the low is buyers, not
sellers. I'm not sure they're done
selling this yet, but we will see.
What a market, man. I cannot remember
markets that move like this. 400 points
one direction. What's this? Probably 300
points the other direction. I can't
really remember markets that move like
this.
Nice, fresh. Good work. I don't think
the auction's finished lower yet, just
from what I'm seeing.
We'll see. They did just try and sell
that last candle and failed, but the
lows, current lows on on that uh dip 3,
four minutes ago.
We're not seeing excess selling down
there yet, but we'll see. We'll see. But
this gray box above you, you can see
that's the squeeze trigger. Once you get
through that gray box, you can squeeze
higher. But right now, sellers are in
absolute control.
No worries, fresh. Yeah, I've got
pounding headache. I really want to get
out of here, but market's starting to
move for you guys. I want to call it
do feel dreadful, though.
Back to previous day point of control
here. And if we fail that, well, we've
not got much below. We really do not
have much below.
Do they come back for previous day value
area low? Who knows? Structure is very
bearish right now. No excess on the
lows. Bears coming flying in. Until we
see bears get caught at the on a low
print. I don't think there's any chance
of a squeeze back up. We're not We're
just not seeing it yet.
Remember, the market's in fear. It's in
absolute fear. That's why I'm kind of
surprised they even had the power to do
uh what they did this morning to be
quite honest with you.
But here we go. Like I said, don't think
the auction's finished because we
haven't seen excess selling at the lows.
It's first time we're seeing selling
down here. And is there a response to it
at the moment?
Do we go back to Gloveex, which would be
what? 680.
That would be Gloveex at the moment.
700s. Those old 700s from last month.
Have a look on that shelf.
They didn't defend it. They did not
defend it. We are weak on multiple
profiles right now.
Still, I'm not convinced the auction's
done yet. Still not convinced this
auction's done selling.
No excess.
Oh my gosh,
what a uh
panicky market.
What a panicky market. Where's the daily
bowl now?
560.
Okay, just worth noting.
Still no excess at the lows for me.
We have some structure here, but we
don't have excess.
Still not seeing much of a response here
from buyers is what I'm saying.
Still not seeing sellers get trapped.
Still think there is new lows possible.
Here we go. So, selling back down again.
There's no excess. There's no real
attempt from buyers to do anything. They
are absolutely [\h__\h] themselves right
now. and I don't blame them.
Okay, back to GlobeEx then.
Still not seeing excess. Still seeing
sellers in absolute control. Still not
seeing much of a response.
Oh my gosh. Are we going to make new
lows on the day underneath New York? I
I cannot fathom this market right now.
415 points up. Are we going to go beyond
415 points down? It is absolutely
possible and that is
mental to me like to just say that out
loud.
But it's absolutely possible. We cannot
rule it out. We cannot rule out new lows
on the session. We can't rule out
anything. We're back inside value. If we
fail area high, we can come back down to
here, which is where I said I'd be
interested in buying this morning. And I
certainly will not be interested in
buying it today now. Not after they
completed the lowhanging fruit move
higher and have just absolutely tanked
this market back down. No way would I be
interested in buying down there today
now. No chance.
No way, Jose.
Still the selling comes in.
[\h__\h] me.
total liquidation right now. Absolute
liquidation events at the moment.
Little bit of a squeeze here, but you've
got so much to get through above. I
wouldn't trust it. I wouldn't be trying
to long this. We'd have to like take
many, many levels out.
battle here. Sellers still coming in.
Still very strong selling, folks.
There's absolutely nothing here to
suggest we're going to squeeze out right
now.
There's the tiniest bit of excess sub700
and not much of response above it right
now. It's not like we've traded back
above this box.
Now we're starting to see buyers try and
step in. And if they can't move it
higher, it means there's still a passive
seller on the tape, doesn't it? So just
be careful. Now we're seeing big big
buying step in. Let's see if they
actually squeeze up to this 775 and what
they do with it. What's this new wall?
you up 800s.
Can they respond here? Can these buyers
get any control of this market? They are
attempting to. They're not doing a very
good job right now.
Big selling into that push.
Big big selling into that push. Buyers
trying to respond and they're not doing
a very good job.
So 700. We've got a bid on the tape
there at 700. Trying to attract price
back down to it. He probably pulls it
again. We got an offer up at 775.
We did leave a little bit of excess at
those lows, but really nothing
significant.
Yeah, anyone that took took the short
that was fantastic once you left that
shelf.
They're going to advertise price at 700.
This guy probably same guy as earlier, a
bit less size. is probably going to pull
it as soon as it gets close to it.
[snorts]
Buyers can't even get through this uh
24-hour VWAP right now.
All this gray box. So 56 to 90
basically. Let me mark it out here so I
can see it on Ninja with you.
If they get through that and back above
previous day value, then they've got a
shot at doing something, some kind of
relief. But at the moment, bears are in
control.
Bu just tried to step in again there and
failed to move price higher. They just
came flying in again there and failed to
move price higher. They are attempting.
They are attempting to do it and they
must be a passive seller because they
are not moving higher and they're
attempting to. It's a big battle here.
Someone's about to get hurt. There you
go.
Let's see if the 700 pulls.
No, he's going to actually unabsorb, is
he?
It's not a big enough size to absorb,
tell you that much.
Just have a little look.
They're trying to get back through BW.
Nvidia got just got hammered underneath
VWAP. That's not a good look. Microsoft
low of day. Meta low of day. Pre-market
lows. Google pulling back significantly.
Has lost VWAP. Same story as the other
day. Google squeeze out and then failed.
Amazon
not too bad. Apple under VWAP pulling
back off the highs. It is ugly out
there, folks.
It is ugly out there. No one can hold
their gains. Basically,
that is the story of this market.
Think about Google the other day, giant
squeeze out and basically get the whole
move back. It's starting to look kind of
similar.
What a battle.
It's definitely a bit panicky selling
because they haven't let a response
happen. It's just dumping inventory.
Normally you'd see, you know, some kind
of bigger bounce which is sold into.
They're just dumping inventory. It's
it's fear. It's fear in the market
taking over. The emotion in the market
is fear.
Back down to this 700.
710 most traded level around here at the
moment.
Back to the 700. He's not big enough to
absorb this, so I don't know why he's
there.
Going to get wrecked, might I? Gone.
I mean, that's hardly surprising. 100
lot is not going to hold this unless
they refresh this bid.
And again, no, I'm not convinced there's
enough excess down there. But let's see.
Buyers trying to step in here back to
previous day point of control.
They can't get through previous day
point of control right now. The buyers,
they're stuck. they are stuck and till
they get through that level and the gray
box above and VW up they are stuck here
trying to absorb it without the relief
they need to get above the green box to
get any uh kind of relief rally let's
say at all
still can't get through that VWAP can
they
trading what around 43s or something
let's see
still Nothing.
Here's the attempt to get through it.
Can they get through this gray box
above? That's the big question.
Is there relief up to up towards
say 800 to 830
moment? They just got sold into the
24-hour view up again into this low
volume node. Bears are still in control
defending this area. Bears are still
looking for this. Bulls are looking for
this relief. That's what you're looking
at right now. Those are the two
opportunities in the tape. Again, I am
not trading this. I'm not well enough to
do anything right now. I'm struggling to
even read the price action for you. I'm
sweating buckets.
At least bulls have got it back above
previous day point of control. This was
a straight move up, straight move down.
It could be a straight move slicing back
through if enough bears got stuck down
here which [snorts] I'm not totally
convinced has happened. There was some
strong delta down there but I'm not
convinced yet.
I'd be watching previous day value area
high really.
That's probably kind of your level.
We got on the book above. Oh, come on.
Energy
775 800s
into this gray box. Then do they defend
the gray box or do you get a squeeze out
all the way through it?
Defending the gray box so far. And this
is your next ledge. 30. So rotation
between 30 and 50 now. possible.
[sighs]
Ball zone's pointing down. Momentum is
downside, folks. Momentum is downside.
It's just whether there's a bit of a
squeeze out here and bears sell higher.
So far, I'd say it's panic selling.
Yeah, Mag's getting getting absolutely
crushed.
M getting crushed. No doubt about it.
Bulls need to hold 30 here. Failing to
hold 30, they're in trouble.
Here's the Here's 30. There's the test.
Previous day point control. They don't
hold this, I would say. They're probably
in trouble.
They're probably in trouble.
Oh my god, what a weak market.
Look at that selling on the tape. Look
at that.
Look at that.
Jesus Christ.
I don't think they're done with this.
I don't think they're actually done with
this. You've just rejected the gray box.
You're back under into this little
shelf. This is more liquidity being
built out. You can go much much lower if
bulls can't respond here. Much much
lower. You can give back the whole day
and more if they cannot respond here.
This 700 means nothing. This is like
nothing. You can go right back to here,
no problem. They can sell it right back
to there's fear in this market. Balls
really need to reclaim all of this.
You're not seeing that. I don't give two
[\h__\h] what Nvidia is doing. Like
everything's selling. Everything is
selling right now. Who [\h__\h] cares?
Everything's selling. Like what's
happening in the tape is being sold.
Every Look at the panic. Oh my god. Look
at the panic in the tape. Who [\h__\h]
cares what Nvidia is doing? I don't I
don't care what Nvidia is doing. I care
what the tape is doing in front of me.
The tape is in a panic. They are in max
pain. They are very very scared right
now. The bulls who tried to get the
squeeze all day joined the highs and
they're getting murdered. Absolutely
murdered right now. That's what's
happening.
That's all you need to be thinking
about. That's what's happening.
Previous week low coming up. New York
open coming up. Previous day close
coming up. Previous day value area low
coming up. New York session low coming
up. Lows coming up. Lows coming up. Mass
panic is in the building again. I can't
believe we've gone 400 points up, 400
points down. But that is what we have
done. And VIX's about to break out over
the New York open.
Not a [\h__\h] bull in sight here trying
to hold this market up. This is uh very
very very nasty.
You're a braver well you're I don't know
if you're brave or stupid trying to buy
this to be quite honest.
Mass panic. I can see it in the tape.
Look. Mass panic in the tape. Dump
everything. They're saying, "I'm so
scared." I'm saying, "I don't want to
hold this. Get me out of this." That's
what they're saying right now.
There's not even an ounce of relief.
Uh, I don't believe so, Dex. I don't I
don't think this is about liquidity
being built. I think it got used
already.
I think this got used already
personally, but
we'll see.
I'm not really interested in this market
till next week. I'm going to be honest.
I think he's got to get through so much
nonsense this week.
No, Raph. I'm not well enough to do
anything today, mate. I'm so sick.
I'm literally like dripping out my hands
right now. Not well enough to do
anything.
Okay, gray box. Other great other shelf
here is 715s. I can draw this out for
you for any of you that are shorts. This
is what bears are defending right now.
Bears are in absolute control. There's
been no relief. Straight up, straight
down. No relief.
[snorts]
Yeah. Back to glow. That's orange line.
But you know, bears are still in control
right now.
Oh, amazing, Daniela. You took the
liquidity break of the highs. Really
good. Nice work. Nice work. Just make
sure you're paying yourself, eh? Because
that's a that's a big old move. If you
were short on this liquidation break
from here, you're like 200 Oh, you're
300 points up. That's a big move. Make
sure you're paying yourself.
Yeah, best best way be like it's just
not worth it. It's not worth it when
you're not feeling great. It's not worth
it. Okay, response here. Let's see how
they act. Gray box previous day point of
control. Kind of thick here now for me.
Bulls really need to get back above
previous day value high to have any hope
in really doing much at all.
That 770 guy is still there.
Previous day point of control here.
And they're still selling versus it at
the moment. Oh my god, the size. The
size.
The size is what gets me.
>> [snorts]
>> Wow.
[snorts]
The previous day PC. This is a gray box.
Bears are still defending it. The side.
Look at the size. These are market
orders [\h__\h] slamming the door in
their faces.
This is crazy.
What an insane market.
>> [snorts]
>> 760 is basically the level. Balls have
got to get way above 760s to have any
sort of hope of control right now. I
would say any hope in and I'm talking
about like lower time frame control, not
higher time frame control. Any hope of
like any relief at all. You're just not
seeing that right now. Every pop you're
see you're not even seeing passive
selling. You're seeing aggressive
selling into at the moment.
There you go. Aggressive selling again.
Just slam that door. That's all you're
seeing on the tape. Look at this.
Wow.
Wow. Wow. Wow. 760s for me is the level.
They've got to reclaim 760s to have a go
at anything. But someone is stuck in
this dumping inventory. I'm telling you,
that's what you've seen so far. Every
pop, aggressive selling, dumping
inventory.
I mean, think about this. There's like
300 points down and they're struggling
to move what like 50 60 points up. Buy
coming on a tape here at 12. Let's see
if he's legit. He's trying to support a
bid now for a bit of a squeeze back up
through point control. Let's see if he's
legit. No, he's pulled. All right, more
games on the tape. More games on the
tape.
I'm actually happy I'm not trading today
because I think this is uh I mean, if
you took that short, it was really good.
But I think anything down here is is
just crazy the way they're moving it
around.
This size. Look at this size. God,
someone's really stuck.
Someone is really stuck.
Just going to get murdered again.
[laughter]
Oh my god, someone's so stuck.
Oh my days.
You should be runners only. If you are
short from that shelf now, you got to be
runners only because you're building out
more liquidity here. You shouldn't have
any like notable size here. You've made
300 points. You should be runners only.
So much aggressive selling. This is wild
what I'm witnessing on the tape. There's
a major battle here around the 700
and I'm not convinced. I'm still not
convinced the low is in. When I look at
that candle that printed your like wick
low, it's buying at the bottom side of
it. That is not what I'd want to see.
All the selling happened before it. Yes.
Like you could argue if they hold a bid
above 80s, but what you'd want to see is
is selling at the lows. And you haven't
seen selling at the lows. So I'm not
convinced the auction is over.
I'm not convinced this auction's over.
Here you go. They're still trying to
sell lower at the moment. This is just
dripping down. Lower high, lower low,
lower high, lower low, lower high. Can
they get a lower low? Break all the way
down into this.
Look at this mag. Apple trying to
stabilize around VWAP. Amazon looks
good. Meta looks awful. Microsoft trying
to find a bid.
Sorry. Meta looks okay. Microsoft trying
to find a bid. Nvidia back down to its
New York open. Doesn't look great. It
doesn't look great.
We can't get back above a 30 minute PC
at the moment.
That's not a good look. This is not a
good look at this market at the moment.
25 key and then 60 60 key. Also got to
get above 25 and above 60s to have a
hope of doing anything at all to be
quite honest.
Every pop still being sold into
When has the last seller sold or have
they just not?
Still being sold into
so much light all week. Just sell sell
sell sell sell sell sell sell sell sell
sell sell sell sell sell all their
inventory [snorts] someone's stuck
someone's dumping inventory it is simple
as that momentum's downside
buyers have any control in this market
they can't get above 720 they can't get
above 760 I don't even think there
sellers stuck at the lows right now this
is uh
just a straight puke a race for the low
at the moment.
Here's your shelf through here. Well,
next stop's all the way down here. And
really, if we start getting under that,
oh my [\h__\h] lord.
Like, I think you can see previous day
value area low today if they sell
through this. I I don't think you can
rule out the move to 550. I don't think
you can rule out a move to 440. I don't
think you can rule out a move down to 3
380s. I don't think you can rule out
anything yet based on what we're seeing.
I don't think you can rule out anything
yet.
More lows. They're selling more at the
lows here. There's And they're still
trying to bid off the bottom. I mean,
these buyers need to just stop. They're
going to keep getting hurt. They just
need to stop. Just let them sell it like
you're crazy. All right, there today.
Now we have excess first time, but
they're not getting a response yet.
Still massive selling at the lows. No
response yet. This is coming for New
York open at the moment.
Yeah, it's because it's not
it's not short selling. You got to see
the difference in the tape. It's dumping
inventory. Yeah. So, it's not like, oh,
we're going to make money selling short.
No, this is them being like, [\h__\h] get
rid of everything. Like, get rid of
everything. That's the panic. Very
different to short selling. It's a panic
cell. It's buyers stuck in the tape on
every time frame, panic selling
everything. We do have excess for the
first time today. On that last move, we
have excess. You do not have any reclaim
of any notable level, but you do have
excess. It's way too early to say that
that's a low in, but there is excess on
that last move down for the first time,
I'd say, in this kind of roll over,
let's call it. It's the first time we've
seen sellers at the lows, but I mean,
right now, you're still defending every
level. Buyers have still got to get way
above.
I'd say you still got to get above 725,
730 for the buyers to have any form of
control in this. any form of control at
all.
Yeah, there's no there's literally no
reason to be buying down here, right?
Right. The momentum is so heavy. There's
no reason to be buying down here. You
would need to see a reclaim of all key
levels. We're now we're inside a
previous day's value. Think about this.
We haven't held previous day high. We
haven't held previous day value area
high. We're back inside yesterday's
range. They want to come down for this.
They will. There's wh where why why buy?
Why buy? Like there's no reason to be
buying. Look, lower high, lower low,
lower high, lower low, lower high, lower
low. We haven't even had a change of
character. Flow zones are in a cell.
We're under VWAP. There's literally
you're under everything. You're under
everything. So if we're under
everything, take yourself and your ego
out of it.
Who else is under everything? Who else
is stuck? Everyone. Correct. Everyone's
stuck. So, don't [\h__\h] buy it. All
right. Don't be a bottom picker.
Can I explain what I mean by excess? I
mean, they tried to sell the low down
here. Sellers
market sold this. It's the first time
they didn't do that here. They market
sold it here. It's the first time we've
had market selling at the lows. So, if
we don't move lower than that, then
we've got notable sellers stuck at the
lows. But right now, you're still not
seeing a response. All I'm saying is
it's the first time Delta was maybe
offside at the low of day. Not low of
day, low of this move. We're not at low
of day yet. Low of day is probably the
target.
Yes, I see it in the footprint and in uh
input map.
So they got stuck under 660. So if we
trade through under 660, they're
comfortable again. We're right there
now. So, we're probably going to trade
new lows now at this point.
Vick's new high day here. This is so so
heavy.
So heavy.
Previous week low is right below us as
is uh New York open. Everything's there
for the taking right now.
Everything is there for the taking at
the moment. And if you get through that,
we're just going to sell through all the
overnight range, folks. Like, you've got
to understand, those of you looking for
longs, like, you've got to understand
what you're looking at here. Like I
said, where is the structure to buy off?
There wasn't any. So, what's going to
happen? We're going to [\h__\h] repric
it, right? They trapped them up there.
We talked about this. If you leave this
TP1, TP2, who knows? They come under
here. What are you looking at? You're
looking at light volume created
overnight. We can come for this. They
want to come for that. They're going to
come for it.
It's a short squeeze. It's a counter
trend short squeeze. That's all it is.
If you've been tempted to buy it, I
don't know why. I don't know what is in
your head saying I should buy this. I
can't see anything in this.
Guys, today is not the day for me to
answer the same questions I answer on
stream every day. I haven't got the
energy for it, guys.
Trumpet 12 there. Well, can he save the
market? I would doubt it at the moment.
What's he going to say? What's the
meeting about? Uh, Raph,
do you know what the meeting's about?
Has he has he announced what it's about?
Who's it with? Probably Saudi Arabia or
something. Is it? Is it about the chips?
Yes, Saudi Arabia. I mean, what's he
going to say? Oh, they're giving us a
trillion dollars. Yeah, of course they
are, mate. [snorts]
They're [\h__\h] not. They're not going
to do [\h__\h]
Every pot still being sold into. Buyers
are trying to take control here. Every
pot you do have at that low 68 lot sell.
But
my mind is a bit blown here to think
about
what they could do with this.
Every pop still been sold into
go. They're just selling every chance
they get, folks. Every chance they get
to get out of their horrible stuck
position, which they must be in for some
reason, they are getting rid of it.
What's that balance there? 705
725.
You got to get way up. You got to get
back above previous day point because
really they got to get about back above
here
at the moment. Every little drive is
being sold into.
Starting to see someone trying to
support the bid here
at 95 and 90s. There's someone trying to
support the bid up.
But like I'm just going to remain saying
there is someone stuck in this tape
because every chance they get to sell
their inventory, they're taking it. It's
not a short seller. It is it's someone
who probably overleveraged long this
morning and is caught.
Seven pops again.
Seven pops again. Look at the tape. Look
at the tape. It's telling you they can't
support a thing getting run over right
now. [snorts]
uh shorts
shorts or people trying to guess the
bottoms and and shorts lifting and
letting them come up. Shorts getting
stuck and then lifting and let letting
come up. Remember, if if you're stuck,
you're not trying to sell the low, are
you? Right? If you've bought high today,
you're trying to let it come up to you
and then get rid of inventory, right?
You want to like minimize your damages.
Right? When you see liquidation breaks
of the low and we dump two, three, four,
500 points and start going limit down,
that's when you know that they've given
up all help and it's margin call time
and it's bank shutting down time. But
right now, it's like dump the inventory.
Remember, if they were stuck yesterday,
right, if they bought, if they were
stuck anytime yesterday, today we traded
back up to previous day high. That gave
them the opportunity to get out. So,
anyone who was stuck yesterday was given
the opportunity to get out in the money
or at least break even.
Strong buying coming in here. First time
I've seen very strong buying coming in
volumewise. Now, can they get through
and then back through PC and then really
take control of anything lower time
frame? At the moment, it's still a
seller up there at 700. He's just
[\h__\h] dumped it on them again.
So, we can't even get through this uh
this gray box here. Not even getting
relief through that yet. It's still
[snorts] just in a very strong
downtrend.
We're not seeing higher highs or higher
lows yet. You're just you're in this.
That's all you're in at the moment.
There is strong buying trying to come in
here. Maybe some guys got stuck at the
lows for the first time. You're not
through the 700s yet. They've dumped.
Every time you got in 700, they've
dumped.
So 720s, I'd say. And then 7. What's
this level up here? 722.
There we go. They're going to have to
take control of that gray box above. And
they dumped again. They dumped in 700
again.
I'm going to use a bathroom here. How
long we got? 10 minutes. Can't believe
I've actually made it.
Oh yeah, it's dumped it more. Yeah,
they're still not done. You're going to
get low of day here, folks.
There's no relief to sell into it for
low of day, but that's what they're
they're going to go for low of day.
That's your max pain move, isn't it?
It's your New York session low. So
that's what they're going for.
There you go. Just sell sell.
So all I'm seeing on the tape. Sell
sell.
Keep selling. Just keep selling. Sell
sell. That's all that's happening.
There's your downtrend
again. Did they reclaim 700? No. They
got sold into 700. Did they reclaim 720?
No. Didn't get anywhere near it. No
reason to sell.
[snorts]
Still no excess. They just put in a new
low and there's no excess down there.
That was buyers down there. That's not
what you want to see. That's not the end
of an auction.
Yeah, Peter. Yep. Yep. I don't disagree
with you, mate. It's possible. Uh I'd
say the first stop though, you that New
York low 575 and then previous day value
area low. Uh and then you're just back
into that range.
What it what's what's bizarre to me is
that they let it squeeze out so high,
but
it is what it is.
It's just such a directional take. Like
I don't know if you guys have actually
like looked at a five minute today, but
like that is not your normal five
minute. Let's go straight up. Let's do
one inside bar and let's go pretty much
straight down. Okay, we had one little
stop start inside bar straight up. One
inside bar straight down. One inside
bar. Probably gonna take this out now.
You think that's normal? That's 400
points. That ain't [\h__\h] normal, mate.
That that that ain't a normal market.
That is a really panicked market.
Uh I've got some gaps on bookmarks
starting to show up. So, I know what's
going on here with the liquidity. What
is that here? Why have I got a gap there
for a minute? It's not good. Bit worried
about data now. Not even going to be
able to read data to you if that starts
going funny. [snorts]
I mean, yeah, the move down's been on
more volume for sure, Jack. You're not
You're not wrong there, my friend.
You're not wrong.
I still don't think this is finished. I
don't think the low's in.
I think it could do with some relief for
them to sell back into, but I don't
think the low's in. I just don't.
There's nothing in this to suggest the
low's in yet.
And what would that H1 low be? It would
be Just Mark
your IB low. Oh, it's there for IB.
Anyway, you don't need this.
>> [cough]
>> So just keep holding your runners.
Anyone short like downella from the
highs
as long as you pay, you should have paid
yourself 70 80% hold your runners that
lower day. If you get it, magnificent.
Check the ES.
ES did actually catch a bid on that New
York open.
Still trading around it.
spiders.
Spiders
there's a bit more to go. Bit divergence
there between the ETFs.
Bit more to go.
Do they get any relief here at all for
them to sell back into?
And they're literally sell selling the
tiniest pops when you think about like
20 20 point pop they're selling rather
than letting it drift 200 points or
something and selling into like a decent
void or pivot.
Lots of stops down there now. I'll tell
you that much.
Lots of people with their stops down
there now.
So, back to these 700. Remember, they've
been selling at these 700s nonstop.
If they get can get through these, then
you're looking for point of control. And
that's where the battle really starts of
what happens next. Back to these 700s.
Oh, guess what? Oh, there's a seller up
there still.
Oh my god, he just slammed that [\h__\h]
door.
[laughter]
How's he got so much size left?
Oh my god.
Whoa. My god.
Uh, I'm really sorry, Mo. I'm not going
to I can't right now look at anything
else. My brain is killing. I'll have a
look later. But like I like I've said in
Discord,
your sales on Bitcoin are 80% sales off
the highs. So if it wants to go back to
50 35K, it will. I wouldn't be [\h__\h]
touching that that [\h__\h] right now. Like
it's a Bitcoin is a risk-on asset. We're
in a riskoff market. I don't know why
anyone would attempt to do anything with
it right now. It's finished its thousand
day cycle. Like I've said numerous
times, right? Bitcoin traditionally has
a thousand day cycle.
They're not done with this.
Night. Night. They're not done with
this.
[snorts]
I've lost connection.
No way.
Lost all connection. Ninja. Anyone else
had that? I've lost everything.
Thought something was weird when Butmat
went down. There's obviously some data
issue out there at the moment.
Okay, PC move down here now. We've been
down here so long.
Let's zoom out.
This is a huge distribution here. Now,
this is your rotation level now for the
day in here. Bulls need it above to
offer anything. Bears just want to keep
washing at low and they'll try and
defend a high into 7 770 or whatever it
is. That's your levels.
That's your levels for the rest of the
day.
Lunchtime coming up. I don't think
they're done with it. I really like when
I say that I mean I don't think they're
done selling it.
still can't get through the 700s. Huge
level that 700s.
Every time we popped up there has been a
massive seller. If he's gone, then you
might get some relief to 20s, but every
time we've popped up into it, there's
been a huge seller right here. He's
gone. He might get up into 20s, but uh
let's see. There's the 700s. Is he gone?
Is he done dumping it? Does he allow
relief up to 20s?
What's this previous day point control?
Basically close to the 30s actually,
isn't it?
So, do they hold 700s on a retest
or do they just uh dump it straight back
down now?
Psychological level here.
Some selling coming in here just above
the 700s. They can't hold it yet. Buyers
need to get up to 720s for any relief.
This gray box above you or 730 is
previous day point control.
Big battle going on here.
Seriously, can they not get to 20s?
Yeah, no worries.
Hopefully some of you made money.
I don't think I would have caught the
long no matter what today. Even if I was
well enough. Maybe I would have caught
the short. I don't think I'd be in it
now. I think I would have already got
out of it. Man, they just dumped sevens
again.
Oh my god, dude. You bulls are [\h__\h]
terrible.
You got to reclaim 700s again
to go 720 730s for relief. There's
sevens.
They're really struggling up here.
Really struggling up here to get any
follow through.
There's bid support coming on.
I just haven't I wouldn't trust that bit
support, but it's there passively trying
to step on the book. Okay, they've got a
chance now to go up to previous day
point of control.
They've got a chance here to get to
previous day point of control. And if
they get through that, then uh maybe
sort of 780 800. So bulls have got a
chance here for a squeeze for some
relief. You've got a new Audi bar coming
being very careful.
I don't think sellers are done with this
yet. I'm just going to make that very
clear. I don't think sellers are done
with this yet. I think this is a squeeze
relief which is probably sold into
I'd say [sighs and gasps] above above
can trigger a bigger squeeze, but I
would say bull traps will probably live
in here.
So, I can imagine that happening today
above here, but you'd have to watch the
tape.
You would have to watch the tape for
that move. I can I can imagine that kind
of thing playing out. [snorts]
Oh [groaning]
my gosh, I can't believe I made it to
lunch with you. I'm literally like a
puddle of water underneath this jacket.
[snorts]
And they're selling that 720s.
Like I said, I don't think they're done
with it. It's a It's just a question of
when they come back into sell. Previous
day point of control right now is when
they're coming in. That red line. Is
that current point of control? What is
this? No, it's previous day only.
Where's current? Oh, is it both? They
flipped it to both. All they have
That's an ugly look.
Big level here.
Lunchtime coming folks as well. You're
Well, you're at lunch now.
Thanks, Jeff.
Hopefully, it's helped some of you.
Yeah, I can't believe I made it to noon.
I actually can't believe it.
I must look awful. I better look very
washed out. I feel dreadful.
Absolutely dreadful.
Absolutely dreadful. All right, team.
I'm out of here. Um, I'll do my best to
be here tomorrow, but I'm not going to
make guarantees because I can feel
myself going downhill. I can't see
myself recovering. So, if I'm not on,
just trade safe tomorrow. Um, whatever
we do with Nvidia, it could quite
happily do happily quite easily do the
opposite with it tomorrow. So, just be
aware of that. It's very, very trappy
this market at the moment. Um, just be
aware of that. All right. Like I said, I
don't think they're done with this
selling it. But, it's a question of what
levels do they want to sell from. Peace
and love everyone. Be safe. All that
usual good stuff. Look after each other.
Especially if I'm not here tomorrow. I'm
not going to be in Discord, guys. I'm
going to go straight back to bed after
this. All right. Sorry. Really sorry.
I've got to rest. Take care.