All right, good morning team. Morning
everyone. Trying to catch up here. Some
of you in chat would have already seen
there's some issues going on uh with a
lot of websites to this morning.
All right, Cloudflare issue. So, some of
you will have troubles log logging into
some of the uh prop firms and maybe some
other spaces as well or did not mean to
do that. Let's uh where have we gone?
There we go. All right. So, just be
careful this morning. Um I don't think
there's a problem with trade of eight,
but uh just warning you now is never a
nice thing to wake up to all these
issues.
Okay, let's start on the daily.
[cough and clears throat] And you can
see on the daily possible breakout,
possible breakout here. So this set
yesterday's range. This was set in
GlobeEx. This was set at the lows. We're
into this huge sort of cluster that I
talked about in the weekly newsletter.
All right, you have to be aware of this
cluster. Remember this is your yearly
profile. We get thick in here and then
we thin right right out. They are trying
desperately to hold on to this cluster.
Guess what that cluster is? 700s. All
right, who remembers the rotation 7 to
25K, right? It's very possible that we
do that same kind of rotation. We
basically have done that overnight. If
you think about we dip below, washed out
previous week's low. All right, so we
took these stops, turned back inside,
came back up to 25,000, turned back
down, came back down to 700. That's what
we've seen. So that's what we're seeing.
The same thing that we saw here for days
and days and weeks and weeks and ends.
So we have to be aware of that rotation.
It likes rotating there. We are also
near the low Ballinger band. And this is
currently pointing upwards. In a few
days or so, you're going to start to see
this. So, location not ideal for a short
down here because we know the market
does not on a regular basis like trading
outside the extremes of these two
standard deviations. However, we do have
black swan events. They do happen. Okay.
So if for some reason we start losing
these 700s and this market goes into a
bit of a panic and cannot find a bid.
All right, if that happens then we can
think about expansion down here. But our
location for a new money short there
unfortunately is not good. Like if you
were short swing short any of these or
you're long S triple Q's and you're
having a lot of fun right now. But for
day trading it's a little bit harder to
think about getting short down here. So
we need to be careful of the location.
Right, we have to be careful.
Okay, let's move into this
into the hourlys. Make this a little bit
bigger so you can see it. There we go.
Okay, so hourly you can see
yesterday like we talked about once we
started letting go. Those in Discord
will know took the continuations, right?
Once yesterday built out all this
liquidity. Look how long it took to
build build it out. Lots and lots of
time to build it out. But once lunchtime
fa let go and they failed to complete
that rotation, it was a short all day
long. Okay. And we've continued that
overnight so far. So, so far what we're
seeing here is lower lows and lower
highs. Now, it's very possible, all
right, that we've got one of these going
on and this can build liquidity to break
down. All right, it absolutely can do
that because on the higher time frame,
this is exactly we just zoom out what
we're doing. It's fractal. Right? Think
about this push head and shoulder
breakdown. This this push head and
shoulder break down this. Right? This is
this pattern inside of it. So it's very
very possible. All right. It's very very
very possible because you're starting to
see weakness in the markets. But again
our location is not ideal here and we
have swept previous week lows which is a
big low to take out. But we need to be
aware of that if this market is going to
find a rally this morning. But remember
in bare markets you get short squeezes
and they can be violent. You would have
seen on Friday and the week before. So
if they're going to start breaking out
of this, right, bulls will attempt to
reclaim previous day value area high
that and previous day low for me are
going to be huge levels today. How we
act into previous day value area low and
previous day low. Right, we're currently
trading at sort of previous day low. If
we reclaim that and they want to get a
little short squeeze on, then how we act
here is going to be important. Can we
reject this kind of area for that trade
back downside? Now, if we have a look at
the volume uh profile built in yesterday
after
we're just going to have to do it from
9:00,
we're on an hourly chart. All right,
we've got a bit of a bit of a a move
here. 950s up to up to 25,5.
So, that kind of level
we're going to have to be careful of.
[snorts] All right. So watching to see
if they do that this morning. So
potentially there's a squeeze out to
there. I'm going to focus on the shorts,
right? I want to see if we come into
here. Do we fail for that rotation?
If we reclaim, all right, this is going
to be like yesterday. If shorts get a
squeeze up here and they build and
reclaim previous day value low, then
that rotation back upside is very, very
possible all the way back to previous
day value area high, previous day point
of control. Can't rule that out on a
squeeze back up. Okay. So, that would be
your rotation. If you're someone that's
looking to play rotation, that will be
it. If they do that, what else can we
think about? Well, break out of the loan
and fail breakout of the low. I don't I
don't really want to be looking for a
new short down here. It might well play
out, but the danger is you've got that
lower Ballinger band here, and you can
have a look below, fail, reclaim, and
upside we go. So, if you're looking for
a long trigger, you'd want to see a look
below and a fail and a reclaim. Ideally,
a previous day low and ideally up here.
Really, that's where it's a safer bet.
So,
location is really less than ideal. If
we zoom in here, this is our overnight
kind of rotation. You can see we built
out lots of volume here. All right. Lots
and lots of volume built out here. We
have to uh note this. hanging out here a
long time.
All right, that is a bit of a shelf. All
right, so I'd be watching this kind of
level at the open, under, over. Do we
get over it and base above it for a
squeeze up? Do we fail under it? Retest
it, stay heavy for a wash of those lows.
Overall, we are bearish. There is
absolutely no doubt about it. Like I
said, I think the edge has been with
bears. The newsletter quite clearly
states the edge is with bears. These are
lower lows and lower highs. But we can
get rallies which are resold into. So,
if we get too many shorts at the low and
they don't break down, that's when they
get stuck. And that's what you have to
be aware of in these markets, especially
when we're opening up near lows, just to
make it extra hard for us when they do
that. Right, moving up the time frames.
Okay, you can see we're trading right
now at overnight PC and at uh previous
day lows. These are the interesting
levels for now. Let's move up to a five
minute. Let's look at the ETFs,
right? ES very much the same thing. This
is your level above that we've been
rejecting. Um but the more important
thing for me right now is the ETFs.
Okay, SPY. You can see I've got an alert
here. All right, 660 is a big put wall.
All right, it was 6 it was 672,
right? 672 670. They've now had to put a
new wall down here because we've drifted
so far down. This is a big level down
into this. All right, this is a huge
options level. Be aware of it. Okay, be
aware of it because we're into OPEX as
well this week. So, be aware of that. If
we start letting go of that, then maybe
there is a deeper move possible. Clean
out some of these stops. 57s and 52s or
53s I'll be looking for if we go mega
mega heavy today. Uh Q's also has a wall
at 660.
All right. And you can see it's finding
a bid in front of it or around it for
now or at least it's trying to. This is
where we sort of washed under came
failed breakdown reclaimed last Friday
and absolutely ripped. This is the level
660 a put wall. Just be aware of that
folks. That's all I'm saying. Just be
aware of it. Look at the dicty because I
haven't looked in a little bit. Yeah,
starting to look bullish for that move
back up upside to 100s for me.
VIX very dangerous. All right, very very
very dangerous. We talked about this.
Your volatility is high. Okay, this is
not what you want to see. Everyone's
saying that the uh bottom's in blah blah
blah blah blah. I've seen so many retail
traders talking about this. Shut the cup
if you don't know what you're talking
about. This is a very dangerous move.
Okay, this is sustained bullish control
there. Um there's the breakout, there's
the pullback, there's the hold. This is
frighteningly dangerous right now,
folks. We have elevated levels on the
VIX for a sustained period of time and
we're putting in higher highs and higher
lows and we've got a clear level up here
that's going to break out or look for if
it can sustain this bid through this
supply zone. So I am very very cautious
right now. The volatility is high. Do
not be surprised to see 100 point candle
moves. And I'm not joking. I'm very very
serious. Right. So if we break through
here, next job is a spike like this up
into here. You know when this happened,
this is your April low. All right. So,
think about what we did before April.
Big spike up into this level, pull back,
hold, big spike up into this level, pull
back, hold. If we start breaking out of
there, this is what happened in April in
the tariff news. So, just be aware of
that. I'm not saying be uber bearish,
but it's not a swing long time right
now. Everyone calling for dips on this
swing long. You're you're not seeing
levels hold on the spiders which are of
notable interest yet. You're seeing them
start to fail. All right, we're letting
go of 50-day etc etc. All right, Apple
news here yesterday. Tim Cook might be
leaving internal um meetings on that.
More news this morning of another board
member who designed the new iPhone might
be leaving as well or the iPhone air. Um
so it's still holding up really really
well. It's very very impressive that
Apple is looking pretty good but uh you
know pulling back off the top side.
Here's your bottom side of the range
under 65s. You see a bit more weakness
but so far relative strength in this
market where it's weak is the chip
names. Okay, Amazon gapping down again
underneath previous day low. That is
heavy. There's no doubt about it. That
is absolutely heavy. Are we coming into
a level of interest anywhere?
Yes. Okay. Okay, into its next level
here. So, I'd say
25's down to teens is what you're
looking for. Can it find a bid down
there? But this is uh been heavy and
gapping down. Goo
gapping up again. All right, so we
gapped up, sold off yesterday, closed
the gap, trying to gap up again.
Remember, this is all on Burkshire and
Haway buying it. That's just retail
flying in trying to copy uh Warren Meta.
Well, like I said, I didn't think that
was done bleeding and it's not. Um, that
is a nasty gap down and we're seeing
mega weakness in that name.
Where are we trading into? Look, we're
not too far from these April levels,
folks. This is how weak Meta is. Look at
this. Massive weakness now. It's uh
coming into areas of interest. But, uh,
you wouldn't want to be long yet. Hasn't
found a bid. Microsoft massive gap down
as well. Look at that huge gap down and
selling. This is this market is
aggressively selling right here, right
now already. Uh Nvidia getting
absolutely slammed now as well. So I'd
be watching previous day low here on
Nvidia. This uh is it previous day low
or is it Friday? I'll be watching
Friday's low. If Friday's low starts
breaking, you're going to see um this
market really start to let go. So we can
even set a price alert in here.
set price and ready for it. And Tesla
that looks uh well slight gap down it
looks better than the rest. So market
opening up very very weak. Um
it's always tricky when we see this.
Let's just check a couple other names.
Oracle very much like Nvidia. AMD
following suit like Nvidia back into the
lows. So this is always tricky when
we're gapping down this much. When we've
got this much fear in the market, these
are the areas where unfortunately shorts
can often come flying in a bit late. We
don't have prime position and so we have
to be a little bit careful
about how we operate in the open. Not a
bad day to just let it um figure out
what it is it wants to do
and go from there. I'm not going to get
a chance to do the good mornings today,
folks. I'm sorry. But uh good morning
everyone. Thank you for joining.
Hopefully you had a good afternoon
yesterday. Okay, it was a really nice
breakdown yesterday
and let's just see what we get here this
morning. Um, be careful as well. Like I
said, some of these sites are already
down. Um, Apex does have a new 80% sale
on with $40 resets, but I think
currently they're struggling with this
CloudFare like everyone else. I also
have my Black Friday sale on code BF
will get you 25% every off everything on
my site right now. I haven't announced
it um or done anything on socials, but
some of you taking advantage of that
already. First come, first served on
that. So, good morning everyone.
Welcome. Let's see what we get. Smash
that like button nice and early, please.
Let's get those likes up and let's see
how we go here, folks. Let's just see
how we go here. 10 seconds to the open.
Most of the market is gapping down here
into the open. Let's just see.
Yeah, all of the market other than Apple
and Google on a gap down at the open.
So, let's just see here, folks. Let's
see what we can um gather
informationationalwise from here this
morning. So, coming straight into this
sort of dense area, this gray box that
we've uh
been trading in all night, right, this
is the thickest area that we've been
trading in all night.
Let this develop for a second.
Okay. So, up to the lower time frame al
goes
through our PDL. Is that right? I just
want to make sure that's correct.
Yes.
Reclaimed PDL
gap fill and previous day value area low
all the way up here. Long, long way
away.
Long, long way away. It's crazy, isn't
it? Getting stuck here in this thick
volume already. It's pretty scary. And
that just got rejected pretty hard on
that thick volume to start this session.
That's some big big selling coming in
there to start the day. So, just be
careful here, folks. This is a a very,
very aggressive whipsy market right now.
Be very, very careful. expanding lower
here to start the day by the looks of it
into this blue box.
Nice and easy, please folks. Nice and
easy here to start the day.
So, rejecting
this big cluster from overnight. This
gray box, remember, was our under over.
So, if we keep rejecting that, you might
see weakness in the market. The worst
thing is the location right now. It's
very, very heavy market. So, that pushup
got sold into at the start. We've let go
of volume and we have a GlobeEx low down
here. It's 600s that it might want to go
to. We have lost location.
Unfortunately, the traders with the best
location of those traders who played
overnight. Just be aware of that. I'll
give you a readout on the market as
well. Tesla 0.72% down. Nvidia 1.85%
down. Microsoft 0.90%
down. Meta 1.61% down. Google 0.18%
down. Amazon 1.70% down. Apple relative
strength again. It's incredible. Like
I'm absolutely buzzing that I'm holding
that. So finding a bid off that blue
zone right now. Let me just check the
cues. Trading right at that 600. Okay.
So they're trying to get a bid on that
600. That is the put wall that we talked
about. They came right into it at 600.
They're trying to find a bid. Wow. Wow.
Wow. All right. So there's Mr. Put
saying you're not going lower. This is
why we don't short the lows because
we've lost location. Straight up we go.
That put wall huge. All right. And like
I said, don't be surprised to see 100
plus point candles with this volatility.
And there you go. There's your 100 plus
point M1 candle that happened in a
matter of seconds. Okay, I know that
this is likely to happen because of the
VIX. This is why it's very, very
dangerous to be trading like this at the
moment. Let's just see. Let it settle
down.
So this put wall, this blue box is
basically your put wall on QQQ and we
just bid right off it. They are not
willing to let price come below that.
Remember, it's OPEX this week as well.
That is a big reaction off that put
wall. And it's also reclaiming previous
day low and it's also not allowing it.
I'm just going to double check this to
drift under. What was that low there?
75. What was our low on here? That's the
lower Ballinger band. All right. Put
also at that lower Ballinger band. Same
Peter just just sat sat waiting because
I know we've lost location. I know
higher time frame wants to move lower,
but I also know like we talked about in
the morning briefing, shorts often get
caught at the lows in these markets.
Which is why I don't know how long some
of you have been traded, but if any of
you have traded bare markets before, you
will know bare market rallies are some
of the most violent moves that you can
get. As per that, we just literally
talked about it 10 minutes ago. This is
what happens in bare market rallies.
Shorts get stuck at the lows into a put
wall and they don't go anywhere and then
you get this explosive move out of it.
Google finding a bid here as well.
For me, this is just a let it let it
settle down, let it calm down, decide
what it is it wants to do because right
now this morning, we've already got 167
point range in the first four minutes
and that was actually made in the first
three minutes. So, just be aware.
Where is my anchor? There you are. All
right. Back down to New York view up
right now.
Just let it settle down, folks. Let it
settle down. It's going to be violent.
Honestly, these moves are going to be
violent the next few days. We got to we
got to get through Nvidia earnings and
see how we react in my mind. After
Wednesday evening, it gets a bit
probably a bit easier or Thursday.
probably still very very volatile, but
the read on the market will be a bit
easier because if they're done propping
it up, holding for Nvidia and they sell
it, we move lower. If they're going to
prop it up, push on Nvidia and then sell
it, it will also be of interest. All
right, back down to this New York open
then range pretty big right now.
Then don't enter red plasma. If you're
having a hard time entering, hands off
the mouse and just let it do whatever it
is it's got to do. So, back to this sort
of condensed box.
Pushes this morning failed. Google's
selling back down now. So, it just had a
wild popup. Selling back to this New
York open now. And we have to see what
happens around here. Again, I'm just Q's
are under the 600. That is a worry. That
would be a worry for me. Q's have moved
under that 600 level or they're over
under over under over under. So, there's
a battle here
on the Q's. SPY is not at 660 yet. Big
big battle in the options market I would
say at the moment.
Big big battle.
Just let it develop.
Just look at your uh London and Asia.
We've not really moved. I mean, yes,
Asia sold off. London retested, came
back down to the low. What I mean is
where we're opening up, we've not taken
out London or Asia. We're just sat in
the middle of that range right now. Sat
in the middle of their range.
Vick's finding a bid of previous day
high there as well, I think. Is that
previous day high? Yes, it is.
Just happy to let this develop for a
bit.
Just make sure you're staying zoomed
out. Right, I'll show you what I'm
looking at.
Right. Here's Asia.
Here's the double bottom. Here's the
London print. Here's where we are.
Here's the thickest area. This is the
battle zone. Battle zone. Battle zone.
Let them dictate because if they can
hold bids over here, maybe they want to
come and revisit this. If they fail
this, maybe they want to come down here.
This is what I'm seeing right now. But
the location is not ideal to look for
that kind of move lower. So, I'm just
going to let it develop. If they want to
squeeze out, they can squeeze out. Let
them squeeze out. It's a bit like
yesterday. Those of you trading in the
afternoon, if you're patient enough to
let the squeeze out happen,
this little one here, once they got
exhausted, it offered a nice trade back
down. So, we can wait for something like
that so we can have a better location.
Let me just see. Not every day, perfect
trade day. You might see like huge
candles and think, I could have made
loads of money, but you got to ask
yourself, what's your entry? So far,
we're protecting this blue box and we're
reclaiming gray box. And if they can put
a squeeze on, they're going to come from
gap fill and previous day value area
low. Big ifs right now. Remember, if
you're going to play that, you're
playing counter trend to the higher time
frame, which is why I'm not going to
play it.
Did any of you catch those shorts
yesterday for the continuation? I know
guys in the in my Discord did, but any
of you not in the Discord, did you did
you get any of it?
Where's that yield
falling off a bit actually today?
Interesting.
Jack, you got it. Nice.
Okay, back down to VWAP. Back down to
this gray box.
Back down to this New York open
sensitive areas. Nothing's changed here,
folks. Same levels, nothing's changed.
Big back and forth here. Big big back
and forth.
Nice Jack. Good work. [snorts]
You're having a hard time g uh doing
what's very hard time gauging momentum
during GlobeEx. What do I recommend?
Higher time frame. zoom out and then
look at where the liquidity is. If there
is if there is no momentum, if it's in a
range, then that's probably why while
you're struggling. Last night, I would
say we're in downside pressure. The move
was to clean out previous week lows,
right? Because we left those on the ENQ
uh in yesterday's session and SPY took
them. That was the obvious draw in
liquidity. So, that's why we traded down
to that.
And if you watched, I talked about it
yesterday. the treasuries and bond
market in Japan is causing pressure on
US equities. It happened again last
night. That's what caused once that got
released that caused that that uh
cascade, let's call it back down to this
New York open. I'd be watching this New
York open. So far, they're holding this
gray box. If they start letting go,
we're going to go all the way back down
to these lows. It's not very pretty, but
that's uh what's we're looking at. If
shorts get stuck here, trying to force
that, we're going to go right back to
the highs. It's just midpoint of the
range. And the range is big. 167 points.
so far in this opening print this
morning. Vick's trying to catch a bid at
New York open as well.
Apple now the only one red. Only one
red, only one green. Everything else
started to sell. So Google had that
morning pop and got sold off.
Dangerous. This is a very dangerous
looking market to me. I think both sides
probably trapped here at the moment.
Dangerous looking market. Just let it
develop.
Yeah, that's just overnight. It's the
thickest level from overnight, that gray
box, Julian. So, it's where it's traded
under over basically point of control
from overnight. That's where we've
chopped around, which is also why you've
got both flow zones there. You've got
lower time frame algo there, you've got
previous day low there, and you've got
both VWAPs there, and you've got New
York open there. Okay, this is telling
you, look at everything sideways.
There's your New York open. There's
previous day low. There's flow zones.
There's New York VWOP. There's lower
time frame algo. There's 24hour VWAP.
It's telling you, isn't it? We're
condensed in here. This is dangerous in
here. We need to outside of that range.
Otherwise, we're going to go back and
forth and back and forth and back and
forth. Very, very dangerous.
Okay, they're starting to try and take
over underneath New York open. Now,
if you start rejecting that box, you
might get a move back to the lows.
Remember off these lows we had like a
hund and something point candle. All
right. Off these lows we had a hund and
something point candle because this is
that big put wall that we saw on the
Q's.
We are under that level now on QQQ.
We're not under that level yet on the
spiders. Spiders need to get under 660.
They're currently trading at 662. Q's
need to be under uh 600 which they are.
So I'd be watching this for an
overunder. Now, just be aware that down
in this level is where all those shorts
last time we came down here, this is
where they all got um well, I don't know
what you want to call it. Face ripped.
Face ripped is probably a good word for
it. Back down into these levels.
Probably some covering at these lows.
Do they get a breakdown underneath is
what they will be looking for. But last
time we came down here, they got
nothing, did they?
Here
we go. So, they're going to try because
we're under the put wall. So, they're
going to try for expansion. Here you go.
You're starting to see it now. Oof. Oof.
Oof.
So, GlobeEx down here if they can get it
600s. Be very, if you're taking this
short, be very, very careful because
you're short low of day to try and get
down to 600, which is previous week low
625. So, all I'm saying is be careful.
Bears are in control for sure. We're
underneath the key levels, but spiders
are holding up a little bit better than
tech today. So, we are short on the
right asset. If you're going to take the
short, location is not ideal. You need
to be locking in and then holding
runners. You do not need size in this
market.
You do not need size in this market.
So, finding a bid, expanding IB low.
It's trying to find a bid here in this
big blue box. This is where we found a
bid twice last night. Just be aware of
that. Twice last night. This is where we
found a bid and this morning around this
area. So, we know it's a big area. they
start breaking down under here,
then they can get more follow through.
But just be careful.
You've got that previous week low at 25s
and then overnight low at 600 and under
there, we're probably going 400s. If
they're really going to break down under
there, that would need an expansion
underneath the daily Ballinger band.
Remember, that would be kind of like a
black swan event. It doesn't happen very
often when you see that. This is again
very wiggly in this tape right now.
They're very very worried about getting
squeezed out here. But if they don't, if
they're successful and seeing downside
pressure will get very nasty for bulls
very very quickly.
All pops being sold here at the moment.
Every little move up being sold into is
downside pressure coming. Look how
quickly this is moving. Wow.
Insane. Tape's moving so fast, folks.
Just sitting out of this for now.
That's an insanely quick take. You could
see it down here when we were down here.
Amount of orders flying through.
There you go. So, shorts getting caught
at lows again. Straight back up to this
box. How we acted this box. Key again.
Wild. You're braver than me if you're
trading this at the moment.
RTY relative strength. Yes, it does.
You're right.
There's probably a small cap um doing
some damage here this morning because if
we're seeing rotation out of big names
wouldn't surprise me to see I don't know
some bio running some fluff running some
sector running on that.
Yeah, pizza. It's mate. It's not for me.
I tell you what, this market is not for
me. I don't want to be short down here.
I If I'm going to be short,
I want to see how we act up here. And if
we reclaim that, I'm happy to like play
the long squeeze, but I don't really
want to be looking for new money shorts
down here. But we're rejecting this gray
box again.
These moves are no joke. These are big
old moves. What did we just move from
three? Another 100 point candle. I said
to you at the beginning of today, all
the time VIX is up here. I can imagine
100 point candles in M1 candles and we
are getting it. We are getting it today.
So back down to this low.
There is some excess sell on this low
but again this market is bearish
overall. So you just got to be careful
there. There was excess down here. There
were sellers stuck at these lows down
here. So I'd say underneath 57s
that's all the time we're holding sort
of 60s basically buyers are in control
under that it's night night time for the
buyers I would say
might be night night time for them it is
night night time for them here you go
expansion lower
so previous week low here green box so
we rejected gray back to uh green here
previous week low snap this this is your
next low underneath that it is good
night science
He is big strong selling. Woof
[laughter]
mental man. So quick. So so quick. I'm
still just sat flat right now.
So next box. This is a huge level on on
the yearly profile. All right. This
green box is based off a yearly profile.
Globeex here. This is the next level
that you can take out. 600s
at the m moment. Sellers in control.
Buyers had the chance to try and take
control. They failed.
Let's put a profile on here now. We've
developed a little bit.
Is it going to come? Where is it? There
we go.
>> [snorts]
>> It's normal. 20% of the internet is
down. What did you expect? Um, that's
got that's not what's causing this,
mate. That's not what's causing this.
Did we sell off on AWS going down? No,
it's got nothing. It's got nothing to do
with it. Absolutely nothing to do with
it.
Okay, back up to edge of profile on the
day that we're developing.
Sellers came last came in with size at
680. So 680 is your control level for
sellers. If they defend 680s, they're
going to look for lower. bull start
reclaiming 680s then a rotation back to
that New York open is possible. I'd say
bears are still in absolute control
right now folks. They are in full
control moving this lower. I'd be very
very worried if I was you. You guys
talking about trying to buy buy this.
I'd be very concerned. Higher time frame
wants to move lower.
It wants to move lower. There's previous
week lows. Globeex. You haven't even
taken out all the key levels. We we're
in a major cell. We got to understand
the macroeconomics. We are in a major
cell. We haven't reclaimed any key level
for you to be buying this.
I want to be short biased on this, but I
don't want to short the lows. So, it it
just will be what it will be. I'd be
very very cautious. Loads of you calling
for uh buy opportunities in here. The
whole market is bleeding out. You are
trying to buy against major fear in the
market. We are rotating out of names.
New lows here like we said. Okay. 600's
next level. And there's your new low.
So, next box is this green box down
here, which is based on the yearly
pivots. Okay, based on yearly pivots.
I'm not going to be a buyer in this
today. I've made that clear. Even if we
short squeeze today, I'm not thinking
about being a buyer in this. I'd rather
let it squeeze out and sell it. Look at
VIX approaching 2450s now.
[snorts]
Uh, very possible, Julian. Yeah, very
possible. And below. And we've not seen
panic fully set in yet. When panic sets
in,
it can get nasty.
So, want to watch for when spiders if if
spiders let go 660, it's major issues
for the market.
Just let this develop. Your range has
just been expanded. You're now at 237
points range. We are
21 minutes into the day. It's huge,
guys. These are these are the size that
we used to have for the whole day. This
was a good day. 220 points for a whole
day, right? Was good. You're at that in
20 minutes. Just be aware. Just be
aware.
Balls got stuck on that last push up
again. Every pop so far is being sold
into.
Every pop so far is being sold into. How
long we got to the new hour? 8 minutes.
New lows coming here, folks. Again,
so 600. I'd watch spy into this uh 660.
It's coming in there now. If SPY lets go
of 660, this market can get real heavy
real quick. And here it is. It's here
now. And if it lets go of this, it can
get real heavy real quick. If it holds
this, this is where you get those sort
of big 100 point squeezes out because
this is the put wall on spy and it's
starting to let go. It is starting to
let go. So it means we've moved from a
put wall of 672 to 670 to 660. So this
is your overunder on the spiders.
QQQ getting absolutely hammered here. If
I sw I would not be bullish today. I'll
be looking for bearish moves, but not
giving me something yet that I'm
interested in. Let's start getting rid
of this now.
Just one of those I want to be swing
short from last Friday's close. Really,
that was the position to be short from.
Hey, Bella, how's it going?
Okay, every pop still being sold into is
the retest of 600. Same on the spiders.
They're still selling every pop here.
This can move lower. Um, but again, you
want to be careful. Short squeezes can
push very, very quick in bare markets.
And then it depends if they get sold
into. But that 600 on spy is your
overunder right now. It's trying to
reclaim it. The 660 on spy is attempting
to reclaim it. You want to be careful
here. You want to be very careful here.
This options market taking over. I'm
too scary for me right now.
Big selling down here, folks.
So, spy trying to reclaim that 660 or
attempting to. So once it breaks away
from that violently um we go leg down
basically
which might be right here right now.
660 660 under over under over under
over. That's what spy is doing. It's
testing under testing over testing under
testing over. This is the put.
So this is about option dealers at the
moment more than anything else. Okay,
reclaiming spiders 66030 now. So can
they offer a squeeze back upside? I'll
be watching us into some of these key
levels here. Remember we've now come
into this is a big this green box is
based on the yearly profile. Based on
the yearly profile
every pop so far still being sold into
VIX is absolutely ripping faces right
now. 2460s still no trade for me. still
waiting for something clean. I want to
be bearish, but uh I just don't think
I'm going to get a location I'm really
going to be comfortable trading at.
Don't really want to trade the lows. And
here we go. Another breakdown. So that's
by losing that 660. So every pot being
sold now. That is clear into this yearly
level. So if you were short, this is a
covering level for you. We're now
approaching 300 points on the day
already. You've got uh 5 minutes left
until that new H1 H4.
Major fear rolling into this market.
Look at everything getting absolutely
annihilated right now. Do not want to be
a buyer in this market, folks. So,
Nvidia crossing that 180. I just got all
my alerts. Nvidia starting to let go of
that 180 kind of level or coming into
that 180 level. If that breaks, there's
a bigger puke. So, I had it at 18060
here on Nvidia. I'm watching a video
into 180 if it starts snapping that
QQQ into oh sorry spiders into a big
level here. Let me watch this video.
Where's that shelf? Okay, first wicks
here. Next wick on Nvidia will be 179
and then down to 176.
Oh, it's so annoying when you got the
bias, but it just can't get an entry
that you want. Cannot get an entry.
More selling it.
Testing these lows.
Don't think we're done. Don't think we
finished this auction yet.
Nice EBH.
Yeah, big level for like all of all of
the mag really. We're coming into huge
levels across the board. They're all
getting absolutely demolished. All
right, so Tesla 2.62% down. Nvidia 3.14%
down. Microsoft 2.74%
down. Meta 2.40% down. Google 1.09%
down. Amazon 2.80% down. Apple 0.22%
down.
Right. Nvidia trying to react off that
sort of 18060. It is finding a bit of a
bounce here after taking some liquidity.
And just be careful. Like I said, even
in bare markets, the bare rallies, the
uh short squeezes can be very, very,
very violent. I've made that very clear
today. I'm focused on the shorts until
we reclaim some big big key levels,
which I'm not seeing, but the rallies
can be aggressive.
That gray box is kind of your sentiment.
Previous week low is right here. See how
we're getting a reaction off this? All
right. And show you where this is. Or we
can actually probably do it on
we get you back to a daily. Where's you
guys?
All right. It's the edge down here.
Right. This right here. This is like
last chance saloon. And you see this
little bump right here. This is it. They
don't hold this. Look how thin we are.
Right? So, they could do a look below
and fail, but if not, or we're coming
right down to 24,000, right? There's a
500 point thin liquidity in here. Right?
So, this is like sort of the last edge,
the green box that we had on our chart.
It's the edge of volume. They don't hold
that. 24,000 is on deck.
>> [clears throat]
>> Nice, John. Nice. Nice work, everyone.
Everyone who got the shorts, well done.
I just never see the squeeze up to where
I want on these. But mate, this was
probably the entry right here. 17s, 20s,
underneath gray box, rejection of gray
box. That was probably it. Is what it
is. I'm not going to get in every day.
It's okay. I did get a piece overnight,
so I'm not um not too worried at the
moment.
More selling. Panic is in. Panic is in
here, folks. Panic is starting to see.
You're starting to see everyone
liquidating everything. I just want a
short squeeze out, not to get long. I
want to see a squeeze out so I can sell.
I want a violent squeeze out that I can
sell into. That's what I'm looking for
at the moment. VIX now 25s.
[laughter] H this thing is going ripper.
All these people saying the bottoms in.
There's 80% chance of shut up.
[\h__\h] people I see on Twitter getting
poor innocent people murdered because
they talk absolute shite. Don't know
what they're looking at. Right. Here's
the edge green box. This is coming to
the edge here on that volume profile.
So, black swan kind of scenario here.
We're outside of the daily Ballingers.
They don't save this into the 500s. Huge
level into the 500. If they don't save
that, I would say we're going 24,000.
Whether it's today or tomorrow or later
in the week, it's possible.
Please, I need a short squeeze out I can
sell into. Please, please, something
violent.
new H1 H4 here as well.
I want to see like 100 plus points at
least upside otherwise I can't do
anything with this market
excess sellers caught at those lows
first time today I've seen that big
selling into 500 caught offside I would
say that just just watching the delta
you can see it on book map here these
guys got caught 300 lot at the lows
right they got caught we're moving away
from them still overall sellers are in
control, but that is the first time I've
seen some decent size caught offside at
the lows. Just be aware. Doesn't mean we
can't move lower.
But I'm just letting you know that that
came in at 508. So from 508 to 500,
there was strong selling and we didn't
move lower yet. Yet it is just yet
because there is panic in this market.
But if they hold this, which they're not
holding. Okay, there you go. Lower we
go.
So full panic. No short for me. No pop
for me to sell into.
Oh, I just need somewhere to get short.
Give me some location. Just a squeeze
out. Developing a shelf here now as
well. Need to be aware of this now.
Let me draw it. Quite a big shelf.
Letting go of this box. So 400s and then
really 24K.
It's very very possible folks. Very very
very possible.
Major selling major panic.
Just I'm trying to be disciplined to not
chase. Trying to be disciplined not to
chase.
>> [laughter]
>> Maybe maybe MZ guy maybe still just
ripping faces here. We're not really
we're not even having if you think about
this we haven't even developed like okay
there's one inside bar to play off and
that's it. But like there's there's not
much development of liquidity is just
like straight downside.
You're now at 372 points downside.
the the more we cascade down, the worse
it's going to get, the less likely I'm
going to get uh be able to get involved.
Uh because you're going to see more
panic. The faster we move down, the more
people are going to sell their
positions.
Remember, we're approaching like lows
from beginning of October.
There's a big pivot into sort of at
24,000 24,175.
And the more we go straight down, the
more stops are going to get popped. The
more bulls are going to sell all their
positions and panic out.
Nice, Jack. Good work, mate. Good work.
All of you that caught it. Lovely work.
So, the first sort of pause we've seen
for a while, about 30 seconds. Still
think bears are in absolute control.
Bulls are getting murdered here. But
this is the first sort of calm we've had
for a second where it hasn't been moving
hundreds of points. But a new low again
here.
and all these guys. We talked about it I
think was it yesterday or or maybe
Friday last week or at some point have
talked about it. When you get a market
where people get used to doing something
i.e. buying dips, they find it very very
hard to then move into a market which
does the opposite. So they continue to
buy dips and they get hurt.
Strong selling here. Nvidia through the
180s now. Big big problems.
Big selling at these lows
and nothing for me to do unfortunately.
Poor Alex.
Big selling at these lows.
Might get a bit of a squeeze here if
they uh hold these. But same as before,
every time I've said that, they've just
sold through it and they've sold sold
again. So yeah, there's panic. There's
absolute panic in this market right now,
folks.
Bit of a wiggle there. They tried to
sell those lows again. Not getting
follow through. Maybe a maybe a small
squeeze out coming here soon, which
would then interest me. The higher the
better. Not that I'm playing long. Just
the higher the better for me to be uh
sell into it. Need to see a few hundred
points though.
Not seeing any shift in uh change
structure or anything like that yet. But
into this blue box, there's an area of
interest. They might want to defend it.
Let's see what they do with this.
Watching this 25 thou 25,000 24,500.
Can they squeeze right through that and
come back to some level of interest all
the way up here? Really
developing a bit. See, we're thin in
here. So if they get through this 40
540s is possible and above. Here you go.
So here's the start of the squeeze.
Those sellers got stuck like I just
talked about. So here's the 500. 40 is
possible. Through that we go reclaims.
So bears will want to defend between 40
and it's 60 point range. They'll want to
defend this range up here. This gray
box. I'm going to get rid of this green
one. Okay. This gray box now becomes
key. Bears are stuck at the lows
currently on for two candles in a row.
has got stuck in the lows.
Here's the push towards 25. 245. God, I
can't get the uh numbers out cuz they're
so moving so quick. And then 40 would be
the retest and then through 40 to the
other side of that pocket. And uh you're
starting to see a bit of a rally here.
So if you took this long once I told you
bears were stuck, you better be taking
some profits between now and 40s and
then just holding runners.
Big push.
They hold 25 on a dip. They uh it's a
psychological level. Here come the 40s.
The push towards 40s. This is a big
test. If they get through this, they can
squeeze to the other side of this box.
Here's the 40 test. And if they get
through this, the other side looks
really good at the moment.
I am small sizing this long. I know I
said I wasn't going to, but once it's
set up, I had to. Beautiful.
Tempted just to hold this. Come on.
Taking some here. Can we get through
this now? What's the other side of this
600?
Come on. Do a massive giant candle
upside for me. Moving stop aggressively
up now. Locking more in here at 40.
Starting to see some sellers try and
defend.
There we go. So, into 40s. This was the
trade. I know I said I wasn't going to
take it, but I did. Once we reclaim this
shelf, that's the move there. locked in
$1,500 on that. Nice. And they're
defending the 40s. All right. So, if we
get through 40s, the rotation now can
happen. So, sellers will want to defend
this for this move back down to here. If
bulls get back through this, we develop.
Sellers need to defend this box. If not,
we're going to get a relief rally
upside. But sellers, your main trend is
down. Sellers will want to defend this
box, right? They will want to do this or
this. They will not want to see price
come back through there. That would be a
look below GlobeEx and a reclaim, which
is what you're starting to see now.
You can set price alerts again for SPY
660 because we traded under it. You can
set price alerts for that re reppush
into it. You're about a dollar away at
the moment, just over. So, as long as if
you took this long, I know I said I
wasn't going to, but it was just too
obvious. I had to take it. Blue box. And
remember, this was all planned
pre-market. Back to here. Pay yourself.
Now, if you get very lucky, you squeeze
out, but your main trend is down, right?
Your main trend is down. You want to
really be focused on the shorts where
possible.
So, VIX trading back downside or pulling
back I should say off the high of 2571.
Okay. Bears currently defending this
gray box like we talked about. This is a
big volume shelf here.
I'll tell you where bears got stuck at
those lows.
24460.
All right. And then at the very low
2436, but I'd say any hold of 24. So,
let's just call 480. Any any hold of 480
can be your first higher low. Bulls, if
they want a squeeze, they're going to
need to hold 480 or above. that that's
the level they have to hold 480 or
above. I'm doing that based on what I'm
seeing on the tape. Okay, 480 or above
if they're going to do a higher low. But
remember, the main trend is lower. The
easier moves overall are bearish in
these market. It is not the easier moves
are not bullish.
This is just a little covering rally, a
little squeeze out after quite a
significant dump. And uh what's the
range now on the day? Just a casual 402
points. Nothing to see here, folks.
Okay, ball's taking control, squeezing.
So, here's the gray box. I'd be watching
VWAP now. So, if you're still in this
long through the 40s, top of the gray
box, 600 and VWOP, that's your next TP.
And if you get really lucky, we go
further. But just remember, this is a
short squeeze. Nothing more than that is
a squeeze out after a big big big
sell-off. gray box is somewhere I'd
normally be interested in shorting. I
just want to like let it uh sort of
shake out for a minute.
And the bulls will want to def defend
480s. It will not want it below 480s.
Under 480s, we will probably make a new
low
is why you got to understand when you
take that long, it's just a counter
trend squeeze. That's all it is. And
that was a short trigger on the flow
zones. and point of control and the
volume shelf. Okay, here's a move back
down to 500. So 480 is the key level.
That's your over under. If bulls don't
defend that, it probably make a new low
there or thereabouts. You got to give it
some uh wiggle room in this market
obviously because we're moving quick
500s here.
Here come the move back to 480 is 89s,
87s coming in 83s. This is the level now
they need to defend here. the bulls if
they're going to have a chance of any
more relief otherwise probably new lows.
Like I said, it's a short squeeze up and
if they can't defend here, they're going
to get themselves in big big trouble,
which is looks like they might well be
in
just a short squeeze up. Sold into at
that area back down to this level. This
is the level. They can't defend this.
They're in big old trouble.
They're attempting to
struggling. They are struggling. They're
attempting to defend it, but they are
struggling.
Look, I'm flat right now, folks. I took
the squeeze out. I'm flat at the moment.
This is where sellers last came in right
here on this big candle down.
So, bulls basically now get got to get
above 95. They got to defend 18, get
above 95. And I'm not seeing that on the
tape. I'm not seeing that on the tape.
seen quite the opposite.
Hopefully that made sense to you all.
Squeeze out. They defended this.
Probably should have just flipped and
got This is what I struggle with once I
take this is just flip and go short back
down. What I should do because it's very
obvious. There's your main trend.
There's the flow zones. There's your
shelf. There's your point of control.
There's a retest of this. So that would
be TP1. And then TP2 is run us down
maybe to 24,000 if they really want to
be nasty.
So yeah, buyers have got to get back
above the 500s.
This level here that we just pushed
into, this is where all the sellers came
in.
The buyers have got to get back above
500s basically. There they go. Back
above the 500s.
Okay, can we squeeze now then for the
first higher low?
big shelf up here into 520 from those uh
sort of three candles up here. So 3500s
into 520s and through that probably take
out this pivot up here. Here we go.
Here's 20s. Big level up here, folks.
Big level up here. This is a huge battle
now. You're going to get whipsaw
reaction in this range while they battle
it out to decide what they do next.
excess there. Balls failed to get
through with conviction yet, but it
might still come. Looks like the first
higher low is in. Here we go.
Come on.
Big level here.
Ball's failing here. They're trying.
They are trying.
That reclaim of uh 500 was was good, but
now we're into where we had excess in
this and this shelf here. If they
reclaim this, there's a bigger squeeze
out towards GlobeEx and VWOP and maybe
all the way up here if they're done with
it for a minute before they resell it.
And this can be a twoleg which is sold
into. It could be a fail two-leg which
is also sold into. I wouldn't want to be
long in this area here. If you're long,
it needs to be from down here. You need
to be selling into this area as they
build out liquidity down here. Remember,
they're going to build out lots of
liquidity here. This can be a big bare
flag, a two-leg which they sell down.
They can build a big bare flag, a two
leg, which they sell down. Any long
today is counter trend on every time
frame.
Back down to test those sort of 490s
areas. 480 490. It's where the sellers
last got stuck. So, this is this is the
rotation now. They're going to have to
make their mind up here. It's It might
look small. It's not. This is fast
moving and big big size being traded
through here. Both both sides.
80s again.
Buyers need to hold this. They're
trying.
I don't have much conviction here for
any more longs at the moment, but they
are attempting to do it. Like I said,
this can be a two-legg or a failed two
leg, which just pukes out and big old
bare flag down. Remember, easier move of
least resistance
down today. I'm going to get a new a new
coffee while I let this just uh do its
thing. Be right back.
Sorry folks, wife just woke up so I had
to make her a coffee as well. All right.
Okay. So, failed two leg then and
possibly uh breaking down here. So,
failed two leg, failed this PC, failed
that gray box. Like I said, any long
today is just a counter trend short
squeeze and that's been sold into now.
So, I think we probably make new lows
here, I would imagine. Let me just check
the excess on that last low. Yeah,
probably not enough. I mean, the excess
was at 34 and under.
Imagine they will probably trade through
it, but we will see.
We will see.
Just be careful, Kevin. You keep saying
that. Keep saying you saying that. Just
be careful. You're going to have to read
the tape very, very well. If you're
playing longs today like I did, just be
very, very careful. The main move,
remember, the main people in control
right now are bears. The main emotion
going through this market right now is
panic, right? It's not exuberance. It's
not buy the dip. Think about all the
people that were buy the dip, buy the
dip, buy the dip, right? They are in
panic. I can tell you, I was on Twitter
last night watching these so-called uh
expert influencers telling you uh
telling you that the the the low is in
because we've had a two or 3% pullback.
What if I missed it?
I don't know what I've missed there,
folks, but please be nice to each other
in chat. No rudeness in this room.
Remember
the weekly lows are protected. Uh we're
under we're under previous week lows,
mate.
We're under everything at the moment.
All right. Your previous week low is
right up here. See this 627. That's
previous week low. So
at the moment or if we go to a monthly
chart,
monthly chart is the only chart
currently which you could say could
potentially be bullish
versus here 157. If we go to a weekly
chart, right, we're breaking weekly
lows, right? Broken this weekly low low,
broken this weekly low. These are the
next areas that we could come into if we
go to a daily chart. So weekly is in
breakout underneath here. If we go to a
daily chart, dailyy's in breakout.
Obviously, if daily is in breakout,
everything else is on breakout. Yeah.
Hourly's in breakout, 4 hours in
breakout, etc., etc. So, all I'm saying,
I'm not saying you can't take the
counter trend squeezes. All I'm saying
is it's the harder trade to take, right?
That's all I'm trying to say. It's the
harder trade to take is this move back
upside. At the moment, it's working for
you, but it's the harder trade to take.
We haven't got back over. for example,
POC's now flipped here. We're not back
over this. Once we get back over this,
maybe there's a relief to here. They
might well resell, right, a pop up into
here, for example. So, that's all I'm
saying, my friend. That's all I'm
saying. I'm not telling you not to do
it. I'm telling you, be careful.
All right.
Big old squeeze. There you go. Here's
VWAP.
Woof. Like I said, bare bare market
squee like the squeezes in bare markets
can be drastic. There you go. This for
me can still be very bearish, right? So,
just be all I'm saying is be careful.
Make sure you're locking in. If you're
playing counter trend, you've got to
lock some in. I'll be watching for a
hold over. So, this is sort of move now.
So, I'd be watching for a for a hold. If
this is going to be a W and a hold,
they've got to hold the top side of this
really for this move here if they're
going to do it.
>> [snorts]
>> God, it's moved so quick. Moved off my
charts. Okay, some bulls got trapped at
the top there. Big big buying at the top
there. Not what you want to see. And
there's probably a passive seller in
there moving it away. Let's see if they
actually hold a dip here or if we just
like wash all the way back through,
which would not surprise me either
because it's a short squeeze and we're
still under VWAP, etc., etc. So, what's
this level here of interest? So, 50s
down to 23s.
If they hold that, bulls can have a
bigger squeeze out. If they don't hold
50s down to 20s and then they're
probably coming back to the lows, right,
we are under the VWAPS [snorts]
by not through 660 yet. So far, they
just hold that dip in 250s
so far. I mean it was there for about a
nancond.
So 50s to 20s needs to hold for bulls.
If they get that there's a bigger
squeeze out here. Starting to see it try
and develop. This is a big area up here
because bulls got stuck. If we can break
this high is a bigger squeeze coming.
I am in this small size at the moment.
Just watching it. I'm taking profit as I
go because I know I'm counter trend. I
know saw that dip and we held that key
level. So watching VWAP and GlobeEx
here. I've already taken some money off
the table here folks. It's very very
dangerous trade. They can absolutely
slam this on the face if they want.
Think we're going to move higher at this
point. 600 bid big overunder. Not seeing
too many transactions here. So I think
we're going to trade through it. There
we go. Beautiful. Okay. Here's VWAP.
Here's GlobeEx. We base above this now.
We're watching for a move into 70s.
Remember, we're counter trend. So, we
expect shorts to come in. Do not be
adding late. We expect I cannot say
enough. We expect shorts to come back
into this market and cause pain.
So, 50s to 20s was the entry. I said if
we hold 50 to 20s. There we go. It's
just very simple. You can make it a W,
can't you? D hold of this. That was a
awful drawing, Alex. D hold of this.
We're bullish to here. Take some profit
off into here. low volume node. If we
get through this, we're looking for 70s.
If we fail this, we're out on the
runners break even or in the money if
you want. [snorts]
Here we go. Back down towards that
level. So again, 50s to 20s have to
hold. Otherwise, we're going back
towards lows. My stop is now in the
money and about to get knocked out.
Knocked out here on the runner. Locked
in some more money. And this is why,
like I said, you have to expect bears to
come back in. This is now the twole that
we talked about. If they fail under
here, they're going to come right down
to here, and this would be strong
momentum, and that is a giant bare flag,
right? So, if they don't hold this, they
come back down lower. This is how we
build liquidity. This is literally how
we build liquidity. This is a liquidity
buildout. Bulls must defend this if
they're going to get a bigger squeeze.
Failing to defend this allows this
rotation for new lows.
50s to 20s is the level. We're still
actually holding at that gray box. Maybe
a bit premature there from me, but
wanted to lock in.
[sighs]
Just cal everyone in chat. Just calm
down. I'm not sure what's happened
because I missed it, but calm heads,
guys. You need calm heads when you're
trading. You'll see me lose my head
sometimes and it means I can't trade.
Just calm heads. If you got something
wrong or whatever, just try and let it
go. So, if you can't let it go, just
shut your screens down or go for a walk
or do whatever you've got to do. But
calm heads.
No blaming anyone else for anything.
You're in charge of your own decisions,
your own trades and chat, okay? There's
always two two trades to be have.
There's both sides. You can both make
money. You can both trade both sides.
Like you said, you would have seen me
today saying, "I'm focused on the
shorts, but I've ended up trading the
longs because the shorts haven't set up
for me." So, um, you know, it's a
two-sided tape. It's you versus you.
It's not you versus someone else. We're
here to support and help each other. I
will give you a readout the best I can
on how the market's moving. But calm
heads, folks.
Bulls. Still holding this gray box and
in control here. VWAP is massive though.
VWAP and GlobeEx is massive.
What's nice is I took a two and a half
grand payout
last night on the funded next and I
basically replenished that already which
is awesome.
Always nice when that happens. Okay,
VWAP here. Edge here. You can see this
edge here. Maybe I need to do one of
these for you so you can see it. Um,
this edge here thin above this, right?
Thin above this. This level is massive
up here for the market to make a
decision. It's GlobeEx and VWAP. If we
get back through this, it's basically
like a failed auction under GlobeEx and
we could trade back upside. I expect
this to be a highly contested area.
First win on the channel. Took the long
for 15 points. No worries. What's
GlobeEx? Just overnight overnight
session. So, London, London and Asia.
So, we're basically, if you look in the
look at the double bottom that we made
at like, you know, 11:00 and 2:00 a.m.,
that's what this orange line is. It's
that double bottom. So, back towards
that double bottom. Now,
spy back through the 660 at the moment.
A bigger squeeze can happen here if they
can hold over this. If they fail this,
you know, the rotation back downside.
All right, so bigger squeeze can happen.
If they go over this, maybe we get up
into here for some relief. But this gray
box, massive level, massive, massive,
massive level.
So far they are defending it.
Overall trend remember is down. Overall
trend is down.
Balls so far have got stuck up above 600
on the last well or both attempts
basically up there. So that attempt at
uh
1024 and that attempt at 1028 both times
up there they got stuck. So back down
towards these 50s and 20s and bulls will
need to defend this point control.
Failing this will probably go low of
day. So these are the rotations now
though they have to make their mind up
or
or it's trouble or it is big trouble. So
back down to these lows and uh we will
see decisions to be made here by the
bulls basically or and by the bears.
It's by both
thinking nasty moves coming. Either way,
they're going to get themselves caught
in these levels as we rotate.
Spy still not back through that 660. I
think it just might have just had an
attempt and failed up there. That's the
big level is the put wall.
>> [snorts]
>> We'll see. I think for us that GlobeEx
and sort of VWAP are very very key. So
rotate between these fail this probably
back down towards this low down here.
That would be a two-legg which has been
sold into to come lower. We're thin in
this area here. Very very very thin.
is trying to find a bid on fiveminute
flow zones at the moment. Very dangerous
uh market here. Very very dangerous
two-way tape.
I don't trade options so I couldn't tell
you Taylor. I just know the the walls.
I'm only interested in the levels and
the walls. Buyers trying to defend that
20s to 50s. Still liquidity now being
built out in the rotation between these
gray boxes. If buyers break out through
here, there's a move up to 70s like we
talked about. This this is major
rotation in between these levels. Here
we go. Can they get this squeeze? Can
they get through GlobeEx is the
question. Every attempt up there,
they've been sold into so far. So, every
pop up towards 600 has been sold into so
far.
and again sold into
big battle. This is a huge battle on the
tape here. They know that this is
pivotal onto what happens next. Both
sides.
Oh, thank you. Yeah, IB now set this
purple line down here. Initial balance
low down here.
Big contested level here.
Big big big contested level here.
Bears trying to step on the gas to force
this back down for this two-leg finish.
Bulls trying to defend point of control
and gray box.
Still can't believe Apple's green. The
strength in that is maddening to me.
Like I'm happy because I'm long Apple,
but it's crazy how strong that is. Like
internal meetings that Tim Cook might be
leaving, Jeff Williams has left, like
all this stuff, and yet it's [laughter]
green on the day. It's amazing. Good
sign. Okay, into this bottom of this
gray box. So bear's got the force down
to there, but Bulls still trying to
defend the edge of this gray box in the
thin liquidity, and they're trying to
soak straight back up. So, the rotation
still continuing. It is a battleground,
folks. Bulls look like they might have
just caught some bears down there on
that last move. Uh, a hold of 36 here is
very, very bullish. So, watching GlobeEx
now. If they squeeze through here, there
could be a bigger move because they just
trapped bears at 36 or below 36.
Balls got trapped up here the last three
attempts to get through 600. So, that's
your level basically.
And again, getting sold into. Every push
up here in front of 600 is getting sold
into. Someone's going to get hurt soon.
There's a lot of liquidity been built
out in between these two gray boxes now.
Huge amount of liquidity.
Big battle. Big big battle.
Takes moving quick. The amount of
borders going through is mental.
Tape is moving quick.
O so fast guys. It's so fast this tape.
[snorts]
The rotation gray box to gray box. Gray
box to gray box. And then someone will
lose outside of these gray boxes.
crazy crazy. It's just the speed of the
tape's crazy.
Remember, the overall trend is bearish.
I cannot say that enough for all of you
looking for the longs. The overall trend
is bearish. I know I've taken a couple
longs today, but the overall trend is
down. And the two, this is a twoleg. And
if they sell through this, new lows are
available. I cannot say that enough.
Here come the bears taking control. So
bulls failed to complete the rotation
above this level. VWAP held, GlobeEx
held. Now they're going to retest these
lows. This can be a two-leg. It can be a
giant bare flag if they want. Bulls
really must defend otherwise. There's
your two-leg. Bulls are trying to defend
this right now. This is the last chance
that they have and it's very dangerous
to do this move here and this is bearish
momentum and it can be sold into into
these next areas if they want.
The main trend is down.
[sighs]
500's here.
SPY failed to reclaim those 660s.
Market's in panic. It is in panic.
What are we doing on the H1?
Hardest thing now is going to be like
shorts because we're outside like for my
rules were outside of daily bingers.
Are they adding liquidity lower? Yes,
they are.
There's so much panic in this market at
the moment. I'm just watching them dump
inventory on the tape at the moment.
Back down towards these lows. It's game
over here, I would say.
Initial balance low there.
Vicks finding a bid
game over here. I would say
we are into a little node but I find it
somewhat unlikely that bulls are able to
defend this given the momentum. It would
be a very very impressive hold.
Aggressive
selling on the tape here. Try. They're
trying to force a new low of day. They
are trying to force a new low of day
breakdown.
If they don't get it through this area,
they're going to get caught and the
rotation will go right back up to this
gray box. They are trying to force a new
low of day breakdown here. They might
well get it. That's what they're looking
for. But
is a such a big battle and the speed of
the tape is something else. It is
something else.
Here's the squeeze right back up back to
this gray box. Probably bears will need
to defend that gray box in that thin
area. Failing to defend that would
probably go straight back to the upside
and retest the VW. And the rotation will
just keep continuing, continuing,
continuing until they've caught enough
offside of whichever direction they're
trying to trade in for the next hour or
two.
Bears came flying back in there. They're
trying to force a breakdown. They really
want to force a breakdown underneath the
current IB low here.
They're attempting
into that old imbalance.
They've got control here if they want to
do it. It's just uh I don't know if
they've got the juice in them
because they keep forcing the lows and
they're not moving lower. But if the
bulls give up, it will snap.
Just the speed, the speed and size going
through.
[snorts]
Crazy, man. I feel like I'm watching
small cats.
The speed and size going through this
tape. I do feel like I'm watching small
caps. It's mental.
Squeeze straight back up here. They're
going to test this gray box up here.
They need to defend it, the bears,
otherwise it's a fail breakdown. Second
or third, second attempt. Second attempt
fail breakdown. If they can't break
under these bears, they came flying in
at those lows and didn't get the move
that they wanted.
I mean, I don't know what's considered
big size now because I'm not seeing any
orders go in under hundreds and hundreds
of lots. It's everything's massive.
Here they go. One more attempt then to
go lower by the looks of it.
Now or never for these bears, I would
say for last attempt to get down
underneath IB and then maybe down to
24,000. What's the next level? 24,200 if
they can get that snap below IB. There
is a 200 point move under here back down
into this level next.
If it's a big if right now because
they're coming piling in and we're not
moving lower. So there's absorption
happening on the tape here.
Just means you got a size down bar.
Just means you got to size right down,
doesn't it?
or you can leave it alone. If you're if
you're uncomfortable, it's also fine.
VIX still finding bids here and we're
not seeing breaking down here. VIX looks
like it's going to break out and we're
not seeing a breakdown here on the cues.
Two-way tape here now. I think you're
just getting a lot of liquidity stuck
both sides here at the moment. This just
feels like a nasty two-way tape.
Someone's going to get really, really,
really hurt
this level here.
Edges with the bears, right? edges with
the bears right now. But draw this.
They've got to Why can't I draw this?
I keep trading. They've got to force a
breakdown under here. They've got to
liquidate balls underneath this level.
Get underneath initial balance and then
there's a 200 break. If they can't do
that, they're going to get themselves
caught. This is what fourth or fifth
attempt down here now. And they're not
moving under. So there is someone here
soaking the tape because it's very
aggressive selling and we are not moving
lower.
You're going to get a really nasty move
incoming.
You can't have that much size in a
condensed area and not see a nasty move
one way or the other.
Yes, they're it's not just that they're
building liquidity. It's the amount of
size
here is huge. This is not a joke. What's
happening in here is massive. These
orders are [\h__\h] huge, mate.
There you go. Told you you can't add
that much size down there and not see a
breakdown and get away with it.
Straight back to the gray box. They go.
And if bears don't defend this gray box,
we go on a [\h__\h] giant squeeze now
because they've all just got caught down
here.
So bears must defend this gray box. If
they don't defend this gray box, well, I
don't really know what to say. They're
going to get absolutely buttth hurt.
They're going to be absolutely butt hurt
if they don't defend this gray box.
So huge, huge rotation, huge rotation is
available. Both sides of this. I
wouldn't I wouldn't want to be bearish
at those lows, which is what they've all
tried to do. They've just got absolutely
wrecked. Oh, you think this doesn't look
big? That's a 100 points and they've got
thousands of orders down there.
Thousands. Which is why I'm saying the
tape is insane.
Absolutely insane what I'm witnessing
here. I don't remember seeing a tape
move like this.
Whoa.
Gray box defended. Back to this gray
box. Rotation continues. One side to the
other, one side to the other, one side
to the other. No change. That's all
we're going to get until someone wins
this game. And these are 100 point M1
candles, folks.
[laughter]
Yeah, it's just massive, massive
rotation.
What are you looking at? I'm looking at
bookmat and the footprint. Looking at
both.
Insane.
Mad, man. This is mad.
Bears have the chance here. I don't not
I'm not convinced yet. They have the
chance. They've got They've got to break
down here aggressively. They've come in
at this level we're at uh numerous times
without any success.
They've got to break down aggressively
here. They've piled in again here. And
there's there's definitely huge
absorption going on here.
There you go. They got caught again,
guys. This is absolutely insane. Just a
casual 480 lots there by side. Just
squeezing straight out.
Absolutely insane.
Absolutely insane. There's no way I'm
touching this at this point. This is
This is mental.
These are hedge funds like betting
against each other. So, I'm not touching
this until someone's clearly won. This
is crazy. These two gray boxes, the size
being traded between these is crazy.
Absolutely crazy. Once you get a
breakout from here, it's I can't
explain. Once you have this much size in
a very condensed area, a breakout from
this area can be violent. like numerous
hundreds of points very very quickly.
Back down to this same level that bears
are attempting to get through again.
Back to this 480 level again as in where
that 480 lot came in. So 500.
Wow.
Bears have the edge, but there is a
soaking going on here. Basically, bears
have the edge, but they they must see a
breakdown sub60. Basically, they've got
to get sub 60 and then they get IB and
then they get a a nasty wash, I would
expect. But at the moment they're not
getting that sub60 move. They're being
absorbed into 70s. Every attempt being
absorbed and absorbed and absorbed and
absorbed and back to 500s we're going to
go. And if they squeeze through here
then back to 40s we go very quickly. And
if they squeeze through there then all
the way back to 600s we go. And that
might sound like nothing but we're
currently trading at 470. So that's 130
points like that can happen like that.
And if bears get their way well then all
of this gets washed out and this becomes
available.
It is a scary tape.
And if you're not scared of this, then
uh I don't know what to tell you. It
means that you're not really reading
what's going on cuz this is a scary
scary tape.
No, Ransom. This is not what it feels
like. It doesn't feel like any tweet is
going to take us to alltime highs.
I don't even know what to say to that.
Do you know where we are? We're
liquidating daily, weekly, and monthly
players. We're not going alltime highs
anytime soon.
Back to these 70s, which keep being
soaked. 70s keep being soaked over and
over and over and over and over and over
and over and over. Does this buyer
eventually give up or is he just got end
is he got trillions of dollars to keep
soaking here? At the moment it seems
like it
Endless supply of money here.
Back to his level again. He's still
soaking off those 75s.
Wow.
Does he give up? He's got so much money
to be doing this.
72s, dude. Bears. It's now or never for
them. Honestly, it's now or never.
It's now or never for them.
Still soaking. He's still soaking the
bid. Oh my god.
[laughter]
This guy's a beast,
man. If he gets out the way, I don't
think there's anyone left to prop it up.
Still soaking. He's still soaking.
Jeez, man.
This guy's huge. He is huge.
Someone's going to get hurt. Like I
said, 100 points
very, very quickly happen.
>> [sighs and gasps]
>> Can't believe how long we've been here.
Can't believe how long we have now been
here. Here he's getting out the way.
He's He's [\h__\h] He's [\h__\h] Down to
the lows we go then. He is absolutely
[\h__\h] Does he soak IB? I I now is the
only question.
Oh my gosh.
Oh my gosh. He spent that whole time
soaking this level here and here. Okay,
so if they crash IBL then I think a
bigger rotation. This huge puke is
available.
Absolutely insane the amount of volume
traded there. Absolutely insane.
This is way beyond what I'm willing to
do right now. When when I see players
this big fighting, it's very, very
scary. Once one gets out the way, which
we're starting to see now, IBL, we can
we can expect expansion. Again, the
problem now is you're trading. Yes,
we're trading a downtrend, but we're way
way way outside of reasonable areas. If
we think about dailies,
right
here is your bowl. Here's the shelf.
They've let go of the shelf. The
rotation is available,
but really, we need the bowl to be
catching up, and we're not going to see
that for a day or two.
>> It's just it's tough how they've done
this overnight.
location I wanted to be short for those
joining late
was up into here which they offered
well they didn't even offer it to Gloex
really or did they yeah they did they
did they offered it to Asia that was the
shorting
down here is very risky but we have got
this GlobeEx shelf which is holding
currently but this just seems uh it's a
very very risky Risky day to be trading
trying to short the lows now. And it's a
very risky day to be trying to buy.
We're going back to this guy's level.
Did he just save it? [laughter]
Where was his big order before? 270 90
again.
Flipping heck.
Yeah, just a 400 point initial balance
range. I know. I know.
Well, look at this reaction of five
below.
That's just under 100 points there. That
straight that straight slingshot.
It's mental, isn't it? Back towards PC.
I don't know what to say here, folks.
This is
It's very rare I see a market moving
this much size this quickly, but that's
what I'm watching at the moment.
Both sides getting hurt at the moment. I
would say bears have got the edge.
They've got the higher time frame edge.
We haven't got an edge as a bear
necessarily, lower time frame because
we've lost location, but bears have got
their edge higher time frame. And if
they want to get a breakdown, they will.
This 500's big level.
This is where that guy basically soaked
there to 70 there to 500 to 70. that
kind of area for a long time in this
gray box. If bulls reclaim this, then
they're going to try and hit this as a
rotation. If they reclaim that next
level as rotation, remember bears are in
control of this market on the higher
time frame. We are in a panic selling
kind of moment in this market. They are
adding liquidity lower now all the way
down to 400s.
First time I've seen them sort of come
in the book more aggressively down
there.
So 440s, 430s,
400. Let's go down and see if anyone's
lower. 350s, 330s, 300s, 290s, 250s.
Yeah, lots of liquidity lower.
Oh, tape's mad. Yeah, the tape is the
tape's mad.
I'm going to use a bathroom while it
does this. I'll come back and hopefully
it's calmed down a little bit.
Oh, look at that. Back to that same
level. Who'd have guessed? Who'd have
guessed?
Crazy. All right, let's get this tape
catching up. See where we're at. Oh my
god.
I can't believe this. There's size
coming in.
Jeez,
there's size coming in. Madness.
Absolute madness.
Okay, bulls trying to force this
squeeze. I'm going to get rid of this.
It's becoming less important.
Bears still have the edge technically
for a breakdown. Bulls are defending
this IBL right now. Let me just check
the ES. Did it break under IBL? No. ES
also defending it. VWOPS are all
pointing downward. Blow zones are all
pointing downward.
Crazy crazy crazy tape. It's literally
like if you look at bookmap, where are
you guys? This is what's nuts, right?
So, we trade into a low,
right? And we catch some guys off guard
here and the squeeze just comes. Look,
there's market orders. This is just a
straight squeeze. Squeeze, squeeze,
squeeze, squeeze, squeeze, squeeze,
squeeze. Squeeze, squeeze, squeeze,
squeeze, squeeze, squeeze, squeeze. And
once we chat, 100 lot dump and straight
downside again. It's very, very fast
moving.
Always trying to defend this PC right
now.
But bears, like I said, bears have the
edge in this market at the moment,
folks. [snorts]
Can I explain the IB range? It's just
the first hour of trading. It's all it
is. It's the extremes set on the first
hour. The highest point and the lowest
point between the 9:30 and 10:30 open in
the New York.
Still not Yeah. Everything's down. TPT
is down, Canvas's down. Everything that
uses that same thing is down currently.
It's it's a pain, but it is what it is.
is reselling this.
They want to break IB. They're looking
for a rotation lower.
I just can't based on rules. I can't be
a short down here. Just cannot. And I
don't want to long this back up right
now. Not right now. Not with what I'm
seeing. Not in a two-way tape. The bears
might get a big panic flush today, but I
We would have needed to be short on pops
and drive out this morning which we
didn't see this. This was it. I wanted
to get short up here. It's very much
like the last two days. There's just not
been a enough strength at the market
open to give us prime location. It's
just unfortunate. So, we have to stick
to rules, but it is what it is.
Head and shoulders forming. I mean,
yeah, you could argue that here if
you're looking for a breakdown. Just be
careful with a look below and fail in
this pocket. But yes, bears have control
right now. No doubt about it. Multi-time
frame bears currently are in control of
this market. Flow zones are point down.
Vots are point down. You're underneath
previous day low. You're underneath
previous week low. You're underneath
GlobeEx. You're into some interesting
levels.
Bears have the edge. It's just depends
if two if if this guy absorbing the
tape. If bears fail, if they fail to
move lower, squeezes will happen. Right?
Like we talked about, even in bare
markets, the squeezes can be violent
like this. Prime example, if bears keep
trying to short down here and they don't
get the break or even worse, they get
the break and they get this, you'll get
a squeeze out because the best short
location is way up higher. Hundreds and
hundreds and hundreds of points higher.
Vick's looking like he's going to do
that breakout to the upside at the
moment.
Heavy tape here.
Big selling here.
Big big selling here.
[snorts]
New Audi bar here, folks. New Audi bar
here.
[snorts]
Just sat patiently waiting. Bought two
of those little squeezes up today.
Nothing else. Did trade a little bit
overnight.
Just waiting now.
Yeah. Since 10:00 a.m., uh, CBD is up.
Yeah.
So you got divergence there really
because if we break this low
you're going to have buyers trapped
don't you
would be up because it would be that guy
on the tape trying to soak it the whole
time. Okay here's your lows. This can
get real nasty real quick. Right. So
you're either going to get a look below
and fail here or you're going to get an
absolute tank just straight down.
Vicks trying to break out here.
Strong selling on the tape here. They
are piling into this. Bulls are all
stopping out now. They're all getting
washed out and you can get panic now.
This thing can really start
getting very, very, very panicky. If it
fails to reclaim any levels, this can
get very, very panicky. Think how many
people have been trying to soak this or
think about that player been trying to
soak it that whole time. If he doesn't
if he can't get a reclaim here, right?
He's stuck, isn't he?
Big sellers came in there at sort of
37s,
37s to 40s, that kind of level. That's
where sellers will want to protect.
That's where they came flying in. It's
where all the size came onto the tape.
They won't want it back above that.
Kevin, you keep saying that, man. I'm
getting very worried about you, my
friend. Every dip down, you're looking
for a buy.
We haven't reclaimed anything.
But we've let go of everything.
More selling coming in here at the lows.
We're running out of things to look for.
I mean, I would say
sort of 150s, 160s we have is not out of
the question right now.
Is not out of the question right now.
150s down here is not out of the
question. Not at all.
you would if Kevin what I'd say is if
you're going to look for a buy at least
let it reclaim a level at least let it
show you something would be what I'd say
or at least let it trap someone or do
something because otherwise it's going
to be very easy to get caught like if
you start reclaiming IB sure like by all
means it makes sense right that's all
I'm saying to you but if you're bidding
here okay you might have got lucky right
now but they can wash this down lower if
they want.
Fix new high day there. Just broke out a
new high day there. Fix. Can it hold its
gains?
400 over under here. Big battle around
this 400 level. Remember, there's not
much here until we get way down here.
Now, I can't really see much. Let me
just check the volume profile. Yeah,
we're very thin here. I'd say the next
little bump in the road is sort of 300
300 to 240 based on the yearly profile
and then uh 150. So, 300 to 240. We can
just pop a little box in. 300
if Trading View wants to let me. 300 to
240.
Okay, that's just based on the yearly
profile. There's a little little bump in
the road there. Right, here's your IB
retest.
This is
key. Now on to what happens next. So
far, bears are defending that IB retest,
aren't they? And the big level is really
up there 60s.
So potential trend day if they defend
that IB.
If we go get back through the initial
balance, potential squeeze for a test up
to 460 is possible.
Not seeing too much excess anywhere yet.
Not seeing too much excess yet.
Here's IB.
Test of IB again.
No drive through it. It's a big level.
It is a big level. That initial balance.
It's not Apex, Dean. It's not Apex. All
right. There's a Cloudflare issue. It's
not Apex. It's TPT as well. It's most
websites currently, 20% of all websites
you look at currently are not working.
No different to when AWS went down a few
weeks ago.
Uh yeah. Oh, definitely if if you get
above here, Kevin. Yeah. If you do one
of these, that's probably a buy. Yes.
But remember, it's counter trend, right?
Main look is down. So, anything you take
long today is a squeeze. It's nothing
more than a squeeze. That's all I'm
trying to say to you. You're playing the
hardest trade in the book. Here's your
initial balance
through here. We can really get going up
to that PC. And then how we at there
becomes key. Here's PC. So, squeeze
through IB. I'm in this longed out up to
PC almost there. 70s partial here.
All right, I let it reclaim and then I
got long.
Really nice. So into PC
taking partial here. Let's see if we can
get going. If we get lucky, let's
counter trend. So I took after we
reclaimed. If we get very lucky, we go
VWAP. We'd have to be very lucky. We are
starting to see that on the tape. Only
worries me is there not not that much
excess at the lows right now. Here's PC.
So, battle here. So, you'd want a
pullback to hold initial balance. Now,
if we're actually going to set something
more, but again, this is just a counter
trend squeeze. They can absolutely shut
this door and come back down to lows.
They can do that. No problem at all.
Beautiful. If we get really lucky, we're
going to get up here. Five. Where's this
edge? 520s. 540s 570s.
I'm down to tiny size now. So, as long
on the breakthrough IB,
I want to see it hold this. Failing to
hold this, I will cut under 70s. Here we
go. If we can get this, we get really
lucky. This be the IB rotation.
Look below and fail.
Hardest trade in the book here, guys,
because a counter trend. It's annoying.
I've had three trades today and they've
all been counter trend, but it is what
it is.
So into this psychological level 500.
Come on. Bit of selling here.
It's a big squeeze. We can drop right
back down. So I'm down to tiny tiny tiny
tiny size. It's either gives me
something else or it doesn't. It's a
nice trade either way.
Okay, back into this pocket. It needs to
find a base here. If it's going to do
any more damage upside, it's got to find
a base between here. You don't really
want it to come back to IB. You'd want
it to protect this level. If we're going
to move any further upside, you'd want
to see it protect this level. And what
we would be targeting is the VWAP
because it's the initial balance trade.
All right. So far, protecting nicely.
Psychological number number 500. If we
break through that, there's a potential
bigger move here. Here we go. Come on
then, baby.
Be careful how much I make here.
Nice. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go.
Let's go. Looking for this little shelf
here into 40s if we can.
Some selling here. That's fine.
Want to see this hold and squeeze more.
Want to be very careful here. Some
aggressive selling coming back on the
tape. Remember, we're counter trend.
Hardest trade in the book. Can't say it
enough. It is the hardest trade in the
book. We look good. Come on. Come on.
Come. Break 20s. Go 40s and then be
what?
Big psychological level. Huge selling
coming in on the tape here. We're We're
soaking it. Well, here we go. Right.
Selling more here. Got to be careful.
There's a big battle going on here.
There's excess at this high. Can we
break these 40s and get up to VWAP?
I'll move my stop up here. Let me move
my stop. There we go.
So, we need to soak this
otherwise I'm out.
Let it develop for a second.
Yeah, patient pays. That's it. We just
trade when the momentum is there, not
when it's not there. We don't guess and
go against it. We trade it when it's
there. And we pay ourselves, especially
when we're counter trend. You have to
pay yourself. 20s here.
If we can get through this and 40s, then
I think we can go up to the 870s. VW
would be my target here.
We can soak that gray box. I'm I'm in
all the time. We're above point control.
Basically, fail point control. I'm out
of it.
Stop's probably about to get popped
here. Here we go. 40's coming and then
we're going to get VW up and then Alex
is going to be done with it.
40s here. Okay, here we go. Here we go.
Here we go. Here we go. Here we go. Come
on.
Don't you dare fail here. Want to be
careful. And in fact, I'm going to move
my stop bit more. Be protective.
Come on. I think we can get VW up. I
think we're going to get the IB trade.
Want to be careful here. Lots of
aggressive buying here on the tape. If
we don't move higher, it means there's a
passive seller sat in this old
imbalance. You can take profit here.
Don't be a dick for a tick. Okay.
Be very careful. Looking for one more
squeeze to VWAP. They're front. They're
front running it here and there's lots
of buying on the tape here market side.
All right, I'm done with it. I'm done
with it just because of what I've seen.
It can still do more, but I don't want
to be greedy just because of what I've
just seen there. Beautiful. Really nice
trade. So, look how big that was. All we
had to do was wait. This is what I was
saying, Kevin. Just wait. Wait for the
reclaim.
122 points in one, two, three, four,
five, six minutes.
There we go. This is why I'm done with
it because I saw all the buying happen
up here above this high and they got
caught.
Beautiful.
Beautiful. Beautiful.
Nice. Anyone catch that with me? I know
it's all been counter trend today. It's
just cuz I'm not getting the short setup
that I want, unfortunately.
[snorts]
Beautiful. Beautiful. Beautiful.
What gave you the go at the IB low? It's
a reclaim, right? It's a reclaim of IB
low. So, if you look under IB low in
that big kill candle, this candle here,
right? Within that candle, most the
selling took place from 440 to 400.
From 440
40 to 400, right? Most the selling took
place in here. Once we reclaimed, they
started covering. I started watching it
on the tape. So, I'm long here for that
move. I really wanted to get VWOP
because the traditional trade is a look
below initial balance and a trade back
to VWOP. It might still happen, right?
So, I had lots of reasons. Look below
and fail. Reclaim of IB held this even
better. And the sellers were from 440 to
400. I could see it on the book. I can
try and
show you here.
All right. This here
was the strong selling. All right.
Buyers got stuck. Buyers got stuck.
Buyers got stuck. So, I was waiting,
waiting, waiting, waiting because I
didn't know if they'd flush this back
down. But once we traded here, look what
happened. These sellers stopped out.
Boom. It's their pain. I'm always using
someone's pain. Always, always, always
using someone's pain for my move.
There you go. VWAP tag. So, if I was a
bit more patient, would have got it. But
like I said, don't want to be a dick for
a tick. So, that IB to VWAP trade played
out.
Alex, how do I know the most of the
selling was done? Uh, it's it's just
from looking inside the candles or you
can use bookmap. Either or.
Like even if we come here again, it will
all be in the new course. But even in
bookmap,
okay, 440 to 400, right? Was that what
what I said? What was the time there?
just before 11:00 a.m. here. Okay,
look at this guy here. 400 lot average
price 430 or 4 429. Okay, 400 lot,
right? And look at all the selling which
follows. They all follow him in. So if
we think about this guy here, that 400
lot, he's massive size, isn't he? So we
think about all this strong selling,
right? Look at all this selling. There's
your low. That's the end of the auction.
And that's the last seller. No one's
selling under here. Higher low, higher
low, higher low, higher low. You're not
going to see that necessarily on a
candle structure. And then this is this
guy stopping out. All right. So this 400
lot right here starts stopping out into
the initial balance. And there we go.
Squeeze. All right. So everyone who is a
seller under IB got squeezed out. Okay.
And the reason I sold early, what did I
sell? Where did I sell? 1111 was right
up here. So this strong buying buy by by
and we didn't move higher off it. We
started to pull back. So the moment I
saw that transaction, I'm done with
this. I didn't want to sit through a big
old pullback there. A 50 point pullback
there.
[snorts]
Okay, probably done. Probably done with
it now. How long we got left? We got 45
minutes. I don't know. We're starting to
see a range develop here.
All right, remember this range overall
is bearish, right? This is a bearish
move
and a range that is a look below the
range. If they hold this, bulls will try
and look for this. We're not technically
above here for this squeeze out. But if
bulls be hold this, they look for that
move or at least to here. We're still
below VWAP, which is trending down.
Everything is still trending down. I
cannot point that enough. This is a
liquidity building phase. I just don't
want to be short at the lows. Where
would I want to be short? I want to be
short way up here, and it's not going to
let me do that. So, fortunately, this is
why I played counter trend today. It is
what it is. It's just it is what it is.
I can only trade what's in front of me.
Uh yeah, Kevin, I mean, you I don't know
what you use, but on on Trader 8 or uh
on Ninja Trader, even if you're sign up
with a prop firm, it's it's all free on
there. So, on Ninja Trader, what you
want to do is go to your
um here,
right? Go to your candle type, which is
here.
No, it's not there. Where is it? This
one. Data series chart indicators.
Where's my candle? Maybe it's here. Data
series. Yes. You want to change this to
volutric,
right? Volutric instead of like a one
minute volutric. Normally you'd have
candle and then that will give you
right this
[snorts]
uh hopefully before Christmas.
I haven't got too much more to do. I'll
do I'll do some more of it today.
B's still got a chance here, but it's
just development of range now. So, I
would imagine we see more rotation.
This will be the rotation in here for a
while. Major squeeze relief will be
above here, but this will also be where
bull traps live in this zone. So, you
want to be careful. So, you see bulls,
they just held this part of the shelf.
See, we made a new node there. Bulls are
defending this. They're trying to force
this up. This would be a two-leg. If
you're still long in this, you've got to
be selling if you haven't sold something
to be up. Definitely to the top of this
above that, maybe you get a bigger
squeeze out. I don't know. But you want
to be careful. You cannot guarantee that
that's what you're going to get today.
We're in range rotation and the overall
sentiment is lower
battleground here. They're developing
another node here. It's 540 550.
We do have excess above that. So buyers
so far got trapped 560 to 570. That's
where they've been trapped so far today.
Every move into that has been sold into.
Doesn't mean it has to continue to be
sold into. But on that first push today,
that's what we saw. So they're retesting
that same level again. There's been a
passive seller up here so far this
morning. If they can squeeze through
this, you might get your move to the
gray box above. So VW up here. If they
can, it's a big if if you're still long,
but if they can squeeze through this,
you might get the top of the gray box.
But again, you're just in range
rotation. VIX is coming back down to the
bottom side of its range. So
everything's matching up. [snorts]
If you get lucky, you get that move all
the way up into this.
And above that, um, well, who knows?
I blew my Apex EVA. I was long 10 micros
at the 1040 chop. I mean, that's quite a
lot of size. 10 micros for range this
big. Here you go. So, top of the gray
box probably coming up here, folks. Or
top of the gray box. Gray box probably
coming up. If you get above this, this
is GlobeEx. All right. Then it this
whole thing can be a look below and fail
if they start holding and basing above
600. [snorts]
Lots of rotation. Again, fast tape
today, guys. It's a really fast tape.
that your sizing is so key. Like what's
the ATR? ATR has remained around 40
really since the open. It's remained
around 40 as an average since the open.
It's a big ATR. So if you're using 10
micros, you're risking what? 8 $800 per
one minute candle. No matter what,
you only need one or two micros in this.
One or two micros are all you ever need.
I mean, if you got long here,
that's 100 points. That's $200 off one
micro, right? So, if you're in 10,
that's $2,000. If you're on the wrong
side of that, though, it's $2,000 loss,
and you're probably done. So you have to
understand what the potential move is in
front of you, what size account you're
playing, how accurate you are.
Exactly, Mr. Slim. 10 points is $200 and
we're making 100 plus point moves.
Exactly. Still think they want to test
this GlobeEx up here.
Starting to see some relief. Apple green
just insane. Don't get me wrong, I'm
super happy. I'm still long Apple from
202s. I'm very impressed. Very impressed
with it.
And we got left here 40 minutes or so. I
think you're into a big range here.
This is your range.
You want to be careful here that these
can be bull trap areas. Look above and
failed. This is a look below and fail.
If they base here though, you have the
ability to come back up and test this
New York open. Can cannot bet against
that. Like if they're going to keep
doing this, you don't want to get caught
trying to short against it. But if they
look above and fail back under,
especially if they build out
considerable amount of volume here and
then fail under it, you might get that
move back down to there again later in
the day. You just have to see the range
is very very big. All right. 400 points
initial balance. How far out of that did
we trade? We about 450 point range
today.
Take care, Peter. Yeah. Awesome. Awesome
day. Happy with it. Mainly happy with my
um
uh funded next account because I took a
payout yesterday. So, it's always nice
to replenish that payout instantly the
next day. Here's the squeeze up to
GloEx. If you're still long in this,
this is your TP. You got to pay yourself
here. And if you get right up to that
New York opener, you are absolutely
laughing. But here's your TP into
GlobeEx. Okay,
lovely trade off that IB. Really nice.
Really, really nice. Anyone still
holding? Anyone get that move all the
way to Gloveex? Looks good. You might
get a squeeze back to previous week low,
which is the green line just above it.
Looks really good here, folks. This is a
big level. Look left.
Huge level, right? This is a resistance
zone. If we reclaim this, we're going to
try and drift all the way up here. But I
wouldn't be long a new money long here
now. You haven't reclaimed it and based
above. So, you're long from down here or
from here. You're not long up here. Not
a new position. You're managing a
position.
Need to pee again.
Like a racehorse this morning with the
coffee.
Nice. Yeah. If you took if you got any
wins with me today, let me know. It's
always nice to see who who got some of
the wins with me today.
starting to get above this level. Make
sure you're paying yourself here,
please.
Would sales on the inside bar on H1 be
valid? Uh, you mean that bar at 8:00
a.m. this morning? It's an interesting
level. Uh, I wouldn't necessarily sell
it straight away, but if we can trade up
towards it, yes. I mean, there's volume
there. This gray box basically is is
that level. That was your over under.
That's where we chopped around. That's
your inside bar effectively. You're
seeing a squeeze here. Short's about to
get squeezed out. So, your next TP is
basically 43s. That's your opening range
low. And then all the way up into the
New York open. Let me use the bathroom
real quick.
Oh, giant squeeze. [laughter]
Huge squeeze.
Huge squeeze. All right, lower time
frame I'll go. Next through the weekly
is 24hour VW up. Lower time frame algo.
Next stops up into this gray box where
we started the session. Right.
Google now gone green again. Pay
yourself along the way. If you've been
long in this counter trend, you must be
paying yourself.
Made 2,000 long. Nice, Kevin.
Nice. Green, good work. Good work,
everyone.
Winning. I'm up 1,52 days for the first
time ever. Now I'm only two trades a day
instead of multiple trades. That's
awesome. Slow stroke. Good work.
Right. So, you're managing this
position. Remember, this is a squeeze.
It can keep squeezing up, but this is a
squeeze. We lack structure. At some
point, the squeeze will end, the auction
will end, and we will start trading back
downside probably. So, just manage your
position. Do not be chasing this long
side, please. And that also doesn't mean
you should be slamming the short, but
the the move has gone. The move was from
reclaim of IB or for hold of this shelf.
And this is the move. All right. I, as
you know, I sold out in front of VWAP,
but uh this is the full move up and then
you've got New York open and I mean, you
never know. You just never know.
[laughter]
You just never know how far they can go
with this.
The VIX getting destroyed now.
Back down under. It's New York open the
VIX. Where we at on the spy? Spy reclaim
660. QQQ's not reclaimed 600 yet. That's
the big level to watch on the Q's.
Still squeezing and still it goes
higher.
Still it goes higher. The lower time
frame algo this pink line on your chart.
Big old squeeze. What a squeeze. It's
crazy, isn't it? how quickly the chart
moves right now once one side's stuck.
Like I said, it can move very violently.
Even in bare markets, trades upside can
be very, very violent. Like we've talked
about numerous times, we lack structure
here, though. This is the it's trying to
hold VWAP now is what it's attempting to
do. It's going to try and hold VWAP for
a move higher into the New York open
probably if it can, but you know, I
wouldn't be a new money long up here.
The move's gone like we talked about.
It's done. It's done the move. you're
you're managing your position or your
cash like me.
This lower time frame algo causing some
issues for it
that to this VWAP.
Big big level here. They're trying to
soak it for one more attempt higher.
Watching the tape. They're trying to.
They might not be able to, but that's
what they're trying to do.
Just passed my second funding tick
challenge. All thanks to you, Alex. Now
I can get a payout. I will most
certainly be looking to do the course
out. Awesome. Awesome. Congratulations.
You've got to click the buttons. I can
just tell you what I'm reading.
And buy starting to get caught up here.
They're trying to squeeze it higher. If
too many come piling in here, they're
going to get themselves caught at these
highs.
The bull guy maybe bought the dip. Well,
the guy here
very possible. Look at this. Look at
this shift from bearish to uh to bullish
on the delta. Huge shift. Very possible.
I'd say his average price I think he was
around. So he was he was loading here.
He was just passively loading and
loading and loading and loading and
loading and loading and loading. Once we
got back above him, he's comfortable.
He's comfortably in the money now, isn't
he? He's comfortably in the money.
He was no joke, though. I mean he was so
big that P is now his price. It was no
joke.
Latch structure here. They can flush
this very aggressively. So manage your
long position here. Make sure you've
paid yourself. Make sure you've moved
your stop up to someone somewhere
reasonable. If they want to flush this,
they absolutely can. It's a giant short
squeeze this.
So the squeeze started initiating at
420s and then they rewent from 530s and
580s. So your 200 250 point short
squeeze out here.
This is a good area where they can trap
balls honestly into these kind of areas.
It's a good area where they can trap
balls because we're above this pivot.
So, lots of breakout balls have come in
back in here. If they slam this door,
like I said, if they slam this door,
this trade becomes available.
Don't think I'm going to trade it. I
think I'm done. I've got to be happy
with [snorts] I've made money today. But
just be aware. That's all I'm saying.
Nice Prrisca.
Nice Wrath. Great work.
Still, they're still soaking VW up. They
want that New York open and previous day
low by the looks of it. They want to get
back into this gray box. But like I
said, this is a good area. This area is
an area where they track can track
balls. The bulls from down here will be
looking to complete the rotation to
here. If they get very lucky up here,
bears will want this area here to do
this rotation back down to trap bulls
above this. Right? If they're looking
for this, they would want that. That's
the battle right now. I wouldn't be uh
new positioning a thing right now. Just
let this do what it wants. You got 25
minutes left. Most of you were long off
the IB. I think
you look good.
We're in Golden Zone. Yeah, I'm sure we
are. It's a big It's a big old push, but
there's still targets both above and
below. I just let this sort of do
whatever it is it's got to do
cuz it's uh a very fast moving market
like we've discussed.
Just close this door a second.
Back to the VWAP.
Like I said, this can be a bull trap
area up here. It wouldn't surprise me
because we're in breakout.
So, how they act under this gray box
becomes important. This shelf here
Still trying to absorb.
We can do another gray box. Now
build one here.
Shelf in here. You can see it
developing.
trying to get another squeeze. They're
trying to get up to that open.
They want to get up into here if they
can.
Big Delta 55s or 50s.
Where's he gone?
Mo so quick. Yeah, some offside delta at
55.
Is X working again now? Oh, it is. Looks
like it is. Fantastic.
They're trying to complete it. They're
trying to complete that rotation opening
range
back into the opening range. Back into
the New York open print. This would be
if we get back above [laughter] this.
It would be a look below New York and
fail. So, so far we're looking below
GlobeEx and failing. There's your big W.
Any hold of this? They're looking for a
bullish rotation back up and a giant
short squeeze right now.
Cuk still not over that 600 yet though.
See a big level.
[snorts]
Yeah, they're all most of them down. Um,
but X seems to be back up. Let me see if
TPT is back up.
TPT is back up. Let me see if Apex is
back up.
Not sure Apex is back up. Can't get Apex
at the moment. So TPT seems okay. Maybe
they're just
the Cloudflare thing. One one thing at a
time maybe at the moment.
Yeah, I can't get Apex, but TPT seems to
be okay.
Traify
is okay. Funded next is okay.
Hopefully they're uh they're probably I
would imagine Apex will probably extend
the sale if there's having problems.
Okay, so next TP coming up. This gray
box up here is your next TP. And
[laughter] then I mean, my gosh, can
they go for IB high? You can't rule it
out. [laughter]
You can't rule it out,
right? They're just trying to absorb
this gray box to get into this one now.
Crazy how quickly that tape flipped.
That delta flipped at these lows down
here. Biggest delta of the day, right at
lower day, sell data, delta, and then we
flipped and then that was it.
Massive battle. It's crazy. The size of
these candles is just bonkers to me. It
is bonkers to me. Back to view up again.
How long we got till lunch? 20 minutes.
You've got time. They've got time to
complete the rotation. 20 minutes here.
They're
trying to soak be what? I would be very
cautious here. If you were long, you
better have paid yourself. You better
have paid yourself if you were long.
We're coming back down to previous week
low here. This line you can barely see
on the screen, but it is there. Let's
make this a bit brighter, shall we?
Let's make this [snorts]
like that.
So trying to see if they can soak
previous week low. But you better have
paid yourself.
[snorts]
Squeeze in again. Crazy
tape. So quick. Vick's trying to find a
bounce. So VIX traded all the way back
down to previous day high. It's trying
to find a bid at New York open. So VIX
to give you an idea of how fast we've
moved. We opened today at 2375.
We pushed all the way up to 2584. We're
back at 2375. It's still incredibly
elevated. We're not in the teens. All
right. VIX is dangerous up here. Very
dangerous up here.
You can see this rotation in this gray
box now
down a bit.
Building out volume here for whatever it
is they want to do next. You got to wait
for them to leave these areas now.
Yeah. Make sure you're zooming out. Look
at this H1. We're just trading all the
way back into where we've been stuck.
Uh where are you guys here? Right, just
think about this.
Right, this was a breakdown. Bare flag.
Bare flag. Bare flag. Bare flag.
Breakdown. We're coming up to retest
this area. Key area, right? If they get
through this, maybe a squeeze out is
possible. Previous day value area low.
Who knows? But so far, it's bearish,
isn't it? Right. So, it's counter trend
up. We expect it to be sold into. If
they reclaim, can think about something
else. But we expect this move from
technical standpoint to be sold into.
Is it a look above and fail? It's not.
No. What's it looked above and failed?
It's not looked above anything and
failed in intraday. We're above GloEx.
It's bel look below globeex. If it holds
this, it's a look below and failed
gloss. It's inside
IB. It's potentially rotation, right?
Maybe we get this. Maybe we get this.
But we're inside the rotation at the
moment.
And previous day low is still up here.
So we've reclaimed previous week. How we
ated daily levels is important. Now, I
wouldn't say there's much edge here.
What should you do now? Just sit still.
Sit still. In my opinion,
I wouldn't want to be long here. And I
don't think there's a short setup yet.
You're building volume, right?
Building volume after a squeeze. I don't
want to be long up here. Remember, we
were long here. I don't want to be short
here. It's not shown me this or this. I
don't think there's anything to do here.
It's probably a no trade zone. Probably
going to be a no trade zone until lunch
to be honest.
[snorts]
Oh,
okay. Just a reminder those interested,
I know I've got to get the artwork up.
Um, everything on flone uhtrader.com is
on sale currently, 25% off. So, if you
want to do the course, you want to do
the indicators, you want to buy the
indicators, you want the indicators for
Ninja Trader or Trading View, everything
is 25% off. Code BF, it is first come,
first served. I will get some social
posts out this week with it all. But is
limited numbers for Black Friday. Code
BF. And those interested in Apex, if it
loads up, they have a 80% sale on at the
moment with $40 activation fee. Uh, code
FCT for that.
They are trying. They're desperate to
get back to that New York open and
previous day low. That's what they're
trying to do. Trying to force their way
up there.
Here they go. Big buyer stepping in
there. Not moving higher yet. So, he got
caught there on 700 so far. Haven't
moved away from him, but it was a big
transaction up there.
I'm just waiting. I don't think I'll get
another trade today.
>> [snorts]
>> um like not not on mic but I type out
what I'm looking at ahead of time uh for
laidback
and I do voice notes. So like if there's
a trade I'm looking at I will let them
know what I'm looking at, the levels I'm
looking at, what I'm seeing on the tape.
It's the same as you get here, but
normally not necessarily on mic because
often I'm on the move.
Big battle here in this gray box.
I do I chart on a time frame. Yeah, M1
for me.
I wouldn't advise you start with M1
though again I'll go through all of this
stuff in the course but
I've been training a long long time
folks so I can read tape pretty
efficiently but takes time to train your
eyes and your brain what you're seeing
exhausted
It's trying to base out here.
We're just hanging out in this gray box
at the moment.
Mr. Gray box. We're just hanging out in
above previous week low. That green
line. VWOP is the do. This is your
previous week low. This is your VWAP.
This is lower time frame algo. This is
previous day low. This is New York open.
If we start leaving this liquidity, you
might get more of a drastic move. But
every time we've moved down, they've
saved previous week low. So far,
we are starting to leave or attempt to
leave some of that volume above. But
again, it's previous week low here,
GlobeEx below. Those can still be saved.
This green box, the rotation can happen
between these two boxes here.
can be like a pullback that holds this.
Bulls can defend this and try and go
higher. So, this can be one of these
into here and then they can try and
reclaim this to go higher. If bears
defend this, the rotation happens here.
If bears defend this, there's a bigger
rotation in my mind. So, it's why I
think the GlobeEx level and that other
gray box is a little bit more important
uh for bears if they're going to take
control otherwise. I think it's still
available for a higher squeeze at the
moment. There you go. like that [snorts]
because they're defending the previous
week. So, at the moment, I'd say weekly
traders are telling us we don't want to
move. We want to defend. Bulls are
saying we want to defend the weekly
level. This level right here. We're not
looking to move underneath this level
right here. This level right here. We do
not want to move underneath this level
right here. Didn't know you could do
that. That's pretty cool. [snorts]
Did you put a buy order on the IB recap?
No, I just I joined as soon as I saw it,
mate. I didn't want to leave it there. I
actually had to mark it in. It left so
quickly.
Uh, are the Ninja Trader Indicators
included when you buy the course? No,
they're they are an upgrade. If you go
if you go on the website and you go and
buy the course, it will offer you the
upgrade and you still get 25% off them.
Hilx the indicator package automatically
marks out the charts correct. So initial
balance opening range globeex
previous day levels previous week levels
everything all done automatically
out goes all of that stuff.
All right, battleground here. The
rotation in this gray box is going to
keep going and going and going like we
talk about until they've got one side
stuck.
I don't think there's edge at the moment
in this market.
Don't think there's not edge yet. It
will develop. Uh maybe in lunch, maybe
after lunch.
What I'd say at the moment,
there is significant buyer trapped in
this wick up here with size.
Yeah, twice. So, there's about two to
300 lots caught up there so far. At the
lows,
we have seen some selling into the lows
and not moved lower. So, it's just a
range.
Buyers caught the highs, sellers caught
the lows. So far, back to this previous
week low again. This is where they
defended the last few times and we've
squeezed off it.
Uh
yeah, Sean, I mean, I don't think I can
teach you to read orderflow on the next
five minutes that I'm here, mate. But uh
I I will release some content soon on
it.
>> [sighs]
>> Bears trying to leave that volume, but
it's very dangerous here with that
weekly level,
which they keep soaking off the bulls.
I don't think bears take control until
we're back under this this gray box. To
be honest, I think this can keep
squeezing. I wouldn't be entering long
here, but what I'm seeing here is not
bearish control. Not yet.
Um,
yo, let's go. I'm burnt out. Had my
first red day in three weeks. Went semi
tilt. I'm a break. Get the course and
dig in. Nice. Look forward to working
with you. Alex, as you are bearish, why
do we
British? Why do we pay in dollars? I I
live in America, my friend. I live in
Los Angeles. I'm English, but this is
where I live.
So yeah, it's uh very early for me. It's
8:52 in the morning still.
Nice Sean. Yeah,
keep turning up mate. It would get it
would get easier. But yeah, I would
agree. It's that ultimate edge, but it
just takes time.
Oh, still trying to defend that previous
week low, that green line, that
horizontal green line. They're trying to
defend that. Bears are trying to defend
that gray box above. I just think this
will be a wash and chop for a while now.
We've had some huge moves in this market
today. Huge, huge, huge moves in the
market. You would have seen earlier I
was just like, whoa, whoa, whoa. I'm
this is crazy. Insane size. Leave it
alone for a bit. So,
it's cooling off now for a minute, which
is not necessarily [laughter] a bad
thing, right? Just let it cool off for a
minute. Let it make some decisions.
>> [sighs]
>> Just reading some of the comments from
the bed here.
Barkin saying he's worried about
exposure to bank banks to private
credit.
Housing supply still constrained. Yeah.
No one's got the money to [\h__\h] build
them anymore.
All right, they're trying to force this
squeeze. Bulls just defended that
previous week low, that horizontal line.
So weekly, bulls are trying to defend
this horizontal line. They're trying to
get a squeeze out to this New York high
and previous day low and this gray box
through that. Can't rule out a gap fill.
It's absolute madness, I know, but
that's the kind of day we're in. You
cannot rule out a gap fill.
>> [laughter]
>> caught short off 89. I mean, uh, you
were in here. I mean, I think I think
bulls are starting to take control of
the market right now. So, I think you
could be in trouble. That's my thought.
They would have to defend 700. You have
bulls are def are stuck above 86 on that
wick, right? We do have excess there,
but the moment you break that, you're
going to get a short covering rally.
was 10k down across all accounts with
the morning chop. I wor my up to 2k
green. I'm going to get greedy and
probably hands off rest of the day.
Yeah, if you were down that much and
you've got greens, walk away. Never sit
here and continue to trade.
Friday, Monday, Tuesday sat on my hands
for explosive moves only to get wicked
out playing reverse counter trends.
Can't win them all. Hey, sorry to hear
that, buddy. Yeah, it's it's tough
sometimes. Sometimes it can be tough. I
really wanted to short. You know that
this is the thing for me. I really
wanted to short. I didn't this wasn't
enough for me. This hunt above here. I
wanted to get above these players here
and then I would have been interested.
Like a little gap fill reversal would
have been amazing this morning. But uh
you know if we could have done this or
even into value, defended value,
defended this, I would have loved that
short. All right, that's an A+ setup for
me. But unfortunately they they didn't
bring it. More balls got caught up in
there again. I don't know who was just
asking about that, but uh all the time
they're protecting Where's this player
on the tape? All the time they're
protecting
85, you look okay. But uh the moment
they reclaim 85, I'd be very concerned
for you guys who are short.
It's just a rotation at the moment. But
85 is your level. This looks more
bullish to me. I'm going to be honest.
It is an area where they can trap balls,
but that 85, they've caught them twice,
but
you're coming into lunch. I don't know.
Who knows, folks? Like, I can only tell
you what I see. I'm not going to sit
here and tell you what's going to
happen. I have no idea.
CBD is going up, but no follow through.
Yeah, but it's been going up since
10:00. I mean, you had divergence from
10 to 11, right? And then, and then we
put in the pivot. I mean, this is why I
don't pay too much attention to CBD. I
pay more attention to what's happening
within each candle.
Mix is looking like wants to bear flag
down at the moment. I'm starving, man.
I'm going to eat. Going to eat. Eat.
Eat.
Oh, sorry folks. Tired here.
Long day.
I'm taking Friday off by the way team.
Uh I might do the morning briefing for
you for like 30 minutes, but uh I've got
a flight to catch Friday, so I won't be
here to stream with you for long on
Friday. Just a heads up for that.
Uh, same in Discord. I I'll be on a
flight. So, I'll do my best.
Okay. They defended that level again.
What did we say it was? 80. Was it 85?
Was the high up here?
Yeah, they defended 85. That buyer, it's
this buyer here. He's stuck above 85. I
can see him stuck above 85. They've
defended it a few times. The moment that
breaks though, I think you get a squeeze
out. So, just be aware. I know some of
you are short right now. I'm obviously
I'm not in a position on cash right now.
Just waiting.
So, I don't think I don't think I'm take
another trade today. I think the A+ is
probably gone.
You see how we're starting? We're right
at we're right back. This is why you got
to be careful
underneath daily Ballinger bands, right?
We don't like trading underneath daily
Ballinger bands. We come right back to
it. Very rare that you find acceptance
below, right? You see wick below and go
up. We wick above. I mean, this did
close outside, but most the time you
will not get follow through outside.
Daily Ballinger bands is very rare. Look
at this. Like prime example, big push
push above, close back inside.
The market does not like trading beyond
two standard deviation. This was the
April low. Even at the April low, we
didn't move below for long. three days
and remember that is a black swan event
with the tariffs and we still did not
like trading below the daily Ballinger
bands. Got to be aware of that. Have to
have to have to be aware of that.
Thought I could give you guys so much
edge in this stream for free. Honestly,
Alex, I'm officially in the course.
Looking forward to learning trading with
you. Is there a video on how to
load the flow zones into Ninja Trader?
Yes, my friend. If you just bought it,
um,
in the if you open the Ninja Trader
course up, should uh there should be
like a script there that tells you
everything, if not a video, might be
both.
You have to apply
um
for the download once you buy the Ninja
Trader Script. apply for the download.
Um, and then I have to accept you and
then
follow the instructions with your
machine ID and everything else.
Still rejecting in front of 85. Still
building so much liquidity out here. If
we're here too much longer, you will
probably see a PC flip. Let's have a
look. It's getting close. It's getting
close to flipping point of control up
here. Getting close. [snorts]
Being on quantile, do I lose some of the
content or can I apply most of them or
twist? Yeah, you can. You can apply most
of them on Quantau, mate.
I don't have a script for Quantau, but
you can apply all the same thesis onto
there and I can look to build you one if
it's if it's helpful for you. Okay,
[snorts] back towards this. Remember
85s. If you reclaim 85s here, anyone
who's short, I think you will get
squeezed out. 85 is the level that is
their pain point for the buyers above.
If they if shorts cannot defend 85, I
think you will see a squeeze out here.
So, I'm just trying to make you aware.
Be very careful. This is your shelf
here.
[snorts] The squeeze out from here can
be nasty because you've been here a
considerable amount of time. Same as the
drop. If you get the drop, but once we
built this much liquidity, remember
we've been here from 11 over 30 minutes,
40 minutes, this can get real nasty
either way. There's 385. You're going to
see the squeeze now, folks. I If you
were short, you you want to cut this. I
would not even risk this high because if
that gets done, you're toast. It goes
very very quick.
massive battle. But I I personally would
be done with this if you were looking
for that short rotation back down. You
can always add back in. If you stopped
out there, you can always add back in
when you see what you want. But this is
just a nasty rotation and people are
going to get hurt
if it crosses 685. Yeah. I mean, very
potentially comes up to New York open,
right?
very potentially comes up to here if
they if they've just popped that and
failed it underneath here. Really got to
watch this previous week low. But this
level here, bears take more control
under this box.
I think bulls have
I don't know. I don't know what to say.
I don't think there's a lot of edge
here, but I think bulls have the ability
to squeeze out here into lunch. That's
what I'd be very concerned about. I in
here. I haven't seen us leave this,
reject this, leave this, reject this.
Looking for that short. That's where I'd
be interested in the short. If it leaves
aggressively this volume and does this,
I'm not into like picking tops, right?
We're in a short squeeze. Flow zones are
trading upside. We're building volume.
We have liquidity above it can aim for.
I'm not into trying to trade the top of
this range. That's way too risky. I
haven't seen us leave this range. So,
for me, it's not a short. It might
develop into a short, but for me at the
moment, it's not a short. It's also not
a long I take. It's a nothing.
It's a nothing.
I mean,
bulls really should have squeezed
through 85 there and they didn't.
It's looking kind of gross. How long
have we got till lunch? Oh, we're into
lunch. I didn't even realize. Well, that
explains a few things.
Yeah, it's it's done. Volume will
dissipate now. As you can see, look,
volume's dissipating. Unless you get a
breakout, the volume's done. We're done.
I didn't even realize we're into lunch
already. My bad.
>> I had no idea.
I had no idea. All right, I'm getting
out of here. Time to eat some food. Go
for a walk. Get off the screens. Uh, be
careful rest of the day. Be very, very
careful. This is a
nasty, nasty, nasty market. All right,
this is what I'm seeing right now. This
is your protrend. This is the breakdown.
We have not retested these areas up here
which were locations I'd want to be
short. Think about the main trend. This
is the main trend. Okay. If a very very
big if if bulls are able to defend this
maybe they can come and run some of
this. I mean it would be really nasty.
But if there was a short covering rally
you would see that if bull if bears can
defend this edge here. You can see this
rotation back into here and this can
build out here. And if you build
liquidity here there's still room to
come lower. But we have excess down
there. So you're in a rotational market.
There's your IB high. There's your IB
low. You are in a rotational market. You
are not in a trending market in terms of
intraday. All right. You are in a
rotational market between IB high and IB
low. And it's violent.
All right. You're 402
uh points for your IB. Remember a normal
IB is about 120 points or something. So
you're 402 points. and VIX is starting
to try and push back upside here. So,
just be careful if you're going to hang
out here the rest of the day. Um, those
in Discord, I'll chat to you in a bit
and we we'll see what we get set up for
this afternoon. Remember, the main trend
is lower, but uh shorts definitely got
caught those lows today. And you're just
going to you're just going to have to
let this build out its liquidity because
it's run a lot of people out of the
market, both sides. This is your level
here. this this level here. That's your
level where they're going to make the
decisions. All right, folks. Big love.
Catch you guys tomorrow. Those in
Discord, uh let me go and get a walk and
make some food and do all the good stuff
and then uh we'll see what we can get
after lunch if there's something good.
All right. Peace and love all the new
students. See you in there soon.