Morning
team.
Welcome back. Happy Monday. Hope you all
had a good weekend.
Hopefully you read the uh weekly
newsletter so you're prepared for this
week and the key levels because we've
got lots to go through this week. Lots
of news coming back into the week.
Remember the government back to work.
Nvidia earnings,
Japan 10 years starting to break out
putting sellside pressure on this market
and uh we are opening up in a very very
interesting part based on the yearly
profile and the last few weeks. So let's
go over it now as always starting on the
daily time frame. In fact, let's start
on the weekly time frame because it's a
new week. You can see right now opening
up
oh it's a bit of drastic right opening
up inside the previous week. When we
think about that previous week's range,
we go from top or from bottom to top.
Wakey wakey trading view. All right,
we're trading reacted. This is basically
a 61 retracement and we're sitting right
in that pocket at the moment. If we look
at the yearly profile, the profile that
we've built out this level here has been
a pretty decent support level so far on
this year. Here, if we move down into a
daily, you can see that same area is
where we found bids on Friday and the
Friday before as well. So, this is your
thick area into 700s. Surprise, surprise
into 700s. All right, and this is the
old range rotation that we did back in
September and October. All right, this
was our range rotation set 700 to 25K
before we broke out. We're coming back
and retesting that. We are bearish in
this retest at the moment. Now, it's
possible bulls can take control. So far,
I'm not seeing enough to tell me that
they've taken control. I would need to
see bulls pivot over here, leaving bears
trapped there for a Santa Claus rally
into the new year. That's what we would
normally expect coming into November and
December. Um, hedge funds have not made
their money this year. Remember, retail
has been net long. Hedge funds have been
net cash. So, they're very upset. So,
one thing to be aware of is regardless
of structure, if hedge funds start
turning this on, well, that's what
they're going to look for if they really
want really want to make their money.
However, macro news is not looking good.
We have Nvidia earnings on Wednesday and
right now on the daily, very simply,
overnight, we've had a look above and
fail. All right, we're not going to pay
too much attention to it, but that is
one of the trades that I was looking for
today, as you would know in the weekly
newsletter, that look above and fail for
retest back to here. If we see sustained
pressure, we need to build out time
because time will allow this to start
expanding and the 5day to come down with
it if we're truly truly going to be
bearish. All right, so so far opening up
inside if we move down into the hourlys.
All right, what we need to pay attention
to
is where we are based on the previous
week and previous days. All right. So,
here's your previous week profile from
sun the previous Sunday all the way out.
Right now, we're opening up underneath
previous week value area low with a look
above in this little pocket and this
thick area. So, we just failed in
London. All right. In this pocket, a
very nice failure in that pocket. Now,
failing
previous week value area low coming down
to test the week before it. All right.
We have to be aware of this. This is a
sensitive level that we're now trading
in. We can create range rotation in here
because we have
this liquidity, this liquidity, and
Friday liquidity. All right, this is a
sensitive area. If this lets go, all
right, what am I thinking about? Well,
I'm very clearly I'm going to think
about this. If we start letting go, I
think about this. But the ideal location
for that short was up here. This is the
worst location. Unfortunately, we are
opening up right in this sort of
potential support worst location. don't
really want to get short there. I'd
rather see a breakdown retest stay heavy
if I'm going to short that otherwise up
here. So, we need to be aware of the
previous week's rotation. All right. Any
hold above sort of 250 260 is it there?
Yeah, 280. All right. Might see a
bullish move back to 500. So, we don't
want to see bulls get above that and
hold or if you're a bear, you don't. If
we're going to see that, then we're
looking for a long back into here and
probably a short from down there because
we're still inside a rotation. All
right, we're still inside a rotation.
Friday's rotation. All right, decent
squeeze out on Friday, I don't think it
was anything more than a squeeze out.
All right, if you look at the inflows on
Friday, it was poor. There wasn't a lot
of buying it. It wasn't a broad market,
you know, it just it was a squeeze out.
That was it. It was shorts covering. All
right, we did eventually get this in
Discord together, which was nice. Or at
least everyone else in my Discord while
I was walking Luna got it. And we have
to be aware of these levels, don't we?
All right,
previous day value area high, value area
low. Like we said, we're trading near
the previous week value area lows and
the week before that value area lows.
So, we can ro range rotate in here. This
might look like nothing, but this is
984.
So, we're looking at 300 point range
rotation in here. That's what we're
looking at at the moment, folks, is a
300 point range rotation. If we do this,
maybe we get lucky and get a retest. But
unfortunately, the best location when
we're in range rotation would have been
short here, which was given beautifully
to London traders. If we look up here,
this was very, very nice. All right,
this is very nice up here. And think
about this one leg, two leg failure back
down to here. Can we trade under or do
we cla reclaim and do this for the rest
of the day? Those are the two things
that I'm thinking about at the moment.
So, I don't want to carry too much bias
into this because location is not good.
You can see since London, this is pretty
much a straight move downside. All
right. Unfortunately, that it is what it
is. That's what we the cards we've been
dealt with on a Monday morning.
Okay. So, you know what I'm looking for?
Let's have a look at this. Right. This
gray area is just the little bump that
we had from D
the edge of
sort of uh Sunday, Monday, Friday from
the 7th. So, two weeks ago, not last
week, the week before. So, I'm watching
that. All right, let's have a look at
the cues and the spiders because they're
actually pretty easy to see right now.
Right. What I would be looking at, SPY
has two big levels here. 70 and 72 were
the big options levels. All right. If
start letting go of that with failure,
you're probably going to see a rotation
back down towards 666. All right. If
they hold 70s and reclaim 72s, then
there's probably a squeeze upside. So,
you can set price alerts on those if you
want. For Q's, the big level was the
600. That was your put wall. We opened
up under it. They reclaimed it. I don't
know if they've moved that gamma coming
into uh today, but we we'd have to see.
Uh filled this old gap, which we can now
get rid of. Thanks very much. See you
later. All right, so Q's
very much the same thing as we talked
about on NQ. Oh, don't do that.
In a range rotation, you can see here's
Friday squeeze up. We're opening up
inside of this. I'd say if a fail is
here, there's probably trade back down.
You can see maybe a look below and fail
for the trade back upside. So, range
rotation until it proves otherwise.
Dixie continues to drift higher. Okay,
trying to find a bid off those lows
and possible push right back into here.
One thing I do want to look at is this
10y year and 30year.
How's that reacted? Yeah, we're starting
to find that bid I'm concerned about in
this green box, right? The big level is
way way higher, but it is starting
to find that bid. If this starts
breaking out,
I get very worried for this market. 30
years strong.
Okay. Anyway, we'll keep an eye on that.
All right. Apple, let's go through the
mag. How we doing for time?
Not too bad. Apple gapping down. All
right. Weaker on new a little bit of
news this morning. What was it right
here? Bur B B B B B B B B B B B B B B B
B B B B Burkshire and Hway cut it Apple
stake from 915 million to 238 million.
You're going to see this a lot. Uh
Warren has taken a huge position in
Google a couple weeks ago and sold most
of the rest of his portfolio at the
moment sitting cash. So Apple starting
to sell a little bit off that news.
Amazon slight gap up inside previous
days range. So Apple week, Amazon inside
previous days range. Nothing really to
see there. Google probably strong off
that Birkshire news. Yes. All right. So
people just starting to see that. It did
come out here, but maybe people didn't
really read it. All right, so there's
your news. Any pullbacks that hold,
we're going to see continued rotation.
Remember, this has all started from when
they got rid of that uh financial
decision when they were trying to cut up
the company into uh different different
levels saying they had the monopoly on
YouTube, etc., etc., and they and
they've let them off and now we're in a
breakout. So relative strength in Google
and some of the market or the big
players in the market starting to buy
into it. Meta
still weak. All right. Inside previous
days range. This is very much like the
cues. If it can't reclaim this for the
squeeze, we come back and revisit this.
I'm not convinced we're quite done yet
on meta, but we will see. Microsoft that
looks pretty good. That looks pretty
good compared to some of the others. All
right. Range rotation push up Friday.
Can it hold to complete that move?
Remember, it's had relative weakness
since the earnings, right? So, it's just
a bid up since the earnings. But, uh, if
they fail to reclaim here,
this is failure, failure, failure, and
new lows coming. So, intraday looks okay
pre-market, but I'd be quite concerned
if I was holding a swing long in that.
Nvidia week, remember earnings coming on
Nvidia on Wednesday. You have uh people
selling a lot of their positions. All
these big whales talking about they've
cut 70% of their positions in Nvidia.
Um, Michael Bur's got a big short
position out on Nvidia after closing his
fund, but a personal short position out
on Nvidia.
We'll have to see what happens
Wednesday. All right, this is all to do
with Wednesday. Are we trimming profits
before Wednesday or does Wednesday start
the bigger move and the crash or are we
going to sell off before Wednesday and
find a bid Wednesday with some outlier
earnings? Who knows? All to play for.
all to play for at the moment, but we
have to be aware of that coming into
Wednesday after hours. Tesla
not too bad pulling back after that big
drive up on uh Friday, but if we look at
the rest of the week, we've broken down.
The question is, does it hold range for
a retest of this level or are we just
going to see weakness?
So, overall, MAG isolate slightly weaker
outside of Google right now. Let's have
a look at these other ones affected.
Oracle
gapping down. AMD probably gapping down
off in video. Yes.
Okay. So, Netflix at quarter bid yet?
Not really.
Split is done. Is it? Is that just done
it split? Okay. Interesting. Wonder if
they rally off that or not.
Okay.
How we doing for time? Four minutes
left.
So yeah, very aware of the range
rotation today. I would have loved to
have been short up here and it's a
perfect location for the short for that
look above and failure. I don't really
love being short here to have to come
underneath and fail.
So location is everything. I do think
we're uh slightly more bearish overall,
but very very possible that today is
nothing more than rotation. We might see
that folks for a couple days, maybe all
the way into uh into Wednesday. Yes,
VIX. Uh, we didn't talk about that, did
we? Uh, currently trading at 21s. Um,
dangerous, dangerous times for those on
the VIX. Uh, it's not a a net long risk
on right now in this market. All right,
let's get through the good mornings.
Haven't done that for a while. Morning
Clint, Chris, Inferrisk, DJ, Frank,
Sylum, Jesse, Troy, Peter, Marrick, Full
Forward, Brandon, ET, John, Dennis,
Toby, Gar, Thumper, AB, Mark, Lifetime,
Dogee,
Oaken, Larry, Otus, Charles, Dojon,
Contorted, Patrick, Jonathan, Erf, Mike,
Three Bar Reversal, Calypso, Beu, Green,
Eva, Rosco, Raphael, Alio, Toby, Miguel,
Cat, Lindle, Red Plasma, LJ, Mr. Slim,
Peter, Lauren, JJ, Prrisca, Jacob,
Stefan, Dex, Cobbs, and Bradley. Good
morning everyone. Do me a favor, smash
that like button nice and early. Let's
get it out the way. And for all those
just joining, welcome, welcome, welcome.
Seeing this market add pressure here
early this morning, it's just we've lost
location. It's uh very very unfortunate,
but this is unfortunately powered it. So
trading into that previous day value
area low right now
and uh demand down here. We could pull
this up so it matches.
What a shame. What a shame. This this
push up here. Any of you that traded
this morning, you should have had a bit
of fun. That was a nice obvious rotation
off value. Like really clean off value.
Look above and fail. These are all the
things that you want to look for folks,
right? Look above value when we're in a
range rotation and fail. And there is
your short and short and all the way
back down to the other side. Right? And
this is your cover point here. And now
you're holding runners just to see if at
the market open they want to dump you
down to here. You'd be very happy people
if if you get that. But for me, well,
I've missed it. It's it's happened in
London. It's happened in London.
So, one minute left here, folks.
See what we get.
Yeah, the VIX's looking pretty uh
pretty dangerous right now. Put in a
sort of double bottom versus Friday's
lows gapping up and it's got those
previous day highs at 23 if it does
really want to go for it. But otherwise,
we're just going to go in a rotation
between PDL, PDC, and PDH on the VIX as
well. But if we go in a rotation up
here, it's uh well, let's just say it's
dangerous. Let's just put it that way.
It's very dangerous.
So, not looking to trade out the gate.
If they flush this out the gate, they're
going to probably do it without me.
But, uh, yeah, all time frames currently
bearish, selling down, but we're in a
bit of a range, but overall momentum's
been bearish.
So, good luck, folks. If you're one of
the people that's looking to trade the
open, here you go. There's your opening
print.
So all of the mag gapping down other
than Google which is 350%
up right now like we talked about
Burkshire and Hatheraway Warren Buffett
buying into that selling his position in
Apple buying into Google that happened
probably he probably started buying
straight after that uh
uh decision from the courts to allow
them to keep everything together
and their cloud company and YouTube and
everything else that they open.
So, flushing down here. You might get
followed through all the way down. We'll
have to see. Google's still running
upside.
And this is going to be tough because
I've lost location. All right. Into a
little bit of a bump here. This is where
we started to find a little bit of a bid
on Friday into these uh 60s down to
900s. So, if you were short, I would say
it wouldn't be a bad idea to cover a
little bit here.
There was a little bump here on Friday.
There you go. They're starting to cover
into it. So, probably should mark that
out. It's right here. You can see this
cluster here where we found a bump
on the profile right there. There you
go.
I'm actually going to remove that one.
Just give this a chance to settle down.
still pushing
now 3.80%
up. Very impressive. Rest of the market
still in a sell right now. I can give
you a readout. Uh Tesla 0.12% down.
Nvidia 2 and a half% down. Microsoft
0.40%
down. Meta 0.66% down. Amazon 0.27%. 27%
down. Apple 1.85% down. Google 4.18% up.
That thing is absolutely ripping faces.
Right. And there you go. So that bump
off uh Friday catching a bid so far.
We've already gone through the New York
open. Where's my New York open print.
Why am I not seeing that? Is it because
I'm not on a one minute? There we go. So
already through the New York open print.
Coming back to potentially close this
gap straight away, I would say. Then we
can see what we do. But already
reclaiming previous day value area low.
So look below and fail. So potential
range rotation back up previous day
point of control, previous day value
area high after a gap fill. I'm not
particularly interested in this market
right now. I think it's uh somewhat
dangerous in this market at the moment.
I think we're going to go into major
range rotation.
That trigger through New York open. That
was probably your long while I was
giving you that readout. But there we
go.
Let's see. 2070. See if catches a bid
there. So, you're probably going to gap
fill here.
It's good for a gap fill here at the
moment.
Sorry folks, just having to change a few
settings in trading view.
Okay, Spiders just found a bid off was
that the 50-day
off the 50-day on the spiders
and uh same on the cues by the looks of
it.
Yes,
just giving this a chance to shake out
at the moment.
So coming up for gap fill reclaimed uh
New York low and the blue line next to
the previous day value area low. So look
below and fail just like we had at the
top side. So think about what we did in
London. We looked above previous day
value area high failed. We came back
down to the other side of value. Look
below it failed. This is uh hinting to
you that we're going to go into range
rotation. All right. We're trading
between each edge from Friday based on
value. So we're in a range rotating
market. It's telling you we're in a
range rotation market because it's
looked both sides and failed. Until we
get outside of that and we start, you
know, staying bullish or staying heavy
outside of it, then we will remain in a
liquidity building process, which as you
well know are my least favorite trades.
That's what we did for most of the time
last week. This is how we build
liquidity for bigger moves. And it would
not surprise me, folks, if we do this
all the way until Nvidia earnings. It
really wouldn't. if they want to build
liquidity out for the next three
sessions, it wouldn't surprise me.
So nice and calm. Remember last week
strong sell week. We started breaking
down. Overall,
I'm uh leaning bearish in this market at
the moment until it proves otherwise.
But within the intraday, we have to play
what's in front of us. I'm not bearish
intraday at the moment. I'm neutral or
range rotation. I'm bearish in the
higher time frames and neutral in range
rotation overall. Right.
Some in this market trying to grab a bid
here. Wow. Google 5.25% up. That's
insane. Everyone finds out Buffett's
bought it and they're like, "Oh, we'll
buy it." You know, you're probably
buying it 50 points late, but okay, you
do what you want. Retail. Um, so I'll
give you a read out. Tesla's 0.35%
up now. Nvidia 1.61% down. Uh,
Microsoft's gone green 0.17% up. Meta
0.84% down. Like I said, Google 5.40%
up, Amazon half a percent down, and
Apple 1.65%
uh down. So, you got complete mixed bag
there. Uh one, two, three of them green,
four of them red. The big winner, Google
dragging the market up. VIX trading back
downside right now, testing that sort of
key level that we just talked about
where it found a bump, but again, it can
very well go in rotation just like this
market.
Okay, so where are we looking at? Well,
previous week value area low currently
sitting at 25180. Previous day point of
control currently sitting at 25160.
Those are probably some interesting
levels. We've got an old VWOP up there,
24-hour VWAP and lower time frame. So,
we're probably bullish in a rotation up
to there. And then if it's going to
reclaim, we're probably going to go all
the way up to previous day value high to
be quite honest because we've gone
straight down like we talked about
lacked structure. How we operate here
and here now become important. But I
would say you're better off playing the
edges. That was probably while I was
giving you the readouts. Unfortunately,
that was your buy opportunity. Sorry,
folks. Happened so quick this morning.
And if you did buy it, then you want to
be locking in some profits as we move
towards this previous day point of
control. So, uh 160, 180, those are big
levels. If you get consistent buying
through those levels, then you can look
for um what's that? 290s
so far seeing big old squeeze back up.
So they bought value. Buyers are saying,
"Hey, we're not going to lose Friday's
value right now. We're staying inside.
We're moving so quick. Bookmap cannot
keep up right now."
So already 220 points off those lows. We
are 7 minutes into the session, folks,
which means we found a bid at the end of
minute one and we have uh ripped 222
points since then.
Absolute wild moves, but that's where
we're at. Okay, into previous week value
area high, previous day point of control
here.
And uh these are very very very
sensitive areas. You do not sort of uh
want to be holding longs too much past
this or at least you want to be taking
some profits. So might very well fail
here.
This is a big squeeze out. And how we
act here now becomes important. So look,
we've just gone from previous days value
look below and fail up to previous week
value area low. All right. If we reject
previous week value area low, they're
going to come down and retest some of
these key levels again because now we're
fighting between the weekly value and
the daily values.
Very, very key how we act now.
Spy into its view up or sorry ES into
its view up here. Spies are actually
already through it as are the Q's. Big
still trading downside
and we are holding pretty well here.
It's pretty impressive. It's a decent
hold. Maybe if they can get a bid
through uh previous week if you're still
long you might even get all the way up
here. But, uh, what I would say is if
you took that look below and fail, you
need to be taking some money off the
table into these moves. All right? You
need to be taking money off the table
into these moves because you're starting
to see some profit taking here.
No trade for me. I'm missed that giving
you a readout. I'm not even convinced I
would have necessarily taken it. If I
did, it would have been small size
because, as we know, range rotation, my
least favorite trades. This is a
volatile market. We we can have, like we
said, we can have range rotation of 300
plus points here, folks.
That's not a joke. We can go 300 points
up, 300 points down, 300 points up, 300
points down numerous times a day. You go
and have a look at what we were doing a
year or two ago when we were doing that.
We're talking about 50 to 80 point range
rotations, not 300 point range
rotations. Okay? So, be aware of your
sizing.
Oh, still holding this up. Nice, Mr.
Sim. Yeah, some of you took it.
Congratulations. Hey, Mr. Five micros
for 200 points is a lot of money. It's a
lot of money.
Very, very nice.
So, testing previous week value area low
here.
The uh mags still mix. So, you got Tesla
up, Microsoft up, Google up, Nvidia
down, Meta down, Amazon down, Apple
down, mixed bag on the mag. Remember,
it's Monday morning. Long week ahead,
folks. We got Thanksgiving after that.
Um, I might be taking Friday off, just
to warn you. I'm probably going to go to
Palm Springs for a long weekend this
this Friday. So, but I will let you know
and book my flight yet.
Okay, 25200 on the book. So just above
coming into uh this Asia low here.
What's previous day high? Is that it up
there? 23s.
Is that right? Let me check that out. I
think it is. Yeah. Previous day high is
into into this 300. Yes.
So some strong selling came in there and
they did not force this market lower. So
they might get caught here if they want
to resqueeze this higher. They just
spent the last 1 2 3 4 5 minutes trying
to sell. Haven't moved lower yet. So
just be aware of that. It's a battle
here as we trade into that previous week
value area low.
And the longer we're here, the worse it
is for bears. Um because they would have
wanted a snap back down and they're not
seeing it yet. So back down to V up we
go. Back down to previous day point of
control we go. They're trying to force
the hand here. Still being absorbed so
far
again. No position for me yet. Just
waiting here. We can build out. If we
build out a shelf, I'll be interested or
something. But right now, just wondering
how big a rotation they're going to do.
Rejecting previous week value area low
for now. Starting to see bears come in
here with more strength.
We have an imbalance here into sort of
39 to 28. This is sort of the edge where
bulls will want to defend if they're
looking to squeeze back through previous
week value area low is somewhere in
here.
Still early in the session. We're still
only 12 minutes in. Plenty of time.
Seeing some absorption trying take place
here.
There you go. So they just absorb that
in front of that imbalance.
You're near Palm Springs. Otus.
Well, if I go, I will be I'll go on uh
Friday and I'll be there Friday,
Saturday, Sunday if I go.
My wife's definitely going. It will just
be down to flights and timings for me.
Okay, so we're back into this bump.
Look, make sure you're zooming out
higher time frame.
Let's uh Where are you guys? Make sure
you're zooming out higher time frame.
What we're looking at right now, we've
traded back into this thick area, right?
This is where we looked above and
failed. If we come back to here and sell
again, we go back range rotation again.
If we look above and fail, we go back
range rotation again. But if we can
start building liquidity above here,
right? This is why I'm trying to be
neutral. They might want to come all the
way up and revisit this up here into
500s because we're thin in here, aren't
we? Think about what we did Thursday.
That's a thin move, right? Bears are
trying to do this. If they don't do that
and bulls get above and defend, then the
next squeeze into here is possible. We
cannot rule that out. Cannot rule those
moves out. That's why I'm trying to be
neutral. Like I think bears have an
edge, but uh they can lose that edge if
they can't defend levels, right? Just
like we talked about in the newsletter.
Stronger selling back down towards this
imbalance. We're building out a sort of
sideways range here. Let's get uh this
on before I forget.
No, you don't want to do it. Come on.
There you go.
It's building out some volume here.
This is where bulls last came in and
defended these lows. Remember, there's a
little imbalance underneath here. All
depends if these bears want to sell
through this now and take us back down
or if bulls are going to defend it yet
again.
We are starting to build out this range
up here right now.
Okay. And if they fail this, we can come
right back to here. If they look below
and reclaim like they have twice already
and this is looks like third attempt to
hold it because we have an imbalance
here right on the order flow. There is a
big imbalance on this spike candle right
here which bulls are trying to defend.
So I'm just being patient overall right
now. We're in range rotation. Bulls have
taken control of those lows. So not
really looking for a bearish move unless
we see a big breakdown. And I'm not
going to buy high either. Unfortunately
I probably missed it. remember might
look like, "Oh, mate, you've only missed
15 minutes." Hey, in those 15 minutes,
we've moved 244 points.
Sounds good, Otus.
It's testing these 200s.
So, we sort of have an edge of volume
into 250s.
Uh, I know previous day value area highs
above that, but 250s looks like a big
level on the weekly.
Just have to see. We'll have to see how
we go.
Nothing for me yet, folks. This looks
bullish, though. They've built, they've
trapped. Bears got caught twice there
trying to force the breakdown in that
imbalance. And this might well complete
this rotation up to here now.
So, up to here, previous day. If you're
still long off this under here, uh maybe
you get lucky and you get all the way up
into this now.
So, previous day high and previous day
value high, try and get up towards 300.
It's still long. That's where you want
to try and get up towards. MAG is
starting to push here. So, Tesla now
1.72% green. Microsoft's now gone green.
0.04 up% up there. Only just green. Same
as Meta only just gone green. Google the
strong one 5.61% up. absolutely flying.
Uh Apple and Amazon just under 1% down
on the day. Nvidia just over 1% down on
the day. So you've got a mixed bag here,
folks. Right, you've got three of them
about a 1% down, two of them flat, and
two of them pushing.
And VIX is still falling back inside.
Like I said, it can very well range
rotate today. It might look for this gap
fill on previous day low, which is what
sort of sitting 50% in the middle of,
but looks like it's coming back to earth
at the moment on the VIX. So why we
can't have too much bias and why we
talked about them this morning. Yes, I
would love to be bearish but the
location wasn't there. London had the
location. We looked below and we failed.
And that tells you rotational market.
So any of you caught it, you are sitting
very pretty right now. Very very pretty
right now.
This is your next target. We get a bit
thicker up here as you can see the red
box, but if you can get up there, you'd
be very happy, I think.
Where's my volume gone?
one
see my profiles come off this chart on
Ninja Trader
go template
There we go.
Okay, you still look good. Holding
nicely,
pushing nicely,
coming into key levels. You look good to
hold.
No worries. Contorted. Nice work. You
got that look look below and fail on
push, I assume.
That's good. This is the target up here,
folks. This is the target up into here.
You've also got the fiveday hit. So
everything's up here. Previous day value
area high, 5day moving average, previous
day high. You got GlobeEx just above it.
All right, that's that's your GlobeEx
high right now printed in London. So if
they want to come all the way back for
that, they can as well. I'd say, you
know, you've had TP1, which was into
this area here, previous day point
control, previous week point control.
We're now bidding above that. So, your
next TP would be previous day value
high, previous day high, and then
GlobeEx and above that. Well, who knows?
Maybe we go 500s in one day. I mean, it
is madness. I'm telling you, we are
talking about absolute madness right
now. We're talking about a 600 POS
possible point push again. But this is
the market we have we have right now.
Can't believe it. on on a Monday no news
day when everyone's waiting for
Wednesday. We uh could possibly do a 600
point move out the open.
[Laughter]
There we go.
This is why you've got it doesn't matter
what you think, how mental the market
is. Uh you got to trade what's in front
of you.
Nice contorted. Well done, mate. to 060
060 in here. Beautiful. Nice work.
Okay, you're getting close.
You're getting close. They're trying to
find a bit of a bid in Nvidia, Amazon,
and Apple. Not Not yet, but they're
trying to. Uh Nvidia has clawed back
over 1% of its uh open so far. We'll
see.
There's probably a rotation back down
coming at some point. It's just uh when
when have they finished? And uh
you know me, I don't love
I don't love ranges and rotations and
stuff. And overall, this this is very
very squeezy. This is like Friday, so I
don't want to be the same as Friday.
Looking to fade it. We had numerous
attempts Friday. Bulls stepped in. Bulls
are showing that they've stepped in
again now.
You could, well, not you could. I will
argue that bulls have now put in a
higher low on the hourly. They will need
to get a breakout above Globeex high and
above previous day high. And if they do
that, then we have to remain neutral
bias for the rest of the week until
there is a major major pivot.
And we basically what I'm saying is
above
previous day value area high, we're
going to go in range rotation to 500.
And then you're going to see liquidity
bu be built out between sort of 300,
250, 300 and 500. And in that area,
you're going to see a lot of traders uh
get very upset with each other because
you're going to see bears defending it
and bulls defending the lower side. And
we're not going to be in alignment on
multi-time frame. So what I'm looking at
that this morning, it's possible that
low this morning could form the start of
a higher low. We don't know yet. It's
too early. But uh that's what they will
be looking to do.
More selling coming in here again. Do
they get their way? Some pretty big size
coming in here on the tape.
Little bit of excess up there, but not a
lot. And I'm not sure they've completed
their rotation. I think uh value is what
they want.
Value and previous day high looks like
what they want to me.
big area here. We've started to get a
little bit denser here.
I'm not sure they're done with this.
I am not sure they're done with this
yet. Still seeing uh soaking on the tape
there.
Here comes a little drive down.
Not much.
Bears trying to come flying in here and
still seeing it being soaked on the tape
so far.
I'm really not sure they're done with
this. If they are, it might be a quick
wash that's soaked back off this level
because we built structure here now. So,
let in fact, let's draw this on for you.
So, you guys are ready.
Right, there's your structure.
And I'm still seeing soaking on the
tape. So, I'm just telling you what I'm
seeing. Again, no position for me, but
there is has been soaking on the tape
there. And you can see it again. Bears
tried to force their hand building
another sort of shelf here. I don't
think they've complete their rotation
yet. So I'm thinking I don't think
they're done that done yet. They want
value area high. Want previous day high.
Maybe they want GlobeEx. Like I said,
who knows? Maybe they want 500. I think
it was Beu on Friday who was saying, can
they go 500? Maybe they do it. Structure
looks good. And you'd have to say she
looks right right now. I'm seeing
aggressive buying coming in. Microsoft
gone back red. So the mixed bag
continues. VIX trying to find a little
bit of a bid, but I'm not convinced it's
come down low enough yet. But it's
trying to defend in front of 20s right
now. If we build a shelf here, this will
be like last week where, you know, maybe
there's a rotation out this shelf down
to this again and back and forth and
back and forth and back and forth. And
if they let go of this shelf down here
and if they defend it, we keep going.
Feels like Friday all over again.
There you go. Did you just say that
before I looked up? I've just seen your
comment. Bounced off demand and it may
be going to retest 25500, the low of the
breakout last week. Yeah. Did you say
that before before I even read I
remember you saying it on Friday. So I
was think I was just thinking about you
in my head how we had that discussion
Friday. You may well be right at the
moment. It looks more than possible,
doesn't it? Looks more than possible.
John Dennis, I'm done for the day.
3,800. Very nice, mate. Very, very nice.
Well, all of you have made money. Means
you took the failed the failed uh
breakdown, the look below, and fail and
the move back into value, which is it's
the best move to take in here. So, I
have to be neutral. I I've missed it
while I was calling everything out. So,
now I have to wait for the potentially
the rotation the other side. The harder
thing now is momentum is flying upside.
Blessie. Let's see.
Little bit of excess on that last push
for the first time. Not a lot, but a
little bit. 116 up there. Where's the
delta? Where you at? What was that high
to 50s?
Not enough for me, but it's interesting.
Back down to the lower side again. Maybe
they come down and revisit 61s. How we
doing for time? 3 minutes until a new H1
H4. That would be interesting.
Retesting this low again. They're
finding bids here for now. No follow
through through that yet.
Very sensitive here. Back to that uh
flow zones. I'm not convinced they
finished the rotation yet.
They just whipped that edge, didn't
they? No follow through back down to
this yet. So, we can draw this on.
Yeah, they're still soaking for now.
Say a bit of a flat top there. If they
break, it would be nasty. But let's see.
Back down to the edge of this range
again.
Still no follow through.
Very tight here.
Someone's going to get hurt soon.
There's the downside pressure back to
the edge of this range again. They're if
they let go, they rotate down to here.
165s. I'm a bit cautious about taking
this because I'm not convinced we
finished the rotation to previous day
value area high. So, I know from a
technical standpoint, if we leave this
range, yes, we've been in a squeeze up.
Where's my pen gone? We have been in a
squeeze up. All right, we are leaving
this range. Maybe there's a trade back
down to here. The problem is for me,
we've left this low hanging fruit, which
doesn't which means it's not an A+ for
me. The difference between that and this
morning's play is this morning we came
outside of previous day value area high,
right? We came into
a volume, right, level where we bid off.
So, we took low hanging fruit, we found
demand, and we bid up. We haven't done
that the other side of this range yet,
which is why I'm not really looking to
trade it back downside yet because the
equivalent of that would have to be a
look above
this and a failure back in. And we've
not seen that. We are testing this
range. Like maybe there's a short down
here, but it's definitely not an A+.
No doubt about it. We've been in a
squeeze for 30 minutes here.
laidback. Hi fellas, on my trading view
I'm using NQ1, but why are my numbers
different from Alex's? Uh, they
shouldn't be different. NQ1 is the same
as this. NQZ is the current contract.
NQ1 is just the rollover. They should be
exactly the same.
So maybe you've just got slight delay.
The delay should be 3 to six seconds.
I've got it set as the fastest humanly
or computer possible for YouTube.
Raph, done for the day. 100 points and
50 for the runner. I love it, mate. So,
here you go. Maybe rotation here. I'd be
somewhat careful if you're really keen
on taking this. They will try and rotate
to here. They can try and hold these
pivots, which is why I'm not taking it
at the moment. Just looking at like the
imbalances and where we have that
cluster. But this is maybe a play. I
would class it as a C setup. It's not an
A plus. It's not even a B. It's probably
a C setup at the moment because we've
left low hanging fruit and we haven't
completed the rotation and we're going
against the grain. But maybe they're
going to do this move here for you guys.
New H1 coming in two 1 zero. All right,
this is what matters to me. This H1,
this H4. Now, if this H1H4 prints above
here and fails up here or even above
Globeex and we get like a nice long
wick, then I'd consider that trade back
downside. If we start printing above all
of this, then we're going to go 500s.
I'm just 500 away from passing my
funding ticks account, but now it's
looking hard for me. Hey, there's no
rush. There's no rush. Just wait for
your setup. If that setup's not today,
it will be tomorrow or the next day.
Don't worry about the money. All right?
But thinking about the money is the
trap. Sticking to the process is how you
make money trading. If you focus on your
P&L, you will lose.
Nice, Peter. All out for the long. Nice
work. Yeah, lots of you getting it.
Jack, you're short on resistance. Okay.
Not quite the level I'm at yet, but I
understand what you're looking for. But
like I said, I'm concerned we haven't
taken the low hanging fruit yet. We will
see. Vix is starting to find a bid in
front of 20.
Let's see.
Back to these flow zones at the moment.
Let's move this.
This is your two ranges,
right? We've got volume here, volume
here. Rotation can happen here. If we
let go of this, there's a bigger snap
possible
because we didn't really build out much
structure on this drive up this morning.
It was like a straight squeeze up. All
the shorts entered at the lows and
they're all getting squeezed out. Here's
the move back to volume. Now, now it's
important what happens now for sentiment
now. Do bulls come and defend this area
where they successfully defended earlier
this morning and caught bids? Right,
that's what they will be looking to do.
If I was short, I'd be covering into
this zone, holding runners in case we
break down below.
This is previous week value area low.
We're finding a bid around that. So, you
can see this is big level and I would
expect rotation between these two zones
at the moment. Right. This is not as
good now because we've sort of built out
here. So, this level becomes key as a
over, under, flip below and fail also
available. The bulls will want to defend
this. Failing to defend this will allow
a bigger move lower. I'm going to remove
that because the way we built that
volume is not too pretty. So this is the
level that bulls want to defend that
we're coming into
starting to push now 2.90% up. So Tessa
and Google look strong. Everything else
has gone red on the day folks. So Tessa
and Google now the only two that are up.
Everything else red on the day or meta's
flat. Back to your VW up here. This is
the area bulls need to defend this gray
box. They will need to defend this area
if they're going to complete the
rotation of previous day high. Previous
day value area high. Failing to defend
this area will cause them to get in
trouble and mean everyone above this
area will get stuck.
Let's just see.
big. The excelling here
is a New York VWAP. We start breaking
down from here, it means the whole
squeeze is going to let go.
Very, very dangerous. Now, if bears now
defend this range, right? If we trade
downside from this, if a retest stays
heavy, we can go all the way back to
open. And we're starting to see selling
in the MAG. Not in Tesla and not in Goo,
but in everything else. Oh my gosh.
Well, that trade up there was the one I
wasn't convinced because it wasn't A+,
but we'll see. Big selling on the tape
at the moment. Want to just let this
calm down. If we're just going to get a
two-way take where we go up for 30
minutes and down for 30 minutes, it's
going to be pretty tough to trade based
on A+ setups and stuff.
Just going to get a bit more coffee
here. Let this settle down, folks. Be
right back.
Up to you. You have a think about it.
All right.
So, a bit of a shelf here into 70s.
Let's see. I just think we're in range
rotation. So, I just want to be really
cautious. And it's a Monday. Monday sets
the tone for the week. I think we're
waiting for Nvidia on Wednesday. I think
that's the big bigger move this week. We
had a massive week last week. So, I'm
not uh
I'm not in a crazy hurry, let's put it
that way.
to force my way in and out of this
market at the moment.
It's starting to find a bid. It's going
to come and retest this shelf. And this
gray box is the key level. If bulls get
back through this, they can go back for
high of day. If bears defend this, then
they're going to look for a lower high
and a sell back down.
So, it's big big level here.
MAG is in a sell other than Tesla and
Google, which are holding gains. They've
squeezed right the way up, right?
Google's just just shy of 5 and a half%
up on the day. Let's let that sink in.
Five, five and a half% up on the day.
It's a big move.
This is the key area. This is your
overunder now, which will dictate the
tone probably for the remainder of the
morning. I would say there's so far
first push in have defended it.
Let's see how we go in here. If they
just squeeze right the way through, we
probably go back for high of day. If
they defend it, well, we'll have to see.
VIX is uh not finding a bid right now.
So, it doesn't look great for bears at
the moment
into this box, but let's see. Let's give
it a moment to shake out.
Last push did leave excess from bulls up
there. I'm in a short now. Small size
stop already in that last excess. Here
we go. Oh my god, this is moving fast.
I'm up big. Woof.
Okay, cover some in here. Got a pivot
into here, which they might defend. And
let's see if we can get a runner to
break down. So, just taking this bare
flag once they left excess into that
into this gray box. That was enough of a
trigger. I'm short from here. Covered
some here. Let's see if we can get under
PDC and roll right the way down if we
get lucky. Here we go.
It's crazy how fast this is moving.
Let's go.
I'm short from 4375
here.
Here we go.
Let's see if we can trade under PDC.
Remember, it's PDC PWC as well. It's a
big level in Monday when we trade into
that Friday close, that cash gap. VIX
finding a bid here, which looks good.
Really nice.
Has it got another flush down into it?
Strong selling coming in here on the
tape. Can they have some follow through?
Here we go, baby. Let's go. Oh, nice way
to start the week. Let's go.
All right, let's go. Let's go. It's a
shame it's not an A+ trade. If they'd
just be kind to us one day on NQ and
take out the low hanging fruit the other
side first, we could have entered this
at the highs. Uh, which I think is what
you did, Jack. I think you're short from
up here. This red box right somewhere up
there, I believe.
Okay. I want to watch this strong
selling cluster into 90 here. Don't want
to reclaim of 90. Really big big selling
into 90. Bears are trying to buy this.
Bulls are trying to buy this dip at the
moment. Might see more follow through
and pain on them because they are trying
to buy this low right now. And if if we
stay heavy versus 90, they're going to
get themselves caught these bulls. But
90 is your level. We've got to stay
heavy versus 90.
Starting to find a bid.
Sensitive area here. 90 is the level.
Defend 90. We're going to go lower. Come
on, baby. Let's get this runner all the
way down to low day. Let's [\h__\h] go.
Give it. Give it. Give it. Beautiful.
Beautiful.
90. Still the level. 85 to 90. Any
reclaim of that, I'm out because we we
sold so strong. It was all sell side
into 90. If we reclaim 90, I'm
completely out of this because they can
repric very quickly. Okay, done. I'm
out.
I don't care. I don't care. I just don't
want to hold if they repric through
this. You need bulls to get stuck again
at 90. Maybe it was a bit apprehensive
me, but yeah. Out by a couple ticks.
This is a big level here. It's a
battleground now. This is where bears
came flying in here. If you look at
bookmap above, right, we came flying in
here and we're really heavy there into
what's that level there? 106 there's a
331 lot and at the same level 109
there's a 225 lot. So they are the
control right now. So I guess maybe I
should have given it 10 more points
until 105
for me on um footprint there. It was 90.
We're trading through it. So I'm done
with that trade now Monday morning. Lock
that in.
Just watching the footprint. So, we're
starting to repric. We're going to come
and test where these massive bears were,
where these 500 lots went through market
side. And if they reclaim this, a little
bit of a squeeze can happen, folks. All
right. So, bears came flying in here
between 90 and 100. And they might well
get squeezed out, which is why I'm done
with this trade at the moment just from
reading the tape. It's just from reading
the tape. All right. I know you're going
to be like, "Structure is still
bearish." I get that. I totally
understand that, but I don't want to get
caught in a squeeze back up like this.
So, it's just from reading the tape that
I've seen this.
There we go. So, he he got one today.
Finally got one. You can see they're
starting to build a shelf out of this
low now. So, everything below this is
thin. And we're going to come retest
this now. And this can be a two-leg. And
if bears got trapped down there, which
we know they came flying in at 90 and
100 and below. If bulls reclaim this,
then they've still got that low hanging
fruit, which is why it was not an A+
trade, right? because there's still low
hanging fruit higher for them to go for
which is looks like they're trying to
get back up towards now. So that gray
box is your under over.
Hopefully that makes sense for you all.
And I'm almost done with the c well I'm
not almost done. I've got uh the modules
I've got left to do on the course for
you guys are bookmap
um and footprint and putting it all
together.
So I have been working my absolute butt
off. So if you look at me and think,
"God, he looks tired for a Monday." It's
cuz I have not stopped working for like
the last three weeks trying to get this
all together for you.
And uh the Black Friday sale, well,
it will be on all everything before this
course because I won't have it done in
time. But I will do a 25% Black Friday
sale. I'll give you a clue. It is
actually running now, but I haven't done
any uh
any artwork for it yet. But on anything
on flowzonerader.com, if you use code BF
for Black Friday, you will get 25% off
at checkout. All right, it's already
started. I just haven't set up the uh
the artwork for it yet. But for those of
you who were asking, yeah, BF, it is
limited numbers on on it, guys. So,
first come, first serve and it will
finish December 1st.
And uh the other thing I will say
because some of you might be waiting for
uh the new course. the new course.
Anytime I release anything new, any
current students always get significant
discount whether it be an indicator, a
course, whatever it is, you always get a
big discount. I always look after
current students.
Okay, so question is here. Do they
defend this 90 and 100 level? Remember
that's where bears got stuck. So far
bears just resold into VWAP. I'm not
convinced here anymore. I've like taken
that trade off. Just going to wait now.
See what sets up next.
There you go. So they're defending it
like we just talked about. So look at
that wick. Where do we come down to? In
front of 110. Remember bears are stuck
right now at sort of 90 to 100. I can
show you guys. Where is OBS? So I can
pull you guys up. Let me move this down
here. Um
this is why we covered. Are you into bit
map? There we go. Right. These guys
here.
Right. See these big orders here? Right.
These came in a bit later. Look at the
size on this. 224 331.
You guys see that? Do I need to squeeze
this over a bit?
Maybe you can see that now. These guys
here 224 331. Those are market selling.
We go to the lows or who who's at the
low of day? A market seller, right?
That's the end of the auction. No one
else wanted to sell. We squeeze back up.
We reclaim. We're holding bids above and
on this sort of rectangle box all the
time. We hold this. Now, where are we
going to revisit? They're going to try
and squeeze upside to where stronger
selling came in. Maybe this guy here,
79. So, 80. So, all the time we hold 100
to 190, there's a potentially a trade
back up towards these guys here, 60 and
80, and then all the way up if they can
reclaim. So, that's why I'm out of the
shorts at the moment. Now, we're going
just let them battle because really,
where's the edge now? If we if we also
zoom out, forget map for a bit for a
minute. If we zoom out and we think
about where we are, we're right at the
mid.
You don't need a fib for this. You can
just look at it, right? We're right in
the sort of middle, right? The best edge
today. It was a short hit. It didn't
give me the A+. What was the A+? Take
that. Leave a wick. Trade down. That's
the A+. Take that low hanging fruit. It
didn't do it. So, I had to wait to make
sure enough were trapped. We took the
short down to here. We're now out
because we're not seeing strong selling.
We're seeing a battle developing here. I
don't want to trade in a range in the
midpoint between value area high, value
area low from previous day. We don't
want to trade in that range, right? We
want to trade up here ideally and down
here. Those of you who caught the longs,
great. Couldn't get the shorts up there,
got the continuation. That's it. We're
done until it gives us the next trade
set up. There's nothing for me right now
that's making me want to do anything. If
anything, I'd probably be thinking, can
bears get stuck and then trade upside,
but it goes against the high time frame
narrative. So, lots of like
not indecision. I'm trying to think what
a lack of confluence. That's the best
way of saying there is a lack of
confluence in the market at the moment.
Lack of confluence. How we can get rid
of these drawings. Clear drawings. There
we go. And you can also see that by the
mag, right? So, Google and Tesla flying
and you've got the rest of the mag down.
They're not doing they're not acting in
unison.
Not acting in unison.
But VWAP is being defended. But 1901 100
is the level. So sellers big cells just
came in there again. So big seller just
came into 100 level and he got absorbed
again because bulls understand that if
they can defend this level here, they
can catch bears. If bears keep coming
flying in here like they just tried
again and they don't get this breakdown,
we can get that squeeze. But at the
moment there's no edge because structure
is this. Balls are defending this. Bears
are defending this. This is the rotation
zone. Balls get above that. There's a
breakout. Bears get under one n uh under
90 and 100 maybe they get back down to
New York open. That's that's all there
is to do at the moment and just let them
battle it out in my mind. So back to
these 190s checking them. Bears coming
flying in here trying to force this
breakdown. They really want a breakdown
in this market. Back to PDC here, that
yellow line.
So, bears can take control of this
market if they sell through this and if
the uh absorption on the tape
dissipates. But this is the level, isn't
it? 90 to 100 was the level.
Go. They're trying to soak off it again
these bulls.
But for me, this is a no trade area at
the moment while they battle out. Right,
we got that trade,
made the money. Lots of you made money
on the move back up. Some of you might
have taken a short before me, which is
fine. Just didn't set up for what I
wanted. Now, we're waiting. It's
possible. I can't rule out a move lower
here, but I'm not seeing them completely
take over of the tape yet.
VIX is kind of in no man's land as well.
Back to these 90s we go again. This big
level here. If bulls get out the way, we
can flush. Back to 90s. Back to 90s.
Aggressive selling at these lows again
from bears.
Got to be someone soaking this tape
here. If he moves, a flush can happen
under 90s.
Last chance to loom for bulls otherwise
they're going to get washed out here.
It's probably going back towards that
pivot low. There you go. So washing
under 90s
back to test the 90s. Bears will have to
step in here again. Otherwise, it's
basically a look below and fail. They're
stepping back in at 90s. So they're
going to try and force this low now.
There's so many orders on the book here.
It's insane. Both sides of the tape.
Bears have got the edge at the moment
because we're under 90s and 100. Balls
will have the edge. If we go back over
that, bears will get stuck. So bears
have the edge at the moment, rejecting
VWAP through the 90s, back down to this
pivot low. And if you snap that, you can
look for previous day value area low
again, which would be your cover point.
If you're still in the short, or you re
hit this short as we went sub 90. There
you go. So watch now. See how we get
thick. You'd want to see a failure under
60s now for a straight flush down to
here. And you want to be covering some
into here. And then you can hold runners
for breakdowns.
But this is the edge of value on the
current session where we are. So lots of
people will cover here and most will
probably cover into previous day value
area low.
Big still trying to find a bid. It's
kind of like up down up down up down.
Maybe an inverse head and shoulders or
quasi starting to build out on a 5m
minute. We we will see.
So it's the same level 90s and the 100.
If they reclaim 90s and 100 just like
before, alls will try and take the edge.
You can see we're see this shelf with
built volume straight back to 90s again.
This is the level bears need to defend
this. If they don't defend this, we will
go back into that rotational potential
squeeze back up to a previous day point
of control again.
That's why I'm just sitting out for this
for now. I'm just for me, I'm happy to
let them battle out. I know there's
money to be made here. You're still
trading in what's that? What's the range
there from you can see 160 to it's a 100
point range is insane insane but the
probability of these you have to be very
quick watching the order flow to get
this right
quite happy to uh sit still at the
moment or me
if we start getting heavy underneath
previous day value area low right then
we can think about a breakdown into this
next box I would. It's so annoying that
they didn't take this high. Did they
take it in ES, by the way? It's one
thing I didn't look at this morning.
No, they didn't take it in either. Well,
that's just that's just horrible.
I don't trust this move when they leave
those in like that.
Yeah. Smash that like button for me,
please.
Are you planning on Black Friday as far
as your course goes? Uh, you might have
just missed it. We just talked about it.
There is a Black Friday sale. I haven't
done the artwork for absolutely
everything on my website right now. It's
25% off. Ends December the 1st. Code BF
at checkout. All right.
So, sorry, Jack. You You might have not
been here when I said it. I haven't done
the artwork yet. I haven't announced it.
I haven't put it on any socials, but it
is live. Um, it's first come, first
serve. There are limited numbers on
every single product on there because I
can't give it out for everyone. So,
first come, first served. Ends December
the 1st
or I should say ends midnight into
December the 1st or 1:00 a.m. December
the 1st.
Yeah. So, if you guys have been waiting
to get any of the courses where whether
it's foundation or beginner to advanced
or flow zones for Ninja Trader or the
flow zones for Trading View, it's 25%
off the whole site.
Prices are going to go up next year
again, folks. They're going to have to
go up next year. And we will make a new
bundle with the uh
all the new stuff as well.
[Laughter]
I know. Procrastination. Uh, for that
stuff, I normally do it for for um
uh YouTube thumbnails and stuff. I have
someone that does it now.
I haven't done a new video for a while
because I've been building this course.
All right. So, reclaim of the 90s to
100. You can see the battle zone
starting to develop. That gray box is
really your overunder.
So, bulls, what are bulls looking for?
They're looking for one of these, right?
They're looking for unfinished business
up here. What are bears looking for?
They're looking to defend this and
really they should have defended this
for the breakdown. They failed to defend
90 to 100 for the breakdown on the
second time. All right, so they failed
first time and they failed second time.
They they got a new low, but they
haven't seen follow through down here,
which is what they want. And you might
get a bit of a W here. And this can be
bullish rotation. And I I wouldn't put
it against them because why? because we
left lowhanging fruit.
But for me, I'm not going to trade in
this area here.
Oh, uh, BF, Black Friday, BF B.
All right, bulls starting to take
control. We left excess on that last low
down here from bears. Bears definitely
got caught sub 66 and bulls are starting
to take control. You're starting to see
Delta pushing even on this last candle.
Bears are stuck underneath 110s right
now. Bulls are starting to take control
of this market at the moment. And when I
say this market, I mean this area here.
It is a battleground, but bulls are
starting. You're starting to see unless
we trade under this wick.
This is why I don't touch these areas,
man. It's just like I watch the order
flow and it's mental.
So bulls needed to defend 110. They just
failed 110. Now we're back to 90 again.
And you're going to see this rotation
over and over and over and over and
over. that strong selling that came back
in here. Let's see if Mr. I'm going to
soak everything you've got is still on
the tape. The answer right now looks
like yes.
The bigger question I guess is when is
Google done?
When is Google done?
Anyone watch the sport of the weekend?
Oh my gosh, the rugby was immense. So
proud of the England boys, beating New
Zealand. That is no uh no small thing.
It's not quite the same as beating them
back in the day now. I think the Spring
Box are the best in the world, but great
performance from the boys. Very happy
for them. Okay, Bears flying in here at
Lowe's again. Let's see if Mr. I'm going
to soak everything you've got is on the
tape or not.
This is the key level. I'd say sort of
69. Let's call it 70. It's a bit of a
meme, isn't it? 69 is the key level.
That's where we left bearish excess
underneath and they just defended it.
So, like I said, I am not touching these
areas, folks. I'm just calling out what
I'm seeing on the tape, but I'm not
going to get myself caught in these
areas. These are the areas where I'm
like, leave alone. We're not at the edge
anymore. We've we played the first
continuation. Remember, like we failed.
We effectively played the first bounce
short. Once they reclaimed, I was like,
"Okay, I'm done with it. They're going
to go into a battle." Maybe they rotate.
That's fine. They're going to rotate
without me if they do it. Maybe they
rotate. That's also fine. They can
rotate without me if they're going to do
it. I don't need every single trade. I
want the ones which are high
probability.
This is mental. Big defending coming in.
So, there is definitely someone soaking
the bid today. He's uh happy to sit on
that bid all day long and soak the
aggressive sell in.
But the rotations are very quick in
inside this inside this box here. So
this is sort of my leave alone box at
the moment. This is I'd say here is
that's my leave alone box. You could
even argue value should be a leave alone
box right now. Right. Value on the day.
It's 100 points but but definitely V up
to this low. That's my leave alone box
at the moment. Hands are off. Leave
alone. It's okay. It's Monday morning,
folks. Monday morning. You either made
that killer 200 point trade up or you
snagged a bit of it to the downside with
me. We just wait now. Long week ahead.
We absolutely crushed last week. Long,
long, long week ahead.
Not trying to be a dick for a tick, but
I won the beginning course and I
completed it. Will the discount code at
the end work on the full course and add
on to I don't think it's a good question
go I don't think it will I think it's
separate and I think the sale you can
double check I think the sale course is
better because if you're doing the full
course
6120 it's probably like 150 off and if
you did the beginner course I think it's
100 off some some somewhere around like
that so I think the Black Friday sales
probably saves you an extra 20 to 50
quid bucks that is Sorry, when I say
quid. All right, squeeze back up here.
Balls coming flying back in.
Your market data feed is messed up.
Saying I have a 10-minute delay, but CME
bundle activated. Anyone on this before?
Uh on on are you talking about Trading
View or are you talking about on Ninja
Trader? Um on Bookmap? I've had it on
Bootmap many many times. Uh
you would have seen lot like lot about
two three weeks ago it kept happening
every day just closed bookmap down. Oh
ninja trader. Oh that's a worry. I don't
know mate. That's that's a worry. Okay
bulls are starting to take control. Come
back to this gray box now. Bulls are
starting to take control of this area
like we talked about. Bears just failed
to get that breakdown. And if you see
bullish rotation there is low hanging
fruit left to go for up towards the high
of day. So here's the move back to
previous day point of control. This gray
box is your trigger. Here is a potential
W. If they start bidding above this,
they have a move back to this high of
day. There's no doubt about it. We've
just traded from the edge of range. They
might come to the edge of this. I said
I'm trying to leave this alone, but it's
uh it's moving very very quick on the
tape. The candles might not look big,
um, but they're of decent size and we
are moving fast on the tape. Your ATR
has been consistently up about 32 points
per M1 candle. That is significant
folks. Most retail traders use a 20 to
30 point stop. That will not work in
this market. You will get wicked out in
a second.
So let's see here back towards these
VWAPS which are flat on the day. We just
defended previous day point of control.
I would say bulls potentially had the
ability to send this higher at this
point after bears failed to get their
rotation underneath this. So if bulls
defend sort of the edge of this, where's
that last area they came in? I'd say
bulls need to defend 25. If bulls defend
25s, there's probably a squeeze higher
here developing. If bulls can defend
developing. That would be my guess. If
they can't defend 25s, then the range uh
gets rotated in more. But again, I'm not
trading this currently. I would consider
a trade back up if they look really
strong.
If they could defend 25s, maybe if I see
them soak 25, but you wouldn't want to
get knifed through, so let it defend a
bit, I would say.
That previous day point of control was
being defended by bears.
Where did they come flying in? Maybe
even as low as 10 again. I don't like
that. Back down to 10 will allow
rotation.
Ugly, ugly, ugly. But balls have the
chance here. They have the chance here
to do something.
25s ideally hold 10 at the worst case.
Under that, they're in trouble.
But you're just you're in this sort of
edge of this potential W. They might
come all the way down to here, which
would be not very nice, and it would
give bears a sniff to go lower. So,
what's doing timing wise as well? 30
minute bar. those last 30 minute bar of
those last two bars. Oh god, it's very
ugly out here, folks. This is uh about
as bad as you get in terms of range
rotation, but I would say bulls
currently have the edge to go higher.
Bulls have the edge to go higher all the
time. They can defend. There's that 25
move we just talked about and they
defended it. If they defend that,
they're fine. Otherwise, we go 110 and
then they're in trouble.
What is the VIX doing? 30 minute bar
does not look great here. It's the one
thing.
30 minute bar does not look good.
Edge of that value 78.
Yeah, that's a leave alone for me.
Thanks very much. No good for me.
that to the 110s and bulls losing that
edge now. So they have the chance to
defend 25s and 110s didn't defend it
back into that range and the chop is
going to continue here.
Alex, do you have a full course with
Ninja Trader Indicators? Uh the full
course is yeah the the
it's called beginner to advance. It's
the 20our course and you can add on the
Ninja Trader uh bundle
and then get 25% off.
So, if you go to check out and click on
uh it should give you like an option for
adding a bundle and you just want to add
flow zone pro for Ninja Trader. It will
give you two options. Flow zone pro for
Trading View, Flowzone Pro for Ninja
Trader. You want to add that on and then
stick in the code if you want the in
trader indicator. Miguel hit my goal
early today. Got to run some errands.
Take care. Yeah, take care, mate.
Okay, back towards low day. So, bulls
lost that impetus there. We're back.
Well, not lower day. Back into this
range. This is the like no trade range
for me. I'm interested in bullish moves
over here. If they held this and then
did it even better. Now bulls are stuck
and bears are starting to take over.
This is stronger selling. Like I said,
the 30 minute does not look good for
bulls right now. PC starting to move
back downside and but we're back into
demand again. So, I just think it's very
possible this is a horrible uh market to
trade until Thursday because it's very
possible we build liquidity out for uh
Invidia on Wednesday.
Very very possible.
Back to the edge for current day. And if
they sell that, they sell this here as
possible. If they defend this straight
back in, this is your box at the moment.
This is the range rotation at the
moment. It can in fact get up here, but
it's pretty ugly. Pretty ugly out there.
Balls are defending this. Bears are
defending this. This is your range
rotation. This is what I'm leaving
alone. I'm interested in under here and
over here and up here right now.
Where's your SC?
Uh, I use everything, Jack. So I have
bookmat
I have uh footprints there and
footprints here on both ninja and uh
and uh trading view.
So I'm look what I'm really looking at
is the market orders the soaking in the
book the delta on the uh on the DOM and
then on footprint I'm only really look I
only really care about the delta when
I'm looking at areas of interest I don't
care otherwise right I don't need to if
you look at it all the time you will
become exhausted because it's so much
data for your brain to absorb what I
care about is when we get into levels of
interest if I'm thinking about a trade
how we're acting in all of this right
it's less interesting you can see the
key areas like the 90 to 110 or 90 to
like even from this big down close
candle PC on that was at 100 right and
if you look left was under over under
over under over under over nonstop into
that 100 um and then if you look at the
lows we've got excess selling at the
lows and if you look at the highs well
we had a bit of excess buying up at
those highs into 50 at 10:29 this
But we're just rotating between the two
extremes. No one's winning here. We're
just testing each level.
Cumulative delta, uh, I don't care about
so much. I care about more about the
delta on each chart. You could use
cumulative delta. I have it on a fivem
minute, but I don't really reference it
much. You could use it if you were
looking for, you know, divergence
between the delta. But I'm more
interested in, you know, support and
resistance or supply and demand zones in
leaving excess and trading away from
that zone. or if I'm looking for a
pullback into say we're looking for that
first pullback like we did this morning
when I saw excess on those buyers up
there. You're not going to see enough
info on cumulative delta. I don't think
unless you're looking for a trend or
reversion trade. Um
I'm more interested in a quicker moves
so to speak. So I'm I want more detail
than a CBD.
But you know each their own. It will
provide you good information. No doubt
about it.
But uh yeah, I'm more interested in
what's happening inside each candle in
in key areas.
Um well, do you mean on winning
percentages, Michael, or do you mean on
uh
uh do you mean on financial? I mean
definitely swing positions more.
not necessarily on winning percentages,
but uh bigger growth obviously. I mean,
my biggest winner this year was a 500%
trade over two or three months.
So, like you will make more money in
swing positions because you're because
you're willing to sit in it, right? And
normally I'm net long. When I'm when I'm
in a swing position, I want to be long
as much as possible until we're going
into like a bearish market. And even
then, I'm very careful. Look, if I was
going to take a swing on SQ,
I'd want to be very careful right now.
But I'm happy to bid in long in big
names overall because chances are over a
20 year career, right? I can sit in them
and they're going to go up if they're
good names.
Yeah. Like my biggest winner this year
was open. I traded that from like 198 to
11s. Um Apple I've been long since 202.
Sold some into the highs into the uh
280s or 290s wherever it was. AMD, I'm
still long from 158. Again, I sold some
into the 270s. That was uh PayPal was
flat on the year. Took that off. My only
loser this year, which was a tiny loser,
was OCR. Everything else uh swing wise
has been a big winner. Not surprising
considering we've been in a very bullish
market, right? So, swing longs will pay
you much more than day trade longs
in terms of percentage gains.
you trade SQ options. That makes sense.
I mean, you probably get better.
I don't know. You probably get better uh
if you're short or take puts on Triple
Q's than you would on calls on SQ
because of how it's built.
They're still defending the edge of this
range. Still nothing to do here, folks.
Vix is trying. VIX is trying to do that
inverse head and shoulder coming back
towards that New York open. But we've
got supply here at 21s. Can't get
through 21s.
Nice ball forward. Up 180 points today.
Not going to try and guess on this
range. Yeah, I'd like I'm the same. I'm
not up as much as you, but range just
looks a bit messy. VIX is trying to get
going here. Like you I'd look at this
and be like downside's coming. But like
there's been someone soaking the bid all
the day all day. It just depends if he
pulls if he pulls his bid. Yeah. Maybe
we trade outside current value area if
he pulls his bid. But do we look below
and fail outside of here? Right. Do we
look below and fail or do bears get that
full rotation? I don't know right now.
But all I do know is we've built a huge
amount of volume in here. We've been
here
for 40 minutes now.
But bears are not seeing that breakdown.
Bulls are not seeing that breakout. And
this is the range. And I'll tell you,
there's a lot of newbie traders who got
short here and lost and got long here
and lost and tried to short here again
and lost and long there again and lost
and short here again and lost. And uh
this is how we build liquidity for a
bigger break. Either a breakout or a
fail breakout will come. It's a matter
of time whether we're here for it or
not.
Jack, have you Here's a question for
you. Have you ever traded the um
short ETFs for
um
for like the quantum names? I'm trying
to think what they are
like the equivalent of being uh short
because they've got some names which are
like short IN short NQ short those kind
of names or long them and you can take
the short side on them because they they
will pay
mega if you can time it well
like I was long GL and it didn't really
pay much if we look at it right so I was
long GLL this here,
right? Why was I long this? I was long
this once gold faded, right? So, this is
a short gold ETF. I was long for this
move, but I mean that's nothing, you
know? It just shows because it these all
in include like the theta and decay.
Same as SQ and TQS. People don't
understand that it won't it's triple
leverage, but it also uh includes the
options market.
Vick starting to try and go here through
the 21s. It's coming up to its higher
day and it's New York open. VIX is
trying to go here.
Got you, Jack. Yeah, makes sense. Makes
sense.
Yeah, that's right. Locky.
All right, I'm just going to use a
bathroom here. Be careful. You're at the
edge of the range. Probably once I go,
you get a move. It's always the way.
I'll be right back.
Okay. Still in this range.
Ball's probably just taken over the edge
here. Let me have a look. Obviously, I
haven't been here to read the order flow
for you. Yes.
Uh, yes. Above 80s, above 280s, bulls
have taken over the edge there. So
that's what balls need to defend now.
Right time. Yeah.
And if you're struggling with this, if
you're looking at this getting chopped
up because you're struggling to identify
the edges of the range or anything like
that, just go to a higher time frame.
All right? Just go to a higher time
frame. Don't get pulled into tick for
tick or anything like that. If you're
struggling, you can just go to even an
M5. Just zoom into this.
All right, there's nothing to do here,
folks. This is your range. You can see
it on an M5. It's about as clear as you
can get. There's your range, right? Edge
to edge, edge to edge until you see a
breakout or a breakout or a fail
breakout or a fail breakout. That's all
you're going to get, right? No need to
force, is there? There's absolutely no
need to force.
Strong buying coming in again here.
Let's have a look at the mag. Google
still going. Google is still going.
Remember, they've got a lowhanging fruit
if they can get out of this range that
they've created. Bulls have low hanging
fruit to go for higher. It's a big if,
but that's what they're looking to do.
Every push to the top of the range,
guess what? It's being sold. Every push
to the bottom of the range, guess what?
It's being bought. Once we get out of
this range, this gray box, there is a
completion up here. If the mag's going
to find a bit. I tell you what, Vicks
just got absolutely clapped without me
being here at the 21s.
At the 21s.
So, what do we say? One. Was it 180? No,
80. Sorry. 80.
And the the rotation is just continuing
here.
And uh bulls got trapped on that last
push up
to VW up. So that gray box still holding
them down. And back down we go. So we're
going to test the 80s again. Look how
quickly it happens, right? It's crazy,
isn't it? VIX instantly found a bid
there.
Range to range to range to range to
range to range to range. Is anything
going to change? This is uh someone got
stuck up there on that last move. That
is for sure.
We just test the 80s. Just shy of the
80s.
Back to the 15s.
Where did that big seller come in?
25s.
Oh.
still defending.
So, we protected the 80s. Like I said,
it bulls defend this maybe, but like I'm
not trading in this.
You can see like look how big this last
candle was. Huge 50 point candle.
I don't know what they're doing with
this market. I don't think they know
what they're doing in this market right
now. Probably the biggest problem
they've got right now is that uh Google
is printing. If Google wasn't printing,
they'd probably be in a cell right now
to be honest. Google's still at 5%.
Bears want this lower at the moment, but
uh here's back to the 80s. This is where
bulls last defended. This is where balls
last defended. They're not going to have
too many more opportunities. Like at
some point, one of these edges is going
to let go. That's what's going to
happen. So, back to the 80s. Defending
the 80s. At some point, someone's going
to lose outside this edge. One of the
edges.
It's ugly out there. We expect this
though. We expect this till Wednesday.
To be quite honest, I expect this till
Wednesday
on an M15. Would I say there's a bull
flag?
No,
I would say it's just a range.
Back down to the low side again.
It's all Google. This is all Google
holding the market up. It's impressive.
5% up. I do find that mad, you know,
like
to start buying it as a retail because
Burkshire and Hathaways announced that
they probably started buying it a month
ago, no, weeks ago. It's why it's been
printing upside. Oh, we're going to buy
it now.
Okay, then.
Nothing's changed here. Big shelf here
developed at this PC, that's for sure.
big shelf at that PC in these 80s
and squeeze back up off it
and bears will try and defend Vup. And
if they fail, we go back to the gray box
and nothing's changed. Let's we can put
a gray box the other side if it makes it
really easy for you. I take this as the
edge, but let me do it.
Right. And there's your range rotation
between these two plots. Right. Now,
here to here.
You're just leaving excess both sides.
What's an M5? Five minute. A five minute
chart. So if you see hear me say M and
then a number it's minute minute 5
minute 1 H1 would be hourly the hourly
H4 H uh 4hour candle
why do I feel like we're not going to
get another trade in this session
probably burning a lot of options right
now I would imagine where are we trading
at on spy. Yeah, like I said early this
morning, 70 to 72 on spy is massive.
That was a huge, huge level. So, so far
defending both sides of that by the
looks of it.
Tesla looks good. Google looks good.
Nvidia 1.36 I'll give you a full
readout. Tesla 3.18% up. Nvidia 1.34%
down. Microsoft 0.38% down. Meta4% down.
Google 5.15% up. Amazon 1.90% down.
Apple 1.52% down. So they're not in
agreement, are they? The mag is not in
agreement. You don't have everything
selling together. You don't have
everything buying together. In fact,
let's have a look at the wider market as
well.
Yeah, most of the market red. All right.
Most of the market red. It's Google,
Tessa, AVGO.
Uh
BRKB, I'm guessing that's Bergkshire and
Hathaway. Uh utilities are up.
Healthcare, some of it's up, some of
it's down. Yeah, really two standout
stocks, Google and Tesla. Rest of the
market, not really.
And the battle continues. You're in no
man's land here. You are in absolute no
man's land.
Can we get one more trade? Is he going
to give us something?
Definitely still someone soaking the
tape this morning. So,
defending the edge of this range
definitely happening.
Um, but same the other side of it.
I wonder if there's a look below and
fail. That's what I'm wondering at the
moment. The bears feel like they win and
then get absorbed.
And we have got uh
Fed talk all day as well, haven't we?
Are they done? What time are they done?
Next one's on at one.
There's 80s again.
The chop continues here, folks.
Sub 80s. Now back towards the edge of
this gray box. This big node here, point
of control on the day. Remember, this is
fair value. This is the most traded
level so far on the day.
Seeing some aggressive selling try and
step in here and not moving lower. So
again, probably got someone soaking on
the bid for now.
And I wonder if they're going to do like
a look below and fail at some point
because you got a lot of stops down here
at this point. So, do they just keep
defending it or do they do a little stop
hunting and turn around?
I don't know, folks. I don't know what
they're going to do. At the moment,
they're defending it
right the way back up.
Oh, you got to laugh
back to the 80s.
I feel like they're going to do a look
below and fail. I don't think they can
keep propping it here. If if their
intention is to go higher, it's almost
like they're going to have to let more
sells come into the market first,
which would be a bit like this morning,
but in this current range basically
sweep the stops underneath this range
and then turn around is possible.
Can imagine that playing out. Can see
that possibly happening.
Fix just looks dreadful.
Fix looks like it's going to go into a
cell rather than uh squeeze out here to
me in my eyes.
Yeah, location not ideal to do much
right now. I would say if you're a range
trader, maybe you're enjoying this.
Maybe some of you really like it.
I'd say there's probably a sweep of
these stops probably coming at some
point. How we doing for time? We've got
a new hourly candle coming. So maybe in
here now we get a hourly sweep. Wouldn't
surprise me in the slightest. Did we
just pop them there? Not quite.
I still think they're going to run these
before moving higher, but I could easily
be wrong. I think they probably want to
move higher today and they probably need
to come and sweep everyone out first if
they're going to do that move. And we've
not really moved on the day. Like ENQ is
0.09% down on the day. We're basically
flat.
So, we're not seeing sellers really take
control of the market right now. We're
seeing liquidity being built. And I know
that we've got low hanging fruit higher.
We haven't got much low hanging fruit
lower because we swept it this morning.
So, my bias
is sort of to go higher, but probably to
go lower to go higher, if that makes
sense. I think we probably want to come
under this and then maybe have
unfinished business here. But uh unless
we get major sell pressure start to take
over here and we back test it. You know,
if we break down and back test this,
maybe we come to here. But I'm not
wouldn't be surprised to see something
like this playing out.
We just have to see.
Back to the 100s.
AMD is about to happen. What do you
mean? Doesn't look like it's doing
anything. It's just literally at the
middle of nowhere of its current day
range. Not sure what you're what you're
seeing. Doesn't look like much to me.
Oh, nice. Haristston, nice work.
All right. Can they pop these stops and
then let's see what happens afterwards?
So, yes is the answer. They're going to
pop these stops. There we go. All right.
This is what I thought would happen.
Now, what happens next becomes
important.
What happens next becomes important
because if they pop these stops and
start turning around, then everyone
who's just entered short for this
breakdown is going to get caught.
And if they defend this area that
they've just built volume at for the
last hour, then maybe we move lower. But
I would say if we reclaim it, then I
wouldn't want to be bearish. Let's say
that way. If we reclaim it,
what's the previous day value area low?
25,000.
Let's see.
So, New York open previous day value
area low here. This is the edge of the
shelf that we've just broken out from.
How we at now becomes important. Are we
going to trade all the way down into
this pocket? Or are we going to reclaim
this? Is this just a big old trap and
we're going to squeeze back higher for
unfinished business? I don't know,
folks. I have no idea. Can only react to
the market. I can't guess the market. It
would not surprise me to see this
reclaim the range and go right back up
to the upside if it does. Wouldn't
surprise me in the slightest.
IBH and IBL. They're the purple lines on
your chart, right? This is your IBL 56,
IBH 254
or something, 255.
Purple lines on my chart are always the
initial balance.
So, it hasn't reclaimed that range yet,
which we broke down from that sort of 60
I guess is the level. VIX is starting to
try and push here. So bears are trying
to take control of this market right
now. We're right back to sort of where
we found a bid from this morning.
Wouldn't surprise me if they reclaim
this range. It wouldn't surprise me to
see a giant squeeze back out. Big if. It
is a big big if right now, but it would
not surprise me. Here's the retest of
this sort of range and let's see what
they do. Because if they reclaim this,
it would not surprise me to see a giant
squeeze. If they reject this, then
possibly we trade lower on the session.
So far, no reclaim with this gray box.
So, bears are in control so far. And
this target would be uh previous day
value area low, initial balance low on
the day, and if we got very weak back
down into uh Friday's lows, I'd be very,
very cautious trading in here. For me, I
would not be surprised to see a short
squeeze in this market. It really would
not surprise me. They played at the
edges all day. This is your sort of
level coming up into 60ish. Seeing some
selling into that so far. So, just
watching to see if they defend or if
they let a short squeeze happen here.
Either way, very, very tricky kind of
day today
as we build liquidity. And like I said,
I wouldn't surprise you to see us do
this all the way to Wednesday. So,
here's the test towards sort of 60 at
the moment. That's just sort of over
under that gray box above you. Even the
point of control 80, you could use that.
we get above that balls probably take
control of the session. You can see a
bigger squeeze out if that happens.
And it can get violent here quickly both
sides, right? Because you're going to
have one side's going to get stuck,
right? They are going to get stuck. One
side is absolutely going to get stuck.
So test of 60. Big buying coming in
here. Can they defend it? These bears.
So this gray box is what we're testing.
60 to 80 is the level. Bulls reclaim
that probably squeeze out that
definitely towards these highs and
probably at that point towards high day.
Bears defend this then they're going to
be looking for IB low
and bears defending it so far.
It's still holding. These are the days
that I'm least interested in trading. As
you well know, I like moves outside of
value. They're the best moves in my
mind.
Google pulling back about half a percent
so far. So, are they done with it? I
doubt it, but we'll see.
Okay, defending that range bears like
successfully so far. defending that
range. Well,
there's day value area low into sort of
25,000. So, if I was a bear, I'd be
covering some into this box now down to
25K
and then I'd be holding for low day and
I'm not in any of this at all.
Bit of sell pressure coming on Goo here.
Not a lot, but a little bit. And here's
your previous day value area low. Now,
bulls will want to defend this. Fail to
defend this. We're going to go New York
open I uh initial balance low.
So, here's previous day value area low.
So, I'd be covering some into this. If
any of you took this move here, retest
stayed heavy. Your cover is here and
here. and runners if you get lucky all
the way down to here. But I'd be
covering some into these pockets.
The high time frame overall for me is is
bearish. It's just I think we're going
to need to build out liquidity for a day
or two.
We are starting to set up the sort of H1
potential head and shoulder, but it's
very very risky.
Very very risky
trading inside of value looking for
something like that.
Okay, so bit of a bid on previous day
value area low there
and I'd say 60s is the trigger for a
squeeze. They get back above 60s as a
squeeze. Until then, bears are in
control until we get back above here.
Bears are in control and they can target
all the way down here if they want.
Back above 60s or back above 60 to 80s.
Balls can take control of a of a squeeze
out. Nothing more than that, but just a
squeeze out potentially.
Potentially.
Remember, it's Google that's been
holding this market up today and it's
starting to uh you're starting to see a
bit of profit taking in GooG here. This
can get violent. These are big moves,
folks. Your ATR still very very big.
There's previous day value low coming
back down to that New York open. There's
the 25,000 initial balance coming up.
So, if you're shorting this, you look
good. Make sure you are locking in some
profits. Please do not get your self
caught trying to short at low of day
here. All right. Not in a rotating
market. You are asking for problems if
we do that.
Just watching the order blow now. Lots
of bears came flying in at those lows.
They came absolutely flying in at that
New York open.
So if they don't get a print under that,
you might get that move back towards 60.
And then how we at there is what really
matters for the rest of the day cuz
that's a range that they've created. It
looks very bearish right now though.
The bears call those lows for sure.
The 25,000 retest
if they flush this
maybe low of day. Well, it should go low
of day if they flush this. If they can't
reclaim, you would expect initial
balance low to be tested.
This previous day value very low is kind
of interesting level.
25,000 interesting level here.
Shorts came in under 98. So back to
previous day value area low. And if they
go back through this, they can might
want to revisit those 60s. This is the
big, remember, it's the same level from
this morning, folks. This is the same
level, previous day value area low. If
we trade under this, we can trade lower.
If we go back through it, we're back
into the internal range again. So,
here's the start of a squeeze. Shorts
got caught there. And now, it's going to
depend how we trade when we get up to
60s. Remember, 60s is the level here.
The bigger squeeze, this can still be a
look below and fail. This level up here
is what's important.
And if we reclaim all of that, oh my
god, it could get nasty. Like I said,
this is how we rotate. This is exactly
what you're seeing how we rotate and
catch people. Okay, so rotation,
rotation, rotation, rotation, rotation,
rotation breakdown. This level becomes
important. If bulls defend this, if too
many bears came in here, which is what's
happened so far, we retest this. We can
do rotation between here, or we can
reclaim and go on a big old short
squeeze if too many got caught there.
This can be a look below and fail on a
reclaim of here. till that point it's
technically bearish but this candle here
did catch bears underneath that New York
open.
We uh if you look at the book map I know
it's small on your screen you can see
look at this selling from uh 2511
down to
94 is basically low of day. They came
aggressive aggressive aggressive and
we've bid back off that low of day.
They've not seen acceptance lower yet.
It is just yet but that's what I'm
seeing so far.
But yeah, we're bearish on the tape, but
we're in a range rotation. So, I'm not
thinking about a trending environment.
Not thinking about a trending
environment.
It's going to have to prove itself.
I hate that ENQ didn't get up to
previous day value area high or previous
day high. I hate that. That's a
naughty naughty NQ.
made my money today. Yeah, nice be you.
Good work.
I've had one one trade. That's it. I'm
just waiting to see if something else
will set up for me. Be nice if it would.
I don't have a whole lot of edge here.
Uh VIX is actually getting above the New
York open, which is impressive.
ES
spy. Oh, did you see that? Spiders and
ES are at 50day and initial balance low.
So they have relative weakness. That's
because Google and Tesla heavier awaited
in the cues.
Still strong selling coming in here.
And are they really going to uh
are they really going to go for Friday's
lows? Not getting back up to the highs
in New York. It's possible. It's not
what I think they're going to do, but uh
trying to remain flexible to the charts.
Okay, ES has taken IB low and trading
back well inside just about. Same with
the spiders. Q's not there yet. So Q's
trying to play catch up.
Tate moves quick here. Tate moving
quick.
Remember this is the kind of area they
bid off this morning.
So I wouldn't want to be a new money
short down here. Let's put it that way.
There's no there's no long trigger, but
I would not want to be a new money short
down here. All right, your short
location really. It was up here. It's
pain in the butt. And surprise, I'm
surprised they just did one retest and
uh didn't quite make it, but it shows
the strength of the bears there.
Yeah, Google's starting to really pull
back about a cent back from where it
was.
down slightly.
Let's get that New York open.
Oh, big selling here. Woof woof woof.
All right, they're looking for 70s now.
They're selling hard. So, if you're in
the short, you look good.
Make sure you've paid yourself around
this level. This is where we traded down
to this morning. If they get under this,
there's a block here. If they get under
this
700's possible, if they get there
without giving me the entry I wanted at
the highs, I'll be a little bit miffed.
Let's see.
No, just just spy and QQQ for me. I
don't really trade any of the other ETFs
like the metals, the energies. Very
occasionally. Like I said, I I did take
a long on goo earlier this year for the
pull back on gold, but that was it.
Don't think they're done with this yet.
Still lots of selling
coming back down to that initial balance
low
and that block there really under IB low
goes all the way down to 900. Yeah, down
to here it's possible and then under
that nothing until we get to Friday's
lows. So if they have set up
this sort of head and shoulder or this
cup and handle to go lower without
taking the uh previous day high out in
New York means London traders get all
the fun. We will see
maybe Dex just remember like overall the
market has been quite bearish. Macro
news is quite bearish.
Momentum is bearish.
We are now underneath uh previous day
value. That's technically bearish. Just
remember all these things, right? We
we're in a bearish market at the moment.
We're we're trying to move out of
previous days value area low and uh
which is here, which means we've gone in
rotation. It's possible. It is. You
cannot rule out a puke down to here
today. I'm not saying it does it, but
just based on rules of engagement, you
can't rule it out. Can't rule it out.
There's your IB.
Tape still heavy.
Tape is still heavy here, folks.
Vick's really starting to get going now,
guys. It's into its next pivot. So, next
next stop for the VIX really is 22.
If it gets over 22,
next stop is 23s
and fast. So, just be aware of that.
We're very volatile. You are outside a
previous day's value area low right now.
Just just remember that we have moved
outside of value. If they want to go for
the Friday lows, they can. I wanted be I
wanted to be in shorts today for those
Friday lows off a push to the highs. But
uh
after what I saw this morning, I thought
maybe we'd save it for tomorrow. But
we're breaking away from volume. We're
looking lower. We're going to look down
to see if we can find fair value. Now,
that might be here. It might be down
here. We don't know. It might be that
they trade back upside. We don't know.
All we can do is react to what the
market's doing.
There's the squeeze back up.
Previous day value area low is an
important level now folks. Okay. If
we're under that, we are technically
potentially in a trend day uh lower,
especially if we move under IB. we
reclaim previous day value area low.
This is a look below. Like one of you
just said that you were looking for a
look below. This would be a look below.
Right now I'm not seeing enough shorts
caught at those lows, but it's possible.
We had like three micro drives in there
which you can't see in a one minute
tape, but if you look at the book map
above me, you can see one, two, three.
There were some shorts down here. 85
lot, 50 lot, 97 lot. There's definitely
some absorbing going on down there. I'm
not sure they finished with the auction
yet, but let's see. We're going to find
out soon enough, but I would be very
very uh
aware of your New York open and previous
day value area low for your bias.
Yeah, Richard, I was short this morning.
Yeah, we've lock we've locked in money
this morning. Uh, everyone was long um
for that look below and fail this
morning. I took where was I short? This
short first b first bounce short.
This short. I wanted to be short above
here. That's what I was looking for
today.
And now we're potentially in range
rotation slash. We can be in a trend if
we start letting go of this. All right.
If we start I just want to make this
clear. If we let go of this
and we let go of this, this can offer a
move here because if we zoom out,
that is possible. Cannot rule that out.
Uh Richard, I know I think you're in
Discord, right? If you look in Discord,
look at what we look the two trades we
talked about this morning. Both have
started happening.
In my discord,
right,
I can get this over to you guys. All
right, this to move lower into 24158
over the week and today probable range
rotation between them to create that
liquidity. All right, so
Vick's still going.
Nothing to bid off right now, folks. For
those of you looking long, there's
nothing to bid off right now. We are
outside of previous day value. We're at
initial balance low. We're at an area of
interest, but we can still trade lower
if it wants. MAG, remember, has been
heavy other than Tesla and Google, which
have started pulling back off their
drives, which have been going all day.
Just be aware of that. If you go in a
squeeze, it will become very, very
obvious.
I'd be very, very cautious trying to
pick bottoms. If we're breaking out
outside of previous day's value area
low, there are targets below. Remember,
we've been in a heavy market. Friday was
a short squeeze up. Today, we've gone in
some range rotation and we're in like a
an area where we've built well, an area
an area up here we've built lots of
liquidity. It just depends what their
ambitions are. I would say before
Wednesday before Wednesday what is their
ambition in this market before Wednesday
that's what matters
structure right now bearish flow zone's
bearish
did any of you take this I'm actually
fairly surprised they let this work but
did any of you take that I mean Very,
very nice. Tight risk for that move. I
didn't take it. I didn't think I didn't
think they'd give it to us.
I thought maybe they'd test twice, but
there we go.
But like, you know, I'm a little bit
more hesitant as a trader when we're
trading in these kind of ranges. They're
not my favorite trades. I know they are
not my strong point. My strong point is
when we move outside of these areas.
This is where you would see last week,
Tuesday, and was it Thursday? Tuesday
and Thursday last week where we caught
two 300 point bangers
in three micros. You took the short on
the Russell around there. Nice. So, lots
of you got it. Good work. Good work.
Good work. As long as you're trading
your plan, it's all that matters.
Remember, I'm I'm human. I can call
stuff, but when I know that something is
not my uh my strong point, I have to at
least be
aware of it. Like I talk about, get get
around the golf course with an eight eye
and I'm not trying to get the driver
out, you know, in a uh in a bunker.
Let's put it that way, right?
Market's moving fast here. The tape is
moving very very quick. Up, down, up,
down, up, down. This is a battle
starting to develop here.
I'd be very cognizant of that uh
previous day value area low and New York
open. That is a massive, massive area.
If they reclaim that,
then are probably all the way back up to
64s.
So, I see bulls try and come in here.
They are trying to come in here to get
back towards previous day value area
low. Bears are defending very, very
well. Man, this tape's moving so quick.
So maybe a 25,000 check and if they get
through that maybe a squeeze to 25,60 is
basically what I'm saying. If they
defend that, maybe new low of day.
So they're trying to get up to that
25,000 like we just talked about.
And if they get back inside previous
day's value, it's going to be a look
look below and fail, right? If they get
back inside of previous days value, it's
possibly a look below and fail. Here's
previous day's value. If they get back
inside of this that I could imagine it's
not the best excess here, but I could
imagine if if they can get back inside
this why bears will want to defend this
for a breakdown. Bulls will want to
reclaim this for a move back to this
area.
This is why these days are definitely
not my favorite days to trade. When we
move outside of these days, they become
my favorite days to trade.
So, as a whole, the mag right now is
flat. Even with Tesla 2.80% up and
Google 4% up, the mag as a whole is flat
because everything else is selling.
No worries, Jack.
Yeah, no worries, Jack. Uh, what did you
take, Jack? You were short today. Are
you Are you long off IB? Sorry, I might
have forgotten. The tape's moving quick.
Here we go. So, here's the test of
25,000. They're trying to test that New
York open previous day value area low.
If they get through here, okay, then a
move to 60 is possible. Bears might come
flying in here, folks. All right. They
might come flying in here, the bears,
and just be like, "What do you think
you're doing? We're going lower." We
don't know.
This a massive level as we come into the
come into these levels.
At the moment, they've not even been
able to test 25,000. Bears defending 90s
at the moment. So, not even into the
25,000s yet. They might not let them
into there. They might keep defending
it.
Little bit of bullish excess on that
last move up.
Let's see.
Google really starting to sell here,
folks. be be a little bit careful. It's
now only 3.83% up. Remember about 10
minutes ago it was 5 and a half% up. So
you're starting to see that pullback on
the Google
retesting towards these lows now. Now
this is where it's going to get very
very tricky. They're going to build out
a range here and you know the
battlegrounds. I've given you the B
battlegrounds. Basically IB low to
previous day value area low. Those are
the battlegrounds. Someone is going to
get hurt. Here is the squeeze up towards
25,000.
Can they get through 25,000? This is the
question now.
If they can, we're going to go uh tens
and then 60s for those of you long. So,
if they can bid over this,
like we talked about, if they can bid
over this, this is available. If they
defend this, they will look for a wash.
This is your rotation. IBL to previous
day value area low. Here you go. So,
here's the squeeze through. Can they
hold above it? It's not just the
squeeze, it's the hold above it. Here's
2510s.
Very important. Now, for those of you
long, lock some in because you don't
know if they sell this. And if they hold
the dip back into it, then you look good
for a move to 25,000. And where's this?
60 to 80.
Big buying came in there. So, shorts
getting squeezed out here.
And the buyers have won this rotation.
So they need to hold a pullback now. The
buyers must hold a pullback now.
Otherwise, it's nothing more than a
short squeeze. Buyers need to hold a
pullback if we're going to go up towards
those 60s.
Otherwise, it's just a squeeze out,
right? So buyers must hold a pullback to
create some structure. And ideally, that
pullback would be around the value area
low. You wouldn't want to see it go
lower than that. Really, definitely not
lower than New York open.
So you look good. You look good.
Hold on to your runners if you can. Make
sure you've paid yourself like we always
talk about. But here you go. All right.
Now, I'm in this long at this point. Can
we get up to 60s?
Can we get up to 60s?
Can we get up to 60s is 40s. I'd love to
get to 60s and 80s if possible.
I got to move my book mat so I can see
the order flow. Look how quickly it
moves. I can't even see the order flow.
It's so quick right now. 50s 10 more
points if possible. Moving my stop up
with it because this is short squeezy.
Okay, stopped out there on the little
piece of it. We want to still hold a
pullback. So, let's see.
I want to see this hold pull back if I'm
going to get any more size into this.
Looks good. Looks good. They just
retrapped there. That's not deep enough
for me to re-enter, but uh it looks good
for everyone long from lots of you long
from down here. Even if you use a little
trend line, look, very nice and simple,
right? Shame we haven't built liquidity
here. That's what would be really nice.
But this is your TP. And if you get
through this hive day, and I'm not
joking. If you get through this gray
level, you can go 55s and then hive day.
And I'm absolutely dead serious about
that because we're in a rotational
market, right? If bears fail,
they failed to break down with
conviction under here. They got stuck.
We've squeezed back over. We need to
hold a pullback here. Really, you'd want
to see a pullback hold this. This is
your TP, then this, and then high of
day. And I'm deadly serious. This can be
really nasty in a rotational market.
It's why you don't short lows.
Here you go, folks. his 60s. So TP1 here
between 60 and 80 is your TP1.
You must pay yourself here. Please
respect the structure. This is a big
shelf. Starts at 60. It gets a bit
thicker into sort of 7780 which is
probably where it's about to revisit.
All right. So as long as you paid
yourself some, just hold on to your
runners now because these shorts are in
big trouble. All right. So the shorts at
the lows are at trouble. We're going to
use their pain to here. If we use shorts
in here's pain. I'm looking for a
re-entry here unfortunately. If we use
shorts in here as pain, we will rotate
between here. If we break out of this
guy, we're going to go for high of day.
So, if you're long from here, TP here.
Hold on to see if you can get up to this
and this.
All right. But you must TP here. You
must must must. It's your point of
control. It's the most traded area of
the day. You can see the volume shelf
here. must TP some out here
because this is a squeeze and they can
pull all the way back down to 25,000.
Why is my mouse going mental? 20. Yeah,
25,000. That's where I was looking to
read on after I sold that last push. So,
they can come right back down to here.
No problem at all because we lack
structure and the squeeze started.
Shorts got caught at
86 86 to 82 and bulls came flying in
from 98 to 07 and we've got a ton of
imbalances on this push up. All right,
so they can we can snap nasty down and
still be uh bullish and then recover. So
you should be like a bit lighter in size
here.
Really nice. Here you go. Squeezing
more. Please pay yourself because
there's a lot of balls coming in here.
You got to pay yourself some money. If
you haven't paid yourself yet, you must
pay yourself some money. If we get
through this, well then I feel very
sorry for those people who don't
understand a rotational market.
They're about to get absolutely butt
hurt, aren't they?
But yeah, congrats everyone. I did catch
a piece of it. Unfortunately, not all of
it. But, you know, like I said, I have
weaknesses. My weaknesses are rotational
markets. I can see them really clearly.
I justing hate them. I love it when we
move outside of ranges more. But at
least I can help you guys. If I'm
helping you guys see it and trade it and
understand it, whether you're making
money or if I'm helping you just not get
caught. If you are someone that would
normally short the lows there, I help
you not get caught. That's also a win
for me.
We're lacking some structure here, guys.
If you look at bookmap, we are literally
straight up since uh we took out those
offers at 24,983.
Okay, so just this why I'm saying you
got to pay yourself,
right? We're lacking
structure. If you're looking at Have I
got you on book map now? Yes. Can you
see that? Hope you can. We are lacking
structure since here. This guy here, see
this guy here? This was the break. We're
lacking structure. That's uh almost 100
points back down. All right, so just be
smart. Doesn't mean it can't keep going.
It can, but I don't want you guys giving
a 100 points back. You'll be very upset
if you give a full 100 points back
without taking some profits.
Big buying up here at the top, which is
not what you want to see. So just be
careful.
Yeah, Dex, that was it was you that
called it, right? You were looking for a
look below the eye below. And I was
saying to you, just be careful. Um, but
it was you absolutely you nailed it. You
nailed it. It did exactly what you
wanted.
It did do what you wanted and it did it
did leave some excess down there. Um, if
we look at these lows,
it's these guys that got caught. Look,
all these guys getting caught at the
lows. This is what you want to see. It's
beautiful. And then, like I said, it was
moving quick. You can't see it in a one
minute chart, but at these lows, they
had three attempts to move lower um in
this in this one minute candle.
Basically, from 1120
to 11:2130. So, where's 1120?
This candle here, they had three
attempts to move lower within that
candle. That's when order flow is
useful. Like I said, I'm more interested
when we're at levels of interest, how we
operate. I don't want to look at it all
the time. You're starting to see a
pullback to point of control. Now, they
can hold.
Guess what they can do? Guess what they
can do. All right, it's told you that's
what it likes to do. They can do this.
They can also come down to here and find
a bid, but they can hold this now and
box in for a while and build out more
liquidity. And if they do that, what are
they building? They're building one of
these intraday. So just be smart.
You're welcome everyone.
It's it's moving quick. So when you
catch it when you catch a squeeze, you
know, if you took uh who is it? Sorry,
Dex. Dex took the look below and fail.
So he would have got in somewhere around
here. I'd assume there's Keep it simple.
Trend line break. Whatever you want to
see. Excess down below. Reclaim. Reclaim
previous day low. Even if you took
previous day value area low, reclaim.
All right. Look how quickly it went.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
Seven minutes straight up. Straight up.
I was I was thinking this was going to
come down, stop me out, and then repick
me up because I had a limit sitting here
for it, but it it didn't. So be it. It
is what it is.
Yeah, Bulls have taken control. Uh,
you've got 25 minutes left. Bulls have
taken control of current day since
11:20ish.
But I'm just going to remind you when we
zoom out. All right, this is why I'm
keep telling you to take profit.
Here's Friday's rotation.
All right, there's your look above and
fail.
Here's excess from Friday, which we've
held. And we are overall,
this is your previous week
rotation.
This is a huge level here. All right.
Technically, we're bearish.
We become bullish if we hold this for
the rotation to 25 and then it's a
battleground in here to decide if they
do that or if it's just a big big dump.
So, we have to be cautious. We're not in
multiple time frame alignment. All
right? We are not in that.
So it's what am I trying to say? It was
a better way of me saying this. See
money, take money, hold runners. Don't
enter late. If you enter late in this
market, this is going to be like what
were the good days last week? Tuesday,
Thursday. This is going to be like
Monday, Wednesday, last week. This week
will be like Monday, Wednesday, last
week until we get outsider value.
Yeah. Lots of you grabbing this. Well
done, folks. Yeah, W's in chat if you
got it. It's always nice for me to see
if, in fact, if you got any big wins
with me today, whether you took that
long of the look below and fail this
morning or you took the little short
continuation with me or you took this
short breakdown or you took the long
back up. I mean, the nice thing with
rotations is they do offer numerous
plays, don't they? Look below and fail.
Oh, look how many plays you've had
today. Look below and fail. Long. First
bounce short breakdown short look below
and fail long. So you've had one, two,
three, four trade opportunities today. I
wouldn't say any of them are A+, but
they're trade opportunities giving you
100 sometimes 200 points.
Awesome. Yeah, lots of them got got
them. Nice everyone.
Nice everyone. Okay, so we are still
squeezing in this market and VIX got
clapped. All right, but you have a
little bit of excess coming up here.
Like you can't be a new money long up
here. All right, you cannot be a new
money long in the middle of this
box. All right, you are already long.
You don't want to be in new money long
in the middle of here. If you just added
there, I don't blame you, but it's
risky. But if you got in any of these on
the reclaimed, that's great. If they can
hold this, it's good. If they can get
anywhere up here, that's a TP. You don't
want to be long up here or up here,
right? You don't want to be adding long
up there. You do not because they can
come up here and go, "Nope, back down."
And this is 100 points. That will hurt.
And if they want to come right down
here, it's going to be 200 points,
right? So, be smart. your locations when
we're in rotation are so important. So I
say to newer traders like trending
markets when we get days which are
trending when we're breaking out of a
range they're easier to trade because if
you buy the pullback is way more likely
to be nice for you. If you buy late
because you're a newer trader and you
miss it. It's still more likely to be
nice to you if you're trading in the
direction of the trade. If you are late
on a ranging market it will hurt you. If
you were late and took short here it
will hurt you. If you're late and get
long here, there's a good chance it will
hurt you. If you were late and got long
here, you got hurt. Same in here. Short
here, hurt. Long there, hurt. Short
there, hurt. Long there, hurt. Right?
Because they don't understand. You trade
the opposite. This is not a trend. You
trade the edges. You trade the edges.
You trade the edges. Right? It's one of
the biggest things that I try and teach
you guys. And the same in the course.
Identify the conditions. It's going to
make your life a whole lot easier if you
understand the conditions.
Oh, I'm due a payout. just see that
funded next.
So, I'm at 20 uh 25. I'm at 5,596
after 5 days. Do I take a payout or All
right, here's another question for you.
Anyone trading funding next with the
Halloween sale on the what the accounts
called? Legacy accounts. Can I trade 30
days without taking a payout? Do I need
to do like a payout every 5 days or can
I just trade to 30 days and then take it
all out?
Squeeze happening here. Shorts are
getting squeezed here. Shorts are
getting squeezed here.
Big level coming up here, folks. Big
level coming up here. This gray box. Big
level.
But Matt cannot keep up. That's how
quick we're moving.
Yeah. If if anyone's traded those
funding next legacy counts, do I need to
take a payout? Like, do I need to do
five days, five days, five days, five
days, or can I just run it up to 30 days
and then take it all out?
Anyone know? It's my first time trading
with them. That's why I'm asking.
150 is here. Oh my god, these shorts are
absolutely cooked.
How long we got left? 20 minutes.
20 minutes. This thing's flying. This is
just another giant short squeeze.
looking for buy. Uh, you're very late.
You don't want to be buying up here.
Like we talked about, you're in the
middle of the chop range now from
earlier. Look left. You can see the
rotations from earlier. The buy was down
here on the reclaim of this, right? This
was your look below, look below value,
came back upside. That was the buy.
Maybe if you're want to trade range, you
can think about a buy to here or to this
shelf.
I would argue it could do something like
this if it really wanted. So, I don't
know how you're going to manage your
risk on that, but yeah, you definitely
don't want to be buying up here.
Hey, nice locket. Yeah, looking forward
to working with you. Yeah, for anyone
joining, I have got a um Black Friday
sale on. I haven't announced it yet, but
for you guys in chat, I know lots of you
are asking, just code BF, 25% off
everything in the on the website. So,
any of the courses, any of the
indicators, and it will uh it's first
come, first served, and it will finish
December 1st.
Code BF
Nice Dex. Yeah, I think that's a great
trade, Dex. That's a great trade and
that's a great read from you. You knew
what you were looking for. You said it
very clear. I'm looking for a look below
and fail underneath IB. There it came. I
don't know if you joined in here or in
here, but wherever you joined, you've
got, you know, probably 150 points out
of it. You probably took some profit on
the way, but it's perfect into here.
Great trade. It's a really, really good
trade. It makes sense and you said it
before you took it. You knew what you
were looking for. It's a really good
trade, mate. Well done. All that
matters. It doesn't matter about the
money. It doesn't matter about the size.
Doesn't matter about anything else. All
that matters that you understood the
trade setup that you were looking for
and you executed that setup. That's all
that matters.
right into this range rotational zone
again. And remember, you're very close
to lunch now, folks. I think we will.
There's a good chance we can continue
rotating and rotating and rotating all
day. Um, let me have a quick look at the
breadth again in this market. Let's
reset this.
Still doesn't look too great out there.
I'm going to be honest, folks. like
Google and Tessa the only ones. So
Google's trying to find a bid or has
found a big bid again. So I'd say like
okay some of healthcare like UNH Johnson
some stuff like that's up. Utilities are
green. Um Google Test are green. AGO up
1%. Um WMT what's that? Walmart they got
earnings this week haven't they as well.
That'll be interesting. Um,
and then everything else just red, just
a red board.
It will be interesting this week like
how much are consumers getting hurt
right now? I think they're really
struggling to pay for stuff.
average price of a uh
four person family grocery shop per
month now over $1,000 for the first time
in the history of America.
That's the average price.
Way, way, way too much. Debt is bad
right now. Consumer debt is also bad.
Not just gov debt. Like uh delinquencies
are up. Um,
inability to pay off credit cards are
highest in 15 years. Inability to pay uh
off your car loans, repossessions also
very high and student debt also very
high. Does it start to show or do we see
the question is for me on things like
Walmart. Do we see things like Walmart
and Costco with really good earnings and
do we see see like the more expensive
brands with bad earnings or do we just
see a squeeze in all of it where no
consumers are really buying? They're
really really locked down right now. And
how does that start to play into the
tape?
Interesting interesting few weeks ahead.
I mean because we're going to get data
for the first time in what 6 to 8 weeks.
You just got a call from student loan.
Yeah. I mean, no one's no one's being
able to make payment. They're re it's
really bad out there, folks. People are
really struggling. People are really
really struggling to make ends meet. Um,
you know, the narrative can be as long
as they want, oh, the stock market's at
all time highs and the stock market and
your own financial position, economic
pressure are not the same things. And
like we saw in the market should have
crashed in 07, didn't crash to 08.
And the other thing is I didn't really
talk about it in the newsletter, but if
you look like Michael Bur, okay, he's
got a big short position out on uh
Nvidia and Palanteer, but he actually
just closed down his fund because he
said his words were basically this
market is completely irrational. Yeah,
no [\h__\h] That's what markets are. He's a
very very good trader and even he's
saying it's irrational. But if you look
back in the history of time, when are
two other big bears, when did they close
their funds? Because they were like,
"This makes no sense." One closed in '
07 and one closed in like 1980 or 1979,
right before both crashes. Right? So the
warning signs are there, but you know,
markets can stay irrational longer than
we can stay solvent. And the one thing
I've got back in the back of my head is,
do hedge funds need this market to go on
a giant Santa Claus rally? and short
squeeze to new alltime highs so they can
get their Christmas bonuses. It's the
only thing I've got in my head. Do they
just go f the macro, f the problems,
let's squeeze this out. We want to get
paid. Who knows? Who knows? The nice
thing is we're day traders. Our job is
to get 100 points plus out of it and
walk away each day.
Yeah. Yeah. Well, Rosco, remember that's
the average price. It depends what state
you're in. So, some states obviously m
much lower. Um, that's the average
price. I mean, it mine would be well
over that here in Los Angeles for sure.
ET, I have five kids and I'm trying to
get better at cooking beans.
I love beans, man. Americans find it
weird. Beans on toast. English
tradition. Best food.
heard some podcasts with biggest
mortgage director in some big US bank
like 70% of house purchases 25 to 35 are
paid by parents cash only 30% through
the mortgage. Yeah. I mean it's m it's
it's hard it's got to be hard to get on
the market right now. Um,
you know, I uh I I bought my place in
when I was 25
or 26. 26.
I was 26. 26 or 27. Um, I got screwed to
be honest. I was self-employed working
as a um DJ and a music producer. So, I
got a horrible interest rate for the
first year because they wouldn't I
couldn't get an interest rate elsewhere.
I I put a good chunk down, put like 30%
down, saved up. Me and my wife lived in
a tiny little flat in Stratford, ate
literally noodles for a year and saved
up um to because I knew we got to get in
the market now because it's only going
to get harder and we've been fortunate
enough to be able to um you know, pay it
off. Um which we did when the interest
rates got put up to 9%. our mortgage
repayment jumped from like 600 600 700
to like something outrageous like uh
like 1,400 a month while we were living
in America paying uh bills here. And
when I say 1,400 I mean sterling. So it
was more like $2,200.
So we paid it off as quickly as we can
but it's got to be tough. It's it's very
tough out there.
Okay. Okay, so here's your previous week
value area low. You're still you still
look good. I don't like how they've
built this structure. But if you're long
from the lows, it's good. At some point,
we're likely to do this move here
because we built this structure out in a
horrible fashion. But if they come all
the way up here, then you guys have the
best trade of the day. Other than that
open one. If you took that and this and
it goes all the way up, it's the best
trade of the day. I'd say this is even
better. That's a fantastic trade. But
just be careful. I would not be long
here. The way they've built this, this
is very dangerous. No one's been swept
out. They can come right back down to
this after taking these highs. They can
come right back down before they go
higher. They can come back down here,
get trapped and go lower. I don't want
to trade in this range. For me
personally, I maintain that here and I
maintain it here. This is a dangerous
spot to be caught in. But if you are
long off those lows, you look really
good. You can just keep holding your
runner. It looks really good.
Oh, not smashed pea. Mashed mashed peas
we call it, Richard. Yeah, fish and
chips and mashed mashed peas.
Or if you're from I don't know if any of
you from uh I'd say the Midlands up into
into like Liverpool and stuff. They love
uh what do you love? You love curry
sauce on your chips, don't you? If
you're from up there. Curry sauce. It's
a big thing.
I know you're busy at the moment, Alex.
How do I join the Discord group when you
get a moment? Okay, go to the uh you've
just purchased the course, right? Go to
the end of the course and there'll be a
module. Uh I don't know if it's titled
Discord or community and it has my email
in it. Um just send me an email from the
email that you purchase the course at
and I'll get you uh I'll get you in the
Discord, my friend.
So, still squeezing up. You've got uh
seven minutes till lunch. Man, like I
said, if they reclaim this, I wouldn't
be surprised seeive day. A bit pissed
off it's uh not pick me up for more
size. So, I had I didn't have too much
size on
for my entry
and I sold maybe was it this little bit
here and then wanted to get repicked up.
Never came. So, that that's my fault.
was badly managed, but I'm not surprised
because I I hate trading range, so
doesn't surprise me at all.
Mushy peas. Yeah.
And the squeeze continues here, folks.
Do please do not enter long up here.
Please. Even if this goes up and you get
paid, it is such a bad entry. It would
just be luck if you get paid in this and
it would be rewarding you for bad
trading. These are the kind of areas you
don't want to trade in. We've just
walked this whole thing up. We squeezed
and then we walked without washing
anyone out. You do not want to be a new
long at these highs.
Anyone that's emailed me, I'll um I'll
get back to you as soon as the stream's
finished. I can see quite a few of you
emailed me. As soon as the stream's
done, I'll get back to you.
All right, Vic still coming down side.
You still look good to hold on. Like I
said, I wouldn't be a new money long
here, but if you are already long, you
look good to try and hold.
Yeah, can it can keep going. Um, the
only thing I'd say is like
when you see these, right, no one's been
stopped out, right? So, anyone who's
chased has so far been rewarded.
Remember the long entry was down here.
They've been rewarded in this pocket. It
would not it doesn't have to do it, but
it would not surprise me to see this
snap everyone out or at least half of
them out into some of this, right? If he
doesn't protect this straight down into
here before bidding back up, which is
why you don't want to enter the long up
here. Think about how fast this move the
moment, look at the look at what happens
the moment people realize, oh, we're not
trending lower. I said it can trend
lower versus this. This is the key how
we operate in here. The moment bears
lose this battle. Look at the size of
these candles.
All right, no look back. That's the
squeeze. There's the rebid.
And that's a grind up. This can come
right back down to here if it wants to,
right? And you're starting to see this
now. It's going to start washing out
probably the late longs. We are building
volume here, but it would not surprise
me to see this come down to here before
it finds a bid because this has been
very, very aggressive.
All you have to do, remember, all you're
doing is in trading really to make it
really simple, is trying to identify a
good location to enter into trade in and
waiting for it to come into that
location and then watching how we
operate in that location. Does it give
you a hint that you're right? Does it
give you that idea of like, yeah, we're
going to go higher, get involved. Yeah,
we've caught buyers offside. We're going
to go lower. Get involved. and trying to
leave it alone when you're not in a
location of interest. And currently, you
could argue, right, you can absolutely
argue that they are holding the top of
this shelf. But you got to ask yourself
if the best buying location, well,
technically was here, but I would say
here is when we confirm. And then maybe
here if you're really [\h__\h] brave
because you're not, you know, I don't
know where you have your stop there, but
maybe you bid P,
but here is not the best buying
location. In fact, it's the second worst
buying location of the day after here
where all the buyers got stuck earlier.
So, even if you buy this and it goes
higher, right? You're not being rewarded
for necessarily buying in a good
location. And okay, you can argue, like
I said, that there's a bit of a shelf
here, but I would argue this is a
subprime buying location.
I would much rather be long down here
for that rotation, and I'd much rather
be short like here or that rotation. And
I'd much rather leave this alone for me
personally. Maybe you guys like playing
these and by all means, I'm not trying
to put you off. I'm trying to make you
understand like especially in a
rotational market, how important the
location is.
Oh my god.
I had to record something I saw someone
post. This is what he said. I'm gonna
play this in the mic and see if you can
hear it. I have never heard.
Watch my language. I've never heard
someone so wrong and lie so much.
Hopefully you can hear this. There's no
algorithm level two, baby. No footprint,
no volume profile, point of control. The
control is me. I'm controlling price.
I'm controlling it. I'm controlling
where this is going to go next. That
pisses you off because I sound arrogant.
Everybody else that isn't using what I'm
teaching is clueless. NO.
THAT'S so silly. Holy smokes. VOLUME
PROFILE MY ASS. YOU MIGHT as well just
call me Mr. PERFECT CUZ THAT'S WHO I'M
GOING TO BE from now on. ICT's retired.
It's Mr. Perfect, baby.
>> Retired. ICT's [\h__\h] [\h__\h] mate.
It's the only thing he is.
Mr. Perfect. What a goon.
Absolute goon.
Oh, I've never heard so much nonsense in
all my life.
H some interesting characters on out
there, aren't there? All right, so
traing back into sort of that GlobeEx
low kind of level, the Asia low.
It's wild. Wild.
And we're about to finish this session
here, folks. You've got uh 30 seconds
left until you hit lunch. I can stay
with you a couple minutes.
Lay back. Uh yeah, just go to the go
into the courses, go to the the bottom
of the courses. There'll be a module
there which tells you how to get into
the Discord. It's an email that you need
to email with a certain title in and uh
you have to use the email that you
registered with. That's all it is. and
then and then you'll be in.
Rosco said, "I was watching interviews
with winners of the World Futures
Trading Competition. They use systems
like you, Alex." It doesn't surprise me.
Um because we're when you think about
what we're doing with h how how we're
executing trades, what we're looking at,
it's really simple. We're trying to
identify the type of market we're in.
We're going to we're trying to look for
clues in the market at the key levels
where we identif let's change that.
We're identifying the market condition
we're in. We're identifying the key
levels of interest that we want to trade
around based on based on what what we've
done previously or if we're at new
all-time highs based on projections,
based on standard deviations, based on
fibs of where we might get to. And then
we're going to use what? We're going to
use volume based on supply and demand.
And we're going to try and be accurate
in those levels of volume to see, okay,
who traded here? Who's stuck here? Why
are they stuck here? Where are they
looking for price to go to? And then
we're going to either trade with them or
if someone's stuck, we're going to use
their pain to trade the opposite way to
them. That's all we're doing. That's all
trading is, right? We're using people's
pain to get to the next destination. And
all we're doing ever is moving from a
place of fair value to a place of
imbalance to look for va value. It's the
same same lesson as I talk about when
we've done the lessons on the Rolex,
right? We can use today. We can use
today. You know what what I love doing.
Okay. So
Rolex Day, we're going to change the
narrative for today, but I'm going to
give you an example. All right. Rolex
Daytona goes on sale today at $25,000.
All right. So, Rolex goes on sale at
$930 this morning at $25,000.
Someone, but not many people are willing
to sell down at $25,950.
Well, guess what? When we got down here,
there were a ton of buyers hanging out
here to buy it. Why? Because last time
the Rolex was down here was here. And
what happened? Everyone bought it and it
suddenly was worth, I don't know, uh,
let's just call this 30k for the for the
sake of it. Suddenly, it was worth 30k
more. So, they made $5,000
very quickly. So, we were on a flash
sale. So, they're like, "Oh, I'm buying
that Rolex. That's cheap. I'm buying
that." Boom. Okay. We got up to 30K. And
then everyone when we got to 30K was
like, "Well, it's never been worth more
than this recently." All right. The last
buyer bought up here. So, we're going to
take our profits into 30K. Okay. So,
this was where the last buyer existed.
The last buyer bought at 30K up here.
Then we went down into the middle and we
found fair value in here because buyers,
right, buyers and sellers both agreed
that this was a fair price for a while.
All right, for this period of time here
about an hour and that's noted by the
point of control. All right, and by the
range rotation. Now, something changed
in the market right here. Right here,
something changed. It could be as simple
as a new watch became available to sell
or maybe an article came out saying,
"Hey, the Rolex Dainer is not very good
and these are the these are the reasons
why." All right, whatever happened at
this point here, people were like, "Oh
my god, I don't want to own this
anymore. Sell this now." Well, so they
sold it and we get more supply on the
market and a lack of demand. So, we move
from balance to imbalance and we find
value again at the same level because
there's still buyers hanging around down
here who are willing to buy. And then
guess what? We went back to balance and
this time buyers were like, well, I
missed buying here. I'm going to buy
here this time. And we come back up to
here. And these buyers from here, if the
Rolex are now selling at, I don't know,
let's call it 28,000. And you've got
some buyers who might want to buy
28,000, but anyone who is sensible
bought 25,000 down the bottom. All
right? And that is all the market is
doing. Take your algo, stick it up,
[\h__\h] ass, mate. You're full of it.
It's nothing to do with that. All right?
It's nothing to do with an old man
sitting in the middle of nowhere wearing
a stupid cap talking absolute nonsense.
All right? It's to do with real market
participants, real people trading
billions of dollars on behalf of the
Fed, on behalf of private equity, on
behalf of the banks. That's what it's to
do with
You blew up a turbo. Oh, sorry to hear
that, Tonio. Hopefully it doesn't um
cost you too much.
Is that my most wanted? Uh,
it's up there.
It's up there.
It's up there. Yeah, that or an AP. I
would never buy a PC. I'd be too I don't
have the money to buy it anyway, but I'd
be too scared to wear it. Um, but really
I don't need to buy anything else. I
have to stop myself. I have I have too
many
too many nice watches as it is.
They are a weakness for me.
Maybe I'll buy one when I'm 60 or
something. I just can't
can't be spending that
and walking around like it's okay.
Tag Monaco. Not a watch I love, but a
watch many many people love.
Very unique shape, very shape, very
collectible, but not uh never been into
tag, to be honest. Not not one of my
favorites. Amigga is my soft point
because I got to watch this through my
granddad
and through Bond. So I used to go to
watch Bond with my granddad and when he
passed away, he left me his AmIgga and
then since then I've bought quite a few
So starting to see some selling where
the top side of this range starting to
feel what this little imbalance previous
day point of control like I said you
might see a failure this has been
straight up this area here this this
edge here becomes important fail this
this edge fail this this edge and this
edge and this edge and so forth. Uh for
me be very very cautious like we talked
about in this area here. Okay,
we didn't sweep anyone out. You're going
to start to see that happen now, right?
Probably start to see some damage done
to some of these participants and you're
into lunch, right? So, imagine if you
were if if you were a fund this morning
and you shorted this and you got long
this, you're taking some money off the
table and you're going to go and have a
beer and get a lap dance knowing what
they're like.
I don't blame you, Rosco. Although, I do
I like wearing a watch. I don't like
wearing um
careful what I say here. Uh I'm not a
fan of watches which tell you too much.
I don't want to get my email on my
watch. I don't want to be bombarded by
text or phone calls on my watch. I used
to have that. That was just overkill. I
like nice analog watch. Nice and simple.
Look down. What does it tell me? The
time. Maybe sometimes it tells me the
date. I don't want to know anything
else. Not interested in getting a news
alert on my watch when I'm trying to
have a break from the screens.
No giveaways today, Awani. No, sorry. We
will we will do some this week. I need
to get some new codes and um we've got
the course on sale anyway. So,
is that your favorite watch, Tonio? The
tag Monaco. That square one, isn't it?
The Monaco Golf is the one that everyone
likes, right? The blue and orange one.
They are nice. It's just not not my
favorite.
But the reason I use the uh Daytona
other than I like it is it's it's a
watch that most people know, right?
The tech. Yeah. Wolf.
Punchy.
No worries. Nihow. Catch you later.
I like the John the John uh Mayo Daytona
golden green. I really like the speedy
golden green as well. Just it's just
silly. Just silly.
But the watch market has cooled off a
bit this year. Same as the car market
cooled off.
Honestly, folks, if if you can be in
cash for the next 6 to 18 months, I
think you're going to get some good
sales on lots of things, whether it be
watches, cars, properties, businesses,
you're going to get some good sales.
I was looking last night even um
why my brain not working
I can't think what it's called
what's it called when uh my brain has
stopped working when you forfeit uh when
you close down your business or
sometimes you have to close down your
personal assets. What's that called? Why
can't my brain work
with D? I search for it in my head.
Someone help me.
Anyway,
bankruptcy. There we go. Thank you. Um,
lots of bankruptcies this year. We still
got two months left. Lots of
bankruptcies. And I think next year will
be worse. So, what does that mean? Well,
turn keys, turnkey companies. When you
go bankrupt, what happens is your assets
are taken by said bank, said company and
they're sold off, all right, to in turn
keys. So let's say let's say I have a
music studio and I go bankrupt, okay?
Then I declare bankruptcy, the bank will
then take that music studio off me and
they will sell the assets available in
that music studio to claw back some of
the money. So like my synthesizers, my
computers, my desk, etc. etc. You're
going to have that with lots of
companies going on, which means, as
horrible as it sounds, and I know it's
awful, but this is how you get a
transfer of wealth if you are cash
positive and you're able to take
advantage
of things like said Rolex when they're
on sale and hold for a few years. So, in
this case, it would be a company, right?
Then you can make money out of it. Same
with houses and like Prrisca said, same
with art. If anyone's interested in art,
go to Prrisca. Prriscar is an amazing
art dealer.
Is that right, Rosco?
I saw like two I saw the two the two uh
banks or uh funds which closed down last
week. Um there was a private secret
meeting between the big banks and funds
and the Fed over the weekend or Friday
because they are worried about the bad
debt, the cockroaches as Jamie Diamond
would call them. And they're also
worried about what's
catch what tell me about
Yeah.
Um
so we have we have bad debt. Um we have
to keep an eye on the bonds
and uh on Japan as well if Asia starts
dumping um US equities because they
started breaking out their treasuries
this morning
last night. So
macro wise doesn't look good but like I
said we can be irrational. The markets
can be irrational. I'll tell you the
other thing, but some of you might be
newer and never traded in a bare market
before.
The bullish moves, all right, the
pullback moves in bare markets are
violent
are very very violent. Okay, so even in
bare markets, the bullish days or the
bullish hours can be nuts
because shorts get squeezed way more
than longsidate. All right, I know
longsidate fast, yes, but in a big bare
market, we go to like a monthly here.
Oh, I'm going to have to go to NQ1.
Uh, can you give me QQQ?
Okay.
In bare markets, we haven't had one for
a long time really. In bare markets
here,
these pushes, these month pushes can be
very violent. Right? This is 08. these
snapback days and the days within here.
If we go into
one week,
it's been a long time. Okay, here's 08.
Right, these days
still offer huge day trading
opportunities. Okay, and bare markets
take time to develop. I'm just going to
point this out to you. What does this
look like?
Possible.
This takes time to develop, right? And
it's it's not too late to liquidate. It
gives you an opportunity to liquidate.
This panic gives you an opportunity to
liquidate. It gives you an opportunity
to liquidate. That is the night night
scenario, right? Before we start going
the other way, it takes a long time. So
the trading opportunity even in bare
markets is is amazing. for day trading
April 25.
Not saying it has to happen.
Very similar. The structure being built
out is not dissimilar at all. But hey,
we will see.
I'm not one of those guys that wants to
call a [\h__\h] huge short and all this
nonsense. We just trade what's in front
of us, right? That's all we have to do.
There's there's a reason uh Burkshire
and Haway is mainly cash and there's a
reason Jamie Diamond is worried about
the bonds and the treasuries
and there's a reason gold's been going
up.
You're in short. How's it looking? Uh I
don't know where you're in short from,
Jack.
You're back into the range that we're in
this morning just about. You're in the
edge of it. you're at point of previous
day point of control.
So rejected uh Asia low into 25200.
You're dancing back into the range. If
they build liquidity here,
if they are able to hold uh this edge in
here,
the 50s,
they can shoot for a high. If they fail
this, you're probably going to rotate
back into here. So you're in lunch now
as well, so who knows what they're going
to do with it. recent top. Um, so you're
in from 200. You're about 50 points up.
If if you complete this rotation,
remember you got both VWOPS underneath
you. But if you can complete the
rotation
under 130, I'd be looking for 100s.
Yeah. And then 80s and back into the
same area as yesterday. But I think
bulls have a chance to step in in that
in that area. But VIX has started to try
and find a bit of a bid. But yeah, I
think we're just into the chopping slot.
short from 180. It's just the only thing
now is just sort of fighting momentum,
but you are uh
you are liable to sweep some of these
guys like we talked about, right? None
of these balls got hurt. They're likely
to get hurt. This is the edge of range.
We've had no acceptance above here twice
today. So, we're probably going to trade
back down to this side of this gray box.
So, as long as long as you're managing
your position, you look good.
You never know. All right. You never
know. Maybe maybe you get that move.
Hopefully.
Yeah, that's one of your favorite
setups, Adam. It's okay. You'll get
more. You'll get more. All right, folks.
Um, I'm going to get out of here. That
was a decent trading session. Nicely
green on the day again.
And no one asked me though. Is anyone
here trading a legacy account on Funded
Next? Before I go,
does anyone here have a legacy account
on them?
Doesn't look like it. None of you are
answering, so probably not.
You trade the rapids.
Garbs, do you Well, maybe you trade with
them. Maybe you'll know. Oh, you just
started as well. Okay. I've got one pass
and I'm at day five and I'm up five and
a half grand, but it's on a legacy
account.
Can I ignore the fiveday payouts and
just trade to 30 days straight and then
pull it all out or do I have to pull out
when it's available? Do I have to do
like a payout sequence? Does that make
sense? Or can I just trade straight to
30 days?
You might get that sell, Antonio. You
might you might get your turbo paid for
here. This is your my first TP would be
here in this low volume area here. And
if you sell through this, you're going
to get that move back down
hopefully towards the 100s if not 80s.
If I can ignore it, I'd be tempted to
just take a very small payout and then
just trade try and build this up.
Yeah, they're trying to defend this low
ball node. That's why I say my first TP
would be here where we just pulled back
into
there. Strong selling down there and it
got absorbed. So there's a buyer on the
tape even in lunch. Just be aware of
that. Strong selling into this. There's
a low volume node here and there is a
passive buyer sat here absorbing for now
on that last move down. He just absorbed
it. Just be aware of that.
No worries, L. Yeah, no worries. I'm
here every day. So, whatever you need,
I'm here. Thanks, Daniela. I'm just
going to wait for I think Garbs is just
having a look for me. See if Garbs can
figure it out. I couldn't figure it out.
The reason we don't have a code and I
haven't promoted them yet is I have not
taken a payout with them yet. Okay, so I
want to make sure everything is good
with them first before we start talking
about them too much in stream. So this
would be my first account
and I think yeah I will be uh basically
I could take 2,00 5 6 7 8 2,800 out
after my first five days which is good
but I could also swing big now I've
built a buffer
if they allow it
protected VUP. the view up in that low
volume node. It's just here, right?
This sort of 30s
down to 16s. If you get failures
underneath this last buyer, you can get
follow through. So, this is where you
last got stuck. Where we are right here
is where all the sellers got stuck into
30s.
Trading through it. You can trade
through 30s and make a new low. You're
good. They're trying to force it.
There's big sellers coming in here. They
are trying to force it. This is twice at
the same level now. Big sellers have
stepped in. So, I would take a TP here
if you haven't already and then try and
hold to see if you can get a flush,
which looks like they're trying to force
this down here.
But the PC, the last two candles is
around 30 and it's been all sell side
down here aggressively.
30 benchmark days benefit legacy count
futures legacy challenge account type
after you complete 30 benchmark days you
become eligible for 100% withdrawal of
your profits that's what I thought as
performance reward whereas before that
you can generally only withdraw yeah
so I think I think I can just wait I
think if I wanted to I could just trade
the 30 days
with no consistency rule now I've got
5,600 $100 to risk and once I get to 30
benchmark days, which I think is $200 a
day, can take it out. It's tempting. Be
a nice little Christmas present.
Probably more likely January. No, I
don't think I get 30 days. Well, 25 more
days green for Christmas. Bound to like
have some slip ups.
I'm at 53 53,500.
I haven't taken a payout. as in you're
at 53,000 profit or you're at 3,500 in
profit on a 50.
So you can see see this new range
developing. See this node here over
lunch.
Buyers are trying to defend this.
Sellers are trying to defend the top
side. That's your range in here. Sellers
want this rotation. buyers want this.
You're not getting selling or you you've
got sellers stuck under 35
these two candles. There's big market
selling under there and they're
currently stuck.
Look at the message above this. Do take
profit allow you to build up the 10K
payment max on a pro?
Yeah, you can do whatever you want on TP
TPT. So, let's say you have a 50K
account. If you hit a 50 grand winner
day one, you're going to take all of
that out above the buffer at a 8020
split.
Um, if you're too con once you hit 20k
payout, I think they move that account
to uh
live.
How do I see if they're stuck? Um, by
using the order flow,
by using bookmap
and by using footprint.
So in here it will all be in the new
course bas basically in here in these
wicks
there were market sell orders and we did
not move lower those are aggressive
orders on the book which means there is
a passive seller which means what there
is someone i.e. a big participant limit
buying here looking for that rotation.
If he leaves the tape then the market
sell orders will win and they'll be let
out. Currently,
this is the level where they're stuck
at. This is the third time coming down
to this same level around 35. From 35 to
23 is where they're stuck.
If we get continuation, if this passive
buyer leaves the tape, then you'll get
continuation lower. But if if he soaks
here again, this would be the third time
visiting here with aggressive buyers
coming on the tape and not seeing follow
through.
Or is it a 10k a day limit? I thought it
was 20k a day limit, JD. My bad.
Uh the new the new course coming in
January goes through all of that. AB,
but if you're if you're already a
member, then you will get a heavily
discounted rate on the new course.
Yeah. Still soaking that same level.
Okay, team. I'm going to I'm going to
get out of here. I need a little break
and a bit of food and walk my dog and
all that good stuff. Um, those in
Discord, I will hop in later. All I want
to say before I go and I remind you, the
conditions are range rotating
conditions. You've got to be careful in
range rotating conditions. If you join
something late looking for a trend, you
are likely to get hurt. All right, just
remember that location in R range
rotating conditions is probably more
important than any other condition. All
right, location is always important, but
because in range rotation you don't have
as much momentum, location matters. All
right, so make sure you understand that.
Also make sure that you understand that
when we are finding someone stuck like
we had where's my mouse down here. These
moves here are very very very big. These
are 40 point 30 to 40 point candles,
right? It' be the same. If we get buyers
stuck and they do 30 to 40 point candles
down, you're going to get hurt. A 30
point stop in this market is probably
not going to be enough unless you're
able to be very very accurate using
orderflow. So size down, right? Size
down. And um I'll see you all tomorrow.
We'll go again. Same thing tomorrow. And
uh where we close today will matter.
Looking at that daily chart, it is going
to matter. Where we close today matters.
Are we going to get close outside of
that previous week range or we just
going to close back inside of it and
rotate until Wednesday is out the way?
Which is what I think is a good chance
of happening because Nvidia's coming
Wednesday afternoon. How we act into
that will be key. Can they trap enough
people and use an outlier print is what
I'm wondering. Anyway, peace and love.
Be kind to each other. Use hard stops.
Hopefully have a great day with me.
Trade safe this afternoon. See you
tomorrow.