Oops.
All right, team. Good morning. Good
morning. Good morning. Good morning.
Lots to get through here. Lots to get
through. Big sell day yesterday. Nice
continuation yesterday for those of you
who held on. Hopefully John held on. He
got all his targets. And uh yes, gap
down this morning as the panic continues
taking out previous week lows. It's
understand it's important to understand
where we're at on the dailies. All
right, so let's just have a quick look
at this. Sorry, move this mic. All
right, we talked about yesterday this
yearly profile and how we've been
developing and the key being
I just lost that already.
The key being this shelf here. All
right, this is where we've built a
decent amount of liquidity into uh well
down to 247s. Surprise, surprise. All
right, 247s. The rotation 7s to 25K back
and forth, back and forth. Right, we're
back to that level, right? We're back to
247s on this shelf. The key being here's
the lower Ballinger band. All right, now
we rarely trade beyond lower Ballinger
bands in one go. You can see when we do
rotations like this, 20-day, lower bowl,
20-day, lower bowl, rally. All right,
upper bowl, 20-day, lower bowl, 20-day,
lower bowl. It is possible to trade
outside of it. All right, if absolute
panic happens, we can have big black
swan event. I'm not saying we go down
that far, but you can see capitulation
underneath it. There are some levels
here which we can come and test. We've
got these equal lows here, 24,420,
right? lots of stops will be in and
around there. We have some old point of
controls and value areas in here. So,
I'm not saying we don't drift lower.
What I'm saying is your location for a
new short down here is far from ideal.
Is it is far from ideal. Think about the
last few days we've been trying to short
up here. Right? This is a long way down.
You're almost 1,000 points lower than
where we were entering before. So, be
aware of that. If we get continuation
over the next few weeks, right, if we're
going to go into the capitulation, then
we are going to get this sharp turn on
the Ballinger. You can see if we zoom
in, it has already already started,
right? It has already started to turn.
You're going to get this and you're
going to get one of these to follow.
What will the target be? Well, if we go
really really heavy. All right, this
node, this has not been tested. This is
your 200. All right, very rare that we
don't test this in a low volume node
area. This will keep trending up. So,
I'm interested that whether it's into
the end of Q4 or beginning of next year,
if we do sell, those are areas I'm
watching. Right now, we're just looking
for inchday plays. This is not a great
location. A back test would be better.
If we get capitulation at the open, then
maybe we can follow the tape, but it's
uh far from ideal to be taking new short
positions down here. If we move to the
hourlys,
you'll see what I'm talking about. All
right, this is previous week low. This
was the capitulation low last Friday.
Remember last Friday, we came down here
and then rallied off it into close and
then gapped up. We are now below this.
This becomes a big level, which is why
I've marked it out as red. And really,
I'd argue up into here into this old
value. So, in fact, let's
do one of these here. All right, this
matters. This bump from last Friday
matters. If we don't fail Friday's low,
we've already wicked underneath it.
We've taken that liquidity. How we act
into this bump here where we built out
liquidity will matter. All right,
because that was a big V-shaped
recovery. Can we sort of reject that old
point of control?
Can we reject that old point of control
from last Friday? If not, where is the
better location here? All right, but
think about what we had yesterday. Nice
B-shaped profile,
right? Beautiful B-shaped profile.
Really, we'd love to reject off the
lower end of that profile. That is the
most ideal play we will get today. All
right, would be a short squeeze up to
here and a rejection off that Bshape. If
we recover previous day value area low
and previous day uh previous week value
area low then it's potential that they
do one of these. We can't rule it out
guys. All right we can't rule it out.
It's a big move down.
Could even easily have a two leg back up
and that can happen over multiple
sessions. I would like to play
continuation short. I just don't want to
get short down here. All right. The only
way I'm going to play short down there
is if I see something on the tape that I
can join and it's very obvious and I
think yeah, I can I can have a decent RR
there. At the moment, I'm not seeing
that. So, either this is going to
happen, a rejection of previous uh
week's value down here,
right? A drift into there, or
the push up into previous days value
area low and a rejection of that. All
right, that would be more ideal. That
would be sort of your GlobeEx level and
stuff. Somewhere into here would be
absolutely ideal if it will offer it.
All right, I'm not going to play the
longs today. You might be like, you're
mad. I'm not playing counter trend longs
um off this heavy momentum because I
don't know that you don't just see that
and a complete capitulation. You just
don't know what these funds are going to
do. Targets to downside all the way down
here. Double bottom. We are coming into
this old value area low. You can see
this is the congested area. Go back to
like a month ago when we were talking
about the 20 25,000 to 700 rotation.
Here's your 700s. Here's your 700s.
Here's just under 700. 700 700 700
255,000. All right, this was a heavily
fought over level for 2 weeks. For two
weeks, we battled in here. All right, so
just be aware of that. If they want to
hold, you can see we've come right into
this value low right underneath this
trying to trade inside. These areas here
hold significance. Okay, I don't think
there's any which are untested. There's
no naked PC's down here. Everything's
been tested. So really if we're going to
liquidate I am looking for all the way
down here 24400 that would be more
more of a black swan more of something
where we go outside of the Ballinger.
It's very unusual but the tape has been
heavy. I'm not going to argue with that
and I'm not going to fight it. So let's
just see what we get. Looking at
overnight you can see right big B-shaped
profile like we talked about yesterday.
Beautiful.
Closing at the lows PC here. Asia tried
to sort of reclaim this pivot, failed.
London came in and said, "What has gone
on there yesterday? Let's sell this
versus previous day value." And we're in
a drift lower. All right. So, here are
your levels. They're marked out for you.
Let's move up
into 5m minute. We can check uh
Yes. So, basically, guys, we should also
mention, let's get out of this a second.
Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. If
we do build liquidity here down here,
all right, that is to go lower. Just so
that you understand why I'd like to see
a back test to move lower. All right,
very very simple
inverse cup and handle. Okay,
let's get to the ES. Looking exactly
same. Okay, bouncing off a key level
which I had marked. Okay, same kind of
thing. Friday low. So, it's got room. ES
has got room to take this liquidity at
655. All right, so that's what it' be
watching for. If you get a push and
fail, 655 is your target. Spiders,
same thing. It's got room. Very, very
heavy. This is a block where we found a
bid on Friday. All right, very simple.
We bid off this on Friday. We're
bouncing off IB low from a week ago on
Friday. At the moment, you can see it's
got a reaction from the IB low. If they
fail, if they push and fail, they're
going to come back for these lows. We
can watch that. Watch that carefully
because what we do after that becomes
important. Do we have follow through or
is that liquidity grab and the end of
this and you know we need to go sideways
for a bit. Q's same story. We're
underneath that low like we talked
about. It has room if we're going to get
really heavy on the Q's. You know we got
tons of room down to 590s. 600 is a huge
uh options level as well. Just remember
that. a 600 big big big big big options
level and under that it has room. So if
they reject uh 600 this morning was a it
was a put wall. They're already
underneath it. Let's see how they act at
the open.
VIX is on a tear. All right. Just
absolutely flying right now. Coming back
to these Friday highs. If we base over
those Friday highs, you know, we'd be
looking for a trade into 25s and then
29s. If we have a sell day today, unless
it's, you know, complete panic and the
market's over, then Monday there's
probably a reaction for a move back
upside, right? Apple still amazing
relative strength. You might be like,
"Oh, we are moving down." We are, but
we're not underneath all of this, are
we? Incredible strength here from Apple
holding up near all-time highs. Very,
very strong. Important to note that.
Came out news this morning. Sales of the
new iPhone in China have been good. But
worth noting in this session we are
gapping down under previous day low
underneath PDC.
Amazon underneath previous day low
underneath PDC. Big old wash out here.
All right. So let's see if we can retest
these for some sales.
Google absolutely slapped. All right.
Abs. This thing's getting murdered. All
right. Is night night time for Google
right now. We're starting to let go of
this shelf. So any back test of there if
we stay heavy is a sell opportunity.
Whether that happens today or next week,
that's what they'd be looking for. If
they reclaim this, it'd be a wash and a
reclaim back to the other side of the
range like we always talk about. Meta,
same thing. Letting go of a shelf. All
right, we talked about this. I thought a
popup would be sold into and it has
been. And uh we're breaking 600s now. It
has room. This is why I wasn't ready to
buy yet Meta yet on the swings. I think
we have room
right down into some of these areas here
where we found pivots in April. Right,
this is weak. This is a weak name. Look,
one, two, three, lower high failing.
It's coming down into levels of interest
here. Don't be early to buy these. All
right, if you're looking for swing
longs, do not be early. We've got a bit
of a liquidation event happening now.
Froth coming out the market. Microsoft
into key pivot. All right, this is where
we sort of based out after the earnings
debacle and we're trying to come back
into it right now. If they can't hold it
again, we move lower. So far, every
magname gapping down. Surprise,
surprise. Nvidia, that's your level,
179. Break 179, we're in a bit of a free
fall for a liquidity grab down here. All
right, 76es. We start getting heavy
under this, we zoom out. It is not a
good look. All right, everything's
looking the same. left shoulder head,
right shoulder failure and we're coming
right back to here. Tesla,
same story. Big liquidation event. Look
at all this liquidity we have left above
us now as we've started to roll over.
Here is your range
and there is the breakdown. All right,
every bull in there, every bull now
since the beginning of September is
getting liquidated. Next stop 355s. All
right. So, if they reject anywhere into
sort of the teens and 20s, you're
looking for that move swing short down
to 355. If they reclaim this, it's a
look below and fail and we go other side
of the range. That is the market. All
the markets looking the same. AMD, the
same thing. Same story here, folks. All
right, we are weak and we're weak in
tech. All right, we are weak in tech
names. relative weakness in the ES
because we're starting to rotate out of
these frothy names
into some other uh
more defensive names. Let's say things
with uh
lower P ratios and more steady steady
ships.
So, that's what I'm looking for. I'm not
interested in buying this squeeze up. Um
I am interested in playing a short if
and when it comes in. It might be that
it just doesn't come in. They just flush
it and I'm sat here holding my coffee
all day. And that is also okay, folks.
That is also okay.
Right. What did you guys think is going
to happen today? Did that ever post?
Good morning everyone.
Thanks John Dennis for the tip. Very
kind of you. Thank you. Thank you.
Market about to open here. Let's see if
we can get through some names quickly.
Make sure you smash that like button
nice and early. All right. Good morning,
Global. Chad, John, uh, Frank, Toby,
Jesse, Jeff, Garbs, Chad, Noah, Clint,
Info, Risk, Dumper, Christy, Futures
Withdrew, Christh, Miguel, Peter, Larry,
GG, Jay, Aaron, Fall Forward,
Adam, Sergio, ErF, AB, Eva, Raphael. Oh,
I've lost you all. Moved so quickly.
Wow, there's a lot of you in here.
Uh, Lero, Jonathan, Green Otter,
Lauren, Sylum, Troy, Marrick, 80s,
Smiley, Anthem, Brandon, Bart,
Contorted, Lifetime, Dogee, Ken,
Antonio, Aaron, Sharma, Full Forward,
Andrew, Stefano, Rosco, Mike, Myron,
Patrick, Sloth, Bill E, Jonathan,
Machai, Three Bar reversal, Peter Illis,
Sebastian, Frank, Allan, Red, Alvaro,
Otus, Antus, John, Jay, Cameron,
Eduardo, Jazz, Omalabi, Carla, Arby,
Toby, Orderflow, Swish, and Holstic.
Good morning. We got through them just
about. Just about. All right, smash that
like button nice and early. You know
what we're looking for? We're looking
for downside pressure. I'd like to see
some relief at the open first if
possible. It may be that this market
will not give it to us, but let let's
just see, folks. What I don't want to do
is short the lows. All right, I'm not
interested in shorting the lows. So,
let's just see what we get. Nice and
patient at the open. If they flush it,
so be it. So be it. All right, we had a
amazing day yesterday. We had a solid
week. We're not going to be here giving
back our money on a Friday with a less
than ideal setup.
Hey, contorted. Nice, dude. Looking
forward to working with you.
Okay, here's the open.
Let's see what we get. All right, some
some covering here at the open by the
looks of it. Some bulls coming in. So,
it's probably a bit of bit of covering.
All of the mag very very very very heavy
so far this morning. All right, I can
give you a readout. Tesla 3.3% down.
Nvidia 2.12% down. Microsoft 0.75% down.
Meta just under one and a half% down.
Google 2.25% down. Amazon 0.90% down.
Apple 0.44% down. All right. Market is
bleeding. There's no doubt about it. The
market's bleeding. It's about where can
we get involved. That's going to be the
hardest thing right now is where can we
get involved? Trading back down to
previous week low right here, right now.
All right. So, this green line is
previous week low. If you've seen
continuation under that, it's possible
that we bleed out. It is like I've
talked about numerous times. It is not a
good location. We're at the lower
Ballinger band. We've taken liquidity.
It is what it is. Unfortunately, it's
just going to really depend if this
market is going to be nice to us and
give us a pop. At the moment, I don't
think we're going to get that. No, Jack.
I'm absolutely not. I've talked about
it. Why would I buy the lows
in a panic cell scenario? It's not like
we've looked below and reclaimed
anything. All right? But we are a heavy
market right now. Not something I'm
going to look to do. I'm going to look
to fade pops into key levels and play
the protrend.
VIX opening up at 2259.
All of the market bleeding here this
morning. You've got that New York open,
New York open, previous week low, New
York VW up. Everything staying heavy
here so far. I just want to give it a
chance to shake out. I really don't want
to join the short down here if possible.
But it feels like we're just going to go
into a straight sell here this morning
cuz it is panic stations. So it's not a
good location into that lower bowl, but
it is definitely panic stations. Market
is very very heavy breaking out leaving
buyers trapped above for two days now.
Here's the lows. So overnight lows now
getting taken.
And are they going to push aggressively
lower under this is the question. Now
this is where it's going to get whippy
without a doubt
selling.
I thought this might happen. It's just I
don't like entering loads of week,
loads of week, loads of months. Not a
good entry model.
Let's see.
Nice red plasma.
Okay, new lows here.
Taking out all this liquidity.
And uh these are the areas if we're
going to get very very heavy today. I'd
be watching the 500s and down into here.
Strong selling at this open. Panic is
here right now in this market.
Panic is definitely starting to set in.
I'd say yesterday was pretty controlled.
If we start breaking heavy today, it
will not be controlled. It will be
panic. So, I'll be watching again. This
previous uh week low
is an interesting level. So far, we've
just rejected it straight out the gate
and just moved 100 points lower. Fair
enough.
Yeah, we've sold 134 points in that
first 3 minutes to give you an idea. All
right, so watch your ATRs. Your ATRs are
way over 20 right now per 1 minute.
No trade for me yet. Just just waiting.
So, be watching to see how we operate
into that previous week low into VWAP
into New York open.
Do the sellers sell that or can we get a
bit of a squeeze back up to test some
areas above like Friday's
um value area? Yesterday's value area. I
don't think we're going to get any hope
in hell in getting up to yesterday's
value area right now. That's trading up
at 25,000.
I just don't see us going there. It's a
400 point drive higher. At the moment,
it's showing nothing. No reason to get
up there.
Ideally, we can get a drive to sell
into.
Here come the bulls. So, here's VWAP.
Through VWAP, we will go previous week
low and the New York open. Again, no
position here. I'm just letting it do
whatever it is it wants to do.
There's VWAP.
Very different to yesterday. We have to
be patient today. We have to wait for
location. Remember, we're at the lower
ballinger band outside of previous week.
So, to move lower, we would need bulls
trapped in the market, right? We would
need either panic either like swing
bulls selling all their positions or
some bulls being trapped in the market.
That will happen if we can move higher,
encourage lots of bulls to start buying
the lows and then sell into them. And
that's what I'm going to be considering
considering. And I think if we sell
today or go sideways today, then I think
Monday will probably be your day where
you get some relief because the VIX is
very unlikely to keep screaming higher
for three sessions in a row. Monday or
Tuesday next week, there will probably
be probably probably be some relief.
Right, here's the squeeze. It's why we
don't short the lows through New York
open VW up here, Asia here, and uh
previous day low. If we can get up here,
I'm very interested in the short. If we
get up here, yes, absolutely. I'm
interested in the short.
You can't. This is the the New York View
Up is created by one of my amazing
members for guys in the Discord. So, if
you've done the course and you're in the
Discord, you will get it for free.
Watching this book. Is there any
liquidity higher?
Up you go. Come on, market. Higher you
go the better. Higher you go the better.
Bit of H1 relief here would be good.
What would that swing look like? Fib to
fib on the H1.
50% would be at 900. We're into the 30s
already. 30%. So,
let's see. Let's just let this squeeze
out. See what we can get.
Big buyers got trapped there again on
this first push. I'd like to see it go
higher, but it's no doubt about it. Some
buyers just got trapped there on that
first push. 100 million%. Some buyers
just got trapped on that first push
above 90.
Like this to go much higher first.
These are big candles, folks. They might
look small, but they're big. Just be
careful.
These are no joke. And VOP's a long way
away.
So testing those 800s, failing the 800s.
Buyers caught up there again so far. If
we get through that, then I think we're
going to go 860s to 900s.
Think that's possible.
Big old squeeze out here.
Looks moving very very quick. Very very
quick.
but it's still coming in here for now.
Still has squeeze potential up to those
VWs. Lower time frame I'll go all the
way up here. It can get very very
violent on the return back up side.
Remember
there's some selling here.
VIX coming right back downside.
Interesting if they find a bid here or
not. If they don't, we're going to go
right the way back to the lows because
this where the buyer stepped in. So,
it's interesting kind of areas around
here holding the 800s for now. Okay. If
they hold the 800s, they have the
potential to move up towards the 860s
and then 900s. If they fail the n the
800s, we can go and test that New York
open again.
So, watching this opening range,
watching how we operate here
back to these sort of 800 780s. It's
clearly a key level for them to try and
hold at the moment. And if we start
failing here,
it's less than an ideal location, but
it's uh something I'd be watching, but I
think the squeeze higher is possible
still.
Here we go. So, they're trying again.
Just waiting here, folks. Just waiting
to see what we can get.
Remember, if a seller gets caught
offside, this can rip faces very, very
quickly. So timing today going to be
very very very very hard. Yes, exactly.
Someone just said about the PC here.
That's exactly it. This is what we're
looking at fri from Friday last week.
These are interesting levels as
overunders.
My bias is still potentially for
downside, but we've lost location for
looking for downside. Okay, so easiest
way to put it. Still bulls are trying to
take control here.
Still squeeze potential here. So you're
seeing short covers coming in here.
When it's finished, it's finished. You
know, when it's done, it's done.
Fix back to 22s.
Coming up to this VW up through that we
have Globeex. So, big old squeeze. Maybe
they get all the way back to previous
day value area low. That would be a
really interesting level for me to think
about short if we can get that there.
Guess it's not that far away if they can
squeeze hundreds of points this quickly
cuz the range already today is already
212 points
already. Big old range.
No blowoff yet.
Bull still stepping in here. Still feels
like a squeeze to me. Once it's over,
it's over. I'd say once once they're
done, they're in big trouble. Right now,
they're still holding. Look how whippy
this is. These are not small candles,
folks. These are very, very big candles.
Here's your 800 test under here. There's
a bigger flush. I'm watching this now.
Probably sub 780s.
If they're going to let go, I'm watching
it sub 780s.
Big exchange.
Huge exchange here. Are we going to
flush down through this now is my
question.
Feels tight. Feels very tight in this
range here. We've built out lots of
volume here. In fact, let me make sure
you've got this volume on.
All right. This is why I'm saying sub
sort of 780s. There's a bigger move down
here for now. They are still holding it.
Still exchanging here for now. No
change. Nice and slow.
Patience, patience, patience.
Yeah, 780 now the PC on the day for this
current session.
Vick still sliding lower. There is a
shortcoming here. It's just whether it's
going to be now or all the way up
previous day at value area low. You do
not want to get caught in the squeeze.
Remember, we're just repricing up. This
area here is the level of interest from
last Friday for me, right? From previous
week. This was sort of the balance zone
from the previous week. So, how we
acting here is key. If they get through
this, we're going all the way up here.
And this for me is going to be the prime
location to be short. If we fail
anywhere up here, this is a prime short
location. Remember, gap fill is all the
way up here. If we fail here, this is
any of these interest levels are of
interest to me. If we reclaim this, no
shorts for the day because we're going
to go back inside yesterday's range.
I am expecting like a squeeze out in the
morning maybe till maybe another 15
minutes or so and then we'll see what's
what.
Like I said, I want to play the protrend
which currently is down. It's down
VWAP here. ES doing look.
Did ES take those lows on that morning
drive? Nope.
Okay,
ES coming back towards its VWAP as well.
Spider's already through their VWAP.
Back towards the 50-day.
More squeeze possible, I think. More
squeeze possible. I want to time this
short. I want to make sure I'm on the
right side of it.
So, wiggle here. I still think there's
more in this. The higher, remember, the
higher we shove up, if we're looking for
the protrend, the higher we squeeze out,
the better. To move lower, we need bulls
trapped. All right? So if we can squeeze
out here into a key level and bulls
chase that's when a great short
opportunity will arise. We have taken
out um low of weak previous week lows.
So we have to be aware of that low
hanging fruit is gone. I'm not playing a
counter trend today. I said I'd like to
see this squeeze higher and then I'm
going to look for the shorts. This is
what I wanted to see. This is the first
thing I wanted to see. Now I need to see
if and when they get stuck. If they
don't get stuck, so be it. We have no
trade
so far. Intraday
the bulls are trying to take control. I
think this is just shorts covering to be
honest. And this is VWAP right here.
SPY and ES got a little bit to go to get
to their VWAP. I'm watching this GlobeEx
low as well. 900. Once we get through
900, maybe we get previous day value
area low. So again, I'm just letting
this squeeze out. Do what it wants. Can
keep going. It's absolutely fine.
Orb now set. Yeah. Well, you're above
the orb.
This
globeex and then previous day low gap
fill all the way up here if they can do
it. If you're longing this and you're
playing a counter trend, it does make
sense and you're making money from it.
But just remember, it's a counter trend.
If and when sellers come back in, all
right, it's going to be heavy.
It's still dropping down nicely, but
still just at 2175. It's coming into
some areas of interest with pivots.
So 2160s
on the VIX all the way down to 21 is an
area where I think buyers might step
back in in the VIX unless it flushes
straight through which might indicate
when we start to top out again. I'm just
going to watch the tape here.
See what we get.
Nice Tonio.
Yeah, lots of you taking the counter
trend. Like I said, I'm focused on the
protrend today. Looking for this squeeze
up into some of these levels, any of
these levels up here. Ideally,
get a bit more coffee. Very small mug
here this morning.
Okay, nice. Keep going. Higher the
better.
Through GlobeEx
London low here.
Nice, John. Yeah, nice work.
Lots of buying exuberance here. Probably
lots of shorts getting stopped out here.
The higher the better. Remember, I'm
looking to play this back downside once
it's finished its morning squeeze out.
It's finished its morning squeeze out.
This is GlobeEx 900 here. So if they
hold this then we should get those
25,000s. Previous day value area low,
previous week value area low, previous
day low into into like 25,000s. There's
an old New York VW up to 25,100. So I'm
interested either here or up there. The
edge of this red box or this box. It
depends where we where we see failures.
Might want to wait for the new uh H1
transition. I don't really want them to
fail right here right now.
Not much excess there. Some strong
selling coming in though.
Back to VW up maybe. I'd like to see one
more push higher. The higher the better.
Please squeezy squeezy squeezy would be
ideal.
Watch your ATRs here folks. Please.
Right. The ATR is very very very big.
These candles are 35 plus points.
Still above that opening range, still at
this GlobeEx level. Wouldn't be
surprised to see some monster candles
come soon if uh shorts get caught
offside.
Still printing above VWAP. Still holding
these 900s.
Big exchange here.
I'm not convinced the top's in, but a
big exchange here for sure.
Some sell pressure here. Watching VWAP.
They can still soak off this VWAP.
Here's the flush to it.
If they fail through here in orb, we're
going to go all the way down.
Opening range is here. VWOPS's here.
Shelf here. You can see we've built
volume here. I'm not convinced that
we've got enough excess in this yet,
which is why I'm not really quite
interested. We caught a little bit, but
really we had a PC there at 910
on a transition. So, I'm not convinced
there's enough excess yet. Yes, I'm
being extra cautious today, guys,
because if you get this wrong, you're
going to get caught in 100 point ripper
the wrong way. So, very, very, very like
slow today. Interview up again.
VIX fi starting to find a bid at that
2160 that I talked about. All right, so
2160 down to 21 is an area where I think
VIX will start to find a bid. That's
what we've just started to do. If VIX
can start to turn, I'd like one more
push on excess here. Let me just check
ES. ES stuck at the 50-day.
SPY stuck at the 50-day. QQQ is not
quite there yet. The 50day is basically
previous day low on the Q's. I would
like a bit more excess. I'd like one big
drive up and a load of buyers to get met
with a big passive seller who just says
no more. That's what I'm waiting for.
That is what I'm waiting for.
So, let's see. Like I said, patient,
patient, patient, patient. I'm looking
for the protren. You guys can be long in
this. Like I said, this is common for me
when we come here in the mornings when
we see stuff like this. I'm not going to
short the lows. I'm going to stay
focused on one side of the trade, which
is the short. I'm going to wait for a
retest of some key areas and wait for
buyers to get trapped. If you wanted to
long this, you've had your triggers.
There's your big buy signal through New
York. That's absolutely fine. I'm
focused on the short. It doesn't mean
that this squeeze up isn't a good trade
for you guys to take. I have to trade my
A+ setup, which is a protrend after a
squeeze. Very much like yesterday.
Remember, I missed the opening flush
yesterday. We squeezed out into my key
level. We trapped buyers and then we
slapped it for 200 plus points.
Bit more excess there. Still not enough
for me. Come on market. Up you go. Let's
keep squeezing. Higher the better,
please.
Higher the better, please.
Peter, if you're confused, I'd leave it
alone.
Like, Nvidia's up at 0.22% after like
flushing heavy. You've got to zoom out
like I do on this and look at the
levels. Where are your RBS levels?
That's all you've got to do and wait.
All right. If you got anyone that got
short in here or here or here or here or
here or here is getting squeezed out,
we're going to wait. This was a level of
interest. This is a level of interest.
I'm interested how we operate here. I'm
interested how we operate here. gap
fills all the way up to 25,094
as well. Top of GlobeEx all the way up
here. Po all the way up here. If they
keep squeezing, they keep squeezing.
That's absolutely fine by me.
It's about waiting. Let the market come
to you and then once it's into an area,
then I zoom in in the order flow. Then I
zoom in looking for structure. Until
that point, just let it come to your
area of interest. Why important to have
a plan?
I didn't think we'd come up to previous
day value area low. I didn't think we'd
have the juice, but I'm very happy that
we are because this is where all the
volume was built yesterday. This is the
bottom of the B shape. Remember, big
B-shaped profile into here. Previous day
low, previous day value low, previous
week value area low, previous day close.
This is a thick level where I expect
sellers to come back in. If they don't
come back in, then by all means, a giant
squeeze is very much possible to recover
yesterday. But I don't think that is
what we're going to get. All right. It's
not what we're going to get. Or it could
be. It's very unlikely that we get that.
It's much more likely that this is a
squeeze up into 10:00 10:15 met with
sellers and bow back down we go and we
go into a range rotation day.
Right. Your IB is massive right now,
folks. 328. We still got half an hour
left. So just be aware of that. Starting
to get stuck here. Want this market to
move higher.
Yeah, Gatfield could be good. Troy.
Yeah, for sure.
For sure. But like we said, I'm not
going to short the lows today. The clue
was in the Ballinger band, wasn't it?
Remember very beginning of the show,
maybe some of you are joining late. We
do not in this channel short at these
lower Ballinger bands. All right, but
50-day gap fill like
this profile here into some of these.
Yes, very interested for a retest of
this low and then hold runners just in
case. But uh I'm not getting short down
here and I don't want to play the
counter trend long. There's not enough
for me to be thinking about a counter
trend long today.
That doesn't mean you guys can't do it.
Like I say, I just stick to my A+
setups. They are what gets me paid. They
are what makes me profitable.
So there is some resting liquidity at
25,000. I'd imagine if we take him, we
might as well go to uh 25,020 25,60.
Let's see. This is straight up squeeze.
Really nice. This is everything we
wanted to see. Come on, market. Up you
go. Up, up, up, up, up. We don't want
this to just be walked. We actually want
aggressive big candles up. That's where
buyers start to chase, right? Once we
like this, this is what we see. Want to
see big big big big big big candles
please
with lots of buyers market buying their
way in at the top after we've squeezed
out 344 points. That is exactly what we
want to see.
Higher the better.
Just Yeah. Not it's a normal standard
deviation uh sloth. So when you put
Ballinger bands on, they will always
always be two standard deviation away
from your 20 SMA on any chart. Yeah. So
I use it on the daily chart. Why on the
daily chart? Well, your 20 SMA is your
average price for the last month because
we have 20 trading days in a month. So
two standard deviation up, two standard
deviation down. That gives you the the
elastic bands. It's very rare that we
trade outside of that. We can trade
outside, but we normally close inside.
Okay, which is why we don't get short
when we've just come down to it. Same as
everyone who tried to long at the top of
the Ballinger band, I don't know, two
weeks ago and got trapped. Same thing,
right? Sometimes we have black swan
events which change things. You know,
you go into COVID, you're going to slice
through those two standard deviations.
If you trade small caps, you're going to
slice through three standard deviations.
Three standard deviations is normal for
small caps. Two standard deviations is
normal for the Q's and spy and the mega
caps because they move a bit slower.
Come on. We want more. You've got to get
higher here. I don't want this to just
sort of slowly roll over. We want a huge
face ripper where all the shorts get
scared, all the balls chase in, and then
they're met with a wall.
I tell you what though, that uh
600 um cool wall or put wall I should
say on QQQ held up, didn't it? All
right. Big big transition here. I'm
still expecting higher prices, but we
are starting to see much more aggressive
selling up here. I want to see this move
higher. Please don't move lower. Please
please please. We got to move higher
here. This is no man's land right now.
Check ES. Where's ES? Coming into
GlobeEx.
SPY at its 50-day. Think we've got more.
I want to see SPY ideally get up towards
previous day low. I think we've got more
upside here. Please market,
please flag this and go. Don't drop it
100 points upside, please.
You still look good. If you're in this
long, you look good.
Come on market up. You get near the 200.
Sorry the uh yeah the 200 on the 5m
minute here.
Higher the better. Higher the better. I
want to treat this like a sort of
blowoff top type scenario.
Still not I don't think there's enough
excess up here. It's starting to go
sideways. So, we could trap volume up
here and do like a volume shelf crack,
but I'd much rather see a squeeze out
than that play.
Here's the new H1. So, hopefully we can
make a new H1 H4 high here. One 1 2 3 4.
So, the H4's printed a new high. Yeah, a
little squeeze higher and then sold into
would make sense on every time frame now
because we could rebalance this H1.
Please move higher first though. Please
move higher first. Otherwise, you're not
going to give me an A+ setup. I'm
looking for H1 to make a new high above
this and then fail and repric this huge
H1 bar. Please move higher first market.
Don't just leave this volume trapped
here, which is what you're looking like
you might want to do. Please don't do
that. It will not be an A+ setup.
You mother
clucker.
Remove this. Now, we don't need this,
right? Watching this volume how we build
out here. They lead this volume up here.
It's going to be a pain. I want to move
higher. I want three drives into this,
please. A+ scenario. Get up there.
Get up there.
No. No, [\h__\h]
Okay. If they keep rejecting this volume
here at 30s, there's potential for a
short. This is like a couple weeks ago.
I don't want to see this. I would much
rather we see three drives higher and
sold into. I don't think there's enough
excess here and we haven't made a new H1
high. Well, we have, but
we haven't. Sorry. I want to see us
print over whatever this is 70. I'd much
rather
we do this. If we reject this though,
it's a legit play. It's just not very
nice.
Ah,
please find a bid here.
VIX starting to bounce off those uh
2160s
we talked about. Please go up. Please go
up. Please go up. Please go up. Please
go up. Please go up. Please trap them.
Please trap them higher. I need you to
take the low hanging fruits. The reason
being we're this close to previous day
low and value. Taking a short here is
very risky because we've not fulfilled
the obligation. Now we've got this close
to taking all this. we might as well
come and test it, which is where my
head's at. Please come and test it and
leave no more lowhanging fruits. So then
I know the trade should be downside.
Remember this is that H1 high. So a trap
over here would be absolutely ideal at
the moment. They keep rejecting this
volume up here.
They definitely keep rejecting volume up
here. Oh my god, you buggers.
You absolute buggers.
So A+ would be up here. This would be a
B a B setup I guess only because we're
leaving lowh hanging fruit so close but
it's possible if they reject this volume
we do a full rotation back down into
839s. All right. So there's a 100 point
trade there available. I want to see us
come into here first to make that very
very clear. I want to see us trade
through this volume and squeeze higher.
But at the moment they are unwilling to
do it. We have left some buying excess
at those highs. We are over GlobeEx
though. We're over both VWAPs. It's
worth being aware of that. We are
holding flow zones. We have not flipped
yet. So, I'm trying to remain patient
here. I'm talking to you almost like I'm
talking to myself so you can see what
I'm thinking. I want this to trade
higher first because I think that is a
much much better trade. It would be a
much much better trade if we can trade
up anywhere into into previous day
value, previous day close, and then find
rejection after a blowoff top. But at
the moment, this gray box, you can see
it's starting to reject. Point of
control is now up here. is now the most
traded level on the day is up here in
terms of volume. So, it's a big level.
We can get over that. Maybe we can get
up into here, which would be great. Come
on, market. Be kind. Give us the A+. Get
up into there. Squeeze everyone out and
then offer it.
Would I call this parabolic? Um, no, not
really. I mean, it's very aggressive.
It's very aggressive, but we have sort
of walked it. It's aggressive, but we've
walked it. I'd say if they were all like
these candles, I would call that
parabolic. But this is like fairly
controlled right now. We need something
like this, like a big nasty candle and
then we leave a wick on it and we go see
you. Right. That's what I'm looking for.
It's a hard trade because the uh moves
are aggressive. You're still trading at
34 ATR per one minute candle here. Even
going sideways.
So if you're someone that risks 20
points a candle, you or 20 points to
trade, you can't trade this. So, you
need to size down so you can give
yourself more room.
Yeah, that's what I'm thinking, Scott.
That's what I need to see. We're still
rejecting this volume, though. Oh my
god. This is getting heavy. This is not
what I wanted. But, uh, you can see this
volume just rejected. They failed to
make a new high. They did just reject
it. This is getting heavy here. Oh gosh.
This is not what we want. Can they do a
two-legged hold and go higher? Pretty
please market. Pretty pretty pretty
pretty please. All of the mags still red
by the way. And Vic starting to find
that bid and starting to squeeze higher.
Starting to go and test 22s now. Please
market higher. I want an A+ trade on a
Friday after such a good week.
What we going to do team?
It's building out thicker volume here as
well to make it very tricky. So, this
has gone from being here to really
they've built it out all the way down to
here now, which is not ideal, is it?
Look how much thicker we've got because
we've traded in this range. They've made
a very big range up here. Much better
when the ranges are small in terms of
being able to risk off. So, let's just
see. And still no position for me. I'm
still I know what I want to see. I've
million times.
Hopefully it comes to us.
I'll give you a readout on the mag so
you can see what I'm looking at. Tesla
1.88% down. Nvidia just about red,
pretty much flat. Same on Microsoft.
Those are both closed the gaps. Meta 1%
down. Google just under 1% down. Amazon
3/4 of a percent down. Actually more
than that. And Apple 0.18% down. Right.
So most of them well most of them a few
of them are trying to close their gaps.
and probably starting to find some
sellers around those gap bills.
Here we go. Good, good, good, good,
good. Go, go, go, go, go. Beautiful. So,
there's the two-leg holder flow zones
reclaim. Can we get up into here over
this H1 somewhere up into these levels?
If we start basing, I want to make this
really clear. I will not short. It would
just mean I'm wrong on my thesis. If we
start basing up here, this is a long all
the way back to previous day point of
control, previous day value area high.
This is your balance from yesterday. If
they reclaim this balance, if they don't
reject it, the squeeze goes all the way
up here. I'm not going to like add add
into that short, you know, that would
just mean Alex is wrong, which is fine.
Alex's thesis is wrong for the day, and
he gets no trade setup.
But there is the take of H1 high. No
excess there. That is gross. Can we have
some excess, please? No one wanted to
participate up there at all. No buyers
and no sellers at all up there. That was
just an empty void. Could be the end of
the auction bug. We want excess because
we want traps.
Spy doing spy rejecting GlobeEx right
now or ES sorry rejecting GlobeEx right
now. Spying to its 50-day QQQ got very
close to previous day low hit 50. That's
a big reaction there where they failed
to trade. There was literally no trades
really took place from 64.
H
well this is what we talked about. This
structure though is not very good for
it. Back to PC. We want like a candle
with a big excess and a wick and a
turnaround. Not not a flat top like that
at 84. You gross gross thing
back to the low side of this range.
Are they going to go all the way back
for it now?
Imbalance above 60.
Mate, what are you doing? You're going
to make this impossible for me. I can
already tell.
Battle here. Massive battle here.
Still no excess at the high. Here's the
move back towards 60.
Selling in front of it. Oh, mate. This
is gross.
This is tight and gross.
Starting to see some failures here.
Still no flush below
PC here. This this candle structure here
is really bad. All right. So on
basically from 63 we have a void from 63
up to 80. There was no transactions
really above 80 in terms of market. The
delta there a little bit. You can see
delta was buy side but it wasn't great
up there. It's not a good looking candle
for a reversal at the moment. But let's
just see. Still not seeing exactly what
I want. But we're back to the edge of
this shelf. We can pull this gray out.
I'm still not convinced the top is in
yet just based on what I'm looking on
order flow.
Yeah, Apple's like the relative strength
in Apple's been amazing.
It has been amazing. Like it's
incredible. But again, we've talked
about it, haven't we? Every time we
shift out the chips, the money is going
into Apple. It did have positive news
catalyst this morning like the iPhone
sales remember what it was up 20% year
on year. uh compared to the old iPhone
which which was a flop in China. The
iPhone sales in China, the new iPhone,
was it 17? Up 20% year on year. So
that's a big look for them. That's a big
part of the market.
Lots of shorts I see on Bookmap.
You you can't see shorts on Bookmap,
mate. You can just see buying and
selling. You can't see whether they're
shorts. This this can be buyers selling,
right? It's not necessarily shorts.
I don't really take tweets like that
into account. I just think I try and
trade technicals like Fed's going to say
whatever they're going to say. Markets
market's going to do what they want to
do.
Failing here to reclaim. So, did we fill
that imbalance? Build a lot of that
imbalance and failed. Remember the
imbalance was all the way up to 80. It
was from 60 to 80. Failed there. Big big
volume being built out here in the gray
zone. If we leave gray zone, it gets
very nasty for a drop. If we hold gray
zone, they still have the chance to go
and fill low hanging fruit above
previous day low. Previous day value
area low, previous week value area low
here to the bottom of the gray zone
again. Point of control here again.
Sellers trying to be more aggressive
here this time than last time round. Do
they get follow through outside of gray
zone at the moment? No follow through
outside of gray zone. If they snap this,
you probably get follow through down to
VWAP. Watching this very very carefully
now. This is GlobeEx here. This orange
line. This is major major major battle.
Still no position, but I am interested.
It's perking my interest after failing
that imbalance
and creating a new imbalance as well.
Think we're ready to get heavy very
soon. One more pop up and failure would
do it.
If I can see them come back into 30s and
40s and fail, that would probably do it
for me. Oh my god. Don't do it without
me after me being this patient. You
flipping buggers. No. Oh, that is
annoying. They've left an imbalance
here, which I'm waiting for.
Man, they made that hard.
Wait all all session for this and they
never came and filled it. Okay, let's
see. Let's see. Let's see. Don't want to
chase down here. They can still soak
this. Want to see how we act into this
shelf here at 15s. We've left an
imbalance at 40s. So, that's probably
the key level. If they fail back into
this shelf, we're going to move lower.
We're just at VWAP right now. I need to
be careful here.
No position. Missed missed my entry
there, unfortunately. That was probably
it now. I've probably missed it, folks.
I've probably missed it. I'm going to be
honest with you. That was probably That
wick there was probably it into 17s. me
waiting for 40s was probably a bit
greedy, but let's see.
We didn't take low hanging fruit above.
That is one thing I'm very very aware
of. Yeah, 200 on the 5minute.
Absolutely. Into the same shelf. It's in
this. It's in this block.
Come on. Come on. Come on. Otherwise,
I'm not going to get my entry. I'm going
to be very upset, man.
Very hard when you're this patient and
then you miss it.
They're trying to buy this and they're
not getting a move higher here. There's
a passive seller here. They're trying to
buy. I want to see a squeeze higher
first.
Oh, you [\h__\h] You're really not going
to let me in at all.
Be calm.
I think it's cooked, guys. I think I
think I think that was it. I think that
was it. I think that was it. I think
Alex has missed it. I think we didn't
repric and they're trapped now. [\h__\h] So
patient.
Okay, so I'll tell you what I'm looking
at on the order flow. There was an
exchange at 1010 and uh that level of
24,941
was massive. We failed under it and I
was just looking for one more retest
into it at that point and it hasn't
come. So 941 which is up here. So this
exchange here at PC was really big in
these candles here and this was the
transition from buy delta to sell delta
and I was waiting just waiting for that
little look there and all that we did is
fail this volume and that volume is now
trapped. You're probably going to get a
wash. Now if I get very lucky
they offer this and I see selling in
here and I can consider it. What's
careful now is one, two, and if they
reclaim again, they still have
lowhanging fruit. So, still no position
for me. Let's see. Let's see.
At least you get to see emotions raw.
You get to see how patient I am and how
sometimes it just doesn't come. Okay,
maybe they come back to that 41 now.
Let's see.
So, 35 to 52 with 41 being the thickest
level. 35 to 52. If they trade through
that, we're going to make new highs.
Here we come. Almost there at 35. 35 to
52 is where there's no volume at all.
Watching the book here. If we just buy
through this, we go straight back to new
highs because it's done a two leg.
Very calm here. They're not repricing
yet. 35 to 52.
They've tapped the imbalance. There's
some sellers up there. No aggressive
buying up there. We're rejecting it so
far. Bit early though. Structure- wise
still bullish. I would say structure
wise still bullish. Here's the imbalance
being tagged into. Okay, this is the
area. If they don't reject, if we trade
through this new highs, trading through
it, not touching it. So, no short here
for me because we've just traded
straight through it. So, would have had
to see sellers defend that and not
seeing it. So, no entry still.
I'm just watching the order flow.
So, I expect new highs now at this
point. Now, we've got this flat top with
no excess. Traded through the imbalance,
reclaimed this volume. No rejection.
There was nothing in here for me to see
a rejection, which is why there was no
entry. I thought maybe that would have
been it and they flew away, but they've
reclaimed and now you know what they're
looking for. Previous day value low,
previous week value low, previous day
close. Still waiting to see that A+
short that I want to see. Still waiting
for that
25,000 on deck. Let me check the ES and
spiders.
Spider's still got a way to go to get to
previous day low.
Relative strength Apple and Microsoft.
Rest of the market still reds. Come on
then. You've got to take that high now.
You can't [\h__\h] around up here.
We've got no excess up there. Go on. Get
your get your ass up now.
Hands off the mouse. Off the mouse.
Mouse. Mouse. Mouse. Hands off the
mouse.
Are they adding liquidity higher?
which would be
gap fill. Okay.
He has moved up there as well.
Still no trigger short for me. Still
waiting. I I'm very interested. Just
still not quite seen what I want. We're
close. We're close to it. I've just not
quite seen what I want yet. VIX also
just rejected 22. Worth being aware of
coming back down to PDH. VIX needs to
hold bids between 2160 and 21. If VIX
can't hold a bid between that level, all
shorts will be off the table today
because we will probably snap back down
lower, which will allow a bigger relief.
Time and sales. Yeah, when I'm order
flow is time and sales, mate. So,
I'm looking at I don't look at the time
and sales for what goes through on a on
a physical time and sales. I look at it
on bookmap. That's what that is time and
sales. All right. This is time and
sales. I can see what's going through
with the bubbles. So, it's just a visual
representation. The bubbles being market
orders, the uh lines being the limit
orders, right? And then I can see the
transactions here of who's taking
control. I still want to see this higher
at this point.
I had my hands on the mouse as you said,
hands off the mouse. Thanks, Alex.
You're welcome. Yeah, sometimes it's
just good to
let it let it set up. Let it present
itself. At the moment, we're still going
sideways. We can still build this volume
up. I want to see this trade higher at
this point. If we fail from here, it's a
very, very ugly move.
MC guy, I took 46s down to 73s towards
the VWAP using footprint and your
education. I'm more of a lurker after
four months of tuning in every day and
starting to take my own trades for
confidence. I'm a slow learner, but I do
learn. Thank you for do all you do.
You're welcome, dude. Good trade. Okay,
back to PC. Back into this volume shelf.
This was where the big exchange
happened. What, five minutes ago or so?
Oh, don't don't make it so hard. ENQ,
don't get up.
I think we're going to go into an IB
rotation day. We've got 10 minutes left
to IB. I just want this IB to be
expanded a little bit more. Come on.
I think this is probably retail buying
short covering and then we're going to
see what institutions want to do soon.
No, stop failing here. Stop failing
here.
We're going into a range now.
As you can see, we're just creating a
range now. And we've got no excess. This
is a look below and fail. This is a
reclaim. This is no excess. I want to
see excess up into here. If we base
above this, there is no short trade. I
want that to be very, very clear. I am
looking for something like this. And
then I'll add on under here as well. If
we base above this, there is no short
trade. That would be a rotational day
inside of yesterday's range. It's not
what I want to see. If they want to come
all the way up to yesterday's point of
control, yesterday's value area high,
they can do so on a squeeze. So, you
cannot be front side in this. If this is
accumulation, they're like, "Fuck it.
We're going all the way back here." So
be it. It means the trade sets up for
Monday. I know what I'm looking for. If
it doesn't happen today, it's going to
come Monday.
Big exchange. How long to the new 5
minute? 9 minutes until new 15minute
bar.
And we're just range rotating here.
What's ES doing? Stuck at GlobeEx. Stuck
at 50day. I want to see ES get up to
previous day low as well.
Come on market.
Yeah. So, sorry folks. Nothing I can do
here. Just waiting for my setup to come.
Any of you who took the long, the
counter trend, good for you. Really nice
trade. Soon as you reclaimed New York
really and trigger over here was the
squeeze really. 65. Like I said, I'm
focused on one side of the trade, which
is the protrend side.
Delta at 50 still buy side delta at 50.
It's a it's a big exchange there.
So, it's a bit of an outlier that 50.
165 buy side and then 52 100 lot uh
sellside delta. So, those are the those
50s are a big uh big battle zone.
We had imbalances there for
where's my mouse? Imbalances there at
10:11 10:16 and now we're just sort of
basing around those zones. I want to see
this trade higher.
Love my patience and consistency. Hey,
the consistency came from being patient,
letting the trade come to me and then
waiting to to see the setup. And also
understanding if it doesn't set up,
there's nothing lost, right? Like if it
doesn't set up, having to get that into
my head. If I don't get the trade today,
I will get this trade on Monday or
Tuesday, right? The same as we tra we
tried Wednesday. We were looking for
that clean out of those lows. Didn't
come. We had a couple attempts, didn't
come. We made money, but it wasn't what
we wanted. Yesterday, we get it right.
We get the exact move. We get it.
Nice fall forward. Very nice. Okay, back
to GlobeEx again.
Some stronger selling here again. Still
not making excess at those highs, which
concerns me, but we're coming back to
the bottom side of this range. This is
where they keep bidding off. They fail
this range. There is a collapse
possible. The moment they keep holding
this range, and we haven't put excess at
the highs. Still not seeing what I'd
want. I'd need to see us leave this
range aggressively. Now, if I'm
thinking, okay, we're not going to do an
excess day at the highs and we're just
going to drift lower. At the moment they
keep absorbing that. I would still
prefer to see excess. I'd like to see
lowhanging fruits get taken out which
would be at least previous day low and
ideally into previous day value area
low.
That last push what the push at uh 1022
there was some like it's just like this
is so small up here. It's It's okay, but
not the best. The move into from 50 to
60 was interesting, but we haven't It's
not like we've aggressively let go.
We're starting to get interesting here
to the bottom side of this range. But
you can see every time we've come down
here, we've absorbed and you know, they
can absorb this and go right back up
again. So, I'm not convinced. I don't
see this as like this one tick or
whatever as excess at that high. We
haven't left a lot of buyers there. I
mean, yes. Okay. from 78 to 83 there was
some buy side left up there but not not
a huge amount on the delta 122 64 like
it's not massive
there was more left in the push up into
and even that again I just don't like
knowing we've got low hanging fruits
above and we're just in a range here if
we leave the range yeah fun we we can go
much lower but
It's It's iffy. Is that a better better
way of saying it? This feels iffy.
I think there's a a mega trade setting
up here when it's done.
Like, we're not seeing buyers get
trapped up on a spike. We're not seeing
sellers really aggressive slam this
market. We're not seeing that right now.
We're just seeing sideways action. Okay.
So, I don't want to bet short here and
watch myself get stopped out because I
wasn't patient enough to see it take
this out. I will play short here. If we
move away from it and they and I see
sellers come flying in, then we can play
that short, which we're trying to do a
little bit at the moment, but it's still
just remember we've got this pivot now.
It's like they've made it very very hard
by how they've built the structure out.
Back to GlobeEx.
still holding.
How we act here becomes important. I
think we can probably slice straight
through if they reclaim. There you go.
So, this is why you have the patience is
so important.
Not seeing what I would want to see for
my A+. And I'm not going to gamble on a
C setup up here when the ATR is still
right. Even in even in the range, our
ATR per M1 is about 37 points right now.
You get this wrong, you get hurt.
Previous day value high would be
preferred. I mean, I would prefer
previous day value area low. Value area
high would mean a full reclaim, wouldn't
it? It's all up here. I don't want to I
don't want to be short up there. I want
to be short into here. If we get through
this, there's probably a long all the
way back up. I don't want to trade in
yesterday's value. It's a B-shaped
profile. We want to reject the bottom
side of that B-shaped profile. If we
can't do that, that's showing weakness
from bulls, right? Because if we zoom
out,
right, big selling profile,
we need to reject this, don't we? Right,
to move lower. Because if we reclaim
that, that happens. I don't want to get
short up here because then we're we're
liable for a squeeze. This is a
rotation. I don't want to trade rotation
on a Friday after a big sell. I want to
trade continuation if it will allow it.
Okay, here we go. So, can we see this
now? Into previous day low. previous day
value area low above. Let's see some
exchanges here. That's better. That's
much better what we've just seen in
terms of delta. Now it's all about the
reaction.
So, first time we've seen more buy side.
Still didn't quite tag previous day low.
Still wonder if there's one more big old
swipe up and stop run here before we do
anything else. And yesterday's New York
VWAP is up at 2582s
and PDC up there as well. So again,
still no position, just waiting. SPY
getting close to previous day low. You
got to wonder, are they going to fill
the gap at this point? They're that
close. It's impressive.
Like I said, I might be wrong today,
folks. Like I said, I've said it many
times. If they don't offer the short
today, they're going to offer it next
week, and that's fine.
Big exchange.
Huge exchange. They're still battling
out here. War off. Those numbers are not
a joke.
Is this guy Liquidity up here at 23.
What are you doing?
Okay. Valu area low here. Next spot
previous week value low. Next spot
previous um they close. Gap fill looks
very much possible as does VWAP. Right
now they can fail here for previous day
value area low if they leave enough
excess. We have been in a squeeze up.
Look at the size of these last few
candles. That's the kind of thing we
want to see. Maybe one more push would
be nice at this point. Starting to see
failures back down to previous day low
now already.
This is where buyers came in. So, I'm
still not too interested here. I'd
rather be patient and wait for the
absolute perfect execution here than be
early and get hurt. We are starting to
see some sellers come in, but
structurally they can still hold a 87s.
We have buy side imbalance down to 60.
There's literally no sellers from like
80s to 60s.
Big exchange. Lots and lots of selling
going on here without moving lower.
Lots of selling going on here without
moving lower.
Not what you want to see.
Possible I'm wrong today. Possible.
Possible I'm wrong.
I think a short's coming, though. But I
have to be very aware if we reclaim all
this area without a reaction, I have to
be willing to take no trades today.
That's okay.
Yeah, I I think we're going to get an IB
rotation. I think we're going to get a
failed auction and an IB rotation.
It's just going to be a question of how
much patience do people have. I have to
be aware of the mag a little bit. Have
to be aware of that mag. Oracle's gone
green. Nvidia's gone green. Microsoft's
gone green. Apple's gone green. The
others are still red on the day. This is
huge here. There's massive selling and
massive buying happening here on the
market. Structure still bullish.
No excess. The excess was in these and
we printed above it. So, I'm still not
convinced there's too much buying at the
high of day yet that's been trapped.
And if we flush without me, it's okay.
We can join on a breakdown of structure.
We don't need to pick the top right now.
Structure is bullish in the intraday
time frame. We're holding flow zones.
We're above all the key levels for now.
We're coming into areas of interest for
us to play short. I've not seen what I'd
want to see on the book yet.
Back to this imbalance. Like we said,
there is no selling under this level
right now down to 60. We're back to this
imbalance. They sell through it, we'll
probably go much, much heavier again. I
don't like that high. I don't think
there's much excess here. Three candles
are equal equal size up here. It's not.
No. And I can give you the prince of the
highs. There's no delta up there.
Not I'm not convinced. Still not
convinced the highs in. Not convinced
the highs in.
So if you're long, you're still okay.
And I'd say you're okay all the time you
hold 60. Failure of 60. this thing can
be in trouble because all the buying
the buying which happened at 10:27
right started at 60 got very aggressive
at 77
all the way up to 12. So 77 to 12 if
you're a bull is where you need to hold
it's 40 points but that's the range. If
they don't hold that there is possible
bigger flush because that is where
buyers came flying in. I'm not convinced
how I have days in yet, but I can see
where those buyers came flying in and
where their pain point would be. And
their pain point would be under
basically under 75 is their pain point
and definitely under 60. Huge exchange
here. Huge market selling going on here
again. Massive massive sellings taking
place here again. And we're not moving
lower yet. This is huge exchange folks,
right? You just had 128 lot, 155 lot,
200 lot, 100 lot, all come flying in on
the market and we didn't move lower. So,
what happens? We're going to move
higher. If they're trying to sell and
we're not moving down, they're going to
get squeezed out is why I'm still not
looking to be a short yet.
New node being built out here. And
notice the problem now is even if we get
this short here, we have to respect
this. Once we leave this, it gets really
fun.
Another node being built out here at the
moment. Big exchange node.
Hopefully, at the very least, I'm
keeping you guys safe. And I'm I'm sorry
the short hasn't come in yet. I'm sure
lots of you are waiting for the same
thing as me.
It's coming down. If it can't hold 21s,
our thesis for the day might be wrong
and it might be thesis for Monday. Just
be aware of that.
Patient, patient, patient, patient,
patient. Hopefully, we'll get a trade
here, folks.
Yeah, exactly. Capp that 21s. If you
look at that pivot from was it overnight
or was it yesterday? Let's see. From
overnight that pivot at at uh 20 I'm
calling it 21s. It's actually like 2080
2088. If they fail that they get gap
fill down to 20. We cannot be sure if
fix is going to go for gap fill, right?
We cannot be sure if fix is going to go
for gap fill.
acquiring
so much patience here. This is where it
get where trading trading is tricky is
where you're waiting and waiting and
waiting and waiting and waiting and then
what happens is you lose patience and
you either do one of two things. you
enter a not a valid trade because you
lack patience and you get hurt and then
you get very upset or you lose focus and
then you miss the setup when it comes.
And I don't I'm going to say this I say
every day on stream. I don't care about
midnight.
I don't I literally couldn't give
monkeys about midnight print. Don't
care.
I used to I used to track it. I don't
I don't think it has any value in the
market.
Okay. Look above IB and fail there.
Some buying up there, some market buying
up there. There was an exchange up there
and there was excess left. We are moving
away from it 116, but we haven't moved
aggressively yet.
still have yesterday's VW up 2580
previous day close 20 we just call it
that kind of feels like the draw at the
moment
we need to be very careful as we're
starting to starting to trade inside of
yesterday's value be aware of that if we
do not react in this kind of we're going
to call this a zone up to PDC if we do
not react here right then you're at
Globeex and you're at previous day point
of control and you're all the way up
here and then you're in a range rotation
day aren't you you're in range rotation
up here rather than range rotation under
buyers pain. It's a very different ball
game at that point. I'm not going to
stay short bias if we're going to start
reclaiming the key levels.
I'm clapped. How am I clapped?
Yeah, mate. Clapped.
Yes, I will be doing one Alvaro. I will
be doing one
absorption on the tape. Yeah, they're
still holding.
Thanks, Tonio. Yeah, I can add you after
this. No worries. So funny. I haven't
taken a trade. I have had one trade
pre-market. That's all I've done, folks.
I have not taken a trade in this
session. I'm definitely not clapped.
He's trying to say I've blown up or
something. That's what he's trying to
say, which is hilarious. Mate, you ain't
watching some other [\h__\h] shite
YouTuber here getting you trapped. I've
not told you to pull the trigger on
anything yet. Told you what I'm looking
for. I've also told you that I can be
wrong here and it not set up. You're not
seeing someone with huge emotional bias
trying to force their way in here. Okay,
this is better. Okay, here we go. Come
on buyers, get yourself caught.
Check over to ES.
Okay, ES into previous day low. Gap fill
is still available for both of them.
Exchange here at the highs.
Big exchange here at the highs. Big
sellers coming in trying to pair off.
Still no reaction. Still higher highs
and higher lows. Still the VIX trading
down. If VIX fails this level, we need
to be very careful. All right. Then I'm
willing to say that this trade that I've
been looking for today is probably going
to set up for Monday next week rather
than today, which is fine. It just means
we wait. It's just like Wednesday. I was
looking for the trade on Wednesday.
didn't come into me Thursday. We catch
an absolute A+ banger. The 200 points.
Some of you got three 400 points out of
it.
Alli, yeah, I'm just flat like it. We're
starting to reclaim levels.
Gap fill would be here. All right. And
if they want to come up here, like I I
the more we're inside previous day
value, the less I'm interested in this
now. All right.
This is previous day's value.
The more we're holding inside here, the
more likely we are to come up and f and
come into these. And then I'm not
interested in that because that's a full
reclaim. And what that means is this is
a look below previous day value and fail
reclaiming value. Maybe they rotate in
here. But at that point, you know,
what's to say they don't repric thin
structure up here on a Friday as puts
start to cover their positions? Nothing.
So like I said, it might be that I am
wrong today. I'm a day early looking for
this trade.
I will sit here and watch and that's
okay. Like I said, I'm absolutely fine
with being wrong. I'm cannot control the
market. If the market wants to reclaim
all key levels, it is what it is. Gap
fill on spy. Is it really not for me,
mate? Gap fill on spy for me is uh or is
that what you're calling for? 72s,
right? Right. So, I think you've got
another dollar to go basically on spy.
Remember, the gap fill for me is always
the 4:00 close. I'm interested in the
cash gap. If you're playing ES, the gap
fill is 760. That uh 600 level on uh the
QQQ was the cool wall or put wall,
sorry. And they saved it. We drifted
under. Neil Copen saved it. Gap now
filled on the Q's, by the way. Not on
NQ, but on QQQ. Gap now filled.
gap fill on the Q's, not filled on the
spiders yet, not filled on the ENQ yet.
Higher highs, higher lows persist.
There's a huge amount, right, of market
selling in here in this node and they
failed to move lower. That's telling you
currently that shorts are getting
trapped. This is why I'm very patient.
I'm not forcing my way in. And this is a
level of interest. We're going to remove
this now as well because we've traded
through it.
the same one here.
I don't have an ego, guys. If I'm wrong,
I'm wrong. It is like, it just is what
it is. I have a trade thesis, but you
can see on days where my trade thesis is
wrong, I'm either taking very small
losses or I'm just not entering like
today because I'm not seeing what I
want.
So like
don't worry about it if I tell you one
thing. I'm not not [\h__\h] clapped.
Still absorbing now. They're absorbing
of previous week's value area low. This
is yesterday's VWAP. All right.
Yesterday's VWAP anchored here into 80.
VIX not looking good here, folks. I'm
going to be honest. If Vix is going to
go for the gap fill,
I think my thesis is wrong.
If big big level here on Vicks, if we
fail here, we're going to go gap fill
all the way down to 20. And it's looking
like it's going to fail. So, hand off
the mouse.
He definitely did not mean that.
Yeah, I mean it's hilarious. All you've
got to go go and do is watch any of the
streams.
Literally any of them. Any of them at
all.
Watch yesterday.
You want to see trade management? Watch
yesterday.
Watch the first entry and the management
of that. taking money out of it,
stopping break even, saying that they're
going to squeeze it out, waiting for the
squeeze out to finish, then trading it
for 200 plus points. I'm not entering
like these guys who are just joining
here. Guys, I don't enter for 5, 10, 15
points little moves, the wrong side of
it like these other guys on YouTube
you're watching and screaming and
shouting because they've made huge
amounts of money allegedly
um trading like 10 contracts for a
fivepoint moves, right? I'm looking for
100, 200, 300 point A+ setups. That's
what we're looking for. It does mar.
Yeah, you're right. You're right.
Sorry. It's It's It will be from another
streaming community who are very upset
that I'm performing well on stream for
people. Okay, gap now filled.
ES not too far to go. All right, ES,
you're looking for 760. Is that your gap
fill?
72 on the spiders is your gap bill. All
right. 72 on the spiders for those of
you trading the ETFs
and uh 760s with those of you trading
ES.
And you got to wonder
where was previous week close
here. Okay. This is it. Globeex and 167.
That's PWC.
This is controlled. I wouldn't say this
is very very well controlled. It could
be a twoleg but uh we have accumulated
here. We have to pay attention to the
volume that we've built in the day. It's
not like a straight squeeze and a
rollover or like a straight squeeze and
a slam down which leaves like thin
liquidity like this. That's not what
we've seen. We've built out liquidity.
We have to obey what we're seeing here.
We've built out structure, but bulls
have done a very good job in the first
hour and 15 minutes of building out some
structure.
But do you think bulls are going to hold
calls and hold their positions for next
week? That's what you got to ask
yourself after such a big sell-off. I'm
not convinced, but
at the moment I'm clearly wrong.
Big buying in this move. Big market
buying.
VIX filled. No, VIX is not filled. All
right. VIX is into its gap. The the gap
fill on VIX would be 20 for me.
Yeah. So 20.
20 is your gap fill. You're training at
20.61. You're into the gap now on VIX.
Yeah. Which is why I'm saying like this
could be very very dangerous for more
upside now because VIX VIX has gone risk
off. It's still very high. Let's get
this. Let's not forget one thing. VIX
above the teens, all right, is not a
risk-on scenario. It's a high risk
scenario. Is a riskoff scenario, but
you're seeing a fade from 23s down to
potential gap to 20s on the VIX. It's
this is not a position where I would
feel comfortable as a bull when we're
printing. It's not like when we're
printing in the low teens and we're in
like a steady grind healthy market.
previous week close coming up. This is
so impressive. Really, really
impressive. Can do nothing but applaud
the strength of these guys. All of the
mag now gone green other than Google.
Very, very strong reaction.
And a previous day point of control. I
cannot believe that they have been able
to do this in one in one move. It's very
very impressive. And not just in one
move, in an hour and 15 minutes. All
right, we're looking at a 500 plus point
move. Is that right? 20 over 500 point
move in the first hour and 15 minutes.
That is the size of uh weekly moves we
used to get. All right, so just be aware
of that. It's very very very impressive.
They are starting to get extended from
flow zones. We're starting to get very
thin in here, folks. If you're a buyer,
I'd be very very careful right now.
I'd be uh locking in the majority of
your gains here. Here's pre week closed.
Next stops, previous day point control.
Like I said, my short thesis is could
easily be wrong.
Yeah, definitely MC guy. I mean, they
definitely got short at the lows. That's
the one thing, you know, we were not
willing to do today. But we've cut
through the key levels. The only thing
left is up here. And you have to ask
yourself,
do you want to be short
into these key levels now? Now that
we've reclaimed with strength, there
might be a scalp down. But what I would
suggest today is probably going to
happen is we're probably going to trade
is that yesterday's value inside
yesterday's value. If we get acceptance
above here, we're very, very thin from
yesterday above there. We can trade
right the way up to 500s. Should be
would that be over an,000 point move. It
would be basically a 900 point move. Um
yeah, I mean it is what it is. We are we
are where we are. Big exchange here
again. How are we looking on ES? Has it
filled it yet? Okay, ES has now filled
the gap. Globex is above it. Okay, so
obligation for everything has been
achieved. Just waiting to see if VIX
completes its gap fill. You got to think
maybe previous day. This is previous
week close where we're starting to see
some profit taking out. Uh maybe
previous day point of control. Why is
that? 280. That is wrong on my chart.
280. Previous day value area high. Let's
move this down to 80. Make sure that's
correct.
Have it a bit lower on here. 260s. Okay.
But yeah, bulls in absolute control.
No trade for me in New York session is
what it is. If we start if we start
letting go.
It's uh probably just a pullback at this
point, but we will see. We'll see. I'll
continue to watch it.
Vix almost filled the gap. It's got
another 50 cents 50 um half a point to
go basically.
Still not buy too much buy side delta at
the highs. I mean there was a transition
here but the highest player that's just
changed. That's weird.
See delta.
Yeah, I don't see that as buy side delta
up there.
Little bit caught here. They're a little
bit caught here at the gap, Phil. I
think they want point of control now.
They might as well. They've done the
hard work now to trap all the bears.
They might as well go for PC.
Why is it just lost my previous day
value area high? Thought I just moved
that down
again. What do we say it was? 2
280.
It's 260. 260 to 280.
Hey, still no trade in New York. Very
upset.
very upset.
It might not come. Like Cozy, we got you
got to be aware. It might not come. It
might not be the day for it. It might be
a giant giant short squeeze out.
We don't know. I'd like I'd like to see
it come. I'd like to get one trade in
the New York session. It would be really
nice to have at least one trade in the
New York session, but uh I'm not going
to fight against what we're seeing going
on here. Bulls have taken control. They
reaccumulated here. They had the
opportunity here. They failed. Big
sellers came in here, failed. Big
sellers came in here, failed. If they
want a complete rotation back up to the
top side of value, that is an incredibly
impressive move. It will be like a by
the time we get up there, 700 plus
points. If they do that, we're starting
to see a bit of volume being built out
here. Same story
is Little shelf being built out here.
Draw that on Ninja.
Someone needs to invent like some kind
of thing where you can draw something on
Trading View and it replicates it on
Ninja so I don't have to draw everything
twice.
Amazing.
Saved me so much time.
I mean, do they test that old gap? Wild.
Wild. We've swept now
above that 67s.
I'm just really impressed. Like, I'm
really really impressed by the size of
the move.
You got to think if this ends with it
being so drastic.
It's going to be nasty.
Is this the letgo volume?
I'm going to try a small piece here.
Just a little tiny tiny little nibble.
Tiny Libble versus 40 just in case
they're going to drop it down to 90s.
Here we go. Selling coming in here.
Nice. Going to cover a little bit into
flow zones here into this low volume
node while we build some out. If we get
a drift into here, great. But stopped
gone break even.
It's still holding.
It's not an A+ scenario, but we did
leave that volume. If they reject this,
great. If not, if they reclaim 45s here,
I'll cut this.
What's that actual pivot? 12764. I'm not
willing to risk that. If they reclaim
that, we're gone.
Okay. Stopped out be on the rest. So,
just added, I don't know, a little bit
to my day.
If we reject this, I'm willing to get
back in because we're building out a
shelf here. The only thing is, do we
want to come up here? I hate it when we
get this close, but we have filled the
gap. We are have taken GlobeEx highs,
but every time we've done this move,
we've trapped in these low volume nodes
and reclaimed and gone higher. That's
why I'm being very, very aggressive with
my stops. I'm now completely out of
this, like I said. But if we reject
here, there is a potential move. VIX
trying to find a bid. I'd almost rather
us just go and complete the gap fill on
VIX at this point. And I want to be
careful. Like, I'm still trying to trade
short. I need to talk to myself. Why are
you trying to trade short too much if
we're inside value?
Big exchange happened at 50. Is it 50?
At 52.
Yeah, huge exchange. Buy side delta
caught above 50.
Might be a bigger drift down here when
it's ready.
Starting to see cell pressure here.
And remember, we're very, very, very
steep.
Starting to see cell pressure step in
here. If they start letting go, this can
be a straight wash down. Okay, here we
go. Here we go. I'm in this. I'm already
taking some off because I don't know if
they're going to trap. So, if we can get
through PDC, big buyers trying to step
in here. Limit orders here and big
market buyers stepping in here. Still in
this.
Come on. But that move for me. I need to
be able to read you now. Watching that
control at 30. If they fail 30, we look
good for a bit more downside pressure.
If they reclaim 30, I'm not interested.
That's where the big buyer stepped in
and got himself caught. Looks good so
far.
Nice.
Let's go.
Watching these 100's whole number.
Buyers have got themselves caught in
this now at the tops. Looking good.
Partial here into PDC. If we flush this
watching this gray box and then really
I'd like to get down into 30s,
but I I know this can still be front
side. I'm just trying to time it well,
but hopefully you're managing this well
with me. You do not want to see a
reclaim into into 50s. Ideally, they
reject 32s, but where is this player?
33s.
Don't really want to see it reclaim this
shelf here. Definitely don't want to see
it reclaim any of this. So, I'm not even
going to give it to up there. I want to
see this block here where this buyer
where this big buyer came in in and
around 30. If they reclaim this, I'm out
and it will just be a small win again
and we can just let this squeeze out
again. We are not going to fight the
tape, folks. Okay? We're not here to
fight the tape. If they want to take
control, let them take control. Very
much like yesterday. If they want to
take control, you do not go add ad. You
stop out, make your money, and you let
it squeeze out again.
It's a nice rejection there in front of
those 30s.
Big battle here. Watching bookmat. I'm
playing against this buyer who got
himself caught into sort of his uh price
was at 3375,
right? I want him to say stay heavy. If
we start reclaiming 30s, I will cut this
because I'm not going to get caught in
like a 60 70 point swipe up. Very very
close here to stopping out. Need to see
this reject. We don't reject, I'm out of
this. And I can always re-enter in as we
reapproach the shelf.
Remember, I'm a bit later on my
execution here. The downside,
we are holding flow zone. So, be aware
of that. Technically, we're bullish. I
know I'm playing this counter trend on
the day, trying to play the protrend.
Okay, starting to reclaim here out of
this before we get the squeeze. can
always re-enter if we stay heavy versus
volume, but I'm not going to give it any
more room. If this buyer gets his way,
we squee resqueeze up.
Where's this shelf coming into the
shelf? We reclaim the shelf. We make new
highs. reject this shelf and we could
put in a lower high because we do have
excess on this high and we did leave
118 lot and 88 lot and another guy at 91
lot tried to reclaim that and they all
failed. All right, so we do have market
order buying at the highs who are
currently caught. So if we reject this
volume there is potential to make lower
lows and roll over. If we reclaim this
volume then I think we will go previous
day point of control.
ES back under its gap
relative strength in NQ today. Also need
to be aware of that we're shorting
something relative strength because the
rebound has been
decent out of tech.
Currently flatten this now and just
waiting to see what we do. And again, if
we reclaim volume, then I would expect
new highs. And I just have to not be
stubborn today and keep trying to force.
There's the squeeze. They've reclaimed
that level where he was stuck. This is
why order flow is important. Now, the
next level is these highs here.
There isn't too much delta above. There
was buying up there, but it got paired
off with selling aggressively.
So 65
to
to 75, that 10point range
up here on bookmap is where these buyers
got a little bit caught, but so far
they're comfortable. Okay, right here.
Right, these guys here got caught.
Okay. And then I was playing against
these big players here as we started to
sell under them and came a little
further into volume. We actually tested
the other side of volume there,
which is interesting. So, we cut through
it. Think about this gray box. We tested
to the other side of volume. That's
where they were trapped. And we can
still put in a higher low here. So, it's
very, very tricky timing. This is not
going to be easy. This is very hard
trade to be taking.
And we still have we're close now. If
they want to go PC and value area high
from yesterday, I mean, they can, can't
they? We're that close. It's a good
reaction off that box that you've got
drawn out on bookmap.
Nice aggressive selling here. Now, can
they get follow through is the question
after rejecting volume?
No breakdown yet. Look at the edge of
this gray box. Uh this little shelf
we're on here. That's your sort of new
node. We can move this down. Look here.
They've built out volume in here now. So
that's what we're watching. If we start
rejecting that, there's a bigger wash.
This can still build and come up into
here. The structure is still bullish. I
want you to understand that.
I'm trying to time this really, really
well. It's the hardest trade in the
book. It's going to much easier when we
start leaving all this and the flow
zones start turning and we can have
space down into here. The overall
momentum on the day is definitely
bullish. Cannot argue with that.
Some more aggressive selling here. This
is sort of that edge of that gray box.
How we act here is going to become very
very important if they let go of it for
a bigger move down towards that PDC. So
far they are absorbing absolutely
everything. But there is some selling
trying to come in here. But this can be
a two-leg and straight back up. Like
there's no doubt about it. If they want
to save this, they're going to save it.
That previous day up into that next
shelf at 80s. Get rid of him so I can
see a bit cleaner. They're still
absorbing here.
Bears need a breakdown and new low here.
And bulls will just want to absorb here.
Do a two-leg sort of trap to go back to
the highs, which they're holding
underneath this volume node.
Can we move this? There we go.
It's a good job by Bulls so far. Here we
go. All right.
Can we get follow through? Man, what a
battle.
Passive buyer down here that I can't
see. Once he gets out the way, there's a
flush coming. if he gets out of the way.
Yeah, passive buyer down here. Still
soaking for now.
I think the flush is coming soon.
Someone's about to get stuck.
Here we go.
It's very close.
Here
we go. They need to take out this low,
though. If they can't do that, they're
going to get caught.
Here we go.
Can we have follow through, please? Just
do like horrible 100 point candle.
So, PDC here. Watching this next box. If
we if we trade through this right down
here, we go. Thank you. So, that passive
buyer is now caught. He's offside. Here
we go. [\h__\h] yeah. Patience. Let's go,
baby. Oh, he's clapped.
Good one, mate. Hope ICT told you to go
long in this fair value gap for your new
move higher or whatever.
Get out of there.
All right, so partial here into PDC and
this gray box. We have to respect these
levels. Like I said, bulls have done a
good job building liquidity. If they
hold this, it'll be a two-leg and if
they reclaim, you know what happens. But
right now, we look good for this
rotation into here. This is what I'm
looking for.
And all these bulls are going to get
themselves caught. All this volume, all
the time we're rejecting this. This
rotation here is possible.
Looking good, folks. We're looking very
good.
Have to watch previous week value area
low here into 60s. All right. Big big
level.
Really good.
Can we get some follow through through
all these levels? Go and wash everyone
out. One. Make sure you're paying
yourself into this because no guarantee
here. There is no guarantee.
Come on, baby. Be kind to us. Just wash
the whole thing. Let's do like a 300
point absolute slam on all of their
faces.
adjust this level.
Where did they get stuck?
You want to see sellers maintain control
of 100s. All right. You want to see
sellers ma maintain control of 100s. I'm
just zooming out to see where the big
buyers came in in this last lot.
Yeah, I think there's a move down to
25,000 and below, but we have to
maintain control uh towards these 100s,
I would say. Otherwise, this is a
rotation,
right? This is the rotation,
right? If they reject this, they retest
this. If they reject this, they retest
this. If they hold this and then reclaim
this, then we go back to highs. So, you
have to pay yourself because like we
said, if this is a two-leg and they want
to bid off this, then we go back to
highs. But so far, we're in control of
this move. You want to see bears take
control of this move. Amazon now gone
back to red. Google red, Meta red, Apple
green, Microsoft green, Nvidia green,
Tesla green, Oracle green, AMD. We look
good here. This is really good. Nice
rejection of 100.
Let's go.
Let's go VIX. I want to see VIX reclaim
21.
Didn't close its gap. Came right into
it. I want to see it reclaim 21 for more
confluence. So, I'm not big size on this
anymore. Here we go. Can we get follow
through here? Pretty please. Flushito.
Let's go through previous week value
area low. Let's not fanny around in this
level. Just come and wipe them all out.
Come on, baby.
Bit of absorption here.
115 to 118 looks like the level, but I
don't want to see them reclaim 100.
Otherwise, they're going to do that rip
straight back up to 15 to 20.
Let's go.
Have to respect this shelf. It's why
it's here, folks. Right? These gray
boxes are here because we've created
volume. That thing that um Michael
Huddston thinks doesn't matter and
bizarre. That thing that actually
matters um is holding up. All right. So
the rotation can happen all the way back
to here. I don't really want to see that
because I think it means bears start to
lose impetus for this downside moveing
these 100s. Remember if we get through
100s we can rotate straight back to 20s.
Don't really want to see that. All
right? Because if we start reclaiming
that volume above, this would be a
two-legged pullback that holds and can
squeeze back out to previous day point
control. So, stops into break even. And
again, we can stop out if well for me
stops are into break even and we can
stop out if we need to.
And we can always reenter. And we always
talk about like don't force away against
this. If they're going to hold a two-leg
pullback and they want to achieve
previous day point control, they're
going to do it. And if you don't have
the discipline to walk away, then you
will get hurt.
Very big level here. They can squeeze
straight through this on a reclaim.
Flat now on this into tens. Can always
re-enter into 20s if I want.
Well, the H1 swept uh a major level for
me.
If they want to rebuild here, I think
they're going to have to rebuild
structure on an H1 more than a small
pullback. But I mean, we'll see. You
might well be right. If they want to do
this inverted head and shoulders, but it
still means there's a short back down.
But I'm not convinced. We've just swept
out all that liquidity from GloEx
and what time was this yesterday? All
the way up to close yesterday. If they
want to squeeze above this, we get very
thick above this from sort of 93s
up to 77. Is that right? 193 to 77. If
they want to keep going, like I said,
they can keep going.
I just There's no way I'm longing up
here.
This might be one of those other another
day where I say I'm not going to get the
counter trend longs even though I'm
looking for that squeeze up to happen
first. But still rejecting this volume
here.
Still rejecting this volume here. They
can't reclaim this. This is the rotation
between these levels. Reclaim this
volume. These are the levels. Let go of
this volume straight down to here.
Remember, you're you've traded
you're almost 600 points straight upside
on the session. Just just remember that.
So, if you're looking for any more
longs, you're already 600 points out.
It's a big move.
Reclaiming volume. If they reclaim this,
you'd expect them to trade out to new
highs because we could we should really
at least trade to here now. If they're
going to trade through this, they should
trade up here into new highs.
Are you going to use a bathroom while it
does this?
Put on my phone.
Oh, I've lost my phone somewhere. Don't
know where.
Not good if my wife tries to call me.
All right, back into volume.
I'm probably going to give this one more
shot if at all, but
you know, just have to admit this is uh
a rebalance day higher. I thought this
might come on
uh Monday to be honest. I thought we'd
go into a rotation day and then offer
this price up Monday.
So, off by a day
and everyone and everyone's like, "No,
you didn't. Uh it's in Discord."
was very clear in Discord.
Still rejecting this volume. This is
tricky. This is tricky.
Those balls above are still caught. They
just caught more again into that 40s.
This is tricky.
Structure is bullish. There's no doubt
about it. Structure is bullish. Lower
time frame. Lower time frame being
intraday session. Structure on the daily
and everything above is not bullish.
Right. For me, this is a repric to sell
into. It's just whether they're going to
sell it today or they're just going to
let this drift higher and sell it
Monday, Tuesday, next week. That is
that's all this is.
>> What have I done?
Wife is going to call
it.
>> Here we go.
Okay, back into volume shelf. Like I
said, I'm flattening this. Anyone's
like, "Oh, he's cooked in it." No, I'm
not. All right, we're up considerable
amount, especially on this account,
which I just traded that short on,
right? We're not we're not cooked or
whatever you kids call it.
We're not up massive on the long because
I was focused on waiting for the long to
finish squeezing out.
Um, do any of you here trade with funded
next? Because I've got a question for
you if you do. Does anyone here trade
with funded next?
I think they're going to retest bottom
range from yesterday. 25450.
Um
25450.
If they're going to do anything, they're
going to come up to where we get thick.
Yesterday is 25200 to 25240.
P yesterday 2520 let's call it that's if
they're going to retest anywhere that's
where all the buyers got stuck yesterday
where the sellers come in if they get
through that they're going to go to
value area high of 2576 I don't think
that's a sell point if they reclaim
there is a full reprice available
because above
above 25240 we are very thin right very
very thin and we can go all the way back
to that balance range where We failed
from 25500. It's possible to do that
move in one day is insane. They're going
to do a thousand a,000 point repric on a
Friday after a sale.
I mean,
this is the market we have now, right?
We talk about it. This isn't usual. This
is not usual market. Like those of you
in Discord will know, I said, I I think
we're going to go into a very volatile
market into 2026. I I can see these
moves being huge both ways constantly.
The VIX is like sustained high for a
number of weeks now and it doesn't look
like it's going to get
uh it's going to calm down anytime soon.
It just doesn't. And the cracks are out
there like the the cracks in the economy
are out there, but you have to it like
we talked about this yesterday, right?
It doesn't matter what the macro event
is. If the market's going to move
higher, it's going to move higher.
Right? If the funds are like, "Fuck
this. We want our Christmas bonuses.
we're buying that lower Ballinger band
and we're sending this to alltime highs
because we need to make our money
because we haven't made any money this
year. Then that is what they're going to
do and they are not going to care what
the news is. If they are in bye bye bye
bye bye mode to get our Christmas
bonuses to buy our new Lamborghinis and
buy a new wife or whatever they do. Um
then that that is what they're going to
do. Um which is why we have to trade
what's in front of us.
It's a Yeah, that's it. B. I mean, it's
a stretch, but
look,
I thought I thought it was a stretch
to reclaiming all of this, even though
this is like potential liquidity. I
thought that was a stretch. This was
accumulation and second leg. And we're
still going. So, I mean, I'm with you.
They're going to do what they want to
do. We We can't fight it. All I know is
that what someone tell me where the put
wall is or the call wall above because
600 was it on downside on accuse.
Where's the upside? Anyone know?
Um okay. So lifetime dogee funded next.
Um so I have I'm trying trying an
account there at the moment. I've got it
passed.
Today is day four or five. It's in the
legacy accounts. I'm up like $3,600
plus dollars. I'm due 50% of it. What
happens to my draw down when I take 50%.
So, if I take one and a half out and and
it's 100 100k account, I'll move down to
let's call it uh $2,000 profit. What
happens to my draw down? Does it move up
to 100,000?
I need to check.
So, I don't want to draw too much out or
anything. Locked at zero. So, once
you're past buffer, it it does it lock
there. Is that what you mean?
Or will I will I always have three? What
I'm trying to say is
will I always have $3,000 draw down
or if I draw some out? There's a big
exchange there again. Oh my gosh, that's
a huge exchange. Look at this guy at the
high got caught.
This is so so tricky
original balance.
So, so if I only had 2 and a half
thousand left in the count, I'd only
have two and a half thousand draw down.
Is that what you're saying? Rather than
it wouldn't go under the buffer, is that
right?
Big exchange here. Big big big exchange
here. Delta left at the highs there.
Still buyers are absorbing this. They
are non-stop relentless.
Cannot fight this. I've had it, like you
would have seen today, I've had a go at
trying to play the backside when it's
when I felt people are trapped. I'm up
on the day. I'm up uh not a lot.
$25,000 or something on the day. Not up
huge considering this is huge move
upside. But there we go.
If you're at 100K, you're locked. So go
below. Okay, I understand. Thanks, mate.
That's all I needed to know. Appreciate
it.
Appreciate it. This is still bullish,
guys. The flow zones are hot. Like, you
can't fight it. You cannot fight it.
Look, the flow zones are holding.
There's your buy signal on the reclaim
of New York. I knew that this needed a
squeeze out today and I was looking for
shorts either in here or here.
Um, this kind of area here was the prime
area. We're basing above this is what I
said. If we base above this, it's
probably not a good short day because
we've reclaimed value. If we zoom out
yesterday, this is your B shape from
yesterday.
All right. And we've reclaimed this now.
All right. And we can rotate in here. If
they rotate in here for a session,
what happens next week becomes important
because if we rotate in here, if we gap
up next week, we use this as a base. We
repric. If we gap down next week, we use
a two-day balance to move lower. All
right, so that they are pinning this in
here at the moment. It's unfortunate. It
just it didn't give me what I wanted. It
is what it is. Like we said, I might be
wrong today.
If you all thought we had the ability to
squeeze
uh 800 points in the first couple of
hours, then you're absolute geniuses.
8. Look at this. Look at the buying on
Bootmap. This is just shorts getting
absolutely wrecked right now. Here's
previous day point of control.
This is straight upside market buying.
This is just shorts getting popped. Uh
when this is exhaust, it's going to be
awful.
He was long, wasn't he? Jack,
check your message further up.
What are the rules on people winning
giveaways but get pulled when they
missed it? I I I rolled it over.
Oh, he was short. Oh dear.
What? Short early. Oh dear dear.
That's about five days in a row this
week. He's been wrong then. I think
actually one day he had a good winner.
Okay. Reaction of previous day point of
control. This is where we get thick
value area high 60 through there. Very
very thin. Very very very thin through
there.
Are they offering anywhere way up? Oh my
god. They just keep offering higher and
higher. Oh my god. Oh my god. What are
the Wow. You guys are mental offering up
there.
Wow. Wow. Wow.
Um I wouldn't say we've reclaimed it.
We're We're there. All right. So, we've
not pushed above and held yet. Right.
It's got to hold this level. And then
you got value area high. And this is the
old gap now. But that's the old weekly
gap. Uh I wouldn't be bullish up here. I
mean, if you got bullish below, I'd be
taking partials here and holding a
runner, but I wouldn't be bullish here.
Exuberance. Yeah, it's I would agree
with you. It's just it's a short
squeeze. This is a short squeeze, guys.
This is everyone who loaded up on shorts
at the lows and uh and swing shorts and
they're getting squeezed out. That's why
you're seeing market buying so heavily.
It's just a giant short squeeze. Look,
every little every drive up, you've seen
the stops get popped. Look, look at
Matt. See all, let me zoom out. See all
this green?
This is all market buying. That is
shorts getting popped out of this. The
squeeze won't finish, right, until the
last short is like done. What once it's
like a It's like a small cap trade. Once
they've done wrecking every single
short, remember
when shorts cover, they become market
buy orders. All right? So, if you are
actually looking to here's a big
exchange here. So, if you're actually
looking to sell, you're going to sell
into those market buy orders.
It can't go up forever. It can go up all
day. It can go up next week. It can't go
up forever because at some point there'd
be no more shorts to get squeezed.
Big transition here.
the previous day value high next spot
and then the gap.
Oh, sorry, Edward. I mean, I I don't
make that uh Nightbot up. It's got a
life of its own. Don't worry about it.
You It's not punishing or anything. It's
just Nightbot is
is silly.
Look at this. They are getting
absolutely run over here. Google trying
to go red to green. Value area high
here. And once we get through this, I
really don't have any other levels other
than for it to trade all the way up to
the 500s, honestly, which will be a 900
point day recovery.
I actually can't believe I'm saying
that.
A 900 point day recovery. Look at all
these market orders at the highs.
Oh my god,
someone's so hurt right now.
You see why we don't fight the tape,
folks? You have not seen me pick a top
today. We we wait for the top to come in
and if it's not in, we cut the uh trade.
Uh yeah, I mean, if you were on a a
yearly chart, yeah, u technically
speaking, BEu be. But I'd say like we've
pivoted. We're in we're into uh daily
daily downtrend now because we've made a
lower low. So we made a lower high lower
low. You'd want to see it close lower
though. I just think this is a squeeze
out. Honestly, this is a squeeze out.
Big exchange here into previous day
value area higher. We know if they don't
hold this. I don't know what to say. Uh
yeah, I don't know what to say. Maybe
gap back to the top of the gap. Um maybe
all the way up here. I mean, it's
mental, but look how vertical this is.
There's not a pullback here. It's
literally vertical.
This is just stops getting run over.
They are getting run over here.
Nothing else you can say about it. They
are absolutely wrecked. A flush will
come soon once they once all the buyers
get trapped at the highs and they're
finished with this because we lack
structure. We'll come straight back down
into this. Look how thin this is.
There's no volume here. This is straight
up. It's a straight up squeeze. Once
it's done, there will be a pullback.
Failing previous day value area high
here. Here we go. So, here's the bigger
flush down. High time frame alga here.
Previous day point of control. We can
move way way lower if there's an
exchange here. At the moment, they don't
seem done with it quite yet.
We need to remove this big exchange
there. Big big big exchange.
I'm watching this because we put a pin
high in.
It's moving so quick though. I mean,
it's actually quite hard to tape read
this. It's moving that quick. We did
leave by delta at the highs. We did fail
previous day value area high on Ninja
Trader actually have this here. So, we
were aware.
Someone asked that. It might have been
MO. So, that's an example of where Ninja
Trader was more accurate, isn't it? At
the moment.
Okay, this might be the end of it soon.
Let's see how much more juice have they
got. Google probably wants to get to
PDC. Has it done it yet? I don't think
it's done it yet.
Almost don't want to look away because
it feels like every time I look away,
something moves so quick.
5 10 look at this straight up upsh shot
since breaking out of that volume. Wow.
Okay, here we go. Big exchange starting
to see a flush. I am in this now. Small
size. Going to play down to previous day
point control. Stop at that higher time
frame. Algo stop breaking even because
it's counter trend. What I'm doing is
very risky here, folks. You do do not
need to follow me and I'm just watching
order flow.
I'm not going to give it any room.
They let go previous day point of
control. I think we can flush down 65.
So, if they hold previous day point of
control, probably going to have more
excess put on at the high.
Here we go.
Okay, TP1 here. See if I can get some
more out of this.
Not expecting too much because I'm
counter trend. Remember, don't need to
follow me. This is the hardest trade in
the book what I'm doing right now. I'm
watching the exchange at 40 now because
there's a 113 lot coming in at 40.
Between 40 and 45 is where buyers came
in in this last pull down. So if they
remain stuck, this is where we can trade
lower. This is a big level. 40 to 45ish.
I've already covered some of my position
here into previous day point of control.
I want to make that clear. If we flush
this, then there's a chance to move back
to this volume area into 60.
Trying to make this as transparent as
possible for you.
But 40 to 45 is the big exchange level.
Reclaim that. We're going to make new
highs. Reject that. I think we trade all
the way back down to here. Looks good.
So, I've already taken money out of this
sellers trying to take control here. I
want to see a pop to 45 and see sellers
sell it. That's when I'm going to be
like, okay, we're firming up. If we
don't sell 40 to 45, then we're going to
make new highs. So, this is kind of the
first drive up to test that level I've
just talked about.
It's selling in front of it. Come on,
get up to 40 to 45. I want to see if
you're there. Are you there? If not, new
highs.
Big selling. Nice. All right. They're
protecting it. I think we can have
follow through downside here. We got to
get under previous day point of control.
We will see follow through downside.
Come on. Just slam through previous day
point of control now. Let's get down to
that volume shelf.
Big big exchange. Come on sellers. Stop
[\h__\h] about now. We've blown out all
the shorts. All you guys who know what
you're doing with me, come and take
control of this. Let's get the flush.
Protect 4045. Look for that
follow-through downside. Come on. Come
on. Come on. Come on. You guys are smart
like me. Let's do it together. Let's do
it together. Let's do it together.
Let's go, baby.
Big selling coming in at 230. Don't like
that he's advertising at 30. 40 to 45 is
the level. So, we might get a little pop
up into him. He's probably a buyer
looking to get out there.
Huge numbers, right? He's offering 500
lots at 230.
So, he's trying to advertise to pull the
market up towards him because he's
probably stuck.
For me, 40 to 45 still the level.
Be careful if we build out a base here.
Looks good. Come on. Let'sing go.
Go away, Mr. 230. You're going to ruin
the trade. You are going to ruin the
trade. Look at you lifting high. I knew
that you were stuck. You fraud. You
absolute fraud. You're going to ruin
this trade for me if you keep [\h__\h]
about. Get out of my way. Leave the
tape.
You fraud.
Can we get this move down into the shelf
is what I'm wondering. Into 60.
Come on.
Be careful here if they hold it.
Remember, we've already locked in profit
in this trade no matter what.
40 to 45 is the exchange level.
Don't like that. We've got a fraud on
the tape. We've got spoofer on the tape
trying to lift price higher at the
moment. I don't like that.
Come on.
Be done with it.
Need this 250 guy to [\h__\h] off. He's
trying to advertise to pull us up. We
need to go away. You're going to ruin
this trade for me. You did the same
thing yesterday.
Absolute prick.
40 to 45 is the level. Reclaim that. And
uh this guy's going to start lifting
offers trying to make us make a new
high. So far, we are okay. We are okay.
Short sellers here versus 40 to 45. We
are looking for rotation back down
towards previous week close, which is
this orange line into this volume shelf.
Once we let go of that, oh my god, it
could be really fun. But we're not
looking for too much here because in the
day so far, we're counter trend.
Overall, I'd say we're still prot. We're
expecting rotation. Come on. Come on,
sellers. Don't [\h__\h] this up. Please. You
can do better than this. We base here.
The longer we're here, the less I like
it.
If shorts get stuck, we'll make a new
high again. And and I don't like this
guy at 50. He's being a dick. He will
lift the moment we get towards him and
lift and cause a new high. That's what
he's trying to do. He has already done
it once.
Watch him lift as we get close. He's
being a He's being a silly Billy.
He is being a silly Billy.
Edge of the gap here. Watching the delta
reclaim. I have to cut the runner.
It's all because of this guy's 500 lot.
It's all his fault advertising like
this. You are know what you're doing.
You pleb.
There you go. And he's left. [\h__\h]
idiot.
Has he moved higher? No, he's just left.
What a [\h__\h] knob.
If we reclaim 4045, I'm out. All right.
If we reclaim 4045, I'm out.
I'd like to see this reject here. This
is a big big big level.
Big level. You can see they're trying to
sell this here. Need to see follow
through now. And we need a lower high,
lower low now. Otherwise, new highs are
coming here.
VIX has filled its gap, by the way.
Come on. Very close to cutting this
here.
Don't want to get squeezed out.
He added up higher. Oh, what a tosser.
What a tosser.
Well, I'm out. Yeah, I'm out. They're
just If they're going to advertise
higher, I'm not going to fight it. They
know what they're doing. This is all
This is all nonsense. This is not legit.
They are trying to force the market up
to come and search for them. There's
someone that's stuck. This is not a
legit exit. He's done it numerous times.
rejecting previous day value area high
again here.
Oh, what a pain. What a pain.
But flow zone's holding. I Yes, I am
trying to trade against them. Like I
said, I said you don't have to follow
me. Is the hardest trade in the book is
trying to time these, especially when
you've got guys like this uh spoofing
the book. They know what they're doing.
He's already moved four or five times
today. So, here we go. Back to new
highs. I said if they reclaim 40, you
have to be out. And look, he's left the
tape again. What a [\h__\h] surprise.
What a surprise. One absolute ass.
If we make a lower high here and start
flushing, I will consider it. But I
don't cannot be keep trying to do the
same thing here. And we're starting to
build out more volume here again. This
is the level now that that 200
Has
he gone higher again? [\h__\h] This guy's
an [\h__\h]
This guy is an absolute [\h__\h]
advertising like that. I don't think you
can play this. I I don't think there's a
there's a play here. Short. Not unless
they break down and he starts leaving.
VIX still trading around PDC. Still not
found a bit like a good bid there yet.
Amazing strength from bulls. Cannot deny
it. Amazing strength from bulls.
Bears had the opportunity there. They
had bulls stuck at 14 and 45. They
didn't take advantage of it.
And we've got a spoofer on the tape
trying to lift the market higher. You
have to be aware of them. This is this
is their game. Let's keep lifting it
higher and higher and higher and higher
and higher and higher and higher. That's
what they're doing right now, right?
They're offering above and then pulling
and offering above and then pulling and
offering above and then pulling. Once
they're done with it, we can have some
fun maybe. And that might be Monday,
folks. It doesn't look like it's going
to be today at the moment, does it?
Running out of time. We got 20 minutes
till lunch.
And this thing is still in an absolute
tear upside. I mean, look at the 5
minute and 15 minute chart. It is
bonkers. Look at that.
Mental.
Absolutely mental.
He's advertising at 300. So, that's
where they're going to try and go
because this market is an absolute
liquidity hall at the moment. and he's
going to search for it. Even even though
he's not real and he's pulling,
they're going to keep searching for him.
It's just a short squeeze, Mo. It's a
short squeeze. That's all this is. It's
why it's so violent.
I'm starting to wonder, are they going
to go all the way to 500s here?
I'm starting to think you're right. Be
you because
I mean there's no sign. Every time
they've had the chance to trap someone,
there's no sign of weakness.
Let's see.
selling at the highs there. Not really
buying at the highs there. Let's see.
Same levels. 40 to 45. That's your
overunder. That's where the big buyers
came in. If we start letting go of that
and snap below 20, then I think there's
a move. But we keep holding 4045s.
There's no move lower.
In my opinion, that's where they kept
absorbing. So, here's the test of 40s.
If we snap this and snap 20s, we're
going to get the move. It's the first
retest.
Okay. What are we doing here? Are you
going to let go of this shelf for me? We
going to get aggressive here. This is
nice. Got to let go of previous day
point of control. Going to keep
absorbing here.
Big selling. Heavy, heavy, heavy. That
buyers caught. Maybe you needed to
advertise just to get into it.
Very interested now in slamming this
back down for 60s, which is what I'm
looking for. Again,
you don't need to follow me into this,
guys. It's the hardest trade of the
book. This is not a easy trade. This is
a very, very, very hard trade because
you're going to have to time with order
flow. I do not advise you take this if
you're a newer trader. The easy trade
today, unfortunately, has been the short
squeeze upside, and it has not stopped.
So, I just want to make you aware of
that. But right now, I am going to try
and see if I can time this, if I can
catch someone off guard.
I think there's a flush to 60 is coming.
Here we go.
They're still trying to absorb in front
of these 200s. Have we got anyone at
80s? 80s 60s are there. I think it's
coming. It's going to have to be very
tricky. It's going to be very tricky.
Big exchange here. Once this snaps, we
should go down to 60s.
Stop hunt. So basically under the 200s,
we might get a really nice wick. See,
still absorbing. Need this absorber to
get out the way.
Meta now red with Google. Come on, baby.
Enough already. This is your chance,
Bears. This is your chance. Here we go.
Okay, second attempt.
This is going to be a final attempt
because we got 15 minutes to lunch.
Can we get to 60s?
Here's the 200s. Whole number here. You
can take some profit here if you want.
Can we get all the way down?
Stop. Just stop. Stop the absorption,
please. [\h__\h] off with your absorption.
[\h__\h] off just for a minute. Let it have
some relief.
sellers moved down to 250. That big
spoofer.
I really hope he doesn't ruin this
trade.
Come on. Ignore the spoofer. Here we go.
God, we had to be patient for that.
Let's go.
[\h__\h] puke it. Wreck these balls. Go,
go, go, go, go. Go down to previous week
clothes. Go, go, go, go. I don't want to
see any [\h__\h] pullback. I want to see
you annihilate all of them. No
pullbacks. Straight down. Looking for
60s for first TP if I can [\h__\h] go.
Woo.
Patience, baby. Patience and being
willing to stop out when you're wrong.
That is the key to trading. So, I'm
going to see a little bit of a bounce
here. I want to see 200s and 220s stay
heavy. This node here, we're going to
have to draw this node out.
This guy here has got to stay heavy.
Don't want to see this reclaim. Okay.
Right here. What's the edge of this? 208
to 220. That has to stay heavy for the
rotation into this volume. We look good.
We look good. For the first time today,
we look good.
Starting to see some imbalances here on
a tape where it's all sell side. So,
just be aware they might repric to 210
220 before we get any further. I'm
really sorry this took all day and this
is a tiny move. I'm going to be honest.
This is a pathetic tiny move compared to
the 6700 points up we've done. I know. I
know team. I know. But I made it clear
what I was looking for today. I really
actually didn't want to take this short
all the way up here. But we are in what
we're in. Let's see if we can get down
to here now.
Oh my gosh.
That guy advertising price just had to
make our life very hard, didn't he? Had
to make our life hard. All right, we're
almost there. We're almost there at your
TP1.
If we start snapping through that, what
I would say is if bulls have had their
exit, right? If Smart Money understands
that this is a squeeze and they've
exited up there, if this doesn't hold,
we can come all the way down to here,
right? It is very possible if this shelf
doesn't hold, we can come all the way
down to the 950s. Very, very possible.
Okay, so TP1 runners, if we get lucky,
all the way down into this.
You do not want to see it reclaim up
here. You just don't. You just don't.
And want to be careful into lunch. We're
going to get thin. And it's a Friday.
It's a Friday.
So added another thousand to my winning
today.
Nice try. You caught the long and the
short. That's really, really good.
No, I don't think so, Nihal. There's no
reason for it to find a bid here right
now. We're looking for 60s.
There's a wick. I see what you're
looking at. Maybe you're looking at that
that wick at 78.
I think we're going to trade to volume,
mate. Like I'm just going to be honest
with you. I think we're going to trade
down to previous week lows. If you want
to take partial here, you can. But I
think we're trading into this volume
shelf here, right? Because this is thin.
Think about just basics. Thin liquidity,
thick liquidity. This is a good what?
RBS
zone. This is what an SBR zone. We're
trading failure here. Breakaway into
this. Ideally into this. So we're
looking for this move here. If they
reclaim this, so be it. I know exactly
what you're looking at. You're looking
at that wick. I don't really want it to
hold that wick. It's like
this here is what you're looking at,
right? That resistance, which I get, but
I think we can drift into this. This is
the thick liquidity pool that I'd like
to see us move into. Like I said,
already locking some money in.
Some idiot just sold the low there.
Yeah, you [\h__\h] idiots.
Can't help yourselves, can you? Okay, we
still look good
all the time. We're rejecting that gray
box that I've got lined up for you. The
first gray box. We can do it as red if
you want. So you can see it all the
time. We're rejecting this. We're
looking for lower.
Yeah, I see what you're looking at. It
does make sense like that to wick, but I
would like to see us trade into the
volume shell.
Man, these sellers just ruined this at
the lows. Be careful here, folks. A
seller just caught got himself caught
under 95.
Oh, really? All right. Two leg. If they
get above this red line, break even for
me on the runner. Big selling exchange
here.
Either way, added some nice money. What
am I up now?
1,00 2,000
3,000
3,250. It's not the worst day.
Nihow was right. They went to wick to
wick. Nihow was right. They held above
the volume. We didn't even get to the
volume. We're still rejecting above
here. But I think those shorts, if you
look at Bitmap, these are the guys that
just ruined this trade. So you
understand what I'm looking at. See
these guys come piling in.
These guys here, right? 137 lot, 42 lot,
46 lot, 28 lot, 8 lot, 63 lot. That's
the end of the auction. There's no more
sellers under there. And then they let
them reclaim this. And then look, higher
low there and we're gone. Right. So
these sellers just just ruined it
because they added too low
and Mr. 250 is left. Has he gone higher?
No, he's completely gone. Maybe done for
lunch. That might be me. That might be
me for the day.
Is there a way to edit on? This is one
thing I can't understand on bookmap. I
draw it, change drawing style. No, and I
can't pull it any longer. It's really
annoying.
We just traded into where he spoofed.
Alex is having to scalp out 30 and 40
point trades when the market's up 6700.
That is embarrassing.
When do I get Discord access? Yeah.
Well, if you go to the end of the
course, contorted, go to the very end of
it. Um, if you want to fast forward,
shoot me an email. There's an email on
there on what what to do.
And uh we go there.
No, no momentum indicator bar. I'm just
looking for failures. I mean, like I
said, it's the hardest trade in the book
because you're fighting flow zones and
you're looking for potential collapse.
This is the hardest trade in the book is
to try and trade these um when
we're doing this on the session, right?
This is the hardest trade on the book.
The reason I'm looking for this trade,
I'm trying to time it when we might
rotate back down to here. All right,
because I think unless we base above
this value today, all right, then what
should happen today is we should do this
the remainder of the day, right? And
then into next week, that sets out this
or this. So, I'm trying to time that
rotation back down to a to to at least
the midpoint, if not a value area low.
And it's just looking for when the
aggressive sellers come in after
trapping buyers, which is we've seen
twice, where they fail to take control.
Yeah. Nice. Contorted.
Yeah. I mean, it's true, Miguel. I mean,
the So, this has been the most hated
market of the year by um hedge funds
because they're not net long. They're
net cash. They didn't buy that April dip
and they waited for a pullback. Same as
me. I'll be honest. I am mainly net
cash. I waited for a pullback. I waited
from April. I waited in May. I waited in
June. I waited in July. I waited in
August and so on and so on so on. And it
never came. You'll know the only big
tech stocks I got uh net long in were
AMD at 158 and Apple at 202. That's all
I've been net longing and holding. They
were the only ones that gave me a setup
that I liked. That is the same as most
of the hedge funds. they're not going to
get net long at the highs without a a
good pullback. And uh
that's why they hate it. And retail is
flying in. And you know, these hedge
funds won't get their Christmas bonuses
if they can't get net long for a push.
Maybe they got net long this morning.
And if we go back to if we make new
all-time highs by January, you know, is
that enough of a pullback for them to
make money from? I would argue probably
not. But let's have a little look. We
went over this yesterday. How big is
this pullback? It's not very big. If
they got net long at the absolute low,
right, 6.7% pullback,
right? We want to see 10 11% pullback at
least. It probably needs 20. And I'm not
convinced that this isn't going lower.
where you think about retail who bought
the April dip.
Why trading? Why do I have to click it
10 times? We bought the April dip are
currently up 60%. All right, 60%. All
right, no pullback in here. So, what why
hedge funds hate this? Once we got over
this, they would have been waiting for a
pullback into this. Didn't come. Once we
got over the 200 day and broke out, they
would have been waiting for a pullback
into the 200 day. Didn't come. Even this
tiny. They're looking for a retest of
this. Didn't come. How about here? Had
the ability to break down. Come down to
this shelf. Doesn't come. Squeeze,
squeeze, squeeze, squeeze. All we've
done all year. Squeeze, squeeze,
squeeze, squeeze. So, they are uh not on
track for Christmas bonuses right now.
But we are protecting I mean we did talk
about this. We are protecting this level
here. This is out the newsletter,
right? Trading back into this node here
on this is remember this is the yearly
profile. Make sure you can see the same
thing. All right, this is the yearly
profile. This is what all the liquidity
we've built in 2025. We are currently
trading from here to here. I would
expect some rotation here. If bears win
that, we will get this rotation down to
this, right? Because that's very thin in
there. If bulls win it, they will hold
this, reclaim this, and this will be
bump bump bump bump bump bump for the
end of the year. They have a choice to
make. I would argue this is our lower
high now set. We have a gap above it.
Lower high is now set. For me, it's very
simple. I expected a squeeze out today
or Monday
based on structure,
right? We expect this we expect this to
be met with sellers in a tenth of a
breakdown. It might be that we like
let's say we come here and Monday we do
an inside bar and Tuesday we do a look
above and fail and Wednesday we explore
lower. It's possible based on weekly
model next week. We're gonna have to see
where we close. It's why I'm trying not
to be too rigid. I'm really trying not
to be too rigid at the moment because
this level here, anyone that's been in
this chat or watched the newsletter,
right, 700
700 to 25,000
is a big battleground, isn't it? We know
it's a huge battleground
inside fell below failed above failed
below inside support.
This is your battleground. We start
breaking like this kind of neckline
here. We're coming into this next node.
So everything's to play for for the
remainder of the year at the moment.
And our job is just to make money when
it's available. Like
I will review today and I will probably
question this is three drives now. I
will probably question if I should have
got long here
and I probably I've probably been I'm
going to be honest. I've probably been
too focused on the rotation because that
is a long that is a long flow zones are
long. We're net long over value once we
reclaim value. If you go premarket, I
probably said it. Once we reclaim value,
there is probably a long opportunity up
to previous day value area high. The
hard thing there is we've already done
this.
My expectation
is not to do another 500 points up, but
this market don't give a [\h__\h] about my
expectation or yours or anyone else's.
Um, and that's the thing with markets,
right?
And uh it is about controlling your
risk. All right? Controlling your risk.
Entering when it's available, not
entering when it's not.
Big selling here again. Back to these
sort of 40 levels. I'm done now for the
day. We're 2 minutes to lunch.
You I will laugh if they just drop this
into lunch.
I will laugh. They did just trap buyers
up there again into 58s.
I will laugh.
Nice guys. Yeah, everyone is leaving.
Have a good weekend. I use TV footprint
as you do. Noticing PC near the high
lows with accompanying delta combined
with price fading the volume has been a
nice sign of reversal. Yeah, probably
very right there. I would say
crazy. Yeah, I mean the news I don't
know how I'm going to write this
newsletter right now.
If we close high today, it's going to
say this. Yet again, bears had the
chance to take control and didn't.
That's what it would probably say at the
moment if we we [\h__\h] squeeze up and
reclaim a previous day value high.
That's probably what it's going to say.
They have the chance to take control.
It's been the same newsletter since
April, isn't it? Bears can't take
control. They they just can't.
Uh in the chat underneath, um Loy is am
I saying it right? Loy Ant in the chat
underneath. It's completely free. Yes.
So any of you watching who hasn't signed
up, it's completely free. Doesn't cost
you anything. Goes out on a Saturday or
Sunday. Normally goes out on a Saturday
now.
VIX still under PDC. So, just failing on
a VIX. Man, my timing is off. I thought
I really thought this move today would
come Monday. I thought we would probably
stay in a range rotation near the lows
and we would do this move Monday. My
timing is off.
Yeah, you're right. Inferris risk. Oh,
maybe I'll do that. I'll quote you. Same
same newsletter this week, guys. Just uh
But I mean, I'm trying to remember what
were the levels. Let's go through that
newsletter from last week. Let's see how
accurate we were. We might have uh
Do I have it anywhere?
You can see it.
Can't even see it. I'm going to have to
get that up.
Yes. Uh,
Angel. Yes. Extensions. Fibson and
measured moves.
See if I can find last week's letter.
See what we said. What were we looking
for?
Let's get through the first bit. Let's
go down. Is this the right one? This is
the right one.
From a technical standpoint, last week
marked the first clear instance of bears
taking control.
However, we can overlook we can't
overlook Friday's late rally into the
close. After persistent selling through
this week, that's very much like today.
And particularly heavily aggressive
selling during Friday's morning session,
momentum finally shifted. Price reached
the bottom of the rotation near the 700
and aligned with a 50-day SMA. Same as
today. So, you might be right. We're
going to repeat it. Selling pressure
subsided sharply. The rally into close
and extended sessions. The squeeze was
strong enough to push NQ back inside its
weekly range. Same as today, this
squeeze was not
d and it even helped spy finish the day
in the positive. Same as today. Looking
ahead to next week, we will demand
persist as traders digest last week's
volatility. Friday's rebound underscores
the importance of prior balance zones
and the respect of it amongst
participants. Still, the move should be
viewed as short covering squeezes rather
than confirmed reversals. True bullish
momentum won't resume until key
resistance levels are reclaimed. Same as
today, same as this week. So, bullish
scenario last week. Bulls have their
work cut out for them. Momentum has
clearly shifted in favor of the bears.
And until selling pressure is fully
exhausted and key levels are reclaimed,
most upside moves will remain as short
covering rallies rather than sustained
reversals. Same as today and this week.
That said, look below and fails of last
week's value area low near 25,000 could
spark the short squeeze towards the
volume cluster around 25,675
with a divi divisive pivot at 26,000. So
where were the highs of this week? Let's
see how accurate was I.
We said 25,680
to 26,000
sorry. So Wednesday's high going to
Thursday. So Wednesday's high was shy of
that. So no reclaim of 26,000. All
right, which is what bulls needed to
reclaim.
Bearish scenario for bears. Momentum
remains fir firmly in their favor, but
the exhaustion is whether they can build
out on it. Friday's session showed
showed signs of exhaustion at the lows,
suggesting sellers might be losing
steam. Still with significant amount of
volume trapped above, bears simply need
to defend resistance levels to remain in
control. The first level to watch is
25350. Holding below that will keep
downside bias intact. If that fails, the
levels are 680 and 95 being the last
major line in defense. Each loss of
these label levels increases upside
potential for squeeze as shorts get
trapped. Conversely, a breakdown below
25700 will open the door for a retest of
the daily Ballinger band at 24500. And
below that, we thin out considerably on
yearly profile for 24,000 and 2350. Oh
my gosh, I absolutely nailed that.
We nailed that because
this was the move.
Beautiful.
Absolutely beautiful. Pretty accurate, I
would say. Extensions to 700.
Well, there's your 700. And we'd have to
stay heavy for that for rotations down
into it was pretty good newsletter. I'd
say fairly accurate.
Fairly accurate. And you are right. I
can't remember who said it today. It's
like last week, isn't it? Short covering
rally on a Friday. We're starting to
build out a huge amount of volume here
and not moving, folks. Right. We are
starting to build out a huge amount of
volume here without squeezing higher and
without failing down.
Well, yeah, you've got uh well, we're
into lunch now as well. You are into
lunch.
I'm down for that. Be you. Yeah, I'd
love to do a Vegas meet up. We can do
that next year. I'm Well, I would love
to do that. I can probably organize if
we do it
uh we can pro I can probably organize
like a a club and a
pull some favors with some old mates to
go to a good good uh club and DJ if
anyone's up for that.
Green otter seemed like a difficult day
for me as a newbie as advised by Alex. I
sat and watched. Yeah, I mean I was look
I got it wrong today.
There's no point me sitting here saying
I got it right. I'm green, but uh I did
not expect this violent squeeze out
today. I thought we would get this
Monday. I'm going to be honest with you.
I thought we would get this Monday, but
this is a short squeeze out. It doesn't
like I would not
I don't know. I don't know what to say.
Either we're going 25,000 or we're going
to look above and fail here and close
right back inside the range from
yesterday. One or the other. This is big
buying at the high of day again. Look at
this. That's huge. Okay, I'm taking note
of this. 530 lot at the high of day
buy side.
530 lot at the higher day buy side.
That's worth noting that is. And he got
sold into passively.
He got sold into or they got sold into
passively, I should say. They got sold
into passively.
Delta's right here at the 40s. It's been
here the whole time. Your level, if you
look at the on the left, 344
buy side delta. If we start trading
under that, you're going to see
weakness. And uh that's what they're
trying to do at the moment. They're
trying to force weakness into lunch.
You're very thin as you get into lunch.
Remember, like very, very thin. You're
starting to see weakness here, folks.
You are starting to see weakness under
these 40s here.
It's still like bullish technically in
terms of setup, but this level here, if
they let go of this, you will start to
seek weakness into lunch. And there was
a big buyer exchange at those highs, but
you're braver than me. I've had a few
attempts. I'm probably done for today.
Like I said, I've been trying to
find an area of interest to fade.
Today's not the day. I've got it wrong.
We did a huge short squeeze and uh
that's it. Like there's nothing more to
say. What I will say, if we if we get up
into the 500s
and they're selling this,
it's tempting.
These exchanges are tempting.
Can't do it. I've made my money. I can't
do it. I can't do it. I can't do it. I
can't do it. It's lunchtime. No. No. No.
No. No.
No, no, no, no, no, no. Can't do it. Let
them do what they want. Um, if we get up
into 500s, we will be closing at the 20
around the 20-day.
I cannot believe I'm saying that. We're
going to rotate from under the daily
Ballinger band potentially to the 20-day
in one session. In one session. Right.
Lower bowl
reclaim 50 and 20 low ball mode.
Don't think you understand. This is not
normal, guys. Not when the bowls are
expanded. Like, yes. When we're in
contraction, not when we're in expansive
bowls. This is this is really not
normal. All right. We're into like these
kind of wildness. Like, this is like
this. This is off of the April low.
Like, this is not normal. This is not
normal. We don't we don't see this. You
give a a non-Trump environment. This
this does not happen. just does not
happen. It's crazy crazy impressive.
No, I'm not doing it. I'm not doing it,
man. It's bullish structure. I've had my
goes. I'm not doing it. Cannot do it. No
chance. No way.
H
wow. I almost want to sit here and just
see like are they actually going to go
to 500?
We're now through yesterday's value.
We are through yesterday's value. What
was the low of day?
How big is this move now?
We're 250 points up or 2.65% off the
lows. I know overall we're only 75% up,
but look at that. They're getting blown
out. Oh my god.
Oh my god. Top of the gap
up here. Running out of things for it to
look at
up here. Probably
thin volume here. A little bit thicker
here into 360s, but this train doesn't
look like it wants to stop anytime soon,
does it?
Let's uh
measure this.
Well, top of the gap looks uh probable
at the moment.
Top of the gap looks probable.
Wild.
Uh,
man, can you imagine being a stubborn
bear in this
back in the day? I'm telling you, that
would have been me. I would have been
fighting with this all day. All day,
like blowing up and fighting with this.
That definitely would have been me back
in the day.
Trying to pick the top and not admitting
when you're offside.
One thing I'd say, not once today have I
tried to short up here. I've been tra
trying to take the breakdowns when they
come, which is always safer because
you've got set risk.
I would imagine you're right. I would
imagine I'd imagine by the end of the
day there's blown longs and blown
shorts.
I would really think that is probably
going to happen right back to where
we've just broken out. I'm really
interested like what are they doing?
What is the uh overall intention and
game? They're holding every single key
level now.
What is it that they want to do today?
How do they inflict max pain? Can we
really go back to the 500s?
Like really, can they actually do that?
I mean, they can.
I'm not sure I've ever seen a move that
big if they do um off a big cell. I'm
trying to think how big was last week.
It was I guess it's the same kind of
size. Let's measure this out. last week
650 points.
Same
same to where we are now. Last week we
exhausted after 650 points. We've got a
long time left. Last week the squeeze
happened into the end of day.
We've squeezed all morning.
No, I don't I don't use a 50
SMA on a one minute. Don't use any SMAs
on the one minute.
This is a short squeeze. It's not that
bears are done. We expect after a big
sell, we expect a trade back upside to
sell into. It's just that this is going
further than people's expectations.
Going further than people's expectations
at the moment. So, all the time shorts
keep coming into it is all the time
we're going to keep going higher, right?
All right, folks. I'm done. I'm out of
here. Time to uh well, I would say have
a walk, but it's chucking it down with
rain. We'll see if my dog wants to go
out. Big love, everyone. I won't be here
this afternoon. Not trading on a Friday
when we're doing this. Let it do
whatever it wants. We come back Monday,
we see what's what. Um, thanks for
joining this week. It's been a great
week on stream. Sorry that today I
didn't have the edge today. We made a
bit of money, but uh we didn't have the
edge that we thought was going to come.
It is what it is. Um peace and love
everyone. Be kind to each other and uh
yes, see you on Monday. Look out for
that newsletter. Make sure you sign up.
You need to sign up today if you want to
receive it tomorrow. Otherwise, you have
to wait another week. All right, take
care.