Morning
team. Morning team. How's it going?
Morning. Morning. Hope you all had a
good weekend. All right. Lots to go over
this morning. Yeah. And uh as people are
already saying in chat, smash that like
button for me nice and early. As always,
we will do giveaways during the stream.
All right, a quick review of what we had
last week then. All right, last week we
fulfilled what we hope would be the
obligation of this 200 day move and
we're finding a squeeze back up off it
on the Friday which we played long this
level here. All right, based on the last
12 months. All right, there's 12 months
of price action. This is the rotation
point. Okay, you can see it right here.
All right, the immediate rotation. So,
we're watching these levels. Okay, we're
watching sort of 9 950s right now. The
edge of this 950s. If we keep absorbing
950s,
there is potentially a back test towards
where we broke down from. All right,
25600s
uh maybe 25,500. So there is potentially
this move doesn't have to happen in one
week, but it's potentially there. If we
start seeing follow through underneath
this zone, then we're going to look for
a rotation back down towards these lows
where we have relative equal lows down
there. And you know, never know, maybe
we get the next leg down. We need to be
careful uh early on in this week for
this rotation. We have a bit of news
today, not a lot, mainly Fed speak, but
we did have some news overnight from
Japan and China. So originally what
happened in Japan was pretty bullish for
the market. Nikkeay finding a bid. We
thought maybe we'd go risk on then we
have some uh treasury and bond issues in
Asia now versus the US market giving us
this pullback. So we're watching this
level into here very very closely. All
right. Do we just do this for a few days
which is my expectation? Maybe we even
drift down and do this build out some
liquidity early on in the week and then
we can use it later on on the week.
because I think the first few days might
be a little bit more choppy than maybe
some of you had anticipated, but we will
see. You never know. We might get some
follow through. All right. On the hourly
chart. So, finding a bid like we talked
about off the 200 day. Here's Friday.
So, this was all overnight Friday. All
right. And then Friday open. We squeeze
up and we get that one final push back
and we're coming back down towards this
key level. All right. This uh 25 or
24,900 somewhere in here. You can see we
found a bid on it overnight. If you
think about this pivot here, uh 969 or
whatever it was overnight, and you think
about what we just talked about on the
daily, all right, this kind of edge into
here, it's the same kind of area, right?
It's the volume shelf somewhere around
there. So, we're watching that. If we
fail that 900s, then absolutely naked
point of control based on a weekly down
here into 800. So, underneath 900s or
950s, there is a 100 point slingshot
back down there. And then you would
expect them to try and bid up for a back
test. So I think we are likely to build
out liquidity today. Maybe between these
areas, maybe between these areas. All
right. And then we can make decisions
once we start bidding over this. There's
a chance to come back up here. All
right. So not until that point. This is
the developing week profile. So I want
to be careful today. I don't have a huge
amount of bias. Like maybe if we fail
900, 950, I'll look for a short down
towards 800. And then maybe down there
they set a little trap. I'll look for a
long back up. I'm not going to be too
overly biased in one direction today. I
think we're going to need to build out.
If we hold bids early in the morning and
we drift up here, I'll be watching to
see how we react at 200s. If we start to
find a bid over it, I think there's a
rep push up into fours. All right. So,
those are my kind of trigger points
today. Short maybe to here, long maybe
to there. Try and leave this stuff alone
and maybe long over this back up to
there or maybe a fail breakout and a
short back down. So, we're going to
provide opportunities, but I'm going to
try and ignore uh 25,000 to 25200 unless
I see a really clean trap.
All right, let's have a look at this
5minute chart. You can see what happened
overnight. We can talk about the open.
So, nice gap up at the open.
All right, big drive up and then it all
got sold off and all we've done is dip
right back down to that ledge we talked
about on the daily, finding a bid and
just trapped between right now. So maybe
market wants to come and do one of
these. We will see. We will see in good
time. Monday morning, we're not going to
push too hard, are we? I'm going to take
our time to see what this market wants
to do. I do just want to mark
this zone here out there just so I
remember it that bigger pivot. All
right, let's have a look at the ES.
All right, that's quite interesting
between the New York VW up and the
24hour. So, gap up, loses the 24hour,
back down to a pivot, back into 24-hour,
fails, right back down to the old New
York VW, pivot back to the 24hour,
probably back down to the New York VW.
So, this is your rotation in here on the
ES. And same kind of story. If we find
weakness, it's possible it can come all
the way back down if it finds weakness.
Remember, we have relative strength
overall on the ES. If we're going to
talk about the rotations in the market,
hopefully you guys read the weekly
newsletter that went out on Saturday
morning.
Uh,
one of those TE's, please. Um,
if you read the newsletter that went out
Saturday morning, you should be prepared
for some of this. But if we have a look
at the strength in the broader markets,
right, ES still holding up pretty well.
All right, no big undercut of any pivot.
You'd struggle to say this was bearish
right now. You would just say more,
okay, we're not taking out, but we're
still in the range in the S, especially
up here. Same kind of story in the RTY
as well.
Um, and probably the DJ as well. Yeah,
RTY still holding look and
Dow Jones.
Yeah, new highs. So, you know, relative
weakness in tech. it starts finding a
bid, we might get going, especially with
some of that software. Way, way, way
oversold right now. Way oversold. Okay,
SPY. Here's the story on SPY. So,
opening up near the highs. Remember, no
overnight market, just a bit of
pre-market and post. You'd be watching
some of these pivots in SPY. Can it sort
of do one of these looks? Same thing as
NQ, right? Is pullbacks absorbed and are
they going to come back to the highs? It
is possible, folks. It's possible. Can't
rule it out. cues. Same kind of story.
You can see this sort of inverse look.
All right. Do we build out liquidity
here? And if so, can we get acceptance
over the 615s to go? Any acceptance
under here? And we probably repair this
low down here. So, same kind of story as
we just went over. Uh Dixie still fading
off. All right. Still fading off.
Struggling to find too much of a bid
here. Um but the same story is going to
be true here. We will be watching this
pivot on Dixie. All right. There's the
breakout. There's the retest. Do they
find a bid here to move it up? If not,
not good. And that will help gold. Uh,
in fact, what we saw overnight in Asia
will help gold significantly. We're
probably already finding a bid. We are.
There we go. So, if I was going to be
long-term swing, I think I'd prefer to
be long-term. If I really wanted to be
bullish on a metal, I'd rather be
bullish in gold than silver. It has uh
more correlation with what's going on in
Asia right now. Okay. Vicks, still we
are in this channel. All right. So every
push outside the channel, we come back
into the channel. Still finding bit of a
bid there. Let's go through the mag very
quickly. Apple holding gains pretty well
up here. All right, really strong close
for Apple. You're just watching these
sort of 76s into 73s. It has had a few
drives. You know, you want to be
careful, but so far really good because
it doesn't have the same exposure to AI,
so we're not going a risk off in the
same way. Plus, Pelosi has been loading
up on it. So, everyone now knows that
the famous inside trader Nancy Pelosi.
All right, Amazon. Uh, opening up. Are
we flat there? Yeah, pretty much flat
there. That's This thing's been getting
absolutely hammered. I'm starting to
perk my interest in this. All right.
Anywhere down towards these. It is
starting to majorly perk my interest.
All right. Down into these lows from
last year. So, I've already started like
feathering in. I want to see if we can
have one more panic uh moment in the
market for me to really load up. Goo
starting to pull back a little bit out
of that range. Zoom this out a bit. Uh
still not too bad. All right, pivot to
pivot. If we think about swing
structure,
swing structure. All right, still
holding so far, but intraday
little bit messy. Starting to lose some
bids here. Clearly seeing some sellside
pressure step into the market there.
meta. Same kind of story. Move this out
on a 15minute. You just want to be
careful. This is being sold off fairly
aggressively as we come back down
towards here where we originally caught
a bid. Um, and you can see that got
absorbed early in Jan. So, are they
willing to come back down there? Is this
an area where they're looking to bid on?
Because it definitely has been before.
I'm going to assume that's not a dark
ball print. I don't think so. So, I
think we're getting into an area of
interest for Meta. So all of these uh
ones which have been selling off more
aggressively coming into interesting
areas. Microsoft same kind of story. All
right. Right back down into these April
lows. We've got an imbalance here or a
gap. Have we now filled it
95s
we have. All right. So that might be
efficient. Probably going to be due a
bounce here soon. And we have a gap fill
back up the upside now. All right. So
interested there as well soon. already
got a feather on. Uh Nvidia still in
that old range. No real change there.
Not something I'm interested in right
now. Tesla that was very choppy. We
eventually left this range. You can see
chop chop chop. Left the range. There's
your double bottom W shape back up into
this shoulder pattern. So, can it find
acceptance over that or do we see
downside pressure? So, this is your big
overunder here. Sort of 15s in Tesla
somewhere around there. I'd be watching
that if you're trading Tesla as an
overunder for sentiment. equally
weighted.
You can see equally weighted wash out
from uh Thursday, Friday. Catch the bid.
This is your key level on the equally
weighted 28s. Um starting to catch a bid
here like we talked about. I did buy
some Oracle down here. So already up
nicely on that. We'll see if we can
retrace. Like lots of these are
oversold. It doesn't mean I want to be
in them long term, but you know, I think
we do a back test in lots of these,
right? Some form of back test. Netflix
starting to catch a bid as well. I still
want to see new lows there first, but we
will see. That's pretty much it, folks.
That's most of the broader market. Um,
let's have a look. Nice uraniums. Uu,
yeah, these going back upside now. I'm
swing long in the small size. What was
the other one I started in last week?
Uh, hood.
Nice gap up on Hood as well. All right.
So, most of these just way way oversold.
You can see way way oversold. So I'm
going to see if I can get back into 50%
somewhere up here 93s and then hold to
see if we can get back through the
hundreds for this relief rally.
Okay, you can see overnight profile
developing here. If you're wondering why
I've got that on, I always put it on the
beginning of the week. It's my
developing profile. So, you can see
these nodes already here starting to
take place. All right, so this is the
big yearly node down here all the way
down to 900. This is our overnight
profile. Can we find acceptance? We're
currently opening up inside previous
days value underneath previous days
point of control. If we lose this,
there's an argument to come back down
here for previous day value or low
previous week point of control. I'd
imagine this session is likely to be
somewhat choppy. So, just be careful,
folks. It's a Monday morning. The last
two weeks have provided us absolutely
insane price action. Um,
so let's not go giving it all back on a
Monday morning. E
this down a bit. Sorry, folks. Some of
you saying I was quiet there. I'm sorry.
It's still, you got to remember it's not
even 6:30 yet for me in the morning.
Thank you.
All right,
let's see. Here we go, folks. Six
seconds left. Watching this area and
this area down here and watching
reclaims above. So nice and patient here
this morning.
Look, just bouncing around like a mad
man right now.
I'm watching this blue box. And if we
leave this blue box, maybe down into
previous day value area low.
Come on. Let's see if we can get down
expanding here. We come into that blue
box. So, let's see if they buy dips here
or not. If we flip this, we're going to
come previous day value area low. So,
interested. Do they buy dips here or not
right now?
Or do we flip it into previous day value
area low? Big sell right now.
Big aggressive sell right now.
Starting to see some absorption down
here. Try and take place. I think they
can still move lower if they want.
So let's give this a chance here to just
settle down for a minute.
If we flip this, there's potentially
short down here. I think they will try
and absorb down here at least for a
first rally up. All of the mag other
than Meta and Microsoft or Meta just
gone red as well. So all of the MAG
currently selling off. Big seller just
came in down there at 60s
and might got himself caught. Big seller
at 60s. Mike got himself caught here.
Has absolutely got himself caught there.
And buyers up here at 96s. So currently
trading between uh 60s and 96es. So 30
points. Let me just zoom this in.
Finding our first reaction off there.
Not in anything yet folks. Going to be
very patient today. I think we might
chop a little bit. But we are seeing a
seller get caught down in those 60s
right now.
Right here like we talked about. Look at
all this selling at the lower day right
down into this. Look at these aggressive
sellers. Was finding absorption and
we're going to trade upside out of that
blue box now
and probably retest this. Great. We can
go from there.
Sorry folks, I'm very tired today. I
have to warn you. Very, very, very tired
today.
We'll do my best.
All right. So, sellers at 80 is still
stuck. Here's the expansion back up to
this gray box. This is a rotation we
just talked about. Blue to gray.
Getting stuck at gray straight away. It
will rotate and chop around in it.
what both the courses and your indicator
how do I join the discord the courses
are awesome and you're a great teacher
thank you discord is at the end of the
uh beginner to advance course here back
to the gray box here how we act here is
going to become key if they start
finding bids over this they can start
coming back for revisit into 100 and rip
all the faces but we can keep rotating
between these until it proves otherwise
all right oh my god Gosh, look at these
squeezes.
Violent. Violent this morning as we go
into violent range rotation.
Spy back to view up
and back down we go to the blue again.
Back and forth.
Where did that seller come in? 80s is
his level 80s.
Back to blue again. Back to this New
York open. It's definitely sellers
caught these lows right now. Watching
this New York open. See if we're going
to bid and hold over this or not.
Then we got to watch the 100s above. If
we are don't want to be too early.
Here's the New York open.
Here's the push over Gloex. Feathering
in now to see if there's a squeeze
through Gloveex. Taking some off
straight away. I don't like it. You got
caught there, didn't you, mate? 75. Yes.
So, break even start the day there on
me.
Don't want to get washed all the way
back down. So, out of that now.
They're gonna have another go now,
aren't they?
I'm going to give this a few more
minutes to settle down. Looks pretty
jumpy. Bookmark quite literally jumping
around right now.
Okay, if they base up here, the this is
the problem right now in this market,
right? If they lose this, we come
straight back down to this. If they base
up here, there is a small rotation to
this. This is the chop best. If they
lose this, we come down to this.
Right now, we've got shorts caught at
those lows. There's no doubt about it.
It's just whether they want to retest
them again. And I would say 80s is the
level. I'm not going to play short down
into it. If I'm going to play short, I'm
going to need to see us accept
underneath it because there's too many
guys stuck down there right now in my
opinion.
Meta now gone green, Microsoft green,
Nvidia green, Amazon's the big loser
today.
Check my swings. Make sure I managing
these.
Okay, up 10% on Oracle, 17% on Hood,
5.5% in the I bet. They're going all
right. Those swings looking all right so
far.
This is a chop. This between these. I
still think they want to lift up into
here. It's just uh I've had one go at it
already. So, I actually want to wait for
them to come right back down and retest
that low before I do it or base above
now at this point. One or the other.
Going for Boex again. They're looking
for that squeeze, but they're not going
to get it yet. Might need to retest the
low first. We talked about
big seller here at 87 900 lot. Wow,
they're jumping today. They're jumping.
They're trying to get this squeeze up to
the 100s, but they're just jumping
around on the book quite a lot here.
Here they go. and try one more time
here. See if we can get up to 100s.
Nice. Really nice this time. From gray
to gray.
So, there's a 900 lot here at 87. Once
we get through him, we should get up to
this uh 25,100.
They're just front running this 900 lot
here on the book. 2590s. Peeled some off
straight above that key level. Wanting
to see if we can just take him out.
Can we take him out? Can we take him
out?
Come on. Come and fill this guy. Coming
for these 90s. This guy at 90s.
Here we go. This is the 900 lot here.
900 lot here.
Build. He lifted. He's moved up to 120
now.
So, I hit previous day point of control
there. I'm just waiting to see if they
lift one more time or not before I cut
this the rest of this.
So, let's try and step back in. Big node
here at 70. Big node here at 70
developing.
Nope.
Back to New York open.
So, we got a spoofer on the book. He's
still up there at 120 trying to get
filled. Tiny tiny size left now. The big
node here at 70. Here we go.
Booyah. Here we go. Let's go for this
120s now. The value area high. We will
take profit into here, folks. And
runners will be for Gapill.
Come on.
bit to 120.
Watching that lift to 120. Watching ES
for gap fill. It's almost there. Here we
go. Here's the 120s. All right. Peeling
most off here. You hear me smashing my
hot keys there. Peeling most off here.
And then we'll see for gap fill now be
163. And then the edge will be right up
into here. done 88 to 25200.
Really good. If this is going to be a
right shoulder now and we're going to
get going, we need to start getting
going over the 200s. Really, we got a
low volume node up into 174s from
previous weeks. So, up into here will be
I don't expect us to get much more than
that unless they really turn on the
boosters. Big buyer came in here. 900
lot just came flying in here at previous
day value high. Do not get caught here.
Huge 900 lot buyer just came in here.
You can see this spike on the profile.
That's all by side. Aggressive buyer
stepping in there.
Is the heat map through bookm? Yeah.
Yeah. I wouldn't be entering long here,
folks. Definitely not.
We were looking for Remember today if
dips hold the blue zone. We're going to
look to see if we can hold. If we then
reclaim the gray zone, the rotations
like I talked about it was gray to blue.
I expect blue to hold. Blue held. Blue
went back to gray. I was looking for a
red dip back into here. It never came.
So I had to wait. I got knocked out once
and then got this move. TP1, TP2. And
now if we get all the way up for gap
fill, it be the yellow line above. If my
mouse wants to come up into here and
then older highs up here.
So blue box trapping all those shorts at
the lows. Remember at the lows I said
we've just trapped lots of shorts at the
lows. Look at all these guys getting
caught trying to short into This gray
box in here is the blue box on my other
screen. All these guys got caught,
right? And when we lifted and we have
this big buyer up here now. So this is
our overunder now, right? A 900 lot
buyer at previous day value high. That's
our over under sentiment for the day.
If he gets caught this now old value
area high, current point of control, if
he gets caught, we will rotate down. He
will become liquidity that gets sold
into. So that is your over under this
sort of 120 level that we're back
testing here. ES closed its gap. QQQ
closed its gap. SPY closed its gap. NQ
did not close its gap. We are now under
that player. Be very, very careful here.
We're now under that player.
Do I draw the gray zones off the daily
charts? Uh, they're just done off um
profiles from like previous day or
current day session or previous week
session. They're just areas where I know
we're likely to rotate, where we're
likely to find a bid. Like the blue one
was likely to set a trap for shorts. And
it's exactly what we got. Remember, we
said we would not short, right? Unless
we got under this and flipped it. We
didn't. We trapped shorts and we
expanded, we ripped them higher because
what's the trend right now, right? If we
zoom out, it's a pullback, right? And
the pullback, we are going to take
profit into here because we don't know,
right? If we think about this, we don't
know if we get acceptance through here.
If we find acceptance, we might get one
of these and wash all these guys out.
But we don't know that. So, we buy these
and we sell into that and we hold
runners in case.
I'd imagine we will have somewhat of a
choppy day here. But we will see see if
they turn the boosters on or not.
When I'm moving, take profit. When I'm
taking profit, I'm moving break even.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Definitely,
definitely. Definitely. Remember, I
moved break even very quick here and got
knocked out. So, I looked for this
squeeze. First time I was looking for
this squeeze here, took a scout, break
even. I was like, I'll wait. They
retracted. I took the same trade and
this time got it. As soon as we start
breaking through here, I'm break even. I
don't want this to come back on me at
that point. It's got no reason to. So,
it's already trapped, right? So, I'm
break even. I'm taking profit. I'm
taking profit. I'm looking to see how
high up we can go now. I don't want us
to lose this gray shelf now. It's
massive, massive level here where this
guy kept getting uh buying this 900 lot.
This is our overunder, right? I'm going
to make this gray. So, we're bullish all
the time. We're holding above that. The
moment we lose that, there's probably a
nasty drop down to 100 very, very
quickly. And if they want to be really
nasty, they'll flush it even harder. So
just remember right here is a guy that
bought market orders 900 lot buyer right
here big big buyer all the time we're
above him he's comfortable they're
looking for 160 you can see on the book
they're looking for 160 which will be
gap fill
where's my stop loss on the second trade
it's currently at 63 but I will probably
take it off if we lose 106es is maybe
even 120s. Trying to give it a bit of
room.
Trying to see if we can get up to 160s
right now.
Can we get up to 160s? Fill this gap.
Give you a read out of the market. Tesla
third of a percent up. Nvidia just under
3% up. Microsoft 2% up. Meta half% up.
Google 0.30%
down.
Amazon 1.8.
Nice way to start the week. Amazon 1.80%
8 0% down. Apple 1.22% down. All right,
gap now filled, folks. Yellow line. So,
that should have been your main TP.
Anything above this now becomes a bonus.
But yellow line, we've now filled the
gap. We've now filled the gap.
Job done.
And if they trade back under this gray
box, we can uh give back quite a lot of
the move if this was a big shove up just
to be uh be efficient. But we'll see.
Uh, I've got a tiny guy left, but it's
inconsequential now whether this guy
makes it or not. A tiny guy left, but
it's inconsequential whether he makes it
or not. And I will cut him if we start
losing this shelf here. Right. So, it
took two goes today, but it was the same
thesis. It was basically long for this
trap once we trapped all this, right?
And got knocked out first time. There's
the shelf. And we'll see if we get
lucky. We're going to get all the way up
into here. Uh
where's that old
Where's me old naked? I thought that was
it. Maybe not. All right. Previous week
value high
is a goer this week if they really want
to get going. We will watch overnight
value high into 200s, 210s.
Um
we don't have too much above that. We
can get pretty thin and pretty wild if
we can get above 210s. So, we're
watching up here.
Where did I see that 900 buyer? What
level? Uh 120 right here. 900 lot 120.
Here we go. So, they're going to look to
lift. So, into overnight high here. This
is a big level. There we go. So, the big
level is where they're selling into. And
we're still holding 120s. So, that buyer
still absorbing this tape right now.
They're going to lift straight back up
and look to go upside again. It's a big
battle here now. So, we're trading
between 120s, 190s right now. Huge, huge
battle. This is the overnight uh high,
overnight value area that we're coming
into. This blue line here is your
overnight value area or since the Sunday
print, right? acceptance above that. We
can look for uh this level here, 220s
and then 266s. We are still supporting
this gray box that that buyer is still
absorbing. The big market buyer is still
absorbing down here right now.
What order book am I using? Uh I use
Twin Peaks and Bookmap.
Twin Peaks and Bookmap. Starting to see
some buyers be very aggressive up here
right now. 65 just got aggressive.
Here's the lift back into this same
area. Uh I would say if they start
losing 65s now, I'd be careful because
they've been very very aggressive in
this last few minutes here at 65s.
In fact, I'm going to move my stop up
further now. I want to protect those.
I'm going to move it up to 60s.
We lose 65s. I think we wash back down
fairly quickly. So, I'm going to move it
up 59. Let's do 59. Stops now. Moved up
to 59. Let's see if we can get previous
day high, which is the red line above.
Get washed out here. Might do. Might do.
Come on, baby.
Give me 220s.
Next target is this red box. 220s.
Ideally, right up here. Come on.
Give us 170 point to start the day. You
should be up fairly decent already.
Yeah, about 140.
130 140 points right now. So, let's see
if we can get up into here. Be good. My
stop's right under this node. See this
node that's been developed? They got
very aggressive up here. My stop's right
underneath this now. 59 is my stop on
the runner.
[\h__\h] hell, mate. There's always one.
Why do I show it after the trade?
Because I'm too busy getting into the
trade. Sorry, I can't hold your hand. I
told you what I was looking for today.
Like you even had the option to buy down
here if you wanted. I told you what I
was looking for. I told you where I was
buying. I put it on after the trade
because I'm actually trading. I'm
actually trading. That's why I have to
be reactive.
All right. Washed out here on the
runner. [\h__\h] me. Chat's always a joke.
All right. So they come back down
probably to test this point of control
here. 34s and then 20s again. And how we
act here now becomes key.
Breezy, you're buying that blue zone.
Nice. All right, there's a 120 tap
again. So, they're testing this buyer,
that same level that we were at earlier.
They're testing this buyer here. VWAP as
well across the indexes and they're
holding so far this buyer. So, I'd say
160 is now key. If they fail to follow
through above 160. So your rotation now
in here is 120 to 160s. And if they do
this, they get more. If they fail here,
they'll come back down. If they fail
here, they'll wash. Right? That's what
we're doing right now.
Back to VWAP. Still not under the 20.
That buy is still currently comfortable
on previous day value area high. If we
start leaving this area, there will be a
shove back down probably into PC,
previous day PC. So, this is old value
area high. Buyers will want to bid and
hold above this for the rotation. If
they lose this bid, that 900 lot would
probably flush down here. And then I'd
be watching to see if they want to
reclaim to retest 160s today.
Like I said, I think we'll be pretty
washy and rangy today. So that at the
very start of the day, I don't think
we'll be a big trend today. I think
we'll probably wash around, build a lot
of liquidity.
Yeah.
Not Jordan. The reason is people just
want me to be like buy here and sell
here and do this and they're not willing
to learn the wise and they don't
understand that you can't just say buy
here and do this. I can say this is an
area that I'm interested in but I need
to see people get trapped in and traps
can happen like that. So I can't tell
you before it happens all the time. I
have to be reactive and my job believe
it or not is to make me money. So I
actually have to trade what's in front
of me.
Okay. Losing 120s. Like I said, lose
120s potentially down here to previous
day point of control and VWAP. And then
maybe they trap and regrow back up. We
will have to see if they lose point
control and VWOP. There is a rotation
the whole way down. Right. So remember
our main target was this right here. Gap
fill has been complete. How we at now is
key.
VIX finding a bid here. Didn't close its
gap interestingly on the VIX. All right.
Here's previous day point control.
Finding a bid of previous day point of
control. Trying to reclaim the 120s. Not
able to fully base above that 120s yet.
So getting stuck between these two gray
boxes. If we do a little dirty move,
we'll wash, reclaim, hold, and then
trade 160s if they want to be dirty.
They'll do something like this. They'll
do something. Oh my god, give me this.
If they want to be dirty, they'll do
something like this, this, this, and
this for a move back into that. If they
lose this, I wouldn't rule out the whole
move back down. But we'll see how they
build out in here now.
Back to that 120. Big level, guys. 865
outline by side delta. That's why it's
such a big level at right at 120.
So, still selling versus 120. That buyer
is caught right now. That buyer is
caught offside right now.
Back down to V1. All right. to greater.
Great. And this is key. Now, what
happens if they're going to trap, they
need to trap around here, reclaim 120,
and squeeze. You got a big shelf there
now. So, if they're We just drew out the
trap. If they're going to trap, if you
lose this gray box, I wouldn't rule out
a rotation all the way to the lows. But,
if they're going to trap, this is where
they're going to need to do it. But
remember, low hanging fruit, like we
always talk about, technically gone
here. It's technically gone.
Back to 120. If they start to squeeze
and bid above this, I am interested and
I will take a partial into 60.
Here we go. Squeeze. So, they're doing
the trap. Here we go. Oh, he didn't tell
me. Uh uh uh. He didn't tell me. Tell me
when to do it. I think I drew it out
before it even [\h__\h] did it for you.
So, watching now. Can we bid and hold
one over 140 now? So, we're long now.
There's the trap. Reclaim 120. Can they
bid and now hold over 140? If they can,
I'm going to peel some off into 160.
Hold my hand while I go pee pee. Please,
daddy. All right, there we go. We're
looking now for this. So, I'm long from
this trap once they started doing it.
Pilled some in off into this just in
case. We have a little imbalance here.
140 is key. Over 140, we'll go 160. over
that. We're going to squeeze
and stop has moved straight up. By the
way, I'm not I'm not going to because if
we want to fade this, if they want to
retrap here and do this move, they will.
So, watching this very care very very
carefully here.
And this is why trading is reactive.
All right, here we go. Come on. Let's
go. 160s.
Let's go, baby.
Want to get over this shelf here. 50s.
You can see there's a little edge right
here.
Get over 50s. We should get the 60s.
Phil. Looking to get over there to get
into here ideally. Already paying
myself.
No, Billy. I'm sorry.
Come on. Lift it. Lift it. Lift it. Lift
it. Lift it.
60s is where the buyers got caught,
right? So, I'm looking for a retest of
them. So, if we think about what
happened. I said here, be very careful.
There's lots of buying upside. We failed
that 60. We rotated to 20. We failed 20.
We rotated to back to the previous uh
day point of control. This is the area I
said if they're going to trap, they're
going to trap here. We We're playing
this now to just see if we can get into
here. I've already paid myself no matter
what because if this is failed follow
through and they lose this, this will be
a dunk. So, getting ready to get out on
the rest out now. Can always read back
in.
Why out there? Because we left this
shelf. All right. Technically, you could
risk this, but I'm risking this shelf
here. So, I can always add back in if I
see it reabsorb and want to play the
same move again.
Am I trading a one minute? Well, you're
looking at a one minute. I wouldn't
necessarily necessarily say I'm trading
a one minute. I'm observing it. Um, what
matters to me more than anything is the
hourlies and the dailies.
This 120 massive level still. They're
still trying to bid rebid off this now.
They might knock me out to go and do it
now. We'll see.
Oh, you dirty bgers. You dirty buggers.
You left that shelf to knock me out to
go and do it. Here we go.
big level here. We can move this up.
This is like this now. See this node?
That's why I stopped out at the bottom
side of the node.
I'll wait for a re-entry.
Mag is just rotating non-stop. So, I'll
give you a readout again. You'll see how
much it's changed since last time. Tesla
0.18% down. Nvidia 3.19% up. That's off
all the news in Japan. Microsoft 1.60%
up. Meta now down 0.18% down. Google
down 0.89% down. Amazon 2.63% down.
Apple 1.58%
down.
Oracle 9% up. Oh, I must be printing
over there. What am I now up on Oracle?
13 and a half%. Let's [\h__\h] go. It's a
nice swing.
So, up 13 and a half% on Oracle. up
approaching 20% on hood.
Really nice.
So those who were trading that in the uh
discord with me, the swings uh you can
always lock in your risk here. There's a
sellers just jumped on the tape here at
120. What is this guy doing?
Bought leaps. Yeah, nice breezy. just
for that retracement.
We're starting to reject 120. We're over
under over under back over again. They
can't make their mind up here. It's a
big level.
Back to the top side of this block.
Here we go. Do I only swing with
commons? Yeah, pretty much. Like
sometimes I'll take leaps, but mainly
commons. Mainly because I'm trading my
um investment account, so it's taxfree.
So, I can only trade commons on that.
So, if we lift 140, we should get 160.
We lift 140, we should get 160. There's
they're actually adding liquidity up at
180, but if we lift 140s, we should get
160s.
I'm out of this
payment link for Discord. Lis Discord is
free when you do the 20our course. It's
no monthly subscription. The links are
pinned to the top of chat. They should
be pinned anyway. Did I pin them? Did I
never pin them? I'll put it back in chat
again.
Did I not pin it? My bad.
There you go.
Pin now.
Am I leaning bullish today? Um,
I think it's just more relief. Like when
we look at
this,
it's not that I'm bullish necessarily
overall, right? It's that we've been in
a big wash. We left volume. We washed.
We hit the 200 day. We've seen relief.
If we consider that leg one, this is a
pullback. We're holding key levels here
on the pullback. I'm thinking
potentially we're going to come back up
here. Not necessarily today, but we're
going to create rotation here. Maybe a
lift and maybe bears resell that level.
If they don't resell this level, I think
they're going to resell this level back
down. And I think we'll have something
like that. And I think we'll build out
here for a little bit of time while they
make their mind up what we're going to
do. A lot would depend on the broader
market.
A lot would depend on the broader
market. Remember, we're weaker in tech,
but we're seeing like a rally in
software like we talked about at the
open.
They cannot get this through this 40 to
get to 60. All right. Be very careful
here if you were in this long now.
That's a failure. So the rotation
happening. You can see each side of this
very very sensitive. No acceptance
above, no acceptance below. If you get
under this, this is very much possible.
This is what I was anticipating today. A
lot of chop and slop. Yeah, that's it.
Big chop. Universal authorizer. That's
it. That's what we expect today. We
expect that liquidity to be built today.
If you look at the last three sessions,
like even if we go to the daily,
all right, and then go to the daily.
We're not really finding acceptance
outside previous day high, are we? We
can chop in here. We know that this is a
big level. This is volume from the high,
from the all-time high. All right, we
know that this is a big level on an all
from the all-time high. So if you did a
profile from all-time high, this is a
huge level. Through this level, they can
maybe lift for a back test of there. On
the yearly for the last 12 months, we
know that this is a huge level. All
right. So really what we're saying is we
are probably going to do a bit of a
dance in there for a bit. Yeah, we're
going to do a dance in there for a bit.
We're going to build out liquidity in
there for a bit. Now, if bulls want to
take it higher or if sellers want to let
bulls take it higher, they will let them
do this move. All right, and let bulls
chase in up here and then they will sell
them back down. Right? If bulls want to
set a trap for shorts, they'll let it
come under, reclaim, and do that move.
If sellers just want to get aggressive,
they'll wait for this break here and
look for this clean out here to then
come into the next level. All right? So,
we want to be careful when we're dancing
in between two massive levels based on
one year worth of volume. All right? We
don't want to be too aggressive, right?
We're aggressive when we leave volume.
We're aggressive where we trap and we
come back up. We're not aggressive where
we create volume.
Not aggressive. Oh, or I'm not
aggressive. I'll just say that. I'm not
aggressive where we're creating volume.
I'm aggressive where we're leaving
volume. So, no acceptance under reclaim
again. And now they're going to have
another go to try and get back up to
these 60s. Obviously, I'm not in
anything right now. There you go. So,
you're going to get your 60s. Now, I
would be selling some into 60s. Okay.
And if you get acceptance above 60s,
right, I'd be selling some into this red
block. So, it's the same trade. It just
knocked me out. So, it's same trade.
There's your 60s, right? So, sell a
partial here. And now you should come
and lift all the way up here now. You
should get all the way up here now on
the squeeze. There you go. So, they're
starting to do it. They just faf around
too much down there for me.
But we lower our expectations, right? So
when we're looking for these longs
because we know,
all right, we know that it's a relief
rally. We're not like piling into it
looking for like a huge protrend move
where we're going to break alltime
highs. We're in a relief rally where we
know we're coming into some big levels
and we're going to sell, right? Partials
because we don't know at what point the
shorts say, "Hey, enough's enough. [\h__\h]
off. [\h__\h] off." Or do they go like,
"Okay, you can come up here." Or do they
go really really bullish and let us What
was the level I just said we could come
into
25800 or here? All right. I'd imagine
one of these will be a higher time frame
sell. One of these up here. So we have
to manage our expectations as we get
into those levels
going after 200. Yeah, pro probably
trying to get to 220. I mean if you look
at the ES, it's just reclaimed its
20-day. SPY is getting a bid off its
20-day. Q's bidding off the 5day this
morning coming up to previous day high.
Yeah. So we might get alignment here
between the cash market and the futures
market. So I'll be watching that
previous day high. The red line on your
screen is probably what I think they're
going to do. The 220s like we talked
about is where they're trying to get up
to. So, if you are long in this, you
look good. Just make sure you're paying
yourself on the way. The blue line on
the screen is the current week
developing profile since Sunday.
Almost there, folks.
So, the trap worked. They just took
time. They took too much time for me. It
would have been nice if they did it
first time. Probably should have
re-entered here, but there we go. But
this was your track gray box and this is
your TP up here now. And you can hold
runners above that for GloEx high which
would be 265s.
And over there if you got very lucky
you'll get 350s if they really turn it
on. But I would be selling like 80% of
your profits into this move up here.
Into this move up here. You want to be
selling 80% of your profits and then you
can just hold runners.
No, I'm not in the long. I tried. I had
a go at it. I had the first go at it.
Right. So, once they did the turnaround
here, so I was long here.
Sold a partial. Move my stop under this
shelf. Got knocked out. All right. And
then they kept trapping under that shelf
unfortunately. And then did the move. Is
what it is. It's all right. It's Monday
morning. I don't mind that. It's fine.
This is your final TP. Red block is the
TP, but ideally you get a sweep of this.
But just make make sure you paid
yourself some.
What about shorting at the highs? Well,
there's no reason to get short right
now, is there? All right, we're bullish
in momentum. Look at the flow zones.
We're opening up. I would say you'd want
to see them trap at the highs, wouldn't
you? So, if you're going to be bullish
at the highs, uh bearish at the highs,
you'd need to see something like this,
some form of shelf built out, leaving
the shelf, rejecting the shelf for that
rotation. Otherwise, you're just
guessing and hoping it swip it swipes
liquidity and then comes back down. You
don't know it's going to do that.
question. I bought the indicator. Does
that suite on Trading View like you have
mark out the levels you have? Uh, it
marks out all the horizontal levels, all
the lines, but not the blocks. The
blocks you'll have to draw in yourself.
Like these gray and red boxes you have
to draw in yourself.
Okay. Like I said, VIX coming to close
that gap now. It was odd that it didn't
close it earlier, but it's looking like
it wants it now. Uh QQQ did just tap the
previous day high on the uh cash market.
So, we got very very close here. I think
they will probably want to swipe it.
Am I down for the day? Uh no.
What do you mean done for the day? No.
I'll look for another trade. That's all
I've got today. Couple thousand bucks at
the moment. rotating the accounts, but I
will look for another trade.
Now, remember this trade here is like
118 points. It's uh you only need one of
those a day. One of those a day gets you
paid. This trade here, if you make it,
will be 125 points. But already into the
red block. There's another 100 pointer.
If you manage to stay in it wiggled me
out. I told you I moved my stop under
here. Like it is what it is. Oh, don't
move that. I need that guy.
No, I don't need that guy. He can go.
So, they're trying to lift. They're
looking for the 220s. Through 220s,
you're looking for 265s. Just be careful
up here, though. I would not be joining
long up here, that's for sure.
Alex, why is the EMA trend friend
indicator not accessible from my end?
Did you apply from it? Did you put in
your Trading View details correctly? Um,
normally if it's not working, it's
because someone you haven't put like
your you've misspelled your username on
Trading View or something like that in
the uh form that you have to fill out.
What's the red box? Red box is a supply
zone, right? If it's a blue box, it's an
area I think buyers will will step up.
If it's a red box, it's an area where I
think sellers might step up. Gray box is
a volume that we are building out.
Do I prefer ENQ over ES? For me, yeah, I
but I just know the personality of ENQ.
Okay, they keep trying to sell under 200
here. Um, we have imbalances. The big
buyer came in at 180. A big big buyer
came in here at 180. So maybe they dunk
down to that and then save it. Here's
the dunk to 180.
Do they save it now at 180 or do they
wash this all the way back down to 150
now?
So big buyer stepped in at 180 first
time round.
Sellers getting caught that low.
Watching the 180 here. They're trying to
do that next trap to move up right here.
Here we go.
So saved 180.
Sellers caught under there right now.
All right. So here 180. There's the big
buyer. They tried to sell under 180.
They got caught. All right. And buyers
now stuck top side at 204. So the
rotation is 180 to 200 right now.
Literally instant rotation. 180 200.
They have enough juice to trap and go
here now.
So if you were quick there and I said do
they trap at 180 that's where the big
buy was then you could have taken you
know 20 odd point trade just up here and
then now hold your runners again. If
they come back under 180 and lose it
though I would be out of this
completely.
There you go. That is the 200 tag. This
is the sell side imbalance. All right
and over this is where buyers got
caught. But if we find acceptance over
this, you can still have 220 as a
lowhanging fruit to go and attack.
You took it. There you go. Some of you
took it.
Some of you took it. So this the trap
right here. Once you understand how they
built the liquidity, all right, it was
here for you. Once you understand like
this is a big buyer, sellers sell
underneath the buyer. They get caught.
That means there is a passive buyer here
absorbing. We absorb and run it back to
the 200 where the buyer got stuck last
time. If we can get through two 200,
we're going to look to trade 205s.
Through 205s, you probably get a new
higher day.
But what do I know? Like I always talk
about, I'm just a numpty on YouTube,
right? What what the fudge do I know?
I'd be looking to see if you can get
220s here. If if you're lucky, you
they'll reload this for 220s for your
runners. But just be smart, folks. And
be adding up at the highs. You want to
add on a trap. Otherwise, you want to
leave it alone. Here
you go. You should get 220s. If these
buyers can just get out their own way
here, then you should get 220s.
So, here we go, folks. Here we go. Very,
very close here. Very, very close here.
It's a bit jumpy. There's a seller at
215. You should once you clear him, you
should just pop and run it all. Here's
the 215 guy. Once you pop him, you
should just be able to run it on. Come
on, guys. Just step up and run it for
them. 215 215 215 215. There you go. Did
you get it? It's pretty close. It must
have been a tick away. Here you go.
So, here's your TP. So, even if you took
that trap we just talked about down
here, there's your there's your next TP
through that. Now, you're looking for
265s. And if you got very very very
lucky, uh, you could look for higher
into like 350. I don't think I don't
think we'll do it. I don't think we'll
do that. I think we'll rotate. There's
your TP.
There's your TP. And here's the
expansion. So, GlobeEx next.
GlobeEx next. So, you can look for 260s,
265s. And through that, if you got very
lucky, you'll get 350s. So, through all
this now, that trap, beautiful down
there. That's why I said don't short the
highs. You don't short the highs.
There's the trap into this guy here.
Even if you weren't watching footprint,
all right, you had a node there which
they supported. They rebid. They
reclaimed and it's expansion right now.
Yeah, it's a great trade if you
understand it. It's a great trade.
That's a great like ability to play the
momentum there. Okay, we've just cleared
out high day here. ES not quite there
yet, folks. So, ES has got a little bit
left to go.
Little bit left to go.
See how many of you are on stream right
now.
Yeah, you should have lot most in.
Right. ES now taking previous day high.
Spy taking it out. So, we are now
officially an efficient market. So, you
want to be very careful here, guys. Over
1,400 of you watching and only 400
likes. Come on, folks. Is that fair? Is
that fair when you've had about 250 plus
points out of me today? Even if you
wanted to take this trap, which I just
gave you. Even if you wanted to take
that trap.
Come on, smash that like button. We'll
get the likes going and we'll give away
some stuff on stream. All right. So your
TP1's in here, TP2 is here, and TP3 is
this gray box. I I would not be long up
here now. No way, Jose.
Can still see them stacking on the book.
35, 40, 45, 250. I'm just going to have
a quick look higher on bookmap to see if
there's anyone stacking. 29300's are
being stacked and 350
Well, you've got guys stacking into
these boxes uh into orange and gray. So,
maybe maybe you get lucky here. Maybe
you get the full move. I would not be
getting long up here now, though.
Vick's getting crushed here. So Vick's
next level we can look for is previous
day low which will be 1728. So this can
keep lifting if VIX is going to keep
doing that. You might get lucky. Oh my
god, this one's going to hurt, man.
Because if I had this original position
and not moved my stop under that shelf,
I would still have 10% left looking for
this, which would be 200 pointer.
Never mind.
I'm going to remove this red block now
that we've traded through it. All right.
Pretty thin nodes here.
Where to price anchor volume profile
from? Uh from the 9:30 open. 9:30 open.
Guys, when you have any questions, just
check Nightbot because it might answer
some of them. If you're new here and
you're looking at what I'm trading, what
instrument, what the volume profile is,
what the indicator is, Nightbot there
will tell you. All right, so looking for
this next move now. off your long into
65s.
There is a seller stacking here at 50s,
but hopefully you get the 65s. And then
through 65s, you can look for 300 and
even 350. What's that high? Yeah, it is
354. Just going to mark this out. This
guy right here.
All right. Possible here.
If they really shove it, I'd be
surprised.
The most recent TP that you're looking
for is this orange line.
ES about to do the same move. So, it's
about to take out its orange line as
well.
What is that? Level 66.
They are still lifting, folks. They're
lifting.
Big seller here.
I think they'll get through it. I think
they'll just do a nasty swipe.
VIX probably wants previous day low at
the moment by the looks of it.
There's the 50 tap. You should get this
move now
into the 65
and through there. 300 and 350. It's
possible. I know, but it is possible.
This was the pullback today with a
double bottom. So, the bottom was 6:00
a.m. and then that pullback we we looked
at the blue box, same level. They've bid
it back up
and I think they want this at the
moment. Big buy got a little bit stuck
there at 50s, folks. Decent size lot.
100 lot stuck up there at the 950s now.
So, worth thinking about that. Even if
we explode above him and then come back
under him, we have imbalances down here
into 30s and 20s.
I think it wants more. ES ES did just
take out that Gloex level.
I'm not convinced this is done yet. They
might just want one more trap before
they try and finish it. We'll see. We've
got imbalances, like I said, 30
twos and 28s and 23s.
Might come and fill some of these
imbalances. We have just been efficient.
So, into that first imbalance here.
Cleared it out. Buyer is caught at a
high. I'm in a tiny little sell here,
guys, just to be honest with you. Once I
saw that buyer trapped and we came back
under 40s for these imbalance fills.
That's the third imbalance now tapped
into there into 22s.
Still in this now seeing if we retest
16s or not. I don't want to reclaim a
30s here where we've got a sellside
imbalance. It's just a scalp and I'll
watch this if we come to 16s and if we
back test and lose this gray box. Here
we go out here on a runner. Just had had
a little scalp there just cuz I saw the
player get stuck at the highs. All
right. So show you again. I can't always
do this because I have to be very quick.
That was the buyer getting stuck. See,
the buyer got stuck. We came under his
level once we lost lost. Where did I
start attacking? 40s. We had some
imbalances to fill here back into this
key level here. 28. I want to see if we
get under value. I'm out of this now.
And uh we'll just see around this gray
box if we do a bit of a dance for a
while.
It's just a scalp,
a scalpy scalp scalp, right? It's just
understanding that guy got caught once
we left him and left 40s was like might
might as well put something on. Too good
not to just into the gray box. Still
think they want more upside but could
use his pain for a minute.
High day auction does look good. It does
look good. It's just interesting they
didn't want to swipe that out, but it
does look good.
ES bidding on previous day high here as
well. So ES did swipe Globex is now on
previous day high. Watching that
carefully.
Very, very carefully.
Are the gray boxes where approximately
70% of higher volume nodes are at? No,
they're just where the nodes are.
They're just where we're developing
nodes.
No, I'm sorry. Uh, money peek king. No,
no. a sale on that course right now.
Sorry, buddy. It's pretty new, Alex. Do
I need to buy the Trading View version
to work? Trading View. Don't have Ninja
yet. What do you mean?
You can get the Trading View version of
the indicate. I'm not sure what you're
asking, Nick, but yeah, you can get the
Trading View version of it. Thanks, man.
Out with profit anyways. Green on the
day. Thank you, man. Amazing. Look
forward to using tax money to buy
classes and to join Discord. Thank you
for the tip. That's very kind of you.
All right, gray box to gray box here. We
can just move this one over. That trap
didn't quite make it. So, you got your
first TP. Hasn't quite made it. Gray box
to gray box is possible here.
I would say ES has done the move,
though. It's now losing previous day
high. We have to see now. If they fail
to reclaim, they might shove this all
the way back down into these kind of
areas. There are other nodes, though.
It's kind of messy how they've developed
this. I'll be honest with you. Not the
prettiest. This is the big level, right?
Where was that big player? I've got to
remind myself where that huge player
was.
Was it 20s? Why can't I remember this
now? Where is he on my book?
120. Okay, I need to remember that.
Okay, it might come down for this and
retest it. It might be backside here,
but we'll see if they protect this low,
then they'll have one more shot to go
back up. Like I said, I think we're
going a rotation day.
Watching the 80s. 80s is where that
buyer stepped in before
here. This trap.
So they might do 200 to 80s rotation
here. And then what we do after that,
it's going to become hard. Here we go. I
[\h__\h] have the short as well.
Oh, there we go. They might come all the
way down. If we start losing this level
here, 80s, uh, we can come all the way
back down into this block down here,
which is where that big buyer had been
participating. So, I would say now we'll
rotate between these and make a decision
of this or this. This is kind of nasty
how they've got this double one. If they
lose this, we come down
and I'm short from 40s. Oh my god.
Oh my god.
So that player at the high is becoming
the liquidity. This guy up here got
caught and we're kind of come back down.
We have more imbalances to fill down
here. Maybe into 50s and 45s. Very, very
possible.
This 80 player here, Key, if we stay
under him, we probably fill all of these
now. Oh god, too late for me now. Wanted
to play the edge.
Wanted to play the edge.
you just start using trading view for
charting and realize it's delayed data.
Well, for futures it will be delayed
data unless you pay for CME or you log
into I mean if you have a prop firm and
you log into trade of a on trading view
you will get the data but um otherwise
you can pay I think it's like five or
eight bucks a month or something for CME
on Trading View or at least it used to
be.
Okay, down to previous day close here
filling these imbalances. Oh, that's
painful. That is painful.
I seem to be using two to three
different tools. Well, volume is free.
Uh the flow zones, a version of this
comes in the course and footprint is
right here on Trading View. This is like
I don't provide this like you can get
this though.
I teach you how to use footprint. Um,
same with Bookmap. I teach you how to
use it. I don't I don't provide it.
I don't make it. I don't own it.
Yeah. AZ, that was it. Swipe of
liquidity, trap buyers at the highs, and
go back down. So, it's the same concept,
right? Think about what we've had today.
That 100 lot guy got caught up at these
highs, right? And once he's stuck and
they've sold into him and they pair off
and they trade back down inside. If we
think about the low of day, the big 100
lot sellers came in where we thought
buyers would step in. They get caught
and we use their pain to go higher. What
I don't really want to do is trade like
around the mid. Right. So the longs were
here and the shorts were probably here.
So I might have to sit this out for a
bit now.
It might be that sit this out unless we
can get a pop to fade or a real dump
that gets soaked up. I don't want to be
trading the midpoint of the range. It's
going to get harder and harder to trade
in here. We've got all these the way
especially with how we've developed the
nodes, right?
Especially how we've developed these
nodes.
the tool you have a 100 lot um that's
just orderflow you can get that for free
there's a video on my YouTube you can
get that for free I provide it for free
um trade of vape
up 1524th for the day thank you Alex
you're welcome
Okay, so gray to gray again. Probably we
have an imbalance here at 200. If they
lift 200, we're going to trade 26s again
up here.
So, I'm interested how we operate up
here. Obviously, we didn't take out the
the final low hanging fruit, the GlobeEx
on um n on NQ
and main order flow today has still been
bullish. So, we just have to see. Do we
see failure to follow through up here,
right? Do we see a move up here where
buyers get stuck and they resell it or
are we going to see this? That's the
question right now I'm posing. I don't
mind which. I probably won't play the
long, but if I see buyers get stuck
there and I think this is going to be
failure to follow through, I'll consider
the short
previous day high. Not seen buyers get
stuck yet. They're being aggressive. I
think they're going to try and resqueeze
this.
Trading View and Ninja Trader are not
indicators. They're platforms. I can't
tell you which is better. It's whatever
you prefer. It's very personal. It's
personal preference.
They're still looking to drive this
higher top side of this gray box. And if
they get through this, then I think uh
up here and maybe even up here is
possible.
Want a big old squeeze out. Yeah,
exactly. What? squeezed gray box to gray
box. Held the PDC, reclaimed same level
that they trapped in before, right? Same
level, same kind of thing. Did the dance
at 180, reclaimed and gone and right
back to this top side. I just don't want
to play the midpoint anymore when we
think about where we are in the IB. I'm
not really interested in playing that.
So, I'm interested now if we fail here
or if we're I
I guess I could think about an IB
expansion or an IB failure. We'll see.
We'll see. Just got to let it set up
now. Let it build some liquidity.
Watching this previous day high that red
line how they act there
are trying to absorb there right now.
Yes, breaking out for a new high of day
as well.
Nice DTN. Look forward to working with
you.
So, node being developed here. That gray
box. No entry for me yet. I still think
there's a chance to break out here, but
we'll see. I'm not going to play the
longs, but I think it wants to break
out. I'm more interested in fades once
we get stuck. Unless we can set like a
giant trap. We'll see. Maybe that would
might have done it already under that 80
again. Remember we have liquidity stuck
at 50. That big buyer, the high day
buyer, he's stuck at 50. I really need a
coffee right now.
What do you do to cross the intraday
trading on a brand new TPT Pro in terms
of what your maximum takeprofit or
points is or stop loss? Well, your take
profit and your stop loss should be
based on the liquidity in front of you
where the levels are, not based on a
cash amount. So you should work out what
you're willing to lose or what you're
trying to make and base it upon your
contract size upon where those that
trade's no longer valid in terms of how
to deal with it. Well, probably size
down, take your time, you know, break it
down into 10 days or 5 days or 20 days
to get past the trading draw down or
whatever it is. Don't be too aggressive
on day one. And once you're past the
trading draw down, you can do your set
and forgets, right? Gets a lot easier.
All right, back down to this previous
day high. Still don't like how we're
shaping up here. I still think there's a
chance they shove it again.
How do you get anchored volume profile
to now to not cover candles? Why have it
set to the right pin to the right?
How do I calculate value levels? Any
chance they might be wrong because I see
different? It's a chance they're wrong.
It depends how they calculate them. Uh,
depends what time frame you're on. It
depends what you're using. Trading View
is normally slightly different to Ninja
Trader. So, I have both on my screens.
Yes. Breaking out here. I think ENQ
wants to go. We still got that bias
stuck at 50s. Once you get above 50s, I
think you're going to get a rip. But
it's just whether they turn on the juice
or not here.
They're trying. They are trying. The way
they're building out the liquidity here
is not great. I still think there's more
upside in this which why I'm not playing
downside. 250 is coming up. There's the
test towards 250s. Once you get through
that, there's a resqueeze because that's
where that big player that 100 lot got
stuck before. So if you are long, I'd be
taking a partial into this guy at 250.
And if you get through him, you'll be
looking for
uh 66s and then this gray box above. So
here's the 250. You need this guy not to
become a seller. You need this guy up
here not to become a seller. So you want
to break through 250 and just rip some
faces. There's the 250. He's started
selling there. So he's got outbreak
even. Now if you rebid this above it,
you can look for 66s and 300s, right? So
like we said, there's a the buyer was
stuck at 250s. Look at that. right into
250. He became the seller. So, whoever
market ordered there before has probably
now got out. Now, if you re bid above
this, you should get the squeeze. There
you go. So, we should now get 66s and
potentially 300s if ES wants to carry
it. You should be taking a little bit of
a partial into high of day again.
They've caught buyers up here into 55s.
You want to see a base out above IB high
now. Here we go. You're going to get
this finally going to take this uh
orange line out.
Here
we go.
Well done, guys. You finally got it.
Nice. All right. So, runners now would
be 300. So, if you rebid this. All
right. Your runners now are into here.
300. And then to this level here, 350.
Um, I'm just going to do a measured
move. I just want to see is initial
balance set. It is. Let me just see what
that's going to look like today. It's
going to look pretty big, isn't it?
Oh, look at that.
Look at that. 1618 right into previous
week value area high. I would be
somewhat surprised if they were able to
do that today, but
who knows.
All right, liquidity taken on GlobeEx.
The only thing left are these these up
here now. Gray and then red line.
All right, folks. I'm going to grab
myself a coffee. Let's just check how
many of you are here. What's the time?
And I would like to do an early giveaway
here. 1,400 of you here. Uh, smash that
like button. 678 likes. When I get back,
we'll give away like an introduction
course. And then we'll do some Apex
giveaways as well. Coming right back.
All right, coffee is boiling
or brewing I should say.
Is he actually trading? Like what the
[\h__\h] are you lot on about?
Yes, a version of the indicator is in
the course. So, if you open up the
course and scroll through it, you'll
find a version there as well, a version
for it there in the course. So, you've
just got to go down into the course and
find it. If you want the pro version,
you will have to upgrade for the pro
version.
So I'll be using IB and 250 as your over
under. That's where the buyer came in.
250 this level here. And definitely
this this level here is huge. This node
down here. So back to 250 where this
buyer came in. Going to fill all this in
so quickly.
Yes. Holding up pretty well here.
So this imbalance being filled back to
this gray box. Do they rebid here or
not? Or are they now going to sell IB
and 50s for a bigger wash?
VIX has just come back under previous
days low and found a bid. So we know. So
we're watching these 50s and IB. If they
start rejecting here, we might move
lower violently if they start rejecting.
So what I'd be looking for now is are
they going to do
Are you going to let me draw? No, you're
not. Are they going to reject 50s, come
under here and wash is what I'd be
watching carefully for. If not, they're
going to do it. They're going to do the
same trap and come back up for this
again.
So, these 50s big big level. They're
still adding liquidity higher though.
They're still adding liquidity at like
90s and 300. So, it looks like they're
trying to lift and ES is holding on
really really well. Doing all the work
so far. So, back to these 50s again.
They have to make their mind up here
soon.
Are they going to go for one more shove
up? Do they really have it in them
today?
It is impressive. VIX right that
previous day low. That's going to be key
for VIX.
That's going to be Ke
back above the IB, back above the 50s.
They're trying to rebid this now.
They're trying to force another squeeze
up. It's a very sensitive area here.
They're adding liquidity higher at 90s
right now, trying to drag it up.
Yes, I'm trying to go for a new high
here on ES. I think it's going to break
out again. You know, it's it's
impressive. Shorts might keep getting
caught here.
Where's my They're making it really hard
to draw today. Trading View. It's
starting to annoy me.
Sensitive area here then versus the IB.
Do we get the IB to VWAP trade today?
Do we see failure to follow through? Are
they going to hold the 50s? all these
questions
waiting for them to develop it. It's
possible, but we don't want to be front
running because they keep adding
liquidity higher.
There is no such thing as 1050 macro.
Sorry to say that to you. It's all
bollocks.
It's all bollocks. All it is is
liquidity being traded around an hourly
open and close. It's nothing to do with
some macro
bollocks. Sorry, doesn't exist.
It's big institutional traders watching
highs and lows and open and closes of
multiple time frame candles.
Sorry to sorry to be the voice of reason
with you. Right. Still watching these
50s.
He has failed to break out here. Still
watching these 50s. They're still
absorbing in front of 50s. They're still
looking to shove this up 300 at the
moment. It is impressive the squeeze
here. At some point they will probably
end this squeeze and we'll see. I think
we'll see a rotation date. I do not
think we're going to go into a big trend
date, but I am happy to be wrong. If
they're going to do that, it will be
doing it without me. That's for sure. If
they do it,
what's the hive day auction look like?
It's all right. It's not a lot of
excess. It's all right.
Definitely slowed down here the last 3 4
minutes.
This IB is key. You can see it. The
IBM50 is key right now.
They are adding liquidity higher and
higher and higher though. They are
trying to attract this market. They keep
adding new levels. Someone's come on the
book here. 70 80 90 300 310. They're
trying to attract the market up right
now.
They're trying to get up into this gray
block. It's what they're adding on the
book.
I'm waiting to see if we offer a
rotation trade. They're my least
favorite trades, but I'm waiting to see
if we offer a rotation trade back down.
I will not frontr run this. I will not
frontr run this.
VIX needs to reclaim previous day low.
I can hear my coffees brewed. Can do I
have time to go and get it or am I going
to go and get it and miss the whole
bloody thing? What do you reckon folks?
Shall I go and then you guys will all
get the short without me.
I think I can go and get it. If they're
going to shove it up here, I've got time
to get my coffee. Right. Be right back.
All
right, we're back. We're back. We're
back. We're back.
Oh, [\h__\h] off. You new people in chat
talking bollocks.
You absolute cretins in chat. Get out of
here.
Absolute nonsense.
I would like to see this so I can Yeah,
it's nothing to do with confidence. I'm
telling you what's happening before it
happens. So, it's got nothing to do with
confidence. What you want, my friend, is
someone to trade your book for you. And
that is going to you're going to
struggle with that if you're going to
hop around YouTube place to place to
place. I'm teaching you how to fish.
I've told you every key level today and
what I'd be looking for. Get out of here
with that nonsense.
Get out of it. Learn to trade, my
friend. It might hurt your ego right
now, but the best thing you can do is
learn to trade rather than sit here
being like, I want someone to tell me
exactly what they're doing when they're
going to do it. Go and watch the other
YouTubers. Go, In fact, go and watch
Topstep and trade exactly how they trade
when they tell you they're entering. I
see how well that goes for you.
Get out of there. Get out of there.
That's bollocks and you know it.
Come on market.
Right. Let's give away a free course
here. Give me a second to get set up.
Oh yeah, you can use top steps just
whether you want to follow them. All
right, type course once in chat. We'll
give away a free course for you guys.
Just the introduction course.
Still absorbing here. Still no follow
through underneath that uh 250 and IB
and value now moved up. Right. So this
is a massive level like this kind of
level here.
We are not leaving right now. We're
still absorbing
this level here. Right now, it's not a
node. It's just where they keep trying
to absorb price maybe to complete the
rotation up into here until they're done
with it. Unless we get a backside move.
Definitely seeing aggre aggressive
sellers. Aggressive sellers keep
stepping in down here and they cannot
get follow through underneath these 50s.
That's what we can see right now at the
moment. They're not getting follow
through under the 50. So, I'm going to
remove that so it doesn't confuse you.
But, it's just a big level to be
watching.
You guys another minute to do that. VIC
starting to reclaim. Big buyer coming in
there at 65 now. Another 85 lot. Come
flying in 85. Yeah, 85 lot with a force
up. Here we go. So, they absorbed.
They're trying to complete this move to
300 and maybe even 350s. Like I said on
the book, they kept adding liquidity up
here, trying to attract the market to
come up and fetch it, which is what
we're now seeing.
There we go. There's the resqueeze up
intowards here. You can see it all on
the book. So, they added so much on the
book. Are they going to add any more
above? No, not really.
This might be the limit to where they go
to
into this gray box.
Just watching the previous week's value
here and what can happen if they lift.
All right, let's pull this winner.
Winner is Justin Loren. Are you here
Justin Loren?
give you a free course, introduction
course. It's only the two-hour long one,
but let me know you're here in chat.
Here's the gray box, folks. There's the
lift to 300.
Nice. So, Justin, just send me a uh
email info@flowzonerader.com.
I've made a note of your name. Just show
me you logged in. All right. The only
next thing they can go for is this red
line. All right. So, 300. The only next
thing that they can live for is that red
line. That will be the uh overnight
spike high from Sunday if they really
want to take GlobeEx out. But I'd watch
300 here very very carefully into and
around this box that whole number. But
if they want to do 50 points more, they
will. But we are getting a little bit
frothy up here. Little bit
overexuberant.
We never let go of that IB. So we need
to be aware of it. It's possible they
come for this. But this gray box got
tagged. 300 got tagged like we talked
about.
And we look for volume now to start
getting trapped anywhere from here all
the way up here. If if we're going to
play that downside move until we see
volume trapped, we cannot play the
downside move. Auction at the high is a
45 lot at the high right now. We got
stuck, but it's not very big. Not too
much of a swipe.
Back down we come. Watching this.
watching this. Now, if we leave these
nodes up here and start rejecting 88 and
90s, I'm interested in the short.
Testing this old wick now.
Do they offer a reload here? Do they get
stuck versus 88 and 90s? I'm watching
this now to see if if we reject after
trapping and tapping this box. We don't
reject. There's no trade. Here's the
move back into it. If they reclaim this,
there's no trade. No trade. We need to
wait for a rejection and a leave.
Alex, would you advise copy trading
multiple accounts at the same time or
trade them individually? Guess what I'm
asking is how to trade them? Uh, it
depends on your success rate. Um,
you know, and how how you're feeling.
Like I'm not feeling like 100% today. So
I'd do them one at a time. When I'm
feeling good, I trade them all together.
If you've got a proven strategy and
you're feeling good, do them all
together. Obviously, like it's the
riskier thing to do. But you don't need
to size up. We are starting to see some
rejection up there at the moment. Buyers
just got caught into 290. They are still
adding liquidity higher though into 210.
But buyers just got caught. It's perking
my interest here for a short back down.
89. Yeah, 90s is the level.
I might have just missed that, folks. It
might do it now. I might have missed my
entry there.
Might have missed my entry there for the
trade back down into 66s.
Might have just missed that.
request sent on Saturday to come into
the Discord. Um, where did you send it
to the right email? Maybe it went to my
spam. Sometimes it happens. Let me check
now.
Can you tell me what your email is?
Whoever just sent that.
You'll have to email me from the same
place you bought the course. the same
email.
FTR
can't see anything.
Can't see anything. So, just let me
know. I' I've just checked my spam as
well. I can't see anything.
Spam sent when? Saturday.
Nothing there.
You want to hear Trump? Is that that is
that why this stream's growing? Because
you're all here for Trump.
Bad Bunny,
remove the first name. That's what that
performance was. Bad. bad.
He literally tweeted that. That's not me
just saying it. He actually tweeted that
out.
All right. Still lifting it. Wow. Still
lifting it.
Still lifting it. Still no rejection. I
thought about taking this candle here
once we close back under, but still
lifting it. Are they going to come for
this? Are they coming for that 350s?
I tell you what, if we get through 350s,
you've got to be thinking 4 440s or
400s. You have to rejection into that
box again. So, the short now will come.
If we trap up here
and we do this, there will be a short
here. It's counter trend. I'm going to
tell you that it's counter trend, but
I'm think we're going to have a
rotational day
back to these 90s. This where the buyer
has just stepped in again here up here.
So, we can see this buyer have bought
the high up here. All right. So, 90s is
a big level. They did just get a little
caught here. You can see sellers trying
to sell through 90s, but all the time
we're absorbing here, it's still okay.
If you don't have that, you can just use
this, can't you? You can just use the
volume spikes, right? Use the tools
you've got for you. They continue to
lift this
Asia high all day long. Yeah. So, you
think we're coming for this? You think
350? It looks like it, doesn't it? It
very much looks like it. Let me just
zoom out on ES. ES already done it. ES
has done it. Been and done it.
It's on a move, isn't it? It wants it.
It wants it.
You guys might well be right. Let me
just see what this 20 day is.
Sixes.
Whoosh.
How are we doing on the swings? Do I
need to start locking in some profits?
20% up now on hood. Let's [\h__\h] go.
Let's go.
What a trade. We bought this down here.
Beautiful. We bought the 70s. We're
already trading towards the 90s.
Beautiful. This is where I'm trying to
get up into. We're almost there. Uh so
anyone in Discord that caught me caught
that with me, we're looking very, very
good.
Oh well, it's going for it. It's
definitely going for it. Uh you can't
rule out previous week high at this
point. Cannot rule it out.
I think it's like I've got nothing
against Bad Bunny. I think it's good
that they, you know, have uh
multicultural stuff at Halime and stuff
like
it's one of the biggest sporting events
watched in the world. I just think I
can't believe that he came out and
tweeted what I said. Like it's for me
it's madness.
madness to say that, but there we go.
Your Oracle elite's up 45%. Yeah,
exactly, man. We're we're looking good.
Oracle up almost 10% today.
So, we called all of these in the swing
channel in in Discord
last week.
All right. So,
which one was this? What were we looking
for? Hood. That was when I said starting
on hood already up 20% off that. Oracle
was above.
Palanteer. Did I miss Did I miss
Palanteer?
I might have missed it. I didn't see me
get filled. I must have missed it. Oh, I
missed it. You motherucker.
Oh, I had wish orders down here. Never
mind. Trade.
Okay, going to remove this now. We
traded through that block.
You know where it wants. It's just
whether it can get there. It's
definitely what it wants right now.
Give you a read out on the market how
green this market's now gone. Uh Tesla
1.73% up. Nvidia 3 and a half% up.
Microsoft 2.62% up. Meta 0.71% up.
Google half a percent up. Uh Amazon just
over half% down and Apple 1.74% down.
Okay, we have imbalances here back down
to the 300s. Remember the trade that
we're looking for will be if we start to
fail and leave volume. We have trapped
few buyers up at 25. We have imbalances
now down towards 300s. I will be selling
this if we start to trap and leave
volume, not beforehand.
So, we're looking for like spikes where
we see guys get stuck and I'll be
looking for us to leave volume.
Can't join Discord for free. No, it's
free if you do the 20our course. It
comes as part of the 20our course.
Still, they're lifting. So, still
nothing trapped yet. Still there
lifting.
Do we lock some of this in?
Come on. I actually just want this to
like keep shoving up at this point.
No, no, no Discord with the volume
course. Sorry guys. only because it's
not fair on the other guys that did the
other course and uh you might trade
volume a different way and there's lots
of reasons for it.
Alex, do you have anything you look for
to confirm price isn't going to come
back for the trapped buyers or sellers?
Well, it's more about leaving it. It's
always about the reaction, right? So,
now we have this here. So, if we start
leaving this,
we can look for this, right? This level
now is key. If we start if we keep
failing this level into 20s, this will
now be key. There's an imbalance there
and we have buyers caught above it. So,
I'm interested in this now. But the
thing is, we we need it to push up and
reject it for this trade back down
towards the 300s. If it can't push up
and reject it, then there's no trade.
And if it pushes up and doesn't reject
it, then we're going to trade up to 350.
I'm obviously not going to be long up
here, right? We're so far into premium
now. We're coming into right, we're
right into the top side of premium from
the previous week, right? Which will be
into sort of 420s.
So, still no rejection yet.
They keep bidding now at 300. So, I
think there is a move here. It's a small
move back down towards towards these
300s, 280s, 300s. I think this can
happen. Otherwise, you're going to see
this. But, this can happen. And if they
let go of this, this can happen. It all
depends when they're going to be done
with it. This is obviously the
lowhanging fruit right now that they're
looking for.
They just pulled the bid at 310. What is
There's someone joking around here on
the book a little bit. They're stacking
300 right now. Yes, still going. We're
in a giant squeeze here. Vick's back on
previous day low.
Starting to reject here.
Not sure they're done with it. Honestly,
it's not a big reaction here. It's just
a slowdown.
Watching this buyer at three 310 to 300.
See if he steps back in early.
So leaving those 320s now. Are we going
to SL swipe down? So this buyer that was
at 320s just or 300s has just stepped in
at 307. Watching for this short now all
the way back down into the 300s. If we
if we don't do that move straight away
in one go. Come on then. What we going
to do? We going to revisit 320 for me or
not? We just going to trap again and go
higher.
They're now offering 330. Lots of games
being played here, folks. From the 10 to
30s. Lots and lots of games being played
here on the tape.
Our buyers now stepped in at 315. So,
he's moved from 07, got filled, moved up
to 315 to try and support the bid there.
still think they want higher. ES is
still expanding. They're still looking
for higher here. So, back to the 20s
now. And if they get through this,
they're going to look for those 50s.
A lot of games being played in this area
here, folks. A a huge amount of games
being played here.
still absorbing at the moment. Watching
315 player at 315
315 330s
ES failing in front of 990 there
spy trading spy probably wants the 9 uh
695 again that gamma level I'm going to
assume
spy probably wants that gamma level
and see This shelf being built out now.
Importance of this shelf. The over under
still holding it for now.
Watching this. I'm eyeing up the short
here. I'm eyeing up the short here,
folks. Here's the move to 300. All
right. Gray to gray happening again. I'm
eyeing up the short here. If we start
leaving volume trapped, I will
participate in the short back down.
Watching 300 here cuz they keep trying
to absorb. Sellers coming in aggressive
aggressively down here. They're still
trying to absorb it. We have an
imbalance into 301 to to 97s. Okay, so
watching this gray box. Do we react here
and trade back up or are we going to
start slicing and we can start looking
for shorts?
So, still protecting the 300s back
towards the 20s.
Still the games continue gray to gray,
gray to gray. Still protecting low
volume node right now.
What platform for level two? Uh, I'm
using both bookmap and ninja trader.
Yeah, the guy at 350. Yeah, he's been
there for a while. He's been there for a
while. We can see it here. Right. So,
this is the rotation. So, these are the
imbalances that are holding. You should
see the highs. We keep getting buyers
caught. At the lows, we keep getting
sellers caught, but we're holding the
imbalances. So, we're rotating between
the imbalances. This low volume node,
right? We're rotating between greater,
great, greater, great, greater, great.
Coming back down for those imbalances.
This is where the last lot of sellers
got caught here at 10. So, I'm just want
to see if there's a bit more aggression
on the tape and if these buyers show
exhaustion, but we're not leaving
aggressively. We almost need to be
honest, we almost need a swipe now and
then that
first pullback on ES VIX coming into a
key pivot 1740. So, it's reclaimed
previous day low.
Still eyeing the same trade. I like it
less and less. The longer we're here,
the less I like it. We're starting to
see some rejection here, though. They
are starting to struggle to reclaim and
squeeze. Still no confirmation.
So, they're adding liquidity now. 25
seller now adding liquidity at 25. He's
trying to drag the market up a bit. Now,
he's lifted and moved to 27 and 30s.
Now, he's come down to 20. So, they they
continue to play games in this area.
Someone's going to get hurt soon.
Back to those 20s again. Do they lift
and go 30 now? I almost want them to
clear it out to make it easier.
Big failing that 1740 drive. had a good
go at it. Let me see if it can get back
in above again. Still not through this
gray box. It's getting very, very, very
tight here. But we're building out a
bigger and bigger node because we keep
dropping down and saving it, which
doesn't leave much room. This is where
it becomes like less and less
attractive, right? We keep making this
thicker. Then we're going to have to
play this and we don't get much room for
that that trade there. It becomes like a
onetoone trade unless we get a runner to
go and then it's like a 3:1.
>> So, it's not that attractive at the
moment.
And if they reclaim this, then they have
got this red line to go for, which looks
like they're still trying to do that
GlobeEx high up here, which was the
original trade thesis from down here,
right? The original thesis. If they get
through that, well, that would be quite
the shove up previous week value area
high today. I didn't think we'd do that
in one day.
Buyers definitely just caught caught
there again into above 20s, above 22s.
They got really caught there. 23 to 26s.
They got really caught there on that
last shove. We're still absorbing
though. So, you can see the top of the
gray box. This is starting to per my
interest again.
volume profile on the right is anchored
volume profile. Nightbot has just told
you in chat underneath what you've said.
All right, back to where those buyers
were trapped again. 23 to 26es. Let's
see what they do here. Do we just trade
back through it?
I think we just want to swipe out higher
at this point. It's going to make the
short easier for us if we're going to
take a short today because the flow the
flow zone is a supporting bid. We're
above the initial balance. We're in a
trend up day. It's just I don't want to
buy the high. So, I'm looking for a mean
reversion trade back down if and when it
comes and then we can think about a
rebid. Did we just clear out there? We
just cleared out there again. That's a
high of day taken.
It's still adding liquidity. 40 4550. I
think we just got to let this do what it
needs to do to the upside here, folks.
Let it do what it's got to do. What's my
bias for now? My bias is a rotation. So
my bias right now is this on an hourly.
All right, we were
long from here and here and we were long
this morning from here. All right, so if
we think about this,
I think we're coming into an area where
I think sellers will be hanging out
looking to defend and I think there's
probably a counter trend short back down
into here. Right, so that's my bias. My
bias has been this morning long, but now
we're up into these levels. I think from
here there's likely to be a short back
down. If we get acceptance back through
previous week value area high, then I
will be long bias again for the move
back up to this old level here of 800.
Right? So, if we do that, I'll be long
bias again later in this week. Right
now, I think that this will be sold back
into down here somewhere at some point
based on the hourlys.
Yeah, that's exactly what I said in the
newsletter. Ricardo, same thing.
Your anchor volume profile doesn't look
look right. Uh,
make sure
road is two, width 20, placement on the
right, and it's set to tick. And if you
do that, and you're watching the NQ, it
should look like this.
Still not hit those 350s. We're not far
away. Just still not done it. But we
have now swiped the highs. I just want
this if we're going to protect this gray
box. We want this just to keep going
higher. Now, even for the short thesis,
the higher the better. The bigger the
squeeze, the better. The more bulls that
chasing at the highs, the better.
We do not want to get short front side
though until we leave people trapped. We
do not want to get short front side. So,
back into this gray box. Do they rebid
this now or do we sell through this gray
box back down to the 10ens?
I don't know.
It's the 20s again. Looks a bit like a
fail break out there, but we're still in
this gray box. We still haven't taken
out the high
down to the 10 then.
They're going to make this hard. You can
tell they're going to do it. They're
going to do it out of nowhere and then
just dunk the thing.
All right. Same setups. Looking at the
same setup. Rejection of these levels.
Do we reject these levels for that trade
back down? And I will be covering some
into the sort of 90s and 300s. If we see
that rejection, if we reclaim this block
again, then I'm going to expect 50s for
a clear out.
Reclaiming the block.
So, we expect 50s for a clear out. We
should push up to try and clear out 50s
now.
We just want them to complete this at
this point. Make it easier.
Yeah, M and Q can definitely look funny
sometimes if you're looking at the
profile. That's where I ch why I chart
ENQ.
The best way to trade MNQ and chart ENQ,
honestly, is to use the affordable
indicators. Um, I can't remember what
the the thing's called. Someone else
helped me out. But you can literally
flip from mini to micro, but chart on
the same uh screen. Makes it much easier
rather than having to have two different
screens up. All right. Can they lift
this now to 50s and complete this bloody
move? They are taking their time, aren't
they?
Essential chart trader. There you go.
That's it.
So, this is your if you were still long,
right, guys? If you took this uh or what
was the last trap we tal talked about?
Was it this one here? Right, you're
going to hit your final TP here. If you
got very lucky, they'd come all the way
back up to value. That that is a massive
move if they do that. But this is a
GlobeEx level.
We get thick up here. Very thick up here
from the previous week.
You I would not want to be a new money
long anywhere up here today. It's so far
in premium. Remember, this is the most
premium price of the previous week. It's
why we want to try and bid in discount.
Discount is underneath previous day
point of control. We bid actually on the
reclaim of that. or that move up.
This is absolute premium for previous
week.
Look, we're losing location or uh longs.
What is the GlobeEx level? Uh right
here. 51 is it?
No, it's not. It's here. Sorry. Moved it
down a bit. 46es.
Yes, has already taken it out. So, you
know,
trapping buyers up there again and back
down to this gray node again, which has
now been built out higher again. Look at
this. This time now it's been built out
higher. This is starting to look very
ugly. Every dip is being absorbed right
now.
Here
we go. Finally, they might do it here.
Yeah. Every day, Monday to Friday, here
for free.
So, spike high there. Definitely caught
some buyers up here. I still think we
got to take out this last bit of
liquidity into like 46s or wherever it
is would be ideal. One more shove up.
They're still up there on the book.
They're actually up into 360. Is there
anyone above 360? Not really. Next level
400. So, we're getting frothy up here
into this level. We're going to still
look for the same thing. I'm We I am
going to look for a little like swipe of
liquidity, someone to get trapped up
here. Maybe I get a starter and if we
lose that, get that move there. It's
what I'm going to look for. I'm not
going to keep bidding up here for up and
up and up and up. It's possible they
come all the way up here. So, you know,
we just have to wait for sufficient
liquidity to get trapped. Seller just
came in there market side. What are you
doing, mate? Don't do that.
Unless that's someone taking some
profits and just hitting the market.
Maybe he's scared they can't lift it all
the way.
Which anchored volume profile in Trading
View? There is only one anchored volume
profile in Trading View, guys. Look,
it's right here.
Right here. Volume based anchor volume
profile. That's it.
All right. Back to this gray box. I'm
still eyeing this for the short, guys. I
am still eyeing this for the short. Now,
if we start letting go of this, I will
start to add into this and look for a
scale lower.
Yeah, I like the look of this now.
Watching 15s here.
We now have an imbalanced sell side up
to 29s. Looking to scale some into this.
Especially if we leave, I'll get
heavier. Got a piece on here. If we
leave gray box, I will get heavier.
And we still have the imbalance down to
300. So, if we leave this gray box, I
will scale heavier. Got a little starter
on once we started to sell through 30s.
Watching these 15. See if we push up now
and fail the imbalance of 25s again.
Same kind of level, right?
Watching these 25s. 25s to 30s. They got
to sell 25s to 30s or I'll cut the
trade. It's only a small piece on
25s.
Buyers came in there, got stuck again.
Going to move my stop to 30. So I put it
at 31 just in case. Maybe I'll move it
to 31.
stop at 31.
And if we leave this gray box, I'm going
to attack it or a move down into here.
Watching the tens because they keep
bidding around the tens.
It's possible I'm early here. It is
possible. But I like what I've just seen
in this current candle. If we can close
lower, it would be really good.
Not like that. It's not what I want to
see. Close lower. This candle's got to
drop now.
Get down.
Otherwise, you're going to swipe through
the 30s. Here we go. You got to get down
under this bid. I want to see come down
into tens and 05s. And I want to see
them pull the bid and just wash. Here we
go. Come on.
You [\h__\h] Get out of my way. There we
go. Come on. can accelerate now.
Can we accelerate or we just going to
keep holding this level? You
[\h__\h]
Still have an imbalance above that they
can fill, right? Still have an imbalance
above.
They can still come and fill this
imbalance. So, these buyers got trapped
here. We can still fill this imbalance.
My stop is just above this. If we wash
this, I'm looking for a cover down here.
I don't like that the sellers just came
in there and couldn't get the break
under the shelf, but I'm still in this
for now. If we take out 31s, then I'll
stop out
into the imbalances now that we just
talked about
in this gray box. I got to be very very
careful here. Very very careful here.
Especially if ES wants to do a
fiveminute flag.
Did you tag me? Thanks.
Out is what it is. Like I said, might be
early here.
So, I had a starter on here. Was waiting
to see if we do that to get heavy.
Knocked out starter.
No change.
And they might still want to come for
this low hanging fruit.
That's why I'm starter only.
And now flat.
What do you think about timing? I see
every day contra trend in the time 11 to
12 people eating. Maybe uh no, you don't
see that every day. That's just
something you've decided in your head
happens every day. If you actually
studied that every day and looked at a
statbased thing, you definitely would
not see every day that the trend goes
the other way at that time.
Just something that might have happened
a few times that you've noticed it, but
it's definitely not a thing every day. I
promise you.
Why is low hanging fruit? Is it
liquidity? Yeah, it's liquidity. It's
the Asia High.
Yeah, like I said, my stop was at 31.
I'm out. I I lit quite literally told
you where my stop was.
They might redo it. I'll have another go
if they redo it.
But ideally they just swipe this out.
So I saw buyers get trapped here.
We came under. I was attacking this. I
was willing to add if we rejected this
and get heavy. We didn't reject it. It
can still do this. But this is becoming
very very important now.
Do I not worry about shorting into the
flow zones? Yeah, but like I said, I'm
looking for the counter trend trade.
Like like I always talk about, it's the
hardest trade in the book, right? It's
the hardest trade in the book. The
easier trade in the book. Even this is
counter trade. Counter trend. It's the
hardest trade in the book. Absolutely is
the hardest trade in the book. We talk
about it all the time. That's why I'm
small size on it. And I would get heavy,
right? If we came under here,
like I talked about, if we reject the
gray box, because then we'd be under the
flow zones. Flow zones would flip and
we'd probably see a trade back down into
these,
right? So, that's why it's the hardest
trade in the book.
Okay, can they clear out this liquidity
now? Uh, VIX back down towards low of
day. Need to be careful here.
There is an old imbalance above this
GlobeEx high as well.
I think it's close, folks. They just got
to go and take it. It's close to letting
go here and having like a deeper
pullback for a little reset because this
has been a big old drive. It's very
close. We're watching this gray box
still. If we think about this move,
right, think about this move.
Right. It needs a little reset. Even if
they're going to scoop that to go later,
it's just do they do that? Do they do
that?
Or do they do this? That's the question.
I tell you what, I'm not buying up here.
Take care, Miguel.
Okay. Can they take it out? Can they
finally take it out?
There we go. Finally, they've swiped it.
All right, finally they've taken that
liquidity. So the question now is are
they going to fail here? So if you if
you were long, congratulations. Did
anyone actually hold that long from down
here that we talked about or maybe even
the one from this morning? Did anyone go
from blue box
all the way up here? The question now is
are they able to get up into the 400s or
we going to see this peak out and die?
I do have an old imbalance here into 30
33s. Is it 333s? 353. Sorry, Alex can't
read.
Okay, there we go. That's the imbalance.
353s.
They are still adding liquidity high. I
will be amazed if they come up for
previous week value area high today.
That will be quite the shove.
It's very possible, but it would be
quite the shove, which will be the 161,
right? Didn't we measure it earlier?
No, that would be even higher.
Okay, just tapped this imbalance. It's
an old imbalance here.
We get through this. Oof.
Oof.
Yes. Looks like it wants to go. Yes.
Wants more. I would say spy. Uh
95 would be the level, right? 95. That
same level. 695.
They support a bid here. They haven't
cleared out everyone. They cleared out a
decent chunk. Still guys resting on the
offer above. Still a big seller at 400.
Here they go. They're trying to clear
out everyone now.
Still guys at 60s. Still they bid. And
still they bid. Still no short setup.
Even argue this up here. But really this
and I just wonder are they going to come
for this up here? Are they coming for
440s today? That is one hell of a move
if they do.
How do I determine
95 as a key price for ES? Uh, not for ES
for spy.
It will be a gamma level. There'll be a
gamma level there at 695. I I haven't
even looked, but I can almost guarantee
it. Getting
wonky up here. It's getting wonky up
here. We still haven't cleared out the
guy at 60. It's getting wonky up here.
100 lot just caught trying to buy the
high there folks. It's the first time
we've seen that for a little bit.
Uh I see the one of you who just uh
asked about Discord. Hang on. I just see
you. Where are you?
Luca,
sending it to you now, Luca. It's going
to be a short uh short email just so I
can get you in.
Okay, new shelf being built up here.
This was where a big buyer just came in.
huge buyer. We're going to use that as
an overunder.
100 lot came in at 58.
They are still adding liquidity higher,
trying to drag this thing higher. We are
frothy here, folks. We are frothy. It
might just be a grind all day. Very
possible from how we're now setting up.
I'm somewhat surprised. I thought we'd
rotate more, but we will see. We will
see. But if we leave this shelf, there's
probably a trade back down to here
again. It's like a 25 point trade, but
it's counter trend. Hardest trade in the
book. I'm just want them to flush it
back down and I I'm quite happy to rebid
higher. This level here is a huge
overunder for the day. Technically, the
bigger short won't come until we get
under this, right? We get under that,
there's there's a bigger short in this
market.
Let me mark that out on my other screen.
19.
Yeah.
What indicators do I use? Again, guys,
please read the chat. Read everything
first. Flowzone Pro, it's my system.
Anchored volume profile. That's what I
use.
and then footprint
and put that
new lower day VIX. Still new low day.
Still we can watch this level here. If
we leave this level, all right, and we
stay heavy versus it, maybe that short
comes in. Watching that same level now.
We're trading back into it again.
Sellers just got trapped again trying to
sell through that level. They cannot get
continuation under here. Watching this
now into this same level. So if we leave
gray box, I'm going to look for a trade
back down to 23s. I'm telling you that
now. If we leave gray box, I will look
from 50s to 23s and I will try and hold
a runner in case we collapse the 20s for
a deeper move. Here we go. So, leaving
gray box, looking for a move down to the
23s. I cannot make this like more
obvious for you guys than I already am.
We need to get back under that old high
the uh what was it? 46es.
Still absorbing here.
Watching for reaction here at 53 now.
Lots of selling in this candle.
And it's still absorbing at these lows.
Are we going to wash now?
Imbalance here is 53 to 55. I have to
resell that or I'm not taking it.
Nice resell there so far. Come on. You
got to get a close down now. If you're
going to step on it, just step on it.
Here's 50s. Let's just flush 20s then.
The faf. The faf. Are they going to
retrap and go again? Seriously, guys.
This is getting ridiculous.
Come on.
Like I said, I will he add heavy under
this gray box. If this is a peak and we
get under here, I will add heavy under
here for a rotation. Until then, I'm
very, very light.
Structurally, we're still bullish
technically, but we did just trap buyers
at those highs.
Yes, still holding. VIX needs to get
back above previous day low,
back into this imbalance. If there's no
rejection here, I have to cut
cuz I'm early. Hardest trade on the book
in the book like I always talk about.
It's very slow. I don't like how slow it
is. Come on.
Still absorbing every dip. Still being
absorbed right now. Sellers are get keep
coming in here under 50 and getting
caught. I do not like that. I've cut.
I've cut. I don't like what I'm seeing
there. I have to cut that. There is
someone absorbing this book nonstop.
So, I have to be disciplined out of
that. That is a losing trade there on
that swipe.
You're going to [\h__\h] do it the moment
I cut.
Oh my god. You [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
You
Looking for this again. [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] I can't believe they just did
that to me. I think that's the second
time today. All right. Can we move back
down towards the 20s?
ass.
Can we move back down to the 20s or we
going to reject this? I don't like this.
They keep building out these double
nodes. It's really ugly what they're
doing here today. It's really ugly. I'm
looking for this trade back down to here
and under here. I will try and get
heavy. So, if we now reject this, I'm
looking for a cover here. And I will add
heavy for that if we're going to do
that. Uh maybe all the way back to IB
would be very lucky.
This seller up here is being such a
dick. Honestly, lifting like that. Oh my
god. He's still being a dick.
I don't trust him. I do not trust this
guy.
Come on.
Come back to 20s.
Bid here at 40. We got to snap 40 to get
to 30 and then we should get 20s. Come
on. [\h__\h] hell, man. You guys kept
playing games up here exhausting me.
This might be my last go at it today,
which probably means it stops me out and
then has does it on the next go. It's
normally the way. How far are we into
lunch? It's probably what's exactly
what's going to happen. It's normally
what happens to Alex. He has one last
go, stops out, walks away at lunch, and
then sees it happen.
Still a bid 40s, still a hold. Gray box
above still key as your sentiment. And
if we wash this down here. Come on.
Please at least get me a TP1.
Still absorbing this man. It's crazy.
This fire down here is absorbing
everything.
Everything at 40 is gobbling still.
We need a really strong close under 40
cuz he keeps gobbling everything up.
Gobble gobble gobble. He's still
gobbling.
Back to gray box. They need a rejection
here and a close under 40. They've got
to get this buyer who's bidding 40 out
the way. Otherwise, we will make a new
high.
VIX needs to get back above previous day
low as well.
You watch, I'm going to stop out and
then it's going to do it. It's exactly
what's going to happen.
Well, it doesn't need to do anything,
guys. that like it doesn't need to do
anything. Like I'd like it to flush, but
it doesn't need to do anything. It can
keep trading higher. Like this guy's
just rebid 40s non-stop and gobbled it
up and we're back in the gray box now,
right? So he's just rebid it all and
we're back in that gray box now. And if
he wants to take this up to 400, he will
do so. If his his game plan is to go
440s and he's not willing to let to let
the price come down until he's got his
target 440s, he's going to keep buying
and buying and buying and buying and
buying and buying until he gets his exit
cuz I can see him on the book. I can
literally see him on the book rebidding,
grabbing it, rebidding his same lot size
over and over and over again. I think
we're going to break out again here now.
So he's just come back on the book at 40
again. He's off. He's bidding 40s again.
Is this going to be the failed follow
through of the top of the gray box?
He's moved up to 4750 now. They're
bidding this up. They are bidding up.
Bid bid bid bid bid bid bid non-stop bid
all [\h__\h] day. It's impressive. It's
really impressive. if it's gone beyond
where I thought it was going to go. They
want this. They [\h__\h] want this. He is
adamant on getting this up here right
now. Clearly
clearly wants this up here right now.
He's just forcing his way through it.
It's all buy side above us. Like
everyone's stuck above, but he's he will
not let these sellers out.
No, I don't. The Ballinger bands are
below us right now. Uh 24857
lower Ballinger band.
Rebidding again. They're squeezing and
squeezing and squeezing and squeezing. I
think they want to come all the way up
here.
That's what I think they want to do.
Would I go long? No, I I refuse to go
long. I was long all morning from down
here. I am not going to buy uh deep in
premium. No, look at look how look how
ridiculous this is.
You want to buy up here? Seriously, no
chance. There's no way it I don't care.
I don't care if I think it's going to go
higher. Uh my rule dictates I will not
be buying deep in premium.
Is SPY at 95 yet? Still not at 95 now.
Maybe that's what we're waiting for.
We're waiting for SPY to 95. It's hit
94.85 today. They probably want SPY 95.
It's going to drop down. It might well
drop down. It's what we're looking for,
but it's We've had I must have had two
at least two goes at it now.
same levels. Same levels where they just
rebid a minute ago. 60 is where they
just bid a minute ago.
Top of this gray box. And if they fail
that bottom of gray box and then maybe
I'll think about one more go at it.
Although it's I'm starting to get a bit
exhausted now looking at the same play.
Maybe
the buyer who was at 40s is at 45 now.
Same level top of this gray box there.
We're still rebidding.
Relentless. Honestly, it's relentless.
At what point do they go enough?
Are they really going to shove it for
one, two, three hours straight up to
previous week value area high? I mean at
the moment it looks like the answer is
yes. We have to say at the moment very
much looks like that answer is yes,
doesn't it?
37950.
You're almost there. Is that your guess?
Is that what you're saying? That's your
guess of peakout.
615 is GEX for QQQ as well. Yeah. And
it's very close. That's what I'm saying.
Okay. Spy just hit 95 on the dot. Right.
So if you believe that these are the
areas that the GEX levels then these are
the areas we're coming into.
There's the swipe
new lower Davix.
What was your guess? Where was it? It
was close.
I wonder if they want up here. This is
what I wonder.
Jesus Christ. Non-stop. There's your
7950. Well, we're through that.
Look at these buyers just stepping in,
forcing it up. We're Amazon's just gone
green as well. We're literally forcing
this up at this point. This is uh
frothy. Really frothy.
Honestly, I really wonder if this is
what they're going to do. If they're
just like, "We got to get through the
whole week in one go." It would be an
insane recovery, guys, to do that. Like,
I cannot explain how big a recovery that
is in one go. Insane.
New shelf developed up here. out. It's
how much buying just came in in the last
20 seconds that we've just put a little
shelf in here.
Imbalance here down to 75 76es.
Still they're forcing. Didn't even feel
the imbalance. They are forcing higher
here.
They do not give a [\h__\h] I cannot
explain how aggressive this is on the
tape to be bidding like this.
They clearly in my mind this is a market
maker or a a a institution who's been
stuck on the cell. So they are now
forcing up to get out of their position
without having too much damage. And once
they're out of that position, they will
sell it and tank it back down and rebid.
But I'm This is what I expected this
week. I didn't expect it in one day. I
didn't expect us to literally go
straight back up to previous week value
area high in one day. This is the area
as we get into here where shorts must or
sellers must defend this area. If we
start reclaiming this area, there is a
gigantic squeeze opportunity up to 675
and even 830. We will not do that today.
There's just no way. But this is the
area sellers must 100% defend. They have
no nothing else that they can do other
than defend that area. If they lose that
area,
then I think uh we are in big trouble
for all the sellers at the lows, the
swing shorts.
Okay, there's the peak out
back into this imbalance again. Are we
now backside yet? We have just tagged
all those key areas like we talked about
on uh
the options market
Q's and uh and SPY
still holding that imbalance. We're not
even letting go of the imbalance at
76es. This is so insane right now,
folks. I cannot explain this to you to
bid like this non-stop. It's not so much
that where we've gone. It's like how he
stepped up at 40 and gobbled and gobbled
and gobbled and then just ripped it. To
be buying the amount he was buying here
was crazy for me to watch that happen on
the tape.
And he's now bidding at 77 and 67 with a
target of 95 97 and 400. He's not done.
Uh no, not really Dave. That's not
really how it works cuz if you do that
all right and they pull their position
and you buy deep and premium you got to
understand
when you're saying if you can't beat
them join them. Um they were joining
they they they've probably been bidding
right since here right and even beyond
that they've been bidding all of this
bid bid bid bid bid. They're just trying
to force that last bit up now. You don't
want to be the guy buying the top of
their bid do you? Right. You need to
have some rules.
If we if we buy the top of their bid, we
will get dunked on when they're done
with it because they were going to have
a massive core position which is way
lower than this. It's just that they're
non-stop up here. They want the exit up
here so they can probably get out break
even versus the previous week. It's
going to be something stupid like that.
SPX got a while to go to get there. All
right, still watching these 7475s
or is it 76 75? 76s and 75s. And if we
flush this, we probably trade straight
down. Look, this is a big imbalance
here.
Yeah, just cuz you know the market's
going one like in a certain direction
doesn't mean that we can join. If you
join late,
you're just amplifying issues, right? If
you're joining late like that, you're
not you're not helping your situation,
right? So, just understanding that,
okay, we the expectation is the market
is going to do this at the moment
doesn't mean if we don't have prime
position, why do we want to then play
that market there?
That's also bollocks JT because you
absolutely can. And you can have a stop
here and that can disrespect you down
here cuz it's so thin and you can get
run on that stop.
That's just not accurate.
Not when it's the amount of size that
they've got.
Still we point higher. Still they're
looking for these 400s.
If we I would not be surprised we get 4
and440 into lunch and then they just
stop it. They just go, "Okay, enough.
Be done with it."
Exactly. Buying expensive to sell
expensive is not a great business
strategy. I I agree. It's a force up,
guys. This is an absolute force up. It's
being done on purpose. This is going to
get get them to unload their position
when they're ready, and it it's also
going to provide the opportunity for
them to get short where they want.
I expected this this week. I didn't
expect it all in one go. I did expect it
this week. I'm telling you what, if they
start getting over 520s today, it's
going to get real nasty.
There's the move to fours.
And you haven't got that much left to
get into here. 440s.
Look, where's that old imbalance? 21s.
421s.
Okay, move this up. This is their
support system now. They let go of that.
There's a wash back down.
I don't know if I'll have another go.
Might be done.
460 is expected high of day.
Such a monstrous move. Honestly,
it looks good for it. Where did I say
the 161 was? I keep forgetting.
this morning's first pullback
over the measured move of that pullback
already.
I think we'll see a peak out soon. I
think buyers will chase the tops and
we'll see a peek out soon. Do I have one
more go at this if it's ready?
What was the IB expansion? I've
forgotten that as well.
Oh,
we just hit it. We literally just tagged
it or just missed it by the tiniest
amount.
Yeah, we tagged it. We just tagged that
one and a half IB.
Okay, I'm still willing to play this
back. side if and when it's ready.
Yeah. I mean, I'm with you. Point point,
but you you never know.
You called 405. Did you actually Where
did we hit? We very close.
I think if we get through 400s, we're
going to come up here, but we'll see. I
don't I'd be really surprised if they've
got the juice to do that in one go.
Insanely impressive. Yeah, only Apple
red. That's right. Amazon just went
green about 5 10 minutes ago. Give you a
readout. Uh Tesla 2.14% up. Nvidia 3.35%
up. Microsoft 2.68% up. Meta 2.81% up.
Google 1.37% up. Amazon approaching half
a percent up. Uh, all those that took UU
with me were 7% up on that. 7.40 versus
the 20s. Um,
US AR 4 and a.5% up. Um, what else were
we looking? Oracle, we're over 10% up
now, 10.31% up on the day. Might be an
opportunity to start scaling out some of
these at least to lock in a little bit
on these swings.
Plenty of room left, but could protect
some profits here.
Up on those miners. Where am I at?
Good.
All right. I think they want this.
I can't believe they're going to do it
in one session. It's so impressive. I
Yeah, I think four
4 I just want to make sure this is
right.
This 440 I think 440 is the kind of
target.
I think it might be the target. Uh that
will be
insane to do that in in one day. It's a
really impressive move. Uh the the node
starts we're already coming into the
start of that node. I'll show you what
I'm looking at. Uh
right, we're coming into the start of
this node here. This is previous week
value area high. If we find acceptance
over this, right, and we start basing
this will all become trapped and we will
fill this thing in very very quickly,
right?
If we find acceptance over this, I don't
think today, tomorrow, Wednesday, this
move here can happen. This is why I said
at the very start of the day, I would
expect this level here, it to at least
reject down into this.
I think this is a force up
cuz it's too it's too much too quick
into too much of a giant giant giant
level.
So, I'd expect a pullback soon. I'm
surprised they haven't already done it,
but uh
they haven't. It's really impressive.
All right, let's do an Apex giveaway or
should we wait to see if the short comes
to us first? Maybe I could do the Apex
giveaway first. Hopefully, we don't miss
the short.
Okay, type FCT in chat.
Only need to type it once, please. Only
need to type it once, please. I'm really
impressed that this hasn't done a
rotation day. Wow, this is caught me off
guard. It's not what I thought we'd do
today. I thought maybe we'd do this
tomorrow. I thought we'd rotate today,
squeeze up tomorrow, sell Wednesday,
Thursday, and then go back inside
Friday. But hey ho, market had other
plans. I'm not I don't mind it. My
swings are absolutely printing right
now, so I don't mind it at all.
Best swing I have on right now is I'm
not going to include open is
well AMD's 31% up, Robin Hood 21% up,
Apple 27% up, Meta 10% up, uh BTC 6.45%
up. Those are the big winners for me
swing wise.
Okay, 405. There's a seller here at 405.
I still think we're trying to get 440s.
This is so impressive. It is so
impressive. Another shelf being built
out up here. This is just a trend day at
the moment without a pullback.
They leave this. I'm watching 380s.
I tell you what, I'll use the bathroom
and then come right back and then we'll
do the giveaway.
off and they're going to wash gray to
gray. Still holding that gray box. Okay,
we're building liquidity out here. Let's
do this giveaway and we'll see if we can
get one trade just before lunch if they
set it up. Okay, pulling this winner.
Colobby Yam. Colobby Yam, are you here?
Colobby Yam for a free Apex account.
Colobby Yan, let me know you're here, my
friend.
Where did that seller just come in? 152
lot came in at 88 there. Got caught.
Colby Yam,
give you another minute.
Is this too dangerous to short? Yeah,
right now we haven't left the levels.
We're trading between these blocks.
Yes. Nice. Okay, Colby, same thing as
always. Email me, please. Info@flowzone
trader.com. Send me a screenshot of you
logged in.
We leave this gray box where I get way
way way more interested. I'm watching
this now to see what they do. The Hive
Day auction is not too bad. Over 400.
It's not the best. And they're still
they are still offering though at 405
410. I'm going to guess they're now
offering all the way up into 450. What a
[\h__\h] surprise. Yeah, they they are
they are
it's so extended here. It's unreal. Uh
in this grind, if you want to look at
like a five minute or the ETFs,
you know, this is quite something
without a retest.
Quite something.
It's impressive.
It is impressive.
Where did I anchor the volume profile?
9:30 open. Come on, guys. Help me out.
9:30 open.
They're offering 500s. No.
Oh, that is disgusting.
Look at this thing. You're going to flip
gamma and run it. Holy [\h__\h] balls.
Was that just the dip on ENQ? If we
start we start reclaiming the death
zone.
I don't know. At least we got long
software. It's all I can say.
I wasn't willing to get long all of
tech, but at least we got long some
software.
Every debt run.
Oh, it' be good. Inferris risk. It would
be good.
Gray levels, right? You see this volume
here? You see these nodes? The gray
levels are obviously nodes, right? What
is support and resistance? What is
supply and demand? It is done by volume.
And that's why we mark these out. That's
why price likes to respect these levels
frequently. Nothing magic, folks.
Okay, we're into lunch now as well.
Might have to be done with this, guys.
Don't think we're going to get a trade
setup here at the moment. We're just
going to get a force up. I cannot bring
myself to buy this at this point. So,
uh,
what should we say? We give it another
couple minutes in case they do a dirty
move over lunch.
Cannot stop thinking that this is where
they're trying to get. It is one hell of
an effort to get up there. I tell you,
it's really, really, really impressive.
You look at like the last one, two,
three, four, five hours or four hours.
What was it? One, two, three, four. It's
non-stop. Big buyer just got caught
there. Or he's not caught, but he's just
coming in. 239 lot high of day. 239 lot
high of day. All right. Versus 405. 239
lot.
He was actually 357 lot. But he got
paired off a little bit. So that is the
auction at the high of day. Let's see.
Let's see. Do they let him out and force
this thing even higher now? Jeez Louise.
Some size up there. Why would you do
that?
So right up here in this high there's a
huge node learn show massive guy just
came flying in there massive massive guy
how we act now becomes important we get
back above him he's going to be
comfortable he'll probably add in and we
will keep pushing higher it's [\h__\h]
madness
but it's what's happening
he long the top yeah he did so far he's
long the top but we're still above the
gray boxes right so we know where he's
caught but he's only caught if we start
moving aggressively away from him. We're
not doing that right now.
This level here 86 is
is in balance at 77s as well. Still
absorbing this top gray box right now.
This buyer is still not too far out the
money is like a couple points. Not
nothing. It's absolutely nothing.
That looks terrible.
Yeah, I can only trade my system. I'm
not going to The longs today were in
discount, right? We had the longs
earlier, right? I have to I have to
trade my system. this. I'm not buying up
here, right? I I don't mind buying
discount looking for this trade up. I
didn't think we'd get this far up today.
Said we might, but I I genuinely didn't
think we would. Okay, watching these two
gray boxes now. Watching these. Do we
leave these buyers trap now and start to
get aggressive down? The answer at the
moment is yes, but sellers just came in
at 95 and got absorbed again. Again,
there's still someone absorbing the
tape. Even up here this high, there is
someone who just absorbed that tape
again. Look, the sellers just came in
and got absorbed again. We have to
respect this zone.
Cannot come early here. You will get
absolutely clapped.
All right. Watching very carefully now.
This is where the sellers keep getting
caught under 400s. Do we get more
aggressive here and do we trade and
leave 95s? I would have to respect 90
and 86es. Oh, it's gross. The better
short comes underneath all of this. This
is gross, man. The way they've set this
up is [\h__\h] awful for a short. They've
set so many support systems for it. I
don't like it.
They've made sure there's nodes
absolutely everywhere that can catch it
absolutely everywhere.
back to that higher day. They're going
to let him out and squeeze, aren't they?
Jesus
Christ almighty.
Insane. Insane that we're going to do
that whole previous week on a Monday.
still absorbing here.
Guy just stepped in 402s. He's now
bidding at 98 and 96s.
They're still trying to absorb this
tape.
All I can think of is they have to get
up here to get out. It's clearly what
they've decided at the moment. Unless we
start closing under 95s on SPY and under
15s. I mean, we're already almost at 16s
on the cues.
Flipped the gamma, guys. We've flipped
the gamma.
All right, back to these fours again.
Back to this gray box again. New node.
Flip the point of control. That's not
good for for buyers. If we start
flipping all of this now, that's really
bad for buyers. This becomes possible if
we start flipping all of this.
There's so much volume up here now. We
flip PC. That's not a good look for
buyers. If the sellers want to come in
here and actually do something, they've
got a shot.
Watching this,
I'm so iffy about taking this because
the RR if if they're just going to do
scalps is not going to be very good. But
if they let it go, it would be amazing.
Is this in balance? 77 39
360s.
Still only 40 points, man. I don't know
if I like it. There's not enough reward
in it.
Still absorbing.
I'm really think I'm like trying to This
is what's going on in my head. Do I want
to like attack
like one of these and cover a bit here
and then get that to there? Is it worth
it? And they might stop short in here.
Is it worth it? Is what I'm asking
myself. Is this worth it? Is 40 points
worth this move?
I don't know if it is.
I don't know if it's worth it. I don't
think it's worth it. Not when there's
still a low hanging fruit they're trying
to get to. Not look at the bid like
non-stop nonstop nonstop non-stop
nonstop nonstop nonstop non-stop. Trying
to trying to time it to get 40 out of it
when this morning we had easy 100
pointers.
We're very bullish on the day. I don't
think it's worth it, guys. I think
that's it's going to be a sensible
decision of me calling it. Do I think
there'll be a pullback? Yeah, I think
there probably will be a pullback. Am I
going to be here for it? I don't think
so. Um,
I don't think so. I think I just let
them do what they want on the Monday and
uh come back for this
uh next tomorrow. Tomorrow morning,
maybe the afternoon.
Tomorrow afternoon, we see what we get
tomorrow afternoon. Today in the
afternoon, we can see what we get in
Discord. Sorry, tomorrow morning. I'll
be back. And here we go. They're still
going for more. They are just adamant.
They cannot let this thing go. They have
to get up here. It's clearly they've
decided they have to get that level to
get out. It's just it must they must be
stuck up there and they need to go and
revisit it. That's all I can think of.
Um I don't mind because we're now up
11.26% on the day on Oracle alone on the
day. So, I'm not I'm not totally against
it.
Yeah, that's what I'm saying. I think I
think they're probably it's not even
about the d-risk. I think they're
probably like they're caught offside.
So, they're bidding back up to get out
of where they need to get out and then
they can at that point their d-risk will
be when they get out, right? So, they
can derisk up here. If we think about
this,
if we go to like a 15 minute or
something. All right. So once
once we left this huge value area which
is what like 8 weeks long right and
washed right if they are offside in here
they can force this aggressive move to
derisk here and then get this play back
down and then rebid it back up if they
want. The fact that we haven't washed at
all into this it is a forced move.
There's no doubt about it. It's a forced
move up and I would not be surprised if
we do this if the backside of this week
becomes very very aggressive to the
downside. Wouldn't surprise me in the
slightest. Not in the slightest. All
right, folks. Anyway, those in Discord,
I'll be back in in like an hour, hour
and a half. Um, everyone else, I'll see
you tomorrow morning. Trade safe. Um,
use hard stops. Don't be front siding
this. Remember, it's not left volume.
We've had like one or two goes at it.
It's never left volume. It's holding
every dip. Do not be front side of it.
You will end up crying your way to sleep
tonight if you do that. Peace and love
everyone and I'll see you guys in the
Morning.