What's happening, chat? Good morning,
everyone. Good morning. Good morning,
everyone. What a week. Been an
incredible week, right? Price actions
been very, very kind to everyone in the
Flowzone community. And as you all see
on the daily, well, last night we got
exactly what we wanted. And I did start
some relief longs last night. I will
tell you that. Uh both in swing accounts
and in uh in a couple props. But uh you
can see this is what we were looking
for, right? This is the exact moment we
were looking for. We talked about it in
the newsletter. We talked about it over
the last few days that if we left this
trapped volume from here, all right,
this trap volume here, once we left it
and we rejected it, we would expect that
move down to Mr. 200 day. Don't know why
I call him Mister, but in my mind it's
Mr. 200 day. All right. It's the first
time we've visited it in 9 months.
Straight out the newsletter. Anyone that
got the free newsletter, if you're not,
if you don't get the free newsletter, I
don't know what you're doing. The links
are down below in the chat. And this is
exactly what we're looking for. All
right, so we've come into that 200 day
and we're getting very near this node
here, 24,000.
All right, so that's the next stop. Uh,
do I think we go there today? Probably
not. All right, we probably need some
relief. Like we talk about the mark, it
doesn't move straight down. All right,
it moves in waves and overnight we've
had that relief. All right, and we're
coming back towards this node here,
24800s
and then through that we can look at
25,000 again. All right, so really what
I'm trying to say is objective complete
for the week. All right, failed breakout
last week, failed to get back into that
high this week. Big dumperama, we just
hit our target. There's very unlikely to
see more downside in the immediate
future. Doesn't mean we can't come and
do one of these today. We can, but I
would find it unlikely that we break
this low today. It's possible, but it's
unlikely. What's more likely to happen
now is that we're going to build out
liquidity today and next week, maybe
have a failed attempt to get back in,
maybe come back down, clean these out,
and maybe then we get a waterfall
moment. I don't know. Maybe they come up
for this, or maybe they just do one of
these. We'll find out over the next few
weeks. But right now, this is an
expected move that we're seeing on the
daily. So you guys should have been
prepared for that. You should have been
prepared. Okay. So when we now look at
the hourlys, we can think about the
volume that was trapped over the last
few days where we might move to, why we
might move. So here we come into the
hourly, right? Let's move this up so you
can see enough. You can see we're
stretching back up into the developing
week profile. All right. So this profile
here is from Sunday's open. And you'll
see we have a node here. We get thin. We
have a very thick node here. We get
thin. We have a little node here. We get
thin. And we have a node here. And then
under here, well, we have had no
acceptance under there. All right. So,
this was the gap fill yesterday. This
was the drift into the higher time frame
level. This is the 200 day. We've bid
back off that 1 2 3. The question really
is, do we pull back and hold? Now,
that's the question mark. If we're going
to pull back and hold, that means we're
going to have no acceptance um to
increase value lower in the developing
week. So, if it is a big if right now,
but if we can pull back and hold
somewhere into these 700s, possibly even
down to 640s. All right, potentially
then they have a little bit of a
continuation move higher maybe if they
really want to turn it on. What you need
to be careful of is if we fail to hold
previous day value area high, these 780s
here, and we rotate down to what's 650s,
the previous day point of control, and
we lose that, we're going to come
straight back down to 530s. Now, this
might not seem like enough, like a lot.
That's 800 to 500. 765. That's 300
points in a rotation. And I tell you
what, overnight we were very thin up
there. All right. So, we got to be a
little bit careful of how we place this.
If we're going to be long today for a
relief, you have to be careful because I
will remind you the main trend is still
down. All right, this is a relief,
right? The question is as we come into
some of these levels down here, do the
bids come back in and say, "Hey, enough.
We need a relief all the way back here."
Don't say they have to do it today. But
like this could be the start of what
we're looking for early next week.
something up into that unless this PC
shifts down here, which it's not too far
away from doing. All right, but if it
doesn't, then I'd be looking for that
move next week and then a resell back
down towards the lows. So, watching
these areas here, I'm I'm not going to
be too heavy here. The last thing we
want to do on a Friday after a massive
week, two weeks in a row of amazing
price action. The last thing we want to
do is something stupid, right? So we
will be watching if we hold previous day
value area high or this developing
profile this node here ideally if not
down here we will be thinking about if
this gets long if we do that and we
reject value area high I will be looking
for a short back down into this and this
again and then I'll be thinking long
again I do not want to get long uh short
down here I really don't want to get
short down here right like we talked
about we don't want to be shortening
that 200 day even if it starts peaking
for the day that's all right it can go
without me okay let's have a look what
happened overnight
So in the new session you can see we
lost previous day's value area low and
we drifted into the 200 day. Soon as we
hit that 200 day we found a bid right
higher low starting to bid up and we are
in one of these repricing into here. We
need to build out liquidity somewhere in
here now to offer that relief. And if
they can't get that relief then these
guys will become trapped and we'll use
it downside. All right. So, I'm
expecting a pullback ideally somewhere
into here to get long probably is going
to be the first thing I'd consider doing
and then we can readjust after that. All
right, we'll readjust after that.
Okay, so lower time frame. You can see
it's just a straight pump. Um, I'll tell
you what I can do. You can see some of
the nodes that I've marked out. If we go
to the Asia session, I rarely do this,
but the move has been big, so it's worth
doing right here.
Hello, mate. There we go. All right.
It's a big cluster developing here. I'm
watching the edge of this into previous
day value area high. If we lose this
cluster, like I talked about, if we lose
this cluster, all right, then really
we're very thin here, aren't we? So, I'd
be watching this from yesterday. And if
we lose that right down to here, it's
very, very possible right now we come
all the way back down to 500s. If we
lose sevens or what we call that, 790s.
Let's just call it 750s to be safe. We
lose it under there, there's a chance
we're going to move to 650s. If they
don't find a bid on yesterday's point of
control, then we will rotate down to the
yesterday's previous day value low,
which is overnight point of control. So
this area here is a big big zone. All
right? So if we don't bid here or here,
they will probably bid here, which means
there is a short down to that. And if
they lose that, there's another short
down to that. And there's a bid either
here or here or here. I don't want to
trade between these zones. Don't want to
trade between those zones in that thin
profile. No, thank you very much. All
right. So I'm going to stick to these
zones. One, two, three. That's where I
want to trade those locations. nowhere
else. All right, so wait for it to get
into those and then see what the
reactions are. All right, let's have a
look at the ES.
All right, look at that strength. Oh my
gosh, why so strong? Well, because it's
not had the relative weakness with
software selling off. All right, so if
we think about IGV, want to make sure I
got that right. IGV. All right, this has
been the cell in tech. All right, this
is your oracles and your Adobe's. We
went over this yesterday. All right,
cliff. All right, I did get long, right?
I started like nibbling long. I will get
more long down here just for a little
bit of relief. It might be that it
collapsed the whole thing, but I'm
looking for a little bit of relief
bounce. Whereas ES like we talked about,
all right, relative strength doesn't
have all of tech in it and we have some
of the broader market. That's a great
push. That is a fantastic push overnight
on ES starting to find a bid. So, you'll
be watching for liquidity to be built in
here now. And if it is, then probably a
drive back up to here over the next few
days. So, it looks pretty good. Let's
have a look at the uh ETFs.
Spiders,
same story. All right. Right into our
green zone. Look at that. Right into the
70s and we've caught a bid off that. All
right. So, they lost 75 trading to 70s
after hours on Amazon earnings. Ripped
it. And you know what we have now? All
right. So, there they don't come back
down into this. If we build liquidity
out here, this can then be used for that
relief. Doesn't have to be today. I want
to really make that clear. It really
does not need to be today. Might be a
liquidity building day today given the
size of that push overnight. QQQ, same
story. All right, we lost these 600s and
we came Well, that is a big old wash in
the after hours on Amazon. Didn't
realize it was that big. All right, one
thing I would say there is divergence.
QQQ 200 day is a long long way down. All
right, it is at 77s. All right. So, if
the ETFs are going to catch up next week
and get to their 200 days, these are
going to have to trade right down into
here. All right. So, they've got a long
way to come or the 200 day tap, which
we've seen on NQ already if they're
going to play that catch-up trade. The
same story right inside of initial
balance now. Uh gapping up and we have
an old gap fill which you didn't quite
fill. If we want to be efficient, we can
come into those 60580s. I will be
watching that. All right, let's get into
the MAG and everything else. Uh BTC and
all that good stuff. Dixie still trying
to find a bid. All right, it's coming
back down now, but it's coming back down
into a level that we last bid off. So,
if this is an undercut, we'd want Dixie
to hold here for that drive up if it's
actually going to have a go at it. But
this is just building out a box if we
lose that new lows.
Uh gold and silver did everything we
talked about. All right, there's your
fade back down. There's your cover. And
you'd have to see if it gets runners, if
not relief. Same story on silver. Silver
was actually a better trade. All right,
there's the pop back up which been faded
and they did it. All right, so there's
the bounce which you fade and there's
the undercut and then you'd be covering
there and you just be runners now cuz if
they reclaim this then they're going to
come back up here. Uh BTC we can go over
quickly. We talked about this. We have
talked about this extensively. I kept
warning you guys do not be long.
Everyone trying to long up here is just
like it doesn't make sense based on
history. All right, big wash last night.
I have got long some I bet. I will be
honest with you. I'm long just for a
relief, not a long-term hold. I don't
think this is necessarily the long-term
hold point. I think this is, you know,
measured move drift back up into here
somewhere and then have another go down
into here. Like we said, it we can come
30s. We can come 30s, folks. I know it's
scary, but it absolutely can do it. Uh,
right, Mag, before I run out of time,
right, Apple still fantastic. Fantastic.
Amazing strength in Apple. Starting to
build out here though. These are always
dangerous. If they don't break a new
high soon, then we will expect this. So,
we want to be careful, especially if the
market stays weak. If the market starts
to rally, we might see a resqueeze.
Um, what is going on here? What is this?
Get out of it. Get out of it. All right.
Amazon hammered. Absolutely hammered.
All right. Gap fills all the way up
here. This thing's getting cooked right
now. It's in big, big trouble.
Coming back down towards these 200s. So
found a beard around the 200s. Where are
we into a major pivot? We still have a
gap fill. God, Trading View has gone
nuts. We still have a gap fill into 91s
that we want to be aware of. So can
still see more weakness there in Amazon.
Google Trading View, what's going on?
Wow,
it's a new one for me. Completely froze.
All right, Google underneath PDC
wash yesterday drove drove all the way
back up. Starting to see if it can find
a bid. This is your key level today. 32s
32s 22s 322s
and to 33. So a $10 range here on the
goog
meta.
Same kind of thing. Trying to find a bid
after that overnight wash. All right,
same kind of thing in the markets back
in yesterday's IB. You can see breakout
wash range here. Get above this and
hold. We'll have relief. Asking a lot of
it, but it's a Friday. You don't know.
Freaky Fridays. All right. Uh Microsoft
still breaking down. I've got a feeler
on this. Uh just want to see if we come
back in here. This would be the look
below and fail, but we we will see. This
is quite a way off the highs now, right?
We've already filled in this gap, which
is what I was looking for. So, I have
got a feeler long and this a swing long
feeler on this. looking for a reprice
towards 40s and I'll probably lock in
there because that is possible at 40s.
So, I'll probably lock in most of it
there. And if we start to do this,
great. This is going to be this is a
swing play, right? This is a swing play.
So, I've bid small amount around here
this morning and yesterday. And we we
will see how we go. Uh Net uh Nvidia, it
doesn't look good, does it? That really
doesn't look good. This is your shelf.
Um
it's getting tight. It is getting tight.
If they start losing that shelf, then
we're going to probably have a new leg
down in the cues because that is the one
thing holding up. Okay. If we start
losing that, I'd be watch out time. In
fact, you know what? It's that
important. Let's set a price alert. That
is an important level.
Okay, Tesla
gapping up needs to get back in this
range to have any real strength. All
right, so same thing. There's just sort
of W. Can it bid above 400? If so, it's
looking to get into these sort of tens
and 15s. Acceptance back through that
and we can go back upside again.
Otherwise, this is where the buyers are
stuck. Same kind of thing we look at all
the time, right? Uh Oracle, I did start
a long last night, all right, on a
relief uh a tiny tiny tiny bit because
it's very high risk because it's got a
lot of debt that they might have to
raise. Uh but I do think this is
overextended now at this point. All
right, we filled the gap uh off this
high. We're down a huge amount, right?
60%. So, I'm looking for a relief rally
here on Oracle. So, I do have a small
piece swing long on Oracle just as a
starter just for transparency. And as
you know, I am swing long on Amazon on
Netflix as well, but I'm actually
looking for the 70s. I'm looking for it
to come down, fill this gap in the 70s
before I add any more. So, there we go.
That's me being transparent with you.
Not that you guys are a swing channel,
but I have started some swing positions.
Okay,
those in Discord, just check out the uh
swing tab and you will see the positions
and why. Uh already up quite nicely on
them. I posted some this morning. Where
are we up? I'm up uh 7% on Hood already.
I'm up uh 3.4% on IBIT already and a few
others.
Okie dokie.
Right. Wow, that was quick. Um good luck
everyone. The open is about to start. Uh
we will see. Ideally, they flush down
and offer us something to get long into
ideally and we'll go from there.
So, we'll be watching some of these
zones down here. If we do, if we lose
previous day value high, we'll be
looking for here and here to get long.
Otherwise, not too fast. We've had a
fantastic week. Fantastic week.
Yes, Nightbot got adjusted after all the
questions. Right. Nightbot Nightbot got
told, "Here are the volume profile
settings. This is what we're trading."
Yes. I couldn't deal with it any longer.
All right, let let's see. be watching
down here now to see if we get a flush
into it to to bid off
Amazon the week 18% down. So let's see
folks if we're lucky we'll get that sort
of retest towards uh previous day point
of control maybe even previous day value
area low which is slightly different on
Ninja Trader that's a bit annoying. All
right. So, point of control I have on
Ninja Trader is Let's make sure this is
correct. Is down.
Oh, these are all wrong. I adjust all of
these. Give me a second. There we go.
That was all wrong. So, looking to see
if we come into 50s for a bid at the
moment. They're protecting that old gap.
Remember that old gap? We just protected
it.
So, they can resqueeze above previous
day value area high if they want and
kind of clear all this out. This is
where I'd much feel much better about
bidding. If I was going to bid up today,
I'd rather we tested this naked level
and bid up or even down here and bid up
off that. That would be much much
better. Remember, the main trend is
lower. So, we want to be very careful.
We don't really want to buy value area
high from yesterday. It' be much better
if we can drift lower first. But we will
see, folks. We will see. They might just
uh set a squeeze and go. We'll see.
Zoom in on some of these. I didn't get
to go through VIX, did I? Sorry about
that. VIX is just basing around the 20s
right now. VIX just basing right back to
previous day value high here. Do they
find acceptance back through or not is
the question. If they do, then
potentially there is a squeeze on uh
back to take out these overnight highs,
but it's not the best location.
Nice. I bet up 6%. Let's [\h__\h] go.
Nice. these relief rallies starting to
take place today which is what we expect
right after a big big sell days is what
we expect. We expect some relief in the
market.
All right, let's see folks. Let's see.
And we come to this previous day point
of control. Can we get down there and
trap some people? His favorite. Can we
trap some people down there?
Come on. Come down for us. Come down for
us. Let's get some vol here as well.
There we go. So, into that gap. I really
want to get this blue box if possible.
If they're going to be very kind, that's
where I'd like to go. I'd like to get
down into that blue box.
already squeezing then right watching
this now for a trigger long through all
of this. Let's see if they're going to
do it. Here we go. Here we go. So long
in this now for this squeeze back up for
this imbalance. Oh my god. This is too
much money. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my
god. Lock it. Locking some in. Jesus.
I'm getting too rich here. Stop. Stop.
Stop. Stop. Stop. There we go. All
right.
Too rich too quick. All right.
There was the trap. I would have much
rather that trap happened down here, but
they trapped into here. Reclaimed value
and up we go into here. Trimming some
off now. Had to trim some because I
sized, started adding into that
aggressively. And we see if we take out
this high now and through that we have
this uh node here. So we'll be trimming
some into here. So it wasn't ideal.
Ideal would have been into this and then
do it. But we trapped here. Squeeze
through this into this. This is your
next block. So we're selling into here.
Watch this volume here, folks.
and we'll see the trap again. The same
play that we've had the last two days in
a row. Same play we've had the last two
days in a row. And this gray box above
is where we're going into now. The edge
of this we're starting to trade into now
74s is going to be key. It's a big node
from the developing week. If we get
through that, then we can hit 963s
today. So, this is a huge node of the
developing week. So, you want to be
taking a big chunk of yours off into
this gray box. Here we go. Still
lifting. Still lifting. Next imbalance
is 910. So we've just filled a lot. You
do not want to be adding up here now.
Okay, this is a big squeeze. Look at
this. This is a 180 point squeeze here.
And we joined in probably from a little
bit around here 70. So we've got a good
100 points out of that straight away.
Alex made too much money. [\h__\h] hell.
Alex made too much money there. I had to
join a little bit late, but it was so
aggressive on that rip through. It was
insane. So, I'll show you what I saw.
Look at this. Mr. Seller at the lows
getting stuck. Who'd have guessed? All
right. Same thing as yesterday at these
lows in this imbalance. They came flying
in and we turned around and then we went
straight through value. Buyers stepped
in and then we've just absolutely ripped
faces filling all these old imbalances.
All right. So, the main move that I
wanted has happened in the opening what,
two, three, four minutes. Just wait now.
Be very careful of this shelf now. Okay.
If you're holding longs, if we lose this
shelf, you know what happens? We're
thin. we come right back down. So if we
lose this shelf on a retest, I will not
be trading this short up here. But if
you lose this shelf on a retest, this is
probable because this is very thin,
right? The other option is they do a
naughty and complete this move up into
here if they want to do some sort of
retrap up at the highs.
What indicators are that on the chart?
Blah blah blah blah blah blah blah.
Okay, I'm not going to answer these
anymore. This is why I set up Nightbot.
Nightbot will tell you what all the
indicators are. Okay, Alex cannot keep
answering the same questions every day
100 times. I'm very patient to do it,
but just read in chat. All right,
Nightbot is telling you what's there.
Let us know when you take a trade. I I
did I told you I made it very clear.
I'll be looking for a trap down here and
a reclaim of previous day value can
cause a squeeze. So, guess where I got
long. I told you. What do you want me to
do? Like I say all the time, I'll show
you where the toilet is. I'm not going
to hold your dick for you.
At least tell you where you're taking a
trade. I don't know what is wrong with
you guys. You must have just joined the
channel for the first time. I made it so
clear, right? My preference for a long
would have been down here. But we
trapped on this old gap. If you were
here yesterday, you would have known
that this is a gap. All right? We
trapped in this gap. We found a bid. We
saw sellers trapped. I've talked about
it. Sellers got trapped. I'll wait for
the reclaim. There's the reclaim of New
York open and previous day value high.
There was my trigger long. I'm long and
I'm selling into these gray boxes. All
right. If you are new here, you need to
be turning up every day. A whole at
least tell me this. At least tell me
this. Uh I don't actually need to tell
you everything, but I do and I explain
everything. That's why we catch 300
point bangers here together. All right.
If you're listening, if you're waiting
for me to be like, "This is a bull flag
and we're going to do this." And I'm I'm
not going to give you that, guys. Like,
I'm telling you much more important
levels than that. All right. Still
holding this. Still have this level here
which we can go and fill. This is the
huge level. Remember, of the developing
weekly profile, if we start to hold bids
above this, we can start to get
aggressive. All right? We're talking
about this here. This node here is where
we've just traded into. If we hold above
this, we can run the stops into 9 950s.
All right. Into here. We have an old
point of control, I believe, untested.
And this guy here, 25162s,
PC now for the developing week has
shifted lower, which is one thing. So,
we've just shifted PC here for the
developing week. So, this is fair value
since Sunday now. All right. And we're
holding bids above fair value since
Sunday and driving higher. Here you go.
There we go.
So, let's see if they find acceptance
now.
I'll be trimming a decent amount of
profit here.
Really nice.
Okay. Okay, so the stops we can run are
960 if it has power. All right, you do
not want to be adding long up here. I
will tell you that. All right, the long
the long trigger was down here. We're
now basing above this gray box. We've
developed this in the last 5 minutes.
All right, but our TP is here and here.
All right, so if you were long from
these reclaims, TP1, TP2, TP3, if we get
very lucky today and they do some
disgusting squeeze, then we can think
about 25,000. Remember the main trend is
down. We are looking at a relief rally.
Why people are covering their puts on a
Friday after a multi,000 point move over
the last few sessions.
I had to wait a minute to say this, but
that was the best saying I've heard in a
long time. Lol. My buddy put me on to
this channel. Glad he did.
You're talking about the toilet saying.
Yeah, I say that on this channel a lot.
People come in for signals, but they
want me to say I'm buy now, buy now. If
you're here and prepared and listen to
me and stay with me, I tell you where
I'm going to buy and what I'm looking
for. Right, as we always talk about,
we're looking for shorts trapped at
lows. All right, we are looking for
shorts trapped into low pivots, which is
what we got this morning. Move this into
a one minute. I showed you on Ninja
already. All right, shorts trapped into
the lows down here. All right, they got
trapped down here. It doesn't show well
on Trading View, but I tell you what, it
does show on. It shows very well on my
Ninja Trader right here.
This is where the short got trapped this
morning. He got trapped at 14s. And then
the next level here is 46s. So all the
time we're above 46s that this big
player here is caught offside.
All right, so we're going to go from one
node to the other node. Like I said, you
want to be very careful here into the
900. So, we've just developed more here.
I'm going to put another gray box in
inside here. We're still bullish on this
squeeze. So, all the time we're holding
above this node. This is your rotation
right now between this node and this
node. If we find acceptance, they will
come for up here now. So, dips are
holding. There's your higher time frame
algo hold. Pretty positive there. If we
come up here, 960. And then we can think
about 25K. Be very, very careful if we
lift into 25K. I'm just going to check
the ETFs here while I'm watching. Right,
Q's getting very close to previous day
high here. Be very careful here. Q's
going rip faces at 60480s. There will be
a stop hunt there. Is ES already done
it? Spiders have already done it.
Where's ES? ES not there yet. Right. So,
ETFs already coming up to previous day
high. VIX coming down to previous day
low. So, we are in a trimming position
here as in we're in a lock some profit
in position here on the ETFs especially.
Right. especially.
Let's have a quick look at Finnbiz here.
Let's have a look at the broader market.
All right, if you lose this, this level
here is key for bulls to hold. Right,
there's your PC on the day developing
PC. This level here, bulls must hold
this if they're going to complete this.
If they lose this, all right, then this
rotation here will happen. Oh, but he
doesn't tell me what to do. I literally
have just told you right now what I'd be
looking at, right? I'm done with that
long now. Can always re-enter if I like
it. been viz. Are we going to wake up
today? Why are you giving me a uh
see anything yet? Channel is so bad. All
right, back into this node. All right,
and VWOP. So, this is your overunder now
for sentiment for the day. Like we
talked about, if they lose this, you
will see this flush right back down to
here. If they do a little trap here,
we're going to rotate back to this high.
This is the rotation between here.
Acceptance over there, we come to 60s,
right? So, we will see. There is 100
points in here if they hold it.
Remember the seller got caught here at
45.
It got caught here at 45. So all the
time we're above that 45 that seller is
still stuck. If we get under 45s and
definitely under 30s, uh this is going
to get very very thin back down to 760
770s. Right? So if we lose this, you can
see we're so thin on this squeeze up
that we took. we can come right back
down into here. So, you do not want to
see this. If you're bullish, you do not
want to see this here happen. Right? If
you start losing that, do not hold it.
They will flush this very quickly if
they start to lose this node.
I'll give you a little readout on the
MAG. Let's just check. Yeah. So, SPY
took out previous day high coming back
towards Wow. Coming back towards its
5day and 50-day cluster. Uh QQQ not
quite there yet at its previous day
high, but not far. VIX very close to
previous day low but not far. Right.
Tesla 1.36% up. Nvidia 4.08% up.
Microsoft 1.61% up. Meta 1.73% up.
Google 1.96% up. Amazon 9% down. Apple
1.17% up. How are my swings performing?
Where are you, Mr. Oracle? Oracle 4.3%
up. I want to just check on that to see
where I might want to take some profit
on this relief.
Oh, we've got a way. I'm going to hold
this for a while. I think some decent
relief off this.
Sorry folks, just give me a second.
70s. Where's the gap there? 60s. Okay,
cool.
Might
trim some today just to be smart.
Just to be smart.
Okay. So, held gray box well. So,
greater to great rotation. So, greater
great this rotation here starting to
take place. This will be a buildout of
liquidity. Acceptance above. They'll
come for 65s and then 25k. And like we
talked about acceptance below and they
will wash this. Here we go. So, they're
holding well. Point of control. VWAP
held. If they do this, we will expect
this move here to 960s.
There are lots of stops at 60s. Okay,
lots and lots of stops at 60s.
Um, so if you have a look at that hourly
candle put in at sort of 9:00 a.m. on
Thursday, yesterday, that's what we're
looking at is can we run the stops up
into that. So, you want to be proactive
taking some profits into that level. I
think you've got a shot here, folks.
You've got a shot here.
Here
we go. So bids off here are holding
acceptance through here. Now here on
come the 60s. All right. So if you are
long now you're looking for a partial
through 60s. We have room. There is a
low volume. 60 is a very low volume
node. All right. I'm looking at the
developing week like I keep talking
about. I'm looking at this developing
week. I'm looking
Where's my arrow? Mr. Arrow. Right. I'm
looking at this stop here and this low
volume node here. So, we know that this
is a big level. So, if we pop that, you
want to be taking some profit. If you
get lucky, you'll get into this next
cluster. What's the edge of that?
25,040.
All right. But you definitely want to be
taking some profit into 60s. Okay. In
260s.
I got slip, bro. I got in at 830s when I
saw the trap seller. 8 830s. Oh, so
after you saw the trap seller, but it's
still good. You saw the trap seller
here. You mean on that flush down and
hold, you're still good. You look good.
Look, you're going to get you're you're
up over 100 points. You're up over 100
points. You're going to get this. You
should get this 60s. I would have some
limits out, right? Those of you who are
long or like I'd say, I'd have some wish
orders out because through this, you
might get a stop run straight up and
they can fail up there. So, you want to
have wish orders out up here. So I'll be
trimming some now and having some limits
just put in up here in case this from
here you get a big boner candle and you
can come and fill some of you. Here we
go. So coming up for the 60s.
So 50s on deck here. We got a 50 lot in
deck there and 60s we got 22s and then
975. So I'll be trimming some into this
and then see if you can get it to go.
Uh
what futures are you trading? US 100.
I'm trading the NQ US00 is not is
uh CFD, right? I'm trading the actual
centralized futures market. John Dennis,
thank you very much. Appreciate you, my
friend. All right, back down to this
rotation. So, we just missed these stops
at 60s. This node here is key, right?
You can see this node here. If they lose
this node, we will come back down. If
they hold this node, we will try and
complete it. Be careful because you're
going to be in third drive here, right?
Think about the amount of drives you
want to be careful. Two, three. If they
stop, you don't want to be adding any
more here now. No, no, no, no, no.
Right. It either does it and completes
it for you or it doesn't. Do not be
adding long up here now, please. Because
if they want to do this, they absolutely
can. Right. Lots of bulls chasing this
up on the way up at the moment.
Ideally, they hold this, complete this,
and get up here for you guys. And then
you can lock in all your money in the
day. And then we can all have a a good
time together for the rest of the day.
Oh, I'm on the wrong channel for you,
aren't I? Sorry. I was drawing for you
anyway. All right. Here. This node must
hold. This node must hold. 60 is coming
up. Have your wish orders up here.
Please have your wish orders for above
60. Please,
you might get a uh
you might get an 80 point spike here.
Ideally, they're stacking at 50 and 75
is where they're stacking right now. 50s
and 75.
How much are you paying for the tool
that you use? Well, this one I designed,
so I'm not paying anything, right? And
this one is free. It's anchored volume
profile.
It's very simple. People are asking you
to say, "I'm entering the trade the
moment you enter it." Yes. And it's very
simple. And I do. And I do, Mr. Prodigy.
It's very simple. I'll teach you to
fish. If you don't want to learn to fish
and you want to watch some [\h__\h] idiot
who doesn't know how to trade and what
they're looking at, you can very simply
go and look elsewhere. That's a very
simple thing as well.
Uh funding next and lucid for me uh what
I trade right 60s coming up here. Come
on. There's a 200 lot 50s through that.
Starting to fill that 200 lot stacking
at 50s. Through that we should see a
swipe. Come on. Get through this 200
lot. They've tapped into him a few
times. Trying to put up a wall here. QQQ
now taking out previous day high. So
just be careful. The ETFs have now
completed that previous day high move
which is the 50s which is why there's a
200 lot here. So the ETFs cash have been
efficient. SPY is holding well over
that. And just be very careful here
watching the QQQ.
Come on, get through this uh 200 lot.
You can see him on book lap book book
map 207 lot at 50s. Through that we
should see a little bit of a face
ripper. Come on.
Failing that 50. So that wall still
there. See if they bid back up to him
now. So still holding this light gray
box, this shelf.
You need to see this break the high now.
All right. So, we've just had a lot of
shorts chase. We had a 154 lot come in
at 40s, a 32 lot underneath him, 62 lot
underneath him, a 200 lot at the lows.
We should take this out now. Uh we have
had a huge amount of shorts chasing. We
have to take out the 50s now, otherwise
it's game over for these lot. Back to
this gray box again. Like I said, this
is third drive, which is why I would not
be adding long up here.
They're trying. If you get a 50 break,
you should get a pretty nice squeeze
because there's a lot of shorts who've
come in underneath that on that last
flush down to that gray box. So through
50s, you should get a move through 60s
to 75 pretty quickly. You got to get
through this 200 lot sat above us right
now. Like I said, QQQ is that previous
day high. So watching to see if the
options market wants to take that out or
not. And then you've got 605 above,
which I imagine would be a big big
level.
So I can show you on bookmap which I'm
looking at here. You can see right here
we've got a 200 lot wall. We sold
against it a couple times and you see
all these shorts chasing. Well, if we
get above them, they are all going to be
offside and we will use this guy to lift
up into here. We've got to get through
50s and then we'll use these guys pain
to move higher at that point. They've
got to get through this 950. Here's the
flush through it. So 915 to 60. Let's
see if they can turn this on to 75 for
you and then to 25k. Here you go. Boom.
Boom, boom, boom, boom. So, you want to
be locking some in here. Moving your
stop up. Here's 75. Here's the squeeze.
Alex doesn't know what he's talking
about. Doesn't give it ahead of time.
Yada yada yada. All the new people in
chat talking absolute shite. All right.
And now 25,000 the next level. So, you
should be trimming. You should have 10
20% left. That's it. That is all you
should have left.
All the questions about the indicators,
anchored volume, profile, all that
stuff. Just look at Nightbot in chat.
They will answer everything for you.
It's all there. It's just told you.
Look at that. Locked in 20k withdraw
after close today on my 550k fle uh flex
my future funded accounts. Solid week.
Keep sizing in check. Stuck to my plan.
Amazing start to the weekend. Nice work,
buddy. All right, there you go. So,
there's the squeeze through. Like I
said, I'll just be tiny tiny amount left
now uh to see if you can lift up into
this box. But the damage has just been
done. You've just run the stops. We're
into that low volume node. Remember, we
talked about it down here. We are
looking to run this guy's stopout. We
just ran his stop out. We can fill some
of this in. This is low volume. If
you're lucky, you get 25,000 and this
block here somewhere up into here. This
shelf 25,040.
The damage has been done. This is multi
drive, right? This is just a squeeze. At
some point, they will wash this back
down.
Alex, my previous day point of control
is 24719 Trading View, but your previous
day value high is in that region. Ninja,
am I missing something? I'm fixing it to
the previous day from 9:30 to No, that's
right. Uh maybe just the time frame
you're looking at. I'm not sure.
Sometimes there's discrepancies between
Trading View and Ninja though.
Hello from Surrey, England. Did we
trade? Yes, we did. Where in sorry,
England are you living? Yeah, we have
news. We do have news coming up. Top of
the hour, folks. Top of the hour. We do
have news coming up here. Uh consumer
sentiment.
Top of the hour. And then we have some
Fed talk later on in the day. All right.
So, your damage has been done here.
We've run the stops. Remember 60 was the
stop run. This can be a look above and
fail. If they start dunking this under
here and here, this would be the
rotation back to here. And we can build
out volume in here now. So, you should
be pretty much done with this. Like I
said, this was the stop run. You want
wish orders above this. Job done. Uh, if
you're very lucky, you keep drifting,
but I wouldn't be betting on it.
How much is the cost to access your D
discord? Uh, it should be 699, but it's
probably still 649 because Amir has
still not changed it, I don't think. Let
me have a look.
Hopefully he's changed it. Still 649. Oh
my god, he's getting a bollocking. 649
right now. flzontenttrader.com. Beginner
to advance course.
Hello from Arizona. Hello. Hello. Can't
say enough about how great it is to
listen to your analysis. Thanks so much.
You're welcome. Out now. Titan trader.
Yeah, everyone should be out now on that
on that expansion up. All right. If we
start losing here, what I'd imagine
here, unless they collapse it straight
down to PC, we probably get some sort of
buildout here now. All right. And if
they fail to break this, we can have a
look at the high. I would imagine
there's some uh buyers caught at that
high. There you go. Buyers just got
trapped up here above 60 because they're
silly. They started entering
aggressively above 60 and right the way
up here into 80. And we know that's why
I said take profit. Everything above 60.
And now sellers are taking control. And
guess what we're going to do? probably
come right the way back down here when
it's ready for all these imbalances. All
right, so there's the trade. Here you
go. So, we're starting to let go of
these shelves. And we can if we start
letting go of this PC, right, we can
probably bounce between these for a bit.
We can see we've developed this now,
right? And if we let go of that, that
collapse can still happen because
remember the main trend is still
bearish. We just expected relief, right?
The main trend is bearish. We expected
relief to run these stops. And we can
come back into here now if it wants.
talked about this right at the beginning
of the session. Look at that. Right into
PC into this gray box. So, I'm going to
thicken this up now to here. I'm going
to get rid of this one here because
we've traded through it. And these are
now the levels that we're trading to and
from.
What do you get for uh $649?
You get a 20our on demand course. You
get a version of this, the Flowzone Pro.
You get the Flowzone Momos. Very
similar. Not quite as powerful, but very
similar. and you get free access to the
Discord for life.
Hi from Wales. Good morning.
Good morning. Big game between us
tomorrow. Looking forward to that.
Start of the Six Nations. Ireland got
absolutely pumped last night by France.
France looking very dangerous.
Do you trade with the same strategy? I'm
new to trading. With the same strategy.
Same strategy as what? I I trade the
same way every day.
Yeah, exactly, Raph. Very possible. Very
possible. Thanks, Alex. Up 9K. Nice. Do
you make your developing week profile?
Yeah, just draw it on. So, you just just
draw it on and FRRP from the Sunday
open. It's all you have to do. I'm in
Los Angeles. I'm living in Los Angeles.
They are getting aggressive after that.
Look above. Yeah, after that stop run.
Remember, you got news coming up here in
the next few minutes. So, we'll see.
We're very thin down here. Look into 70s
and we still have previous day value
very high. Remember the trap this
morning came into the gap. We didn't
actually get down to the perfect level.
We trapped under here. We reclaimed.
That was the long. Boom, boom, boom,
boom, boom. Done with it. All right,
you're done with it. We can build out
here now. The question is on this build
out, right? If they fail to make a new
high and they lose this, then we're
backside back down into here if you
really want to trade that. But remember,
we are extended to the downside right
now. We've just this move back here. For
anyone who's done the course or joins me
regularly, guess what? That moved back
there tapped.
Yep, you're right. We just moved from
the 200 day back to the lower Ballinger
band. All right. Two sigma. This down
here was three standard deviation. That
was a spooking huge move down to that.
All right. to the 200 day where we found
that bid right back to two sigma now
question is can they lift all the way up
here not today I don't think I think we
will build out liquidity now and then
maybe Monday Tuesday we have that push
and then fail ideally we'll see though
folks we will see but we what I'm trying
to get through to you is we've probably
seen the big moves that we want for the
week if we think about what the weekly
newsletter said what we were looking for
this week. We've hit the targets. All
right, for those who like, what are you
on about? All right, here is the weekly
newsletter. You guys can read that for
me. That's what I put in the bearish
scenarios this week.
Okay, there are few setups more
attractive than trap participants and
right now bulls remain trapped above
26,000. Weakness entered the market
through a classic sell the news
reactions and the following failed
breakout. It's now on bears to complete
the rotation for downside. 25800 to
25900 must be defended by sellers unless
they intend to spring another trap into
the 26,100 pivot. Broader market
weakness and fears should begin to
surface on a sustained trade below 25500
opening the door to 425 with acceptance
below that targets 300 and 25100. A
downside expansion will require
development of widening of the Ballinger
bands. But if that occurs, there is a
significant stop liquidity below 25,000
with the 200 day SMA still there
untested for 9 months. We've done it,
folks. We've done everything every
single thing we did already this week.
It happened last night. 200 day hit the
end. We don't look for any more downside
pressure. We can look for day trades,
right? trading between ranges now. But
we do not expect expansion downside now.
Now we expect liquidity to be built
because like we talk about the market
does not move in one straight direction.
All right, we have left volume like this
on a daily. All right, we had a a look
above here. We've cracked this. All
right, we've done a huge move. We're in
this part now. All right, we're building
this part out on a daily and then we
probably do this for a week or two and
maybe this and then maybe this. All
right, that's what we're doing. We're in
here, right? We don't want to short.
We're trading from here to here. We
don't want to short that, do we? Look
how extended we are. We don't want to
short this move here. You can scalp,
right? We can scalp intraday, but we
lower our expectations. Whereas
yesterday and the day before when we
were leaving volume, when we were
leaving value, when we were in
expansion, we're looking to slam the
holy hell out of it to get down to that
200 day.
Hi, Alex. Is reducing position by 50%
each TP a good rule in general? Uh well
it depends how much size you've got on
really. That's a really uh interesting
question. It it it depends on a how much
size you got on and b where we think
we're going. All right. So if we're
trading like from here and our
anticipation is here then above this I'm
only looking for like 10 to 20%. I'm
locking in at each level. Boom. Boom.
Boom. Runners collapse. Done with it.
All right. We're leaving this now. This
trade here now is starting to happen. We
just went over this. So, we just went
from gray box to gray box. There's your
bare [\h__\h] There's the collapse. Here's
the news. Back down to previous day
value area high. And if they lose New
York open, we'll come back down to point
of control. Now, this is very similar to
yesterday. So, we ran the stops one
side. We failed to break out and hold.
We put in a lower high. We're coming
down to previous day value area high.
This is current week's developing uh
point of control. So, this is fair
value. So, the question now is can we
find a bid here? All right. Because if
we can, it means we're not willing to
trade into yesterday's value. Right? If
we can't find a bid there, it means
we're going to do this move down here
and retest this level.
Right? So, the auction now is deciding,
was yesterday too cheap or do we need to
retest this? If yesterday was too cheap,
they will hold above here and try and
reclaim this and try and go back up. But
I am expecting a range rotation type of
day today.
Hello from Manchester. Hello. Hello.
Uh, probably in the next few weeks, I'll
probably try and get to Austin. May
maybe next month if if not this month.
There's no there's no consistency rule
on evals. No, no, no consistency rule on
evals for Apex. Sorry guys, I'm just
catching up with what you guys are
saying.
I'm doing the course. Do you think I
should join Discord before ending the
course? Yeah, you can do if you just go
to the end of the course. There is a
module on how to join Discord. You can
do that.
pass my apex. Thanks, Alex. Nice, Joey.
Nice work. What do I consider a scout?
Yeah, 20, 30, 40 points. Um, some
sometimes more, but really like I'm
looking for 100 point trades in in a
market with this much volatility.
Remember, we got the VIX up at like the
20s, right? So, it's going to provide
huge opportunities for us right now. All
right, VIX just undercut previous day
low and has found a bid. So, we might
start getting heavy here. VIX probably
going to come back and retest 1950
through that we're going to go 20s. So,
we're going to watch this area here to
see if they trap more sellers here and
rebid. And if not, and if they stay
heavy here, right, we might go this this
this this this is possible. So, either
we're going to trap here for this drive
up and reclaim or they're going to start
washing this far more aggressively.
Remember, we did just take out the old
highs. SPY hit its 5day and 50-day which
are together at the same point
and Q's got a way to go to get there.
All right, starting to see heaviness
come back in. So, running the stops
coming back down. Funny that, isn't it
funny how that works.
How do I size my stop? We go this all
the time. We size based on where the
trade is no longer valid.
Do I ever trade supply and demand? Well,
it's all the same. Yes, it's exactly
what I trade really. This is potential
demand. This is now potential supply.
This is potential supply. Intraday. It's
exactly what I trade. SNR supply and
demand. Order blocks. Call it what the
[\h__\h] you like. It's all the same [\h__\h]
man. People will tell you it's not. It
It is.
Range rotation means Tyson's trade could
play better later. That's very true.
That is very true. All right. Into this
value area. You can see right now we're
trading right into this value area.
There is a big seller that came in at
the 800s. All right. So
if we get back above him, we might drift
back into sort of 30s. There is a huge
node developed in into 56s. So if they
hold 800s, we're probably going to come
and test 30s and then 58s, 56s somewhere
up there. If we lose 800s, they're going
to come and retest this seller down at
uh 714s.
So they're trying to bid off previous
day value high, this area we just talked
about. Here we go. So they're lifting it
now back towards the 56s. Here you go.
Here's the lift. So 30s and then 56s.
There's imbalance here at 40. The next
imbalance is 50. Then you've got 60s.
All right. And then big node into 60s
like you can see right here. Here's
there you go. Super simple. Right.
Previous day value area high. Do they
find a bid here? If they do, we're going
to rotate to gray box. Gray box to gray
box. All right. So if you wanted to
scalp that, that's your scalp. You
should be trimming here because if
sellers step back in here, they're going
to rotate back down to here. And we can
build out here while they make their
mind up. We are inside the opening
range. We have had a failed break after
running the stops. We're coming back
downside. This can build liquidity and
it can be used if they really want to to
come back down to this guy here.
You have to understand the conditions
today. This is not like a uh big
trending day conditions, right? So lower
your expectations today.
Who I got on Sunday? Liverpool City.
hopefully Liverpool, but I'm not
convinced.
But hopefully for me being a goona, uh
it' be nice if we can stretch out that
lead a bit more.
Alex, after achieving success, did you
go through any difficult phases such as
a series losing days and negative
months? Yes, absolutely. Of course.
Yeah. Yeah, definitely, man. Like, you
can't always control the market. What is
that glitchy? Market's been very kind to
us recently, but I'm human, right? I
will make errors uh if I'm not
disciplined and I start trading more in
range rotation, which is not my A+
setup. What is going on? CME data just
gone. I have [\h__\h] huge gaps on my
charts all of a sudden.
Let me just refresh this guys. Give me a
second.
My hourly is just wow. Trading views on
one today.
Wow.
Oh my god. Yeah, I got no data from
Trading View. The CME data is gone. I
have the most huge gap on my hourly
which has just come out of nowhere.
Look, what is that? What is that?
Trading View. What a joke.
What a joke. How are these looking?
It's that chart. Is it?
That's bizarre to me.
Bizarre to me.
Your data has been bugging all session.
It's not good, man. It's really not
good. It is really not good.
What's up with Tops that always changing
the rules? Well, because they're losing
too much market share.
Why don't trade with them? They're
[\h__\h] All right. All right, like we
said, 800's where that big seller is.
All right, 800's right here where that
big seller is. Under that previous day
value area high under that, we have this
trap seller down at 13. So if they lose
this, they can flush down towards 13s.
All right. So, and if they reclaim 800s,
we kind of retest this again. This is
the rotation that we've talked about a
few times.
I feel a bit blind without that hourly.
Don't like that. do not like that.
Let me see if I change time on it. Will
it? No. It's just literally got no data.
[\h__\h] hell.
Can we trade GC GC on Apex? No, they
just banned it like everyone else.
They're all banning metals because
traders are gambling on metals and
making money. I find it hilarious. Like
I find it hilarious. I have seen
traders, I'm not going to name names,
who um no offense to them, um can't read
a chart properly. They don't understand
what they're looking at. They trade
NASCAR or something else and they
consistently lose money um even though
they've traded it for years and then
recently have decided they're going to
trade gold or silver. What the [\h__\h] are
you doing? If you've never traded gold
or silver and you cannot trade something
which is right in front of you that
you've tried to trade for years, why do
you think you can suddenly trade another
asset which is in the most volatile
period of the entire lifespan of it and
you think you are going to be able to
trade it? Do you
not surprised these people are blowing
up? It's [\h__\h] madness mate. It's like
shiny object syndrome honestly. Oh, it's
a new strategy. I'll try that. Oh. Oh,
it's a new asset. Let me try and try try
that because other people said it's no.
Your job is to make money. [\h__\h] take
your ego out of there. It's cra it's
crazy to me. Anyway, who am I? I better
shut up. Like I always talk about I am a
patchy bearded spectaclewearing
40-year-old
knackered old DJ. I don't know what I'm
talking about.
I've had a big losing day today from
Asia session and don't know don't feel
so good. What advice would you tell
someone like me that it's it's just one
day out of your whole career? Close the
screens. Go and do something that makes
you feel good. All right, rotation back
to gray box again.
So, like we said, we're still bidding
value, right? We reclaimed 800 where
that trap seller is and we can lift now
back up to 60 again. So, they are
building liquidity out here like we
talked about. I'm not going to trade in
the middle of this. Right, this is the
middle of the opening range. This is
between 24hour view up and New York view
up. Like I told you, I do not want to
trade in here. I have zero interest. If
we find acceptance, right, if we find
acceptance above here and they base,
there is a reshot back up here, maybe up
to 25K50. So there is a trade there if
they want it. If they want to do this,
but you want to be very careful between
these two levels here now. All right.
Very, very, very careful. 24-hour view
up, New York view up, node, node from
yesterday.
Hopefully that makes sense for you all.
All right, back to this PC.
It's like I have a crystal ball.
Honestly, it's not. It's just It's just
understanding how the market moves. I I
I know it might look that way, but it it
just isn't. It's You guys can all get
here. You guys can all get here. It's
not like I've had some
I didn't get kidnapped in a white van
and God tell me how the market moves. I
just looked at the screens long enough
that I understood it. Right.
I'm not having Ninja Trader issues. No,
I have having Trading View issues.
I am having trading view issues.
Okay, so in balance now back down to
20s. Let's see if they save this or not.
Feels like they want to try and save
this for a run higher.
Balance down there. Still into 20s. It's
still between these two. It feels like
they want to save it somewhere down here
and then try and get back through that
New York Vat. But we will see except I
don't want to trade in this area
particularly to test back down to the
imbalance of 20s. There's a big node
like we said that big seller is at 800.
So here's the 20s test. Maybe 800 test.
We'll see. I'm going to avoid this whole
area while they make their mind up what
they're doing. So they can set a lower
high here. And we can do that. We can
come back down for this. In fact, I'm
going to move this now. That old gap. We
filled it. Watching this New York open.
So, view up to view up again. Still,
they're just jumping over each other.
They're trying to find a bid here again.
If not, they're going to flush all the
way down into this.
Cannot make their mind up. Vicks holding
previous day low. Coming back up to that
1950 like we talked 1950. If we get
through 1950, then 20 is on the VIX is
possible. That's when the market will
get very, very weak.
We keep banging back into this 800. This
guy at 800. So, it's a big level here of
whether they are willing to push through
this guy or not.
Are they willing to lift it or do they
need now to wash down to 713s? I don't
know.
They are trying to decide, aren't they?
And they're bidding at 50, so
don't look too good.
They snap this then you're going to get
50s by the looks of it.
It's a bit of no man's land bidding 50s.
Honestly,
what are you doing?
Choppy chop chop. It's what we expect
today. Glad we got that first drive out.
Willing to play this uh either on a big
breakdown or on a reclaim and push. I'd
rather a reclaim and push, but we will
see. Just needs to be uh very very
patient now to just let it set up. A bit
like yesterday, right? Once we've used
all the liquidity, we now have to be
very patient. Let that liquidity start
to be built out before we make our next
decision on what it is we might want to
do.
Like I said, they keep bidding 50s down
here. They might well look for a little
tag underneath.
It's be almost weird that they wouldn't
come and revisit 714s and they would
just bid 50s, but we'll see. We'll see
what these guys what their intentions
are here.
Lots of buyers stacking up down here and
they probably get washed out before they
do anything else.
fix through that 1950. Might want that
20 retest after taking out previous day
low.
That 800's still a huge level, right?
800 is still a huge level where that
seller came in. Big delta there. Look,
there's still bidding in front of 50s.
Why not just go and swipe it all out?
It's beyond me. Back towards the 800
again.
Still can't get back through that 800.
Still haven't filled the guy at 50s.
Guy at 50s. And then remember down here
14s was the big level. And actually my
VWAP on Ninja Trader is way different to
this as well. My 24-hour VWAP is down at
09. Right, there's 50s filled. They're
going to add lower now and try and swipe
this by the looks of it like we talked
about. So big seller came in there at
50s again. So he might get trapped if
they can't get down to the uh 14. So
that big seller at 50s might get trapped
now as well. Here's the lift. So
watching the 800s here.
Watching the 800s. seller definitely got
trapped there at 50. You can see it at
the lows. He got trapped here at 50. I'm
watching the order flow if you're
wondering. So, watching 800s. If they're
going to squeeze back through 800s, we
can lift up and fill some of these
imbalances all the way back to 60s.
You can see this rotation taking place.
They have just trapped now. So, watching
this to see if they pull back and hold.
Yep. Go on then. Fill these imbalances
higher. Looking for longs just to fill
some of these imbalances now towards 40
50 60.
needs to hold above 800.
Looks good. Looks good.
Beautiful. His 40s. His 50s coming next.
His 60s. Said I wouldn't trade here, but
that guy got caught. Stop moving up now.
Want to protect eight 15s here.
Filling these imbalances. Trimming more
off there. So, we just tap 40s. Was
hoping we get to 48. might stop out on
the runner here. Not going to sit
through this even though they can pull
back and hold just because we're a bit
washy both sides. So out here on the
pullback and we'll wait now.
So what did I see there? It's just on
order flow, guys. All right, I saw this
guy get trapped. See this lot down here,
this 50s. He got trapped here and then
we went straight back towards the 800s
and then I joined to fill these
imbalances up here. have joined from 800
this like 40 point move up here trimming
some and then stopped that break even. I
said I wouldn't trade there but that guy
getting caught was just too good to not
not trade.
Maybe you were that big buyer. Um I
doubt it.
I doubt it. You're what the buyer at a
higher day at the 920s. I mean we're
talking about thousands of lots. Let me
see. Let me see the delta at 9. Let me
see the delta at 920 is the big buyer.
Hang on. Uh, we're talking about a 445
lot delta. I don't reckon it's you. I
got a funny feeling if you're trading
445 lot, it's not you. All right, back
back to back to these 50s again. Uh,
seller coming in here. We need to get
through point of control. Now, like I
said, there is a chance. All right, if
they just fil it's it's dirty, right?
It's dirty what they've done, but
they've washed out 50s. Remember I said
they wanted to fill 50s. They trapped
the seller. They reclaimed. They've come
to here. If they reclaim here, the drift
will be between these two now. As long
as they can base above this, right? If
they can't base above this, they can
keep rotating in here like they already
have. But if they can base above this,
this would be the next move. And we do
have unfinished business. They really
want to get up into there.
How do we know when you enter a trade
besides the fact of you telling us
you're in the trade when you're taking
profits?
I don't know. Rewind Prodigy again.
You're just the same guy over and over
over again. Guy, dude, I'm not going to
hold your dick. It might be ugly for all
I know. Why does it matter when I'm
entering the trade when I'm telling you
what you want?
Why does it matter? So, what you're
telling me is you don't know how to
trade and you want someone to just
signal you and that's how you think
you're going to make a career trading.
That's that's the truth of what you're
saying.
That's the the real truth of what you're
saying. When you digest everything
you're saying, what you're telling me is
you have no idea how to trade
and you want me to trade for you and you
are willing to bet on my positions from
me saying I am getting long at this
level even though there's a lag and that
you already don't know how to trade.
That's what you want to do.
Crazy.
I totally bet on you over me. Don't
know. Just don't
don't bet on me over you. Like I have to
be reactionary, guys. Like you like
you don't understand. Like if I'm seeing
someone trapped there and I see the
reversal, I've got to take it then and
there, right? I can't be like, there's
going to be a guy trapped here for sure.
100%. I'm ICT. I know. No, we don't know
until he comes on the book. All right,
here we go. So, we just talked about
that for guy that wants me to spell
everything [\h__\h] out. All right,
there's the trap. If we get through
there, we're going to go gray to gray.
And if we lift here, there is a
potential to take out this high of day
and come up for 25,050. I like don't
know. Maybe rewind the last 30 seconds.
Gray to gray. There's greater gray for
you. Do you want me to Shall I hold it?
Is it that big or that big? Two hands,
finger. I don't know. You tell me.
I'm sorry I'm being an [\h__\h] but
jeez, man. There's never like a thanks.
It's always like It's always something
like that.
Okay, back to value area high and if we
get acceptance through this uh potential
stop run. We know buyers got trapped at
the high of day, don't we? All right,
where did those buyers start getting
aggressive? 944s. All right, so we know
buyers got aggressive at 944s. So, you
would want to be trimming some profits
into 44s.
in 244s.
Brett, that's all it all the things that
you're asking for are are all in the uh
in the courses.
Two hands. One of you needs two hands.
Jeez, we got Dirt Diggler over here. I
love it.
I'm not in this long. No, no, no. I'm
not in the long. I took the long from
here to here. Right. And I stopped out
because I didn't want it to come and
retest this node down here, which it
did. So, if I'm playing a squeeze, I
don't I don't want it to like wash me
out. So, I took this to this. Was it
that one? Yeah, this to this. Right. And
stopped out on this part.
Uh, what did I risk? I think I said I
was going to risk 15s. I think I was
risking that low volume node there.
Hoping that would hold. All right, so
gray box to gray box again
over and over and over again. They're
going to keep rotating. We are not in a
trend day. Remember, we're not in a
trend day. We're in a rotational day.
Caught over 100 points on two micros for
the third time today. Look at that. 100
points with two micros. That's 400
points for your third time. 4812. $1,200
trading two micros. There you go. That
is how to trade.
I'm not I'm not grumpy. I'm good. I'm
good.
What indicator on Think or Swim is
similar to the gray boxes? I'm just
drawing these on there. There's no This
is not an indicator. This is stuff I'm
drawing on. It is just understanding
volume.
What is my pro approach to proper evas?
Do you go heavy size and pass them as
quick as possible? Do you take your time
and use the same risk management? I will
be honest. I'm at a point in my career
where I go heavy. So, I would not advise
you guys do that, but I'm at a point in
my career where I call it time delta,
time decay. I don't want to waste time
in uh props. So, I'm at a point where,
you know, I can often be right and pass
them very, very quickly. But, I would
not advise you guys do that. I'll be
honest. I don't think it's how you
should do it. But, if I'm transparent
with you, I'm aggressive with them at
this point in my career. I do not have
time to waste.
Yeah, I use prop firms.
Yeah. Yeah. Sorry.
Instead of teaching you can can I just
have your login. I probably get arrested
for that. I'm also like technically not
allowed to tell you like um buy this,
sell this. All right. I'm not a
financial adviser. So technically that
would be illegal as well. So technically
I can't do that. Although I have told
you numerous times where I expect the
market to to go, my expectations, where
I expect rotations to happen, even swing
positions, where I'm considering getting
long on swing positions.
What's my what's your IQ? handling
trades and channel with your analysis
and crowd education. Damn, you're
rockstar. I have no idea what my IQ is.
I wouldn't say it's that high. I'm not
like an in very intelligent person. I'm
I'm a very hardworking person. I wasn't
like a huge high achiever at school or
university. I had to work hard for it.
Learning doesn't necessarily come easy
for me. All right, they drifted this
back to the PC. Look at this developing
PC from the currently weekly profile.
They just drifted back to it. Caught a
bid. Reclaimed gray. They're just going
to keep rotating. There is a chance to
get up here but low hanging fruit we've
already run it right that first move
here today was the low hanging fruit
trade we expect look at what we're
developing here right anyone tell me
what is this what type of profile is
that what is this right so what do we
expect from that profile
what footprint do I use uh uh the uh uh
uh as in on Ninja trader I assume you
mean um I use it's called city but the
provider is I can never remember the
name. Where's Discord? I always have to
scroll down. The provider for it is Twin
Peaks. I use Twin Peaks.
Uh but you can use Footprint on here
just on Trading View as well. I don't
think it's quite as good, but it's
pretty good. All right, we're trying to
lift for these imbalances. You can see
like I said 40 44s is where they got
really stuck. They are trying to fill
some of these sell side. We can also
also think about you know this you're
coming into golden pocket. So if you get
lucky fill some of this but I would not
guarantee that you get over all of it
cuz we are in a rotation. And where's
the top of the rotation? Well right now
it's right here to here. No acceptance
below. No acceptance above yet unless
we're going to start doing this and
moving value higher. It's possible.
But these are my least favorite days to
trade. So, anyone who turns out
regularly will know that.
Can I hold the D-shape for you? Yeah.
Is FTM FTMO so bad? I've never traded
with them, so I can't tell you. Cannot
tell you. Calypso $1,700 on six accounts
with two micros. Nice.
What was my lowhanging fruit? Low
hanging fruit today was the run of the
stops on the hourly. I cannot show you
it right now because unfortunately
um this has gone down. I don't know why
but we basically we had hourly stops
like here. Maybe I can show it to you on
the lower time frame and just put in an
hourly chart here and it won't be
annoying. No, like I've got no data. I
don't know why it's
what we have to deal with as retail is
ridiculous. Right. Maybe I can see it
here. Maybe it will show me here. Okay,
this was the low hanging fruit for me.
See these stops right here, right? 960s.
Can you see this stop right here? Right.
So, if I was swing short, think about
how the market operates, right? We were
swing short or we were short here.
Right? So, we left for yet another time.
We left volume trapped, we drifted down,
we did a two-leg, and they got short
here, right? And then we collapsed down
and we get the 200 day. So most people
would cover like 80% of their position
into that 200 day. All right, then we
start to recover. All right, so there we
start to recover, right? So where are
they going to run? They're going to run
the swing stops here. All right, so they
run the swing stops out, which means
what? Above that mark, retail starts
buying because they're silly. Also at
that mark, anyone who is short becomes
uh stops out and becomes a cover. That
cover is a market buy order, right? Once
we get enough market buy orders, right,
then it gives the opportunity for bigger
hedge funds to sell into because you
cannot just sell without someone the
other side. So I will give you an
example here. Let's say someone
overnight bought 10,000 contracts down
here long, right, off the 200 day,
right? Let's just say someone bought
10,000 contracts long, a hedge fund,
right? Where are they going to sell
that? they're going to need to sell that
where there is going to be a seller
uh sorry a buyer. So if they're going to
sell their 10,000 contracts long,
they're going to need a buyer of 10,000
contracts long. The easiest place for
that to happen is in a swing point
because here, let's say we have 5,000
retail traders get long for the
breakout. And let's say we have 5,000
short swing traders stop out. 5,000,
right? Right. plus 5,000 is 10,000
because we've got 5,000 market order
buying for retail and we've got 5,000
uh sell stops which become market buy
orders which means this can pair off
this without being seen on the book.
Boom. Perfect. All right. And that's how
the market operates with big size.
That's why it hunt stops. When everyone
wants to know why does it hunt stops?
That's why it hunt stops. It's for the
auction for repairing because remember
we cannot complete an auction. We cannot
shake hands on anything unless there is
a buyer and a seller. And one has got to
be aggressive and one's got to be
passive. Right? What do I mean by that?
One's going to be market side and one's
going to be limit side. Right? So if we
have
up here, all right, if we have stops up
here, they are going to be market buy
orders. All right, a sell stop, a sell
limit there will actually becomes a
market buy order. And if we were buying
here and we want to sell up there, we
can put a limit order. So we're going to
be a passive seller and we're going to
use the aggressive buyer and that is
where the auction is done. That's where
we complete and shake hands. If you just
have two limit orders, right, on the
book, if someone's only willing to buy
down here and they're only willing to
sell up here, this is what the spread
is, right? And until someone agrees, oh,
I'm going to actually sell down here or
I'm actually going to buy up here, no
deal is done. Like I always talk about
the Rolex, right? Someone owns a Rolex
Dayer, they want to sell it for $50,000.
And Alex is a cheapkate and he wants to
buy it for $30,000. All right? And
there's no one in between. And if that's
the auction, right, no deal is done,
right? Until we agree price, until this
guy says, "Do you know what? I'm now
willing to sell for $40,000." And Alex
says, "Do you know what? I'll meet you
there. I'll buy it for $40,000." Then we
complete the auction and a deal is done.
Right? That is literally what's
happening every second of every candle.
So, when we look at the DOM, when you
understand what's actually going on in
the auction, when someone says, "I'm
reading the tape, it's not [\h__\h]
candles." That really pisses me off.
This is the tape, the level two. Well,
technically the tape is the time in
sales, right? And the way we're jumping
up and down is we are filling orders.
So, these are market orders. These are
limit orders. This guy here is a passive
seller at 9:15, right? 100 lot passive
seller at 9:15. To fill him, we're going
to need to have an aggressive buyer, a
market buyer at 9:15. And it's going to
have to be 102 lot size or more.
Hopefully, that makes sense.
You're having the same issue on your
trading view. Yeah, it's annoying, isn't
it?
It's annoying.
I don't know, guys. I don't know why
Trading View is being shite today. I
have no idea. I think CME have had some
issues this week, honestly.
up one 1K today due to your teaching.
Nice call outs. Nice work. All right,
still going gray box to gray box. All
right, gray box. Look at value starting
to increase. So remember 44s. Look. So
see on this auction we have just taken
out this passive seller. So there was a
passive seller there. Look what happened
right here. This bubble 192 lot bought
the market. All right, that's an
aggressive buyer and above in 47 lot. So
we filled the passive seller with an
aggressive buyer. Now they were trying
lift to the next level and the next
level. But look at this here 9:18 right
918 we have 445 lot offside so I know at
9:18 all the time we're above 918 we can
be bullish because that is a big buyer
who's now comfortably in the money and
they will try and lift to four to 950 if
we come back under 18 then we have that
buyer offside that's how I read delta in
the book right all right so gray to gray
through the gray we're going to look for
high of day right so this is starting to
set up now I'm not in this but this is
starting to set up now like we talked
out and I'd be watching the move towards
44. So I tell you right now there was a
buyer stuck at 50. I'm going to give you
the levels. There was a buyer stuck at
50 and then the next buyer is stuck at
73. All right. And we are starting to
lift. So if you want to mark these on
your chart, 18's a big level, 50 is a
big level, and 73 is a big level.
That ain't that ain't guess work. That
ain't some [\h__\h] fair value gap or
anything like that. That is actual
orders which took place on the book
which you will only be able to see if
you are actually watching the book.
Sorry guys, catching up with what you're
saying now.
How am I seeing this? Uh what you what
do you mean? I'm seeing the thing the
the the chart I just showed you was
bookmap. Okay. So you can see it on
bookmap or you can use footprints. Uh
you will not get delta side reads of
delta on footprint. All right. It's the
only thing I don't like. But on Ninja
Trader, right? If you want to see how I
see it on Ninja Trader, I have a delta
footprint on the side. So this is a big
buyer here who came in. All right, at 18
or 17, whatever I called it, there's a
big buyer stuck at 50 and there's a big
buyer stuck at 72. There's a seller
stuck underneath us at 88. And the big
seller that we used to move higher today
was right down here at 50. Right? See
this red line? Maybe you can see that.
Maybe I got to move this up. Right. This
is where these sellers are stuck. These
lows. Right. So we've got sellers stuck
at the lows down here. We've got a
seller currently stuck at 87s, but we've
got buyers stuck into 50. So a buyer
here 18, 50, and 72. So we want to be
aware of those guys because if they get
the chance to get out, break even or
near, there's a good chance they will,
right? Unless we see real aggression
stepping through. So if you got to think
about the psychology, imagine you bought
up here in these levels and you didn't
stop out, right? And you held this whole
thing. When it comes back up to that
level, what are you going to do?
Probably get out break even, right?
Probably just get out break even, right?
So that's like the psychology of the
market. We trap buyers at the highs,
which is what we sold into because we
weren't stupid. We weren't buying up
there. We bought here and sold here. You
could sell this low back down. Seller
got stuck down here. We come back up to
these buyers. They probably get out
break even. We might build liquidity.
Maybe it does this, maybe it does this.
We're in a D-shape. We don't [\h__\h]
care. We make our money. We move on.
Right? But we always respect who's
trapped in the market. Always, always,
always on multiple time frames, we
respect who is trapped in the market.
So, right now we build liquidity to the
upside. It's It's possible. It's
possible. Um
I don't know if this profile's off. Now,
I kind of struggling to trust this
because I don't know if it's adjusted
with this gap or not. But yeah, like if
we think about this, right, remember we
talked about the very beginning of the
day. This is the current week's volume.
Okay, today we've had no acceptance
under this, have we? So, all of this
overnight, no acceptance. Trend is still
very much down and we're coming into
this area, right? If we find acceptance
over this area, we're going to probably
attack this area here, 25,50.
There is a node here. There's a big
reason to get up there. It's very
possible we come up there. I would not
uh through that you could say 25,140s
through that 25,266s
through that 25,400. Do I think we're
going to do that today? No. Do I think
we're going to do that next week? Yeah.
I think probably next week. All right.
We might see something like this and
then a resell down into here. And then
the market will need to make a decision.
Are we going to have the 5day 200 day
cross and then we're going to start
trend lower? I don't know. We can judge
that when it happens. Right. What I'm
talking about there is when we see big
trades downside, remember we hit the 200
day. If we're going to go trend down,
we're going to need, you know, liquidity
to be built out in here, we're going to
need the 5day to come down here. We're
going to need to sell that and get the
cross. And then, and only then, can we
think about this node here
and trading under that to this node here
and this node here. And who knows if
they got really thin down here. I tell
you what, if we come down here, bucking
out. Uh I'm buying everything that
moves.
Everything that moves. Cuz that would be
what? 20 20% down off the highs.
Even that be that much. Might not even
be that much. 16% down. Yeah. If we come
down 12 12%, what are we now? We hit a
low of 9% down. It's not that much. If
we can get down there, I'd be a very
happy man.
Very happy man for multiple reasons.
Remember, the lower we go, the more
panic we get, the more opportunity we
get to buy in discount
for ETFs. I'm talking about mainly I did
start some swing longs yesterday, like
we talked about at the beginning of
stream.
Uh, I have Global Plus, Rick, but I
think you probably only need Global, but
I do have Global Plus. I got it in the
sale, though.
What indicator is that called? Um I
always Why can I never remember it? Twin
I'm going to post it for you. Twin Peaks
for Ninja Trader. It's It's paid. I'll
tell you now. It's paid. It's a paid
indicator. There's the link.
I think when my taxes come in, I'm going
to buy this course. I've lost more money
shooting the dark. Yeah, you're welcome
to join anytime you want. Do I help
learning one-on-one on course? I don't
really do we do I do do some help
privately for people but we don't really
do one-on- ones. I don't have the time.
But what we're trying to do this year is
a group lesson of an hour or more every
two weeks. So I do a group lesson every
two weeks and that's the chance where
students can ask any question that they
want and we review trades and set up so
we help people. But I'm always answering
DMs. All right? You you ask anyone in
chat who's been in my Discord, those who
reach out on DMs, I will take time out
my day to help people. I do not charge.
I just want I want you guys to do well,
right? So, it's not about the money. I
genuinely want you guys to do well, but
I just don't have a huge amount of time
on my hands all the time.
How many screens do I have? And how
different are these charts on order
flow? So, over here, what you're
watching, I have a one minute normal bar
chart. Then I have a 5 minute, then I
have an hourly, then I have a daily. In
front of me I have a one and a five and
a 30 for order flow on Ninja Trader.
Here above that I have my bookmap for
order flow with the DOM. And here I have
spy uh sorry I have ES spy QQQ and the
VIX. All right.
I never answer you. Have I never
answered you? Is that can't be true.
That can't be true. Oh yeah. He said
joking underneath is volume profile on
the right anchored to 9:30 open. Yes,
just read read read the uh nightbot. It
tells you it tells you.
Hey chat, is the course worth buying for
$699? Well, it's actually only $649 at
the moment, but everyone can tell you if
it's good or not.
What's my bias today? Bias today is
rotation. My bias today is rotation.
How do I put it on the right side? Right
here. Anchored volume profile placement.
Right. So, if you go from input to style
placement, right?
When does the Tyson trade come into
effect? Well, at the moment, we're not
at either IB. So, E ES is is at the IB
high, right? ES is at the IB high. We're
not there. So, we would need to see
remember 44s. What did we tell? I'm
going to have to remember these levels
where those buyers were stuck, right?
We're tapping into one now. So, 50s and
then 73s. So, the Tyson trade would come
into effect if we get stuck either
inside the IB or ideally for an IB
failure. So, ideally, it would be a
breakout and a failure back under and
then you could trade back down to V1.
But look at how everything's sloping
today, folks. D-shaped profile flat BWS
like over under blow zones
right 44s is where I said 44s to 50s so
his actual level is 50.25 25. Right. So,
see this reaction? We just talked about
this guy right here. See this guy right
here? We've just come short of him. So,
he's probably starting to try and get
out now. We had another buyer step in at
19s. All right. So, there could be a
failed push here. There could easily be
a failed push here, especially with the
divergence with ES, right? ES taking out
the IB high. So, ES might offer that
trade potentially. It still hasn't taken
out previous day high. has a reason to
go higher the ES, but if they're going
to do a rotation on ES, you'd want to
see this sort of break and then fail and
then come down into these.
But just lower your expectations today.
All right, we're we're in a rotational
market today.
This is not like the last two days where
we've been like gunning for three, four,
500 point trades. All right, it's it's a
different market today. Understand like
when to attack, when not. Last few days,
A+ setup, right? A plus setup. We
attack. We attack. We attack. We attack
today. BC setups.
How long I've been traded? Full-time?
Six or seven years. But like I said, I
started about 20 years ago,
but then had had another career for a
while. You consider any rotation trades
with D-shape? Yeah, D-shaped rotation,
but also think think about the daily,
right? We we it's a pullback day, right?
So, it's a pullback day, but we already
did most of this happened overnight. All
right, so it's very possible we just
sort of bugger about in here for a
while, right? Very, very possible we do
that and then next week we can see
what's what.
So, kind of like this is a fail. It's a
look below and fail, right? If you think
about where we open, look below and fail
back in inside bar, right? Look below
and fail inside bar. So there's your
first clue. Second clue is profile.
Third clue initial balance, right? IB,
right? Lots of reasons, right? Where's
previous day low down here, right? So
look below and fail. Previous day low.
Look below and fail. You can see we
looked below,
rejected, rejected, failed, reclaimed,
held. All right. There's your look below
and fail overnight. That's your cue to
go long. All right. What's the ultimate
target? Ultimate target would be
previous day high right the way up here
because that's the high previous day
right. So we're in inside bar in here.
So that is your first clue that it's
probably going to be choppy. The New
York session opened up where like here
right. So here to here is what I'd be
looking at. Maybe just here to here. And
here's the profile. Right. So all of
this can be chopped. I know that's a
huge range. It is a massive range.
There's no way of denying it. But all
this here can just chop all day long.
And what will it also do by doing that
on a Friday? It will burn the options
out, right? Burn all the premiums.
If they lift like we talked about, this
level is uh open to become attacked.
question, boss. Multiple dogeis backto
back signals uncertainty, but what else
can it signal? Um, that's kind of all
you mean a dogee both sides or do you
mean like a dogee high and then you mean
like a dogee low? I mean it just signals
liquidity being trapped here, trapped
sellers here, trapped buyers. If you
looked inside those wicks, that's what
you would see on multiple dogeis here.
Fair value basically. And you have to
wait for them to make a decision.
when I check MSTR.
Yeah, I'll check MSTR and Microsoft view
shortly. Let's just see if this gets
going here. So, there is a player up at
25,000 right now. ES through its IB. Can
we get up to the IB? So, we're through
that first guy. Remember, we're through
that first buyer. The next buyer that
got stuck was at 73.
So, if we think about what we did, this
seller down here caused the pain. This
is your higher low. This is bullish
right now. reclaimed gray box into next
gray box held gray box 73 would be the
next target because of that's where the
trap player is and through that run the
highs and then up here you got really
lucky you'd come all the way up here I
don't think we will do that today I
think this might be the max effort today
let me just check on the book to see if
anyone is up 25,000 is there anyone at
the 100 oh my god there is
anyone at 150
thin so 100 is a level on the Look, I
don't think we'll do that, but
who knows? Who knows?
Everyone's covering their shorts.
They're all going to keep getting
squeezed.
All right, so 73s. If you're long in
this, you know, 73s is a level to watch.
All right, I haven't said this today.
So, there's was 1,400 of you watching at
one point. We're just under 1,300 right
now. We've only got 400 likes. I want to
do giveaways as I always do, which means
you guys have got to do your bit. You
want to win some giveaways, free
courses, free Apex accounts, then you've
got to smash that like button for me.
Yeah. Uh the the bi-weekly group
training we do record and they get
posted for anyone that's in Discord. So,
if they're not live, if they're not
there, they can watch it back at any
time. Yeah, absolutely. And then Coupe,
he's not well this week, but normally
Coupe does a class every Saturday
morning as well.
link for the course. The link's pinned
at the top of uh chat right now. So, if
you click on that uh right
smart link, is that the right word?
Whatever it is, the courses are in
there. You want to do the beginner to
advanced course.
And am I going to take any trades today?
Well, I absolutely nailed this long
straight up. So, I'm just these are my
least favorite trades down here. So, we
nailed two longs today. So I was long
from
here to here and I was long from here to
here or wherever it was somewhere in
this. So it's two longs. I'm good with
that right now. I don't want to become
liquidity. So I'm just being patient
now. All right. For me personally, these
are my like I always talk about these
are my least favorite days when we build
liquidity. I like attacking the market
when we leave liquidity. And it's a
Friday and anyone that's joined me this
week will know like we have captured
thousands of points this week. Quite
literally thousands of points.
Yesterday, some of you caught a 330
point short.
Yeah, separate layouts for each of my
time frames. Correct.
Does the free course cover volume
profile? There is a little bit of volume
in the free in the free course. No, the
free course does not cover volume
profile. Sorry. Free course does not.
Definitely not. But there is stuff on my
channel for free. If you go to YouTube,
there's a whole section on volume
profile and order flow for free.
How do we get a chance to give away?
We'll do maybe we'll do a giveaway in
the next 10 minutes. So, failed that
high. So, never got to the 73s.
Trading back down to this gray box
again. Okay. And you can see, so we
cleared out this buyer who was stuck. We
never got up to this buyer and we're
trading right back down to this shelf
here at 60s with an imbalance here. This
is why I don't trade rotation. I do not
enjoy these moves. But if you guys like
edges, those of you who like rotation,
well, that is a failure again of the
high. We didn't quite make the IB high,
but ES has just done the IB high to VWAP
trade. We've missed it. We're almost
there. Like we said, might do a lower
high and come. There's There it is. If
we look at ES, it's done it very well.
The Tyson trade as we call it, right? IB
high clear out.
IB high clear out. And there's B1.
Bingo. Bango.
Gray box to gray box again. So this
node, we can thin this out a bit here
now. Starting to become a bit cleaner.
And if we lose this again, we'll
probably drift all the way back down
here again
as we just continue to rotate all day.
That is the objective of today remember
is to rotate and build out liquidity.
Norton's blocking my link. Yes, someone
else said that. Um, all right. Let me
just try this.
There you go. There's Tyson in chat.
Dark nougat. Well, I'm sure Dyson just
absolutely murdered that then.
The candle above my red line is an is an
order block. Line to the left. I don't
know what you're talking about. You're
talking about this. Oh, it's an order
block because it's the pivots. Oh, yes.
It's an order block
also known as supply where where a buyer
is trapped for anyone normal.
How do I would I determine we lost a
shelf for entry? Well, this was very
ugly. This was this was not an easy I
wouldn't call this an easy trade, but uh
if we came to the order flow, you'd
probably see buyers getting caught up
there again. There you go. So, here. So,
I'd say under here was the trigger,
right? Aggressive buyers, sellers paired
off. There's your trigger. Failed to
reclaim. There's more trigger. That's
probably it. Shift of delta positive to
negative.
And back down potentially down to 820s.
Now, if they lose this gray box, we can
keep fading all the way back down. I've
got value low at 26es on here. We have
it at 20. So, we'll see this area here
now a big node. And like I said, we
still have that player. 800 was a big
volume level. It's less of a big level
now because we paired off that delta,
but it was a big volume level.
I just think we're just going to chop
all day long here, folks. We're just
going to keep chopping.
Sorry for anyone normal. Yeah, it's me
being an [\h__\h] Doesn't matter what
what you call it. Doesn't really doesn't
matter. All right, this is developing
point of control. So, we're coming down
to these 820s. Like I said, here's the
edge of value again. So, they're trying
to bid off the edge of value because
we're in a D-shape. So, we're just
rotating that D-shape.
Uh for me, Miles, I look at both, but
one minute one minute when I'm looking
to execute, right? If I'm if I'm looking
if I'm looking to execute like down
here, I'm looking on the one minute. All
right. If I'm just looking to see where
where players have built up, I can look
on the five minute. But when I'm
executing, I'm going down into lower
time frame.
Yeah. 820. Beautiful here. Right into
that node. Right. Right into value area
low. Back to gray box. So the question
now is this. Right. Back to gray box. If
they sell gray box and they come under
820, do we come back to previous day
value area high? We know there is a
participant who got stuck today down at
750s. Right. So they come back down into
here. And do they come back down to 750
and let him out where that VWAP would
be?
Right. 750s
possibly. Possibly doesn't there's
there's lots of levels to get through
first, right? 20s previous day uh
current point of control. All right. So,
this can still be a very deep pullback.
Could be a very deep pullback. Could be
a very deep pullback. It could reclaim
and have another go at it again. Right?
Because we're in this. We're not in a
trend. We are not in a trend. There you
go. So, they're still bidding 20s back
to gray box. If they reclaim gray box,
they're going to go next gray box. They
reject this gray box. They're going to
try 20s again. Then they're going to try
800s. Then they're going to try 80s. And
then the player is stuck at 50s.
Remember down here, right? So, rotation,
rotation, rotation, rotation. You see
why I don't like it? Yes, my hourly
charts have just come back.
Wow. CME,
they just realized that they'd turned
data off for Trading View, had they? It
was nice of them to turn it back on.
There you go. So, Sam just took $300
trade off using the D-shape and trap
buyers at 950 using your insight. Thank
you so much. You're welcome. This stream
is going to get way too popular. Well,
probably.
It's probably going to piss off a lot of
people including prop firms because you
guys are going to well my hopefully you
guys are going to start start learning
how to make good money here by trading
good areas. So, gray box reclaimed now.
So, we're watching this node and through
that back up to where we just came from.
And I will have a look if there's some
imbalances up there. There are. So, a
seller came in here at 87. A buyer came
in here at 80. If they lift through 87
and 80, we will look for 900 and then
914. A big buyer is at 918. All right.
So, a big buyer is offside in 918 in
here. This is where a big buyer is
offside. Right. So, he's out of position
right now.
So
this move here, we'll have to see how we
react. If we do not get through that,
right, then he will remain out of
position. We can use that back down
again. If you're going to scout, like I
said, I'm avoiding all of this [\h__\h] I
This is not a market I like. But I can
read it for you. I just don't like
trading it. Don't enjoy it. Do not enjoy
it.
So I'll be watching here through 88.
Then I'll be watching 900. And then that
buyer who's stuck at 918. They're going
to try and lift towards him at the
moment.
All right. How are we doing for likes,
folks? How many likes have we got? Can
we do a giveaway yet? 1,300 of you
watching. Wow. Over half of you have not
hit that like button. Let's just get
this up to at least 800 likes. Ideally,
a thousand. And we do we do a giveaway
now. Maybe we'd do one giveaway now and
one giveaway in another hour.
I know it's it's crazy the growth of the
channel at the moment. It's insane. I'm
very very grateful for it. But I think
it's a mix of two things. Uh YouTube has
suddenly noticed me. And uh I think I'm
trading pretty well and that probably
helps you guys make more money and then
you tell your friends and then they make
more money and then they tell their
friends and it's one of those things.
All right, so back up to this level we
just talked about. All right, so 900's
coming up here. So 900 through that.
You're looking for that trapped trader.
If you're long, right, you want to trim
some into 900s, trim some into 918s and
then see if you get acceptance.
Otherwise, this can be another lower
high and come right down to Vpo, which
is at 60s right now. Right, right down
here. And if they fail 60s, they will
rotate back down here again. So, you're
going to need this gray box to hold. For
any of you who bought the edge of this,
if you bought the edge,
if you bought that, you need this to
hold. You want 900s and then that. And
then you're holding runners above that.
Above this, you will get going. Nice
hold there of that level. Beautiful. So
watching this now, if you're long on
this, you're watching this to take some
profits into 918s. All right, 918s is
where he's stuck. Keep telling you 900
and then 918s is where he's stuck. Then
if you can start printing above this
gray box, then like I said, this can
just be one of these and you might have
a shot at that. You might have a shot.
But again, this is your edge on the day.
This is where you're building volume
currently. No acceptance above, no
acceptance below. Your rotation is 943
to 8:25. So there's 110 120 points in
there.
Understand the type of day we're in. All
right. Until that changes. Until that
changes, that's the type of day we're
in.
You found me from Austin's podcast.
Nice. Yeah. Very thankful for Austin for
doing that with me. Good guy. He's a
good dude. I like him.
How do you know there'll be
consolidation before it starts? How did
you know the market was about to go into
balance? How can you catch it early?
It's about like we talked about, it's
about understanding like what the higher
time frame has done. So, if you think
about this week, if we think about this
week, I'm going to go daily, right? What
did we set up? Anyone who's been with me
for the last few weeks, well, there's
your gap fill. That's the efficient
market. That's your failed breakout of
range. All right? Here was most the
range. This is like a a balanced range
since the 5th of November that we keep
talking about. All right? No acceptance
below, no acceptance above. But finally,
fail breakout. Anyone who does WOFF,
there's your spring down to the bottom
side, fail to make a new high, break out
of that range, leave that range. What
are we going to do? All these guys who
are who are long are about to stop out
cascade effect. Right. Right. Huge sell
into what? Big pivot. All right. Not
just a big pivot on here. Yearly pivot.
All right. Yearly pivot. 200 day moving
average. We're going to bid off that. We
opened up the session here. So, GlobeEx
bid off the 200 day and we bid up to
here. When we're here, are we expecting
continuation right now when we've just
done a [\h__\h] ginormous straight down
move?
No, we're not. Are we expecting relief
to come too much higher in out of when
we've done this huge move in GloEx? No.
What are we expecting? Probably an
inside bar. Look below and fail. All
right. probably that we're going to
respect the nodes on the developing
week. All right. And then we can zoom
into the lower time frames hourly and
stuff to get get some edge. So when we
moved into the hourly, we knew right
that we had look below. We already
talked about it. Look below and fail.
We're probably going to see a drift up
into some of this consolidation. We know
this node here is absolutely massive.
And we have a low volume node in the
edge of shelf here. This is where we
keep getting stuck. So we're driving
into this. If we find acceptance over
this shelf, that's when we can get that
950 25,50s into here. If they're going
to keep going, then we can run these
stops up here. But we don't expect it to
be too big because here is the move
down. We expect this, we expect this,
right? And after that, they will decide
what they do with it. All right? So,
it's more about understanding what's
gone before us, like what what's
happened just before. Okay? So still
you're starting to drift higher now. So
we are through a big buyer and seller
just came in and paired off at 18. So
you're still watching for that 50s,
right? You're still watching for 50s.
You even 40s now. You got to respect cuz
it's the edge of value. But I think you
have a chance to drift higher here.
There is a buyer stuck at 50. So you
need to make sure you take some profits.
And if we start closing above 50s, you
will probably get a new high of day.
So here's the edge of value 40s. We've
got 50s next.
Show you what I'm looking at. We've got
50s next. We've got this buyer here
who's stuck. We're going to come and tag
into him. See, there you go. Tapping
into him. He's probably front running a
little bit of that. We have an imbalance
through that. So, the question is now,
do they end this auction here or are
they going to start to base out here and
attack up here into 70s again?
What was that high there? We just hit
47.
I think they're going to resqueeze this
and try and get into this 50 and see if
they get going here.
Hopefully you guys are learning with me
as we go. All right.
Which prop phones do I use? They're all
on my channel. My five main prop firms I
use, Apex, TakeProfit Trader, uh, Funded
Next, Lucid, and Traderify. Those are
the five main ones for me. Those are my
top five. Code FCT for all of those.
Other than take profit, you can use Code
Flow Zone. All the links down below. And
I've got a video on YouTube, which you
can watch, which which will explain
which prop firm is good for you based on
your trading style, your experience,
because they all have different
benefits.
England rugby. Yeah, I was watching Cole
Mara highlight all yesterday. Uh when
they were um Oh, Dan Cole and and Mara.
I was watching uh Mara and and um Danny
K. They did a a grillup session. That's
quite funny.
What are the gray boxes, guys? Gray
again. I I'm pretty sure I put it in
nightbot. Gray boxes are my volume
areas. All right. Are there areas of
volume where I know it's important?
Okay, here you go, guys. So, you've just
cleared out 50. So, you have to see if
you find acceptance now. You would want
dips to hold 50 down to 44s. The next
buyer who's trapped is at 74. Through
that, you are going to get a higher day
squeeze. All right. So, now this is
looking more and more possible. All
right. So, we just think about what
happened. They trapped down here again,
right into value, into rotation. They've
now thinned down, thin back up. If they
hold bids here now, this is possible,
right? Anything above this is a takerit
area into this. If they if you got very
lucky, they come up here. I don't think
we're going to do it today, but possibly
into here. Once we get above that, all
right, if they fail back underneath it,
guess what? that trade back down might
happen especially if we move value up
here and then we lose value and we can
rotate it again back to PC and VW up.
So you need to hold sort of 50s down to
sort of 40s here. 50s to 40s need to
hold bullish hold need to be there. If
they let go of that you're going to get
a move to 18 very very quickly. So if
you're still long you want 50s and 40s
to hold here. You do not want it
underneath 40s. It will drift down to
20s very quickly if they are going to be
nasty with it.
Is the 40s back into the 40s here.
Sorry. Every time it flicks like that,
it's cuz I have to get the chat up
because I don't have room.
[\h__\h] hell. It's amazing. Chat now
telling me what I need to do. Great.
Nothing's chang. It's not like we've
moved loads. I told you what's
happening, guys. It's amaz It's amazing,
man. It's amazing.
What brokerage am I using for my swings?
212 and for Here you go. Here's a pop of
five day. So, potentially now 2550s.
So, big delta there. All right. That was
a six. Was that 600 lot? who just came
in there. 789 lot buy side at at 980.
All right, that's [\h__\h] huge, guys.
All right, so 789
lot just came in by side at 980. So if
we come back underneath 980, we know
there is a 700. We're just going to call
him an 800 lot. Will be stuck there.
Okay, here you go. On this screen, it
only shows a 500, but it was uh on bookm
I can tell you right now it was
considerably more. Right. So potentially
I'll be locking in some profits here and
holding to see if you get a squeeze out
into here now. Right. So they set that
lower higher low sorry. So they've set
the higher low higher low held this base
rotated TP into here and then if you get
lucky you get these moves. Very lucky
would be up there. I don't think we will
do that today but we will see. Again
using orderflow here we now know where
people's pain points is. Look at this
guy on bookmap with me. This guy right
here 789 lot market buyer. That is a
huge buy order. Price will need to stay
above that. They might let it drift a
little bit lower, but if they start
losing this guy and he starts becoming
stuck, you will see a big sell. So,
we're coming back to test that level,
right? So, we're watching these now. If
these start to stay heavy, you will see
an IB collapse.
So, remember, you can mark out 80s,
basically IB, right? Just under IB. 80
is the big level. If we start rejecting
this, we can come right back down here.
So, we've just cleared this out. I'll be
watching these notes here and they can
let go this whole thing. That big buyer
came, the other big buyer came in at
50s. So, here you go. They're starting
to sell back down. They're going to test
this here into 50s. If they fail to
reclaim 80s, there's a sell. If they
reclaim 80s, there's a resqueeze.
It's just based on order flow. I'm
telling you what I'm seeing based on
order flow. All right. I know that
there's a huge player at 80s. So, that's
the big level here. Whether they reject
that or not, does he get comfortable or
not?
So, this is like the Tyson trade. It
might well set up here. There's lots of
buyers at the high. It just depends how
much further they want to squeeze this
or if they're done with it. Right. There
is a target up here if they really want
to come for it.
Here's 75s. Do they test 80s here? And
then does that buyer get out and become
a seller at 80 or does he just reclaim
and resqueeze?
There's 80 test. They're stacking here.
95 now has a 500 lot in it. We're
starting to see some big size. We're
back to 80s. They're they're putting
more liquidity higher here. So, if we
lift through 80s, we're probably going
to come to 995. getting starting to get
stuck here a little bit. 80s. They're
looking for 995 here on a lift. So,
reclaiming 80s. This is a big sensitive
area here now. Huge huge level now. This
is the most uh volume we've seen for
quite some time. Some big big players.
Big players. This is not retail. This is
big players deciding what we're doing
next, whether we're going to squeeze up
to 2550 or not. They're going to look
for 995 here where there's a 500 lot.
Here
we go. Try and lift to that 995. You can
see him on bit map above me. They just
fell short of him. Still 500 lot there.
Looking to get filled. A seller at 995
and then through that 25,000 and then
we'll probably get going to 25,50.
So 95. Let's see if they fill this guy.
Still not filled. He's legit. He's
staying on the tape. He's legit. 510 lot
here. He's moved up. He pulled. spoofer
spoofed it. Literally the moment he went
to get tapped, he pulled it.
Right back. What a nasty bastard. Right.
Back down to the 80s then. So, we've got
a big buyer who has been there at 80s.
All the time he's in position, he's
okay. If you start to see drifts under
this, it can get very, very nasty. Back
down to value area high potentially. But
that player so far is okay. That player
so far is okay. And they can drift up
here.
So if they put on a big old squeeze,
they can drift up here if they want to
put on a big old squeeze.
How much is bookmap monthly? I'm not
even sure. It's not very expensive.
No, I'm not currently in, guys. I'm not
currently in. I'm I'm watching. I'll
consider a fade if we come up here and
we start failing. I will consider a
fade, but I don't want to be front side
on it. I want it to perk out if we're
going to do that because it's possible
they want to be really dirty that they
come all the way up for previous day
high. So, I don't want to be front side
on something above IB, right? But if we
leave trap volume, if we come up here,
or even if we do this, this, this, and
this, there's a fade back down to there.
So, I will consider that move if we
leave this or if we poke through that
and we leave excess up here
and then we collapse back down. I'd
consider that. Otherwise, I'm not
touching it.
Where's that next node?
70s. Where's this?
2540s. Yeah, same level.
Okay. Okay, some buyers starting to get
caught at these highs a little bit, but
still no collapse back down. We're still
that 80s is still the big level, right?
980s is your big level.
Back to these 80s, back to this IB high.
We still have this big player. You can
see this big buy. Still comfortable
right now. So they tried to sell through
him. Couldn't get through him. He's
still comfortable until he's out of
position. There's no short trade here
because we can still lift. We have to
wait for it to be backside and him to be
out of position.
CBD still very very very strong. Very
strong.
Patient. Just patient, guys. Patient. If
you're long, it's no reason to sell.
You've taken a partial. You can try and
get up into that red box above you. But
I would not want it underneath this if
you were long. I will wait to see if a
short sets up for a rotation. You would
not want it under this if you're long.
How far do we need it down under? We
need a break of 80 and a and either a
retest of 18 to see sellers step in,
right? Or we just need a break and lots
of aggressive sellers start to step in,
right? It's not so much how far we go
underneath him. It's more like what
happens on the tape. Does he become a
seller? Does he become a seller?
You know, we can
They want to be really aggressive here.
Let me just do
projection on this. Give me a second
back. Measured move would also be to 40.
All right. A port a measured move is
also into 40s and 50s. So I think
there's a good chance we actually get
into here right now. It's also a
measured move on an hourly. There's a
good chance we get up into that right
now.
Oh, it's got a little caught there into
tens, but still buyers are comfortable
underneath. Right. So, we need the big
players out of position.
Why don't I like ranging days? I just
think they provide less opportunity.
It's just it's not my bread and butter.
I'll still make money from them like we
have this morning, but I'm not going to
size and be aggressive on a ranging day.
I am going to size and being aggressive
when we leave a range, especially a
multi-time frame range like a weekly or
a monthly,
which is why the last two weeks have
been so good. So, so good.
How can you get anchored volume profile
for free on NT or does it need to be
paid? Uh volume profile is free if
you're using prop firms on Ninja Trader.
Again, there's videos on my channel
teaching you how to do that. Go to the
volume and order flow section on my
YouTube. It's all there. All right. A
little bit of excess there at 10. Still
not underneath this key level, though.
We'll consider a short under this gray
box. I want to be very careful of traps,
but I will consider this play here under
here.
Starting to like maybe come in now.
We'll see. See if they defend it or not.
Here we go. Sellers at these lows. It's
all about how we react now down here.
Whether they get caught again.
Trying to bid up here. We might swipe to
60 here. Here's 80s. Watching this now.
Reaction here is key. What we do now is
key. We're at the level. It's what we do
now is key. They're out of position. Do
we swipe to 60s or do we pump to 95s?
Want to see us leave this box?
See us leave this box. Ideally, we leave
and retest it because that's going to
make it a little bit cleaner to trade.
If they come up to 90s and reject it and
come back under 80s, I'm also interested
at that point. They're stacking down at
60s and 57. So, they come up to 90s,
reject, snap 80s. They're starting to
stack at 70s. So there might be a swipe
coming here for at least like a 10 20
point fill. Not a lot. Ideally, we'd
love it all the way down into here.
Could be like a 40 point trade.
Okay, that guy at 70's just lifted and
moved to 55. So I'm still watching to
see if they reject 90 and then snap 80
for a trade here. That's my going to be
my entry. For those who don't
understand, if we reject 90 and break
80, I will consider a short entry. In
case I haven't made that really, really,
really clear. Until that point, I will
not consider an entry
for chat tells me off.
We don't do that, I will not be entering
the trade.
Here's
the test of 90
through 90s. No trade yet then. So, we
have to come back under 80s now and stay
heavy. Otherwise, there is no short side
setup. They still have unfinished
business if they want to run up.
Remember, there is a little imbalance to
98. I wouldn't really want to see that
filled though. There is a little
imbalance to 98. Let's uh have not
closed through 90s. That's good. More
buyers just got a little bit caught
there. Didn't feel the imbalance, but
let's see if we get back under 80s and
start letting go.
We will see. Vi
must not be front side, right? Because
if they have not finished yet, they're
going to move 50 points higher. So,
let's just see. Come on. But that might
be pausing me again.
Once we get out of this, we're going to
do the do the giveaway because I almost
forgot there. Almost forgot.
What option for Butmat? Uh just start
with global global CME data assuming
you're just trading uh uh ES or NQ.
If you're trading metals, then you're
going to need Comx data.
So you're Yeah, big gamma level. You're
saying SPX 6900. So we're not quite
there yet. SPX is at 892. So not too
far.
Very slow day. I mean, it's not too bad.
The range hasn't been too bad, you know,
off the uh low seven. Still 300 points.
It seems slow, but it's still 300
points, but remember, we did a lot of
the damage overnight. We did a lot of
the damage over the night, right?
They're back through. So, no no short
trade. They're probably going to come up
for these 25s. This is why we why we're
patient, right? Did we see this? Did we
see this? No, we didn't. All right. So,
they're going to clear out and try and
come up to that. So, anyone who's long
still from here, you still held this
gray shelf. You can still look you get
up into here. This is why I say until we
see this, we don't do anything. All
right? We don't front. We do not guess,
right? We wait to see participants be
stuck. No one was stuck, right? So,
they're going to lift.
See the patients? Nothing happened. We
wait.
Boot map is tick is tick by tick. It's
not a time frame. It's not a time frame.
It's like tick by tick.
More buyers stuck at tens there. More
buyers at 25k here. Thanks. Be much
better now if they just lift it up in
here and get explosive. It would be much
much better. Here they go. Great. All
right. Good for you longs. All right.
So, you want to be TPing out into this
here, please. Into this red red level. I
will tell you, I think 44s is a big
level. If you get through that, there is
an argument.
There are some stops. I'll tell you
where the stops are. Stops are at 59,
65,
96,
130,
182. All right, but I would be taking a
big chunk here. If you got very lucky,
you'll get this red line, but I would be
taking a big chunk out into here,
please.
They're still lifting. Here you go. Into
the red block. Into the red block.
Previous day open is at 61, by the way.
S&P almost there. One of you were
talking about that level on SPX. So,
we're almost there. Big buyers trying to
step in here. Uh, next big shove up. If
they leave excess and track these
buyers, there's going to be a short back
down. If they hit those levels,
sellers coming in here at 24s, this is
starting to be interesting here. This is
where we get excess.
What was that? level 10 and 25K.
So buyers came in at 10 and 25K. If we
start losing that, it might be a good
sign that this thing's ready.
Transition here from buy to sell. So you
can see it on the book. Look at the high
of day. We didn't quite make this red
box. We got very very very close. Uh
this shelf now sort of been developed
more like this, but I really want it
under the lower side. But we can put
this like this, right?
The flow zone indicator available for
trading view. It is everything on the
website, guys. flowzone trader.com.
Everything's on the website.
Just passed another email. Appreciate
the stream, sir. You're welcome.
No, I'm not long, unfortunately. You
know me, mate. Range rotation not my
thing. I I'll wait for a short to set up
now, if anything.
Why did I put the gray box at 980?
Because of the volume we built out. The
volume. You see how we go? We think
about this. Where where's the gray
boxes? All right. So, here gray box. All
right. And we know like I talked about
there was a huge buyer there, wasn't
there? We talked about him. Huge buy
there.
Huge buy there right here. Look how big.
Huge buyer. 600 lot market. I think it
was bigger than that according to
bookmat. But you know it was a lot. It
was a lot. So that's the pain point
underneath there. That buyer will become
a seller. If he's probably if he's
smart, he would have sold into some of
this push already.
This is the measured move on the hourly
as well that we talked about.
I can take you down to show you what I
was talking about. If we think about a
measured move on an hourly from this
pullback, if we think about this as a
hourly bull flag from this high to this
low, we're into this measured move 47.
So you can call it 50. All right, into
that red block, right? So we're
completing a measured move as well. So
we've got confluence that up here the
auction might start failing. We don't
want to be front side on it, though.
Right. Big seller back on the books.
Same guy as before that spoofed because
it's the same size. 709 lot 25,030.
Any specials for bookmat? What do you
mean specials?
A code or something? Is that what you
mean? For cheaper? I don't know. Um I'll
have a look. I don't really do it, mate.
Um might have one, but I don't know what
it's going to give you off. Sorry.
Yeah, I'll post it in chat.
There you go. Let's put that.
Okay, back down to this gray box again.
Buy here at 85 again. 100 light 85.
Remember 80 is the big level. 80s is the
big big big big level.
Same story as before. If we've now got
excess up here, if we leave this gray
box, this trade to here and here is
possible.
Right? If this just trapped all the
balls, this will offer it until we come
underneath and reject or at least
underneath and I see follow through. I
will not be playing short side. It can
still hold this and still try and do
this. All right. It's still front side
of the move, isn't it?
Right. We have not seen that yet.
We might not see it at all. It's very
possible.
I really want to get a trade here so I
can just do a uh giveaway for you guys.
Should I just set the giveaway now? Oh,
look at this guy just jumping in. Seller
just came down. He's chasing the market
down at 25,000. What are you doing,
mate? 100 lot chasing it down.
It's weird. Weird. Someone being
aggressive. Someone's being aggressive.
All right, down we come.
He's come back on the book at 25,000
again here.
Still watching these 80s for me. Edge of
Gray Box. Watching these 80s.
So this guy, aggressive guy stepped in.
So 87s, they're now bidding. Where's
this guy underneath 65s? Yeah, I still
think there's a chance under 80s. I
think think we change trade 65. Still
watching this now to see if we get a
short here. Do we get sort of a cliff
short here? Here it comes. Here's the
80s. Big level here, folks. This is
where the buyer was stuck. If if we
trade under him, I'm going to be looking
for shorts down towards 65. We've got to
get under his level. He is at 80s.
Under 80s, we can get a partial into
1765. Here's 80s. 80s. 80s. 80s. 80s.
80s. Wait and see if we crack this now.
They're getting very aggressive down
here. Come on then. Are we going to do
it? Are we going to do it? Oh, do you
want to give Alex's play or not?
So, watch this same rotation now. 90 and
25k to see if they reject and then come
back under 80 for the sell. Vo now moved
up here as well. So, big point of
control is now at 80 because his volume
was so [\h__\h] big, right? Here's the
retest of 80. They're still bidding on
80.
And there are some passive bids down at
70s which we can fill. If we push up,
fail this imbalance and then sell
through. I will be joining short.
Didn't quite get to 90s. They got close
back to 80s.
Think we can wash to 70s and then snap
here. If we can just start going.
They're still bidding 80s. Someone's
flashing 25,000 now.
So 90s and 25k have to reject here and
then we have to come under 80s and then
we get the sell
otherwise no trade. No trade. If they
start bidding back above this and 25k
obviously we're going to come back up
all the way up to here again. So it mean
the shelf is held at 80s right? You can
see the 80 level massive level. So back
above here 25k retest here. Big big big
level.
Not just because it's a whole number.
There was quite legitimately a big
player up here.
Yes, still holding his IB as well. So,
we're in sync. Vick's found a bid yet?
Not really.
1850s. It's trying.
It's trying at the 1850s
at 25s. Is he? Yeah, that 700 lot back
up there again. He's playing games, that
guy.
I mean, he'll get filled if they start
getting above 25,000. There's an
imbalance up there. So, the imbalances
are at 14 and 25. So, he's trying to
sell sell into the imbalance. So, we
still got to wait for the 80s break
otherwise nothing. So, still above
25,000 now. Value area high for me on
Ninja Trader being tested based on
Delta. They're going to try and
resqueeze this now. So, still no trade.
Up we go. 25s
and they might lift this into this red
box again. And if they get through the
red box maybe up there. It's asking a
lot. Where's SPX? It's not quite there.
Almost there still.
So just filled that guy.
Look, he just moved up. He's at 30s now.
The 700 lot. But we just filled the
imbalance into 25.
700 lots at 30s. He's spoofing all day
long. Same player as before.
Same player as before.
Still waiting for the same levels for
me. No trade otherwise.
How do institutions scalp? Uh they use
high frequency uh robots is how they
scalp. All right, he's still at 30s.
Probably want to fill him, I guess.
Up to 25K again. We have buy side
imbalances here that they can try and
bid on.
It's getting tight here. It's going to
make a decision soon. Don't care which
way. I'm not going to play the long. I
will play the short if we let go. I want
to be very careful of a trap short now.
But if we get one, two, three drives and
a failure a bit like we did here. It
would be nice for this move back down to
here. We're not going to get that many
points out of it though. So, I have to
think about is it actually worth it.
It's not bad though, is it?
60 odd points. 50 60 odd points. We'll
see. We'll see.
It's a one minute chart that you're
looking at. One minute chart.
Should I just get this ready?
up because it's taking a while.
Let's give away an Apex account. Code
FCT, best code to use on all your prop
farms. Other than take profit trader,
you can use code flow zone. Type FCT
once in chat now and we'll pick a
winner. Okay, maybe red box still.
Yeah, still into this. Into this looks
good. This this 700 lot's a spoofer.
He's a complete spoofer. I don't trust
he's going to be filled at all today. He
will be a buyer on the book. Uh trying
to lift. So he's trying to attract price
to him and he's just lifting higher and
higher and higher and higher. He's a
complete spoofer. So he's now moved up
to 2545. I don't believe he's real at
all. Not at all.
Patient, patient, patient, patient,
folks. Patient, patient, patient,
patient.
It's still not there. Got close.
Tell you what, while you guys do that, I
don't want to miss the trade, though. I
need the bathroom. I need a coffee. All
right. Hopefully, this doesn't go
without me. I'll be right back. Wait
here and give away
Okay, into red box. Nice. Let's pull
this winner.
Let's pull this winner. One of you can
win.
Please don't spam, guys. Please don't
spam. All right. Five, four, three, two,
and one.
Massive red fan. That better be Arsenal,
not United. Otherwise, you're not
winning. That is a United fan. You are
banned from winning.
I'm joking, of course.
Massive red fan. Are you here?
Are you here? Let me know you're here in
chat. Did they just fill this guy? Oh,
he's legit. He got filled. That 700 lot
got filled at 45s.
Finally got filled. Liverpool. Oh, well,
I like Liverpool. That would do. Uh, all
right. All you got to do shoot me an
email info@flowzontrader.com.
Send me a screenshot of you logged in
and uh we will get you set up with a
free Apex account my friend. You can see
we are still lifting up. Look at this
700 lot now up here. Huge huge huge
level. Uh previous day open is up here
at 61s. You can see some transition
starting to happen up here. So, let's
see. Uh,
let's see.
Alex, reach to take profit. See if
they'll let you do some giveaways. Be
unreal. Yeah, I will. I mean, they never
reply, but I'll try again, especially
now we've grown a lot.
What is FCT? Flow zone traders. People
were typing it in chat to try and win
the competition for a free Apex
giveaway, which massive red fan just
won. Right.
How long we got? 30 minutes. So, we'll
give it another 20 minutes. We'll do
another giveaway for a free course. Be a
beginner course. Not the 20hour course,
just an introduction to trading course.
Right, this guy got filled at 35s. A
buyer at 35s, buyer at 45. If we let go
of that, they're probably going to trade
tens again pretty quick. Not sure if
they want previous day open first,
though. So, we're under 35s. They just
reabsorbed. Still a buyer on the tape at
the moment. They're getting pretty Oh,
Vicks got absolutely hammered there.
that just got absolutely wrecked in the
last 10 minutes. Let go of those uh 50s.
So, definitely supply zone up here
and we're starting to develop a bit of
node here. It's a bit early. There might
be a trade down to here starting to
develop, but under there is where I get
way more interested if we let go of it.
So, starting to see this. They can come
up here if they really want. Might be a
trade down to here. That would be
counter trend though. uh the rotation
would be underneath this and you can see
we keep moving
value higher at the moment so you'll be
very careful but this I would consider
three drive kind of territory so it will
probably perk out sooner rather than
later unless they want to do something
absolutely mental with it and go for
previous day high which you just don't
know with these lot we've been very
aggressive both sides this week like I
said it's likely to be very aggressive
okay I just see Apex just announced an
80% sale. So those that missed the 90
80% sale now just announced on Apex. You
can use code FCT over there.
Deleting my emails here. Absolutely
full.
All right. This player is not being let
out at 45s right now. You see this? We
just reattempted to come up into him.
This 700 lot is trapped at high of day
right now. The other guy who's got big
size is at 35. So, it's a big battle
here.
They are definitely trapped up here at
45s and 35s. If we start moving away
from them, if we start moving away from
them,
another big seller coming on here at 50
432 lot. [\h__\h] me. We're seeing some
serious size today, folks. You just
wonder, does does the ES want previous
day high? Spy already had it. QQQs has
already had it. Does ES want it? The
cash markets have it. Do we want up
here? Do we actually want that? Let me
see how big IB would be.
It's going to be one and a half, isn't
it? It's going to be
168. Okay. Can't rule it out. Cannot
rule it out.
Oh, thank you. Who just gifted me? I've
just seen that. I've obviously missed it
in chat. Thank you. Who was that? Jeff
Morris.
Very kind, buddy. Thank you very much.
700 lot was a buyer. Yeah, it was a 700
lot buyer. That's how we talk about
people getting trapped. It was a 700 lot
buyer, right? Because you have a 700 lot
seller. Remember what we talked about an
auction being completed? We have a 700
lot limit seller, but we have a 700 lot
aggressive buyer, market order buyer.
Seller doesn't get filled unless
someone's willing to buy it. Right?
That's the delta, the buy delta. That's
your delta.
But we have to have both aggressive
buyers, aggressive buyers and passive
sellers or aggressive sellers and
passive buyers on the book.
Waiting to see. I just wonder are they
just going to do something real nasty?
Right back to that same level. There's a
400 lot up here at 25,050 now as well.
Previous day open is at 60s, folks.
Yes, not too far away from previous day
highs. An incredible comeback. 935 be
previous day high. You're like, you
know, 12 points away from it or
something. Vick still getting hammered
lower. Big old squeeze on up here.
Big old squeezy grinding out of all of
this.
Sellers not getting their way. They're a
bit unhappy at the moment up here.
They're a little bit unhappy. They're
just walking this higher. How's Delta
looking? CBD still very aggressive.
Very very very aggressive there.
What are you guys saying? Chat
who buys up here? uh
institutions, people positioning for you
know big big trades, liquidity
providers,
all sorts.
Yeah, Hood. I'm swing long on Hood as
some of you will know. Uh started that
position yesterday.
Uh, how much am I up on it now? Let's
have a look.
Oh, yes. I'm up 15% on it.
I was up last night on it. So, if we
come down here, this is one of the
advantages of being in my Discord. So,
last night I started swinging positions.
There you go. Nice start to Hood. So, I
told them yesterday starting on Hood
into this golden pocket
and we were looking at some other stuff
as well. I bet as well. So, I've started
long and started making some nice money
on those already. Really good. So, I'm
up 15.35% on Hood, 30% on Apple, 6.77%
on Meta, 6.82% on uh Bitcoin Core, 3.2%
on Oracle, which is just a very small
piece because I don't love that stock,
but I do think it's due a little bit of
relief.
Okay, so that 300 lot, we now have a 700
lot and a 300 lot. See 700 lot and a 300
lot buyers both caught up here. This is
a big level here as well. 35 under that
we've got this imbalance and then we
might flush back down into 08s and then
VPO down here again. So there might be
something coming soon here.
We have definitely caught those buyers
at the highs so far. Don't know if we've
completed the move, but there might be a
deeper pull back into these 10 and 55k
coming here. Might be a trade from here
down to here starting to set up.
We will see. Here we go. Here we go,
folks.
It's the 20s. Can we get tens
to tens? Come on.
Partial here. Waiting to see now if we
can trade through tens to the 500s. I
It's just cuz those guys got caught the
higher day. Like we talked about
imbalance here is at 10 down to 98. All
right. They might well hold this
imbalance. We do not want it back above
33s. All right? If you took this with me
short, you do not want it back above
33s. 33s is the start of where the
buyers got caught. I will not hold it
above 33s. It will be a resqueeze for a
new high of day. So, all we did there is
trade their pain from here to this
imbalance. We're coming back to their
pain. We need to reject this. We reject
this. I'm going to look for lower all
the way down into uh 25K and 2580. Okay?
It's what I'm looking for. Hopefully
that's making sense to you. Just being
patient here for this trade. Really want
it to reject 33s, come down to 25K, and
then wash to 79. Be a nice trade.
Don't knock me out here, you [\h__\h]
35's being tested.
Come on.
Don't want it back above 35s. Above 35s,
I'm out. Like base above 35s is the
imbalance being tested here at 38. If
they close this candle up here, I will
close the position. They have just
removed all the liquidity higher above
apart from 45. So, I think
still look okay here. Still no close
above 35. So we've poked the imbalance
and that's it. Come on, wash this. Come
back down to 25K.
I tell you what, my stop is now going to
38 on the money. On the money or 3825,
that's my stop. Now I'm playing for this
gray box to reject to go down to the
next gray box. If they don't do it, they
don't do it. That would be me done for
the day if they don't do it.
So there's an imbalance here at 10 down
to 98s
and then under that we can trade to 84s.
Come on. One big trade. One big trade to
end the day. Collapse this [\h__\h] thing
for me. I'm going to cover some into
here if I can. I've already taken a
partial here. We've rejected gray box.
I'm looking for here. And if we collapse
this, I will look for 54s and down. So
you guys always want this drawn on,
don't you?
I'm short here. I'm partial into this
because it's an imbalance and I would
like a cover here. All right. And if I
get lucky, I'll get this and this. This
would be ideal. If we reclaim 38, my
stop is at 38.25 right now. We have an
imbalance there. I do not want it to
trade through that imbalance. Make that
as obvious as I can.
So, three drives happened. One, two,
three. Looking for the backside fade
back down into here. So first T next TP
will be here towards 25,000 and then
underneath 80 remember I think we can
have some fun and I will consider an ad
under 80 if we stay heavy.
Going to flip this the other side just
so you can see price action better.
Okay, so TP1 is top of this gray box.
We've already taken a little bit, but
really I want to get top of this gray
box. Want this move here. I want to kind
of wash these imbalances. Do not want
this. Keep bidding in front of this
imbalance.
Come on, baby. Get under those tens and
under the 25k. Stop bidding in front of
it, you [\h__\h] This guy's being
aggressive at 20s. Go away. Go away.
Go away. Stop it. Stop it.
Stop being aggressive. Get out of the
way.
Back on the 20s. Trade through the tens.
Trade 25s.
They're rebidding 05s. He's pulled 05s.
Good. Go on. [\h__\h] off now. [\h__\h] off. Get
scared and drop it.
Someone's playing games at 15s to05s
like flashing in and out, in and out, in
and out. Now walking it up. There's
still a buyer on this tape being a bit
of a bit of a sausage.
He's being a bit of a sausage. We just
need him to stop stop playing games.
Just let this drift down to 25 so we can
hit a decent TP there.
Here we come. Here we come. Here we
come. Move your 05 bid. This same guy
playing games here. Same guy. Five to
15s and then walking up every time it
gets close.
Same guy. If we don't drop underneath
this, I will cut. I don't want to
[\h__\h] get swiped out here if he's
going to be a knob.
giving it a chance. We got to get under
the 10 and 25k. So that the big buyers
stepped in at 10 and uh 25k underneath
us and the big buyers above us stepped
in at 35 45 and 50. Right? So we're
trading between those lots. Those guys
who keep getting stuck. So I'll show you
on here again. I might get [\h__\h]
lifted out of this right now. So, we got
a big buyer here and big buyers down
here. So, these guys are stuck. These
guys are in the money. We need to get
underneath this and we will leave all
these buyers out of the money. But this
auction looks good. This high day of
auction looks good. If they just stop
being clowns trying to like force it up
here, we'll be all right. But if they
force it up, I will just cut it. And I
won't have another go. It's a Friday.
It's fine. I'm out here on that on that
lift up.
Sorry, guys. had a go. Had a go. We got
20 points out of it. Stopped in the
money.
What's my luck? They're going to trap
me. Wash me out by the tick and [\h__\h]
go again.
How's your luck, Alex? How is your luck?
How is your luck? Well, we had a go at
it. We had a go at it. I don't want to
sit through this lift.
Yeah, they're trying to lift. There's a
little imbalance here.
37 38. Here they come. They're going to
lift and test these guys who were stuck
above. I'm probably done.
I'm not going to have another crack at
it.
That was it for me.
Been a really good week. Been a really
good week. Really good day.
I think the auction at the high looks
good. Honestly, that is it's just this
guy keeps stepping in and now we've
reprices 34s and holding if we let go of
that because they've just developed a
node here, but I don't think I'm going
to have another shot. This is trade
three for the day. So, I'm three for
three. This one didn't make any money
though, really.
It's [\h__\h] tempting.
It's tempting. It is so tempting right
now. Not going to do it.
Not going to do it. Do you know what?
I'm going to set up a giveaway instead.
Otherwise, I'm going to look at this
screen and I'm going to con convince
myself to do something.
I'm only human.
You guys do it. Do it.
No, I've had a go at it. I've had a go
at it. There's There's been a buyer on a
tape until he [\h__\h] off.
You know, the fact that he saved it
twice
Oh, the mind games of trading in the
mind games is trying to [\h__\h] lure me
in right now. It is trying to lure me in
to have another go.
I don't fear success. No, no, no. Don't
you [\h__\h] like try and lure me in.
Don't you try and lure me in. No, no,
no, no. Right, we're doing a giveaway.
Right, type course in chat. It's a uh
it's for the introduction course and
it's just a two-hour course. If you've
never traded before, it's good for you.
Finish that course. It does give you
$100 off uh the main course, the 20our
course. You can always give it to a
friend. So, just type it in chat once.
No, no, no, no. Not, not doing this.
We're still We're still absorbing here.
Until this guy's done with it, I need to
be careful. I like the auction at the
high. I think it looks good. The only
thing I'm wondering is like, you know,
the problem is we've still got previous
day high up here and ES is not that far
away. So, I'm just wondering, do they
are they trying to just have one little
swipe up and lift?
Let me just Maybe they want to run this
guy out.
Maybe they want to run that guy out on
ES first. I don't know.
The auction at the high looks really
good on NQ though.
Who's left to run
61s? Did we run that?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh. That's what
they're looking for. I've missed it. Oh
no, we've run it. What am I talking
about? Okay, it's just this block.
It's getting tight. You might get it,
guys. You might get it. It's the same
move. So, if you if you're taking this
TP1's into here to 25K, all right,
underneath 2580, there is a chance
you're going to [\h__\h] get it. There's
a
It took me out by five ticks or
something. All right, it's back down to
this imbalance. You're watching this,
right? This has to let go where this
buyer was 25,000 and 10 to 25,000. All
right, this has to let go. If that lets
go, this 2510, you should get this 25K.
I'm trying to move this up. If 2510 lets
go, you should get 25K. If 25k lets go,
you're looking at 90s and then 80s. If
80s lets go, you're going to have a lot
of fun on the back side of this move.
All right. [\h__\h] me. Well, what can you
do?
All right. course winner coming up. Five
or three, two, and one.
Um, Samir Cay Ced,
I'm really sorry. I've probably said it
like an absolute imbecile. Samir Cayed
2024, are you here? Look, watch these
tens, folks. If you trade through twins,
your next target's 25K. If you trade
25K, your next target is 80s. Under 80s,
you can get fun. Nice. Congrats, Semit.
I'm going to make a note of your name.
All I want you to do is email me
info@flowzoneontenttrader.com.
info@flowzonerader.com.
Send me a screenshot of you logged on to
your YouTube and I will sort you out
with a free introduction course.
Here you go then. All right. Did you hit
25s?
Yeah. Basically, you just got 25. You
can see this imbalance being filled now.
Uh 25k is where that big buyer was that
I showed you. All right. under that you
should go 80s, right? You can see this
under this guy now 25k. If you trade
under here, you can look 90s and 80s. Oh
my god.
If it wasn't a Friday, eh, I probably
would have had another go and just felt
like I've done enough.
All right, so this is the trade. Same
trade, folks. It's literally the same
trade. It's the gray box trade. All
right. So TP here
is uh 90s now top of this gray box. And
then you're looking for under 80s,
right? Under 80s. I will tell you now,
if you see this, this will do this. You
can have a really nice winner here. You
might give you an ad possibility or this
trade up down to here. Be over 100
points to end stream on a Friday to end
the week. I'd love it if you guys get
that.
I'm only human guys. I like you can see
the raw emotion. Here you go. Here comes
the test towards the 80s. So you want to
be peeling a lot off here please. You
want to be peeling a lot off here. You
can always read on if we stay heavy
under 80. So this was the position of
that big buyer. We've just tapped into
him at 80. If you stay heavy here now
you're going to look for a trade all the
way down to 928. So maybe you can peel
some at value 57s. But under this gray
box, ideally you're going to get 27s,
but most of it off into 80s, please.
All right, so this is what I mean. So,
whoever [\h__\h] moaned and bitched
earlier about I don't call stuff, like I
really do. I call so much stuff for you
ahead of time, and I give you the
reasons. And that's the difference
between staying with me on this stream
and hopping between streams going, "Any
trades? Any trades? Any trades? Tell me
when you trade, tell me when you trade."
No. be on this stream, learn why, what
we're looking at, and why. And then even
when I don't get it, you [\h__\h] lot
are, and that's all that matters, right?
Still put in a lower high here. That was
a nice failed follow through. Great
auction of the highs like we talked
about. Massive trap selling at the
highs, right? This is what you want to
see. Huge trap selling at the highs like
we talked about. We auction away from
the highs. You put in a lower high. My
stop. I was worried they were going to
run me out cuz this buyer kept stepping
in. But once he got trapped here in this
gray box, you trade away from it to the
80s. All right. Right to the 80.
Very exact cover point that 80, wasn't
it? Very, very exact cover point. Now,
ICT guys looking for it to run this or
whatever. No, you you need to respect
the actual level. 80 was where he kept
bidding earlier. The exact level.
Yeah. So, W's in chat if you got that. I
think lots of you got it. Let me have a
look. D.
Yeah, lots of you getting this. That's
great to see. That is fantastic to see.
Oh, that every Friday I always seem to
end a stream where I don't get the
trading you guys do. It's cuz I'm so
cautious on a Friday. I don't like the
idea of giving anything back. This is
getting a little bit wonky on the book
map here, guys. What is going on?
This is getting a bit wonky. Be careful
here. Make sure you've paid yourself
some money.
No, guys, it's not. Look, it's that it's
not that anyone's getting to me.
Honestly, it's not. It's just like I
wish it's not about me. It's not going
to make a difference to me. It's going
to make a difference to like the guys
that are like, "I want this. I want
this. I want this. I want this." Like,
"Tell me when. Tell me. Tell me when."
Like, it's going to make a difference to
those guys. It doesn't affect me. I
could never stream again and I know how
to trade. I'm going to be quite
comfortable. I can travel the world the
rest of my life and trade. And that is
ultimate freedom, right? I don't need to
do anything else. I want you guys to all
be able to do the same thing.
Pass my first eval following you. I'm in
tears. I'm a single mom of teens with a
mortgage I need to pay. Thank you.
Learning lots, April,
hiing five, April, way to go. Great
work, April. Love to hear it. Love to
hear it. All those single moms out there
working hard. Congratulations. It's
great.
Great. I love to hear it. That's great.
So after all that any trades? Yeah, I
there's three trades today. I don't I
don't know. I don't get it. Right. Here
are the three trades today. Long. These
are the trades I actually got. Long
up into here. 100 plus points. Okay.
Short. I had to cut that early. Why?
Because I was trading an account which
has consistency rules. Short from was it
here? Did we go short again? No, we
didn't. We went long again. What am I
talking about? Left the shorts. Long
from this trap. No, that's a short long.
Long from this trap. Pull this move back
to here again. Right. It's like another
100 point. Uh, all right. And then left
all the chop out in here. If we didn't
get knocked out here, we would have
lifted all the way up here. And then I
just had a go at this short and I didn't
get much out of it before break even.
What did I get out of this? Like 20
points, 18 points or something. That's
all I got. Oops. And then you guys are
in it here. So you want to see this.
What you will need now into lunch is a
new lower high, right? A new lower high.
And this this is where you make good
money. You must respect this. Okay? Do
not have an expectation below this. If
it does snap this and come down, by the
time you'll get there, you will have
cash VW up. They will be covering into
that. A trap can absolutely live in this
level. All right? If they want to be
dirty, right, and they decided they're
not finished with it, they will do that
in this level. So, that's what I would
be aware of uh throughout lunch if
you're going to hold this short through
lunch in the afternoon. But, you should
have paid yourself no matter what,
right? Let me just read the last few
messages before I get out here.
Single dad here, two kiddos under 12.
Great job, April. I love it, guys. Like,
all you guys, it's fantastic. If you can
make this a secondary income for you
guys, it gives you the freedom to be
with your children as well. It's great.
Alex, you're the best. I'm 95% dedicated
to being here and learning from you
every day. And the other 5% would be
traveling trader, and that's only for
his options insight. That's awesome.
There's lots of traders out there. I'm
not saying don't look at other traders.
What I'm trying to stop is the amount of
newbies who will watch a stream for 2
minutes and then go for another stream
and then go for another stream and then
go for another stream and then go to all
they're looking for is someone to give
them something that you can't learn that
way. You cannot learn that way. You just
need to pick a style. It doesn't need to
be my style. You can there's other good
mentors out there. If there's another
product you want to trade, go with them.
I won't be offended. As long as you guys
are happy and make money, that's all
that matters, right? It's you that has
to look yourself in the mirror at night
and go to bed. So, if you're happy with
how you're progressing, that's great.
Please explain why the target of 80.
Well, other than it being initial
balance, it's because it's where the big
buyer came in.
All right. Earlier today, right, this
guy here was a huge buyer, right? Right
here. 592 lot. He was actually 700 lot
altogether. All right. this buyer here,
we trade back down to his level. We
don't expect to trade under him, right?
So, we partial out into him. So, we're
using these buyers who are caught to
these buyers here over a thousand lots
caught from 45 and above. All right?
We're using them to trade down fill some
imbalances down to this buyer. Now, if
this buyer is still there and willing to
absorb the tape, the answer right now is
yes, then we're going to expect the lift
back up. So, we cover into him. It's why
we have to respect. So here we had
initial balance point of control and a
huge buyer. Are we going to expect price
to go lower? No. So we are going to
cover into him. If we go lower and
reject it, we can add back on in size.
Right? So we trade level to level
especially in a rotational market. It is
so so important that you understand
that. Do not have these huge
expectations. If we got beneath this,
right? Let's say you took 60 70% off
here and we traded under and we rejected
this. You could have put that money back
on and look for that. But we didn't.
Instead, we've come right back to here.
And I tell you what, if this guy's going
to be dirty like I talked about, they
might finish this move. They might even
do this. They might be really disgusting
and do that. I don't know. It's a
Friday. Anything's possible with the
options, right?
You're welcome everyone.
Should we huddle the short? No,
definitely not. Right. You've hit TP.
It's reclaiming levels. You I definitely
wouldn't be holding it. Not at this
point. Not just rip back out. Back up.
Thanks, guys. So many kind words here.
Really appreciate it. Second day here
and paper traded on your guidance and
analysis. This is gold. I appreciate it.
Um, learning heaps in 48 hours. That's
awesome. That's awesome.
So 592 was an outstanding buyer on the
book. He wasn't outstanding.
He'd already been filled. All right. So
he'd already been filled which means
he'd created volume. If there
see how
I was trying to think how to explain
this to you. Okay. If
all right we went over this earlier but
I'm going to try and help you. Right. If
there is a limit seller here. All right.
Limit seller here. These are market
orders buying. That's aggressive
activity. We move aggressively. Delta's
aggressive. Look, 741 because of this
aggressive buyer. We aggressively move
away from there. When we come back to
this same area, we expect him to show
up, right? Because look what happened.
We moved away, we came back to him.
Sellers got trapped. We move away, we
came back to him. Sellers got trapped.
We move away, we come back to him. We're
going to assume he's still there. We're
going to make some assumptions to
protect ourselves that he's still there,
right? Level to level. We're not going
to assume he's not. We're going to
position oursel so that if he's not
there, we can get runners all the way
down. Or if he's not there and we retest
it, we can add back in. But we are going
to make the assumption that he's still
there based on this node, right? This
node right here is telling you there's a
good chance we're going to bounce off
it. And guess what we have? And now
we've ripped through everything else
because unlike you guys who were smart
enough to get short up here with buyers
stuck and trade back down to this, guess
what everyone else did? Everyone else
tried to short this down here without
seeing this. All right? So, they got
short down here. So, guess what they're
doing? They're now stopping out, causing
this, right? And anyone like you who
didn't take profit, they're now stopping
out. Probably going to cause this.
That's how the market moves, guys. It
moves because of people's pain. It only
moves because of people's pain. I
promise you. Regardless of what anyone
tells you about some algo or anything
else, it's just people's pain.
No worries. There we go. Max Max pain
gains. Well, your name is is perfect for
what we've just talked about.
Alex, I've been sitting with my mouth
shut and ears open for two months. I've
been in the market for years and I've
never traded futures until now. Three
days in, three days green following you.
I'm beginning to see it. Hey, there we
go. That's awesome. I've joined your
channel. Do I get access to Discord? If
you bought the 20our beginner to
advanced course for $649, you do get
access to Discord. Scroll down to the
end of the course. There's a module on
Discord. Tells you how to get in.
Yeah, lots of you seem like you're new
here and learning lots.
Is there a good tool to see options
levels correlated to ENQ prices? Yeah,
there is. Um,
why is my brain not working right now to
think of what they are all called?
Oh, come on, bro. Tide. Tide. Uh, from
unusual whales. Uh, what are the other
ones, guys? Help me out. There are some
which automatically print on the Gex
levels.
Mentha Q. There you go. That was the one
I was trying to remember. Well done.
Thank you, guys. Mentha Q. You can have
mentor Q set up so it automatically
prints on bookmap or trading view as
well. So if you pay for it, it will
automatically print those GEX level GEX
levels for you.
Um,
do I have a method of determining the
size of what volume bubbles on your NT
bubble chart? Uh, I can't remember what
I have it set to. I think um, anything
over 50. No, it must be less than that.
But obviously the bigger the bubble, it
might be over 25s.
Might be over 25s. Uh all in one go.
That is obviously like today we've seen,
you know, we've seen a 700 lot. We've
seen a 379 lot. We've seen a 592 lot. I
mean, we're talking about today has been
serious size, guys. Not a joke. That's
uh serious size. Serious serious size.
Aren't we in expansion um for the
current day? Yeah, but remember we're
Friday. All right, remember we're
Friday. So what are we considering in
now? Right. This is the current week,
right? So we're expanding
out of the previous day. So we failed.
Remember previous day value area low. We
reclaimed. We're above previous day
value area high. We're in expansion, but
we're into nodes from the current week.
Remember, we're above this. We expect to
trade to here, this red box which we're
now trading in. If we get above this, we
can maybe fill in some of this into
here, this low volume node, which will
be 175. Be asking a lot. But I wouldn't,
we're expanding on the last few days,
but it's still pullback, right? Because
where's the volume? Where's most of the
volume? Here, here, and here. All right.
For the current week, we'll go over this
in this week's newsletter. I'll go over
it all.
Where do you learn volume profile from?
How long have I been using it in trades?
I've been using it for as long as I can
remember, but um I've been used to only
really look at it on bookmap now. I plot
it on here for you. Uh there's free
stuff on my YouTube, right? I would say
to anyone that's new, go on my YouTube.
There's before you spend money on the
course, do all the free stuff, right?
There's I've got some masterclass
lessons on there. There's a whole shelf
uh on my YouTube dedicated towards it.
Um towards volume and order flow. Let me
find it for you. I'll post it in chat.
There's tons of free lessons on my
YouTube honestly. Right,
this right here is a good place to start
from if you want to learn about volume.
Right, that's a playlist of some free
stuff. If you like that stuff and you
want to learn more, you can do one of
the courses on my website. But only do
it if you like how I teach. If you don't
like how I teach, find someone who
teaches in a way that makes sense to
you.
We're going to 25,080.
Uh yeah, it's possible to go to 80. It's
possible also to come up here, but you
know, this is this is the level here. I
wouldn't be keep buying this up here.
It's like you lose you're losing edge.
Where did I learn from? I just by myself
really. No really good mentors if I'm
honest. Just a lot of trial and error. I
learned more from mentors on what not to
do. I used to have some terrible habits.
I used to pay like you guys. I paid
thousands and thousands and thousands
for really [\h__\h] courses to teach me
really bad things.
The newsletter, it should be posted uh
underneath, guys. Uh or at the pinned,
if you go to the pin message of at the
top, um the newsletter will be in one of
those blocks there. It's completely
free.
All right, folks. That's me done. Um I
really appreciate you guys showing up.
It's been amazing. It's been a great
week. Again, to the last two weeks, we
have been on a heater. Long may it
continue. Um I think next week might be
a little bit more tricky. I think we
probably build out range early next
week. We'll see where we close today. I
think we're just going to have a fail
breakout the low and an inside bar
today. Hopefully we don't get through
that previous day high, otherwise it's
going to start getting messy into next
week, but we'll see. Um I will remind
all of you this here that we do, it is
not your life. All right? It is not your
life. It is just a job. Maybe it's a
side hustle. Maybe it's something new
that you're learning. Maybe it's your
full-time gig. But it is just a job. If
you become too obsessed about this job,
you will stop seeing your family
members, your kids, your loved ones,
your friends. You'll stop going outside.
You'll stop going to the gym. You'll
stop doing all these other things. Those
things are so important in your life
even for you to just do this well. So
this weekend, go and do things which are
good for you. Do not sit and back test
for 48 hours this weekend. it is not
going to fill you with what you need.
Sure, review some of your trades.
Journal a little bit. Do a little bit of
back testing, but go outside, right? Go
and play some sport, go to the pub, go
and do anything that makes you feel
good. Get off the screens. All right,
that said and done, love you all. Peace
and love. I'll see you Monday morning.
Look out for the newsletter tomorrow
morning in your email, in your inbox.
Take care, folks. And use hard stops if
you're going to stay here.