Morning everyone.
Morning. Morning. Morning. Morning. How
are we all doing? Hopefully you had a
great day yesterday. Offered some
amazing short opportunities on stream.
And if any of you hung around until the
end of day, you got that short rally
rally cover as uh everyone covered their
shorts for that move back up. All right.
So this morning we can talk about what
we're looking at. Uh finally, finally,
finally, finally, we'd have to zoom in,
but finally, you can see the Ballinger
bands are starting to expand, right?
We've been in contracting Ballinger
bands for a long time since mid
November, and now we've got expanding
Ballinger bands, which gives us more
range to play with. The 5day, you can
see this is what we've talked about all
week. 5-day, 20-day, 50-day, finally
with a cross. And we will probably start
doing a move like this. Now it doesn't
mean there can't be a mean reversion
first but this will be the target not
necessarily today guys over the next
week or two maybe even longer but we are
starting to leave this range now if we
look at this is the range built out
since the high all right we are starting
to leave this range you can see even
actually overnight they've come and back
tested that Ballinger band and rejected
it and back tested the value from this
pivot high value area low and rejected
it and we've cleaned out lots of stops
there anything really left to look for
we have an old gap fill down here. All
right, we have an old gap right in here.
Oh, market's going to be a pain today
and not draw it out. There we go. So,
I'd be watching if we get downside 24700
to 24575
if if there's continued downside
pressure. All right, it's one of the
things we're looking at. If we look at
this profile here, we can see we're into
a node right here. All right, this is
from the last year. This is 12 months
worth of trading. So, we know that from
the last 12 months, we have a node right
here where we're at right here, right
now. If we start getting heavy
underneath uh let's call it 750, 745. If
we start staying heavy underneath that
and they don't set a trap, we need to be
very careful about traps today for fail
breakouts and they don't set a trap.
There is a move down to 535 which will
fill this gap. So basically in this
little gap fill area 750 700 let go and
we can be looking at 550s. All right 700
750 let go we can be looking at 7 uh
550s but we want to be very very very
very careful about failed breakdowns.
All right the moves we've had this week
have been absolutely wonderful. We've
captured a lot of it especially
yesterday. We don't really want to be
shorting the lows without structure. So
the reason for that being is we can do a
little look below and fail. All right.
It would be very easy for them to come
into this low volume node, have shorts
pile in, and then go, "No, we're not
ready yet. Thanks very much." And back
up into here. All right, we would sort
of expect that at some point, if not
today, at some point soon, unless we go
full risk off. Look, lower high, puke
down. We're expecting a pullback. All
right, so it might happen here. They
might drift it all the way down and do
it, but at some point they are going to
do it. So be very careful about thinking
about to short the low outside the
Ballinger band. All right, think about
the structure of the move. we don't move
in one direction. Right, going over to
the hourlys. Right, here is our
developing week.
Uh, let's delete this. Make sure. Okay.
Yes, there we go. Right, this is our
developing week profile here. You can
see we've left most of the volume up
here. So, all the time we're under this
uh 2500. Technically, we're in a sell.
All right. Technically, we're in a cell.
You can see breakdown, bare flag,
breakdown, bare flag, breakdown. It
might need to build liquidity again
before it moves lower. It might need to
come and do a little trap before it
moves lower. We will have to see. All
right, so we're going to use this
liquidity here. We know there's a
massive node here, 25,045,
the previous day point of control. We
had a big wash here at sort of 7 a.m.
and we're very thin on that wash. All
right, we weren't thin here. We have it
built in structure- wise, but if they
want to repric that 7 a.m. wash, they
can. So, I am aware of that move. Right,
we have targets below like I talked
about this guy right here into this node
619 and then all the way down here into
these uh four and 500s like we've talked
about. So there is a move into 550 today
if they want to do it. But again, I
would be very very very careful about
getting caught shorting these lows.
Anything like this can rip faces, come
and retest here, here, here, and even
here. And then they might want to set a
little bull trap over this and then pop
it back down. So, we need to be aware of
that. Um, what I'm basically saying is
an inside day. We need to be aware of an
inside day building. We're outside at
the moment, but if it's a failed break,
we come back inside yesterday's, we can
build lots of range here for them to use
later on either today or tomorrow. All
right? So, just be aware of that.
Remember, like not every day is going to
be that A+ trade. All right? If we look
at overnight, we just have a look at
what we did overnight. We traded pretty
much inside
yesterday's val, right? yesterday came
under Val drive up. Uh I was looking for
a short here. Anyone in Discord will
know I was looking for the short there.
They did it right on the bell. Right on
MC. I wasn't here for it. I'd left by
then. I'd had two attempts at it. Right.
We came up, hit the IB high, trap some
buyers up there. There's the short back
down. There's the hold and base. There's
the second leg up. There's the failure
to break out the second leg. There's the
rotation back down to the pivot. We
build liquidity out in here and then
they puke it. All right. So, we're
watching to see any retest in here. Is
there an opportunity to get long for
that move there and then short back
down? Long into here, then short back
down. I don't really want to be short
down here. We'd have to build out
sufficient liquidity for me to feel
comfortable doing that today. Swing
shorts. Sure, you guys are having a
great time right now, right? A great
time right now. Okay, so
we're watching these same levels, right?
This is the lower time frame, but if you
want to mark mark out any of these de
levels, now's your chance to do it
before I move to ES. But certainly going
to be watching uh previous day value
area low and 25,000 that gap fill up to
25,000. Do we do sort of fail breakout,
squeeze up, gap fill, and then sell back
down? That's one of the big questions.
Uh if we start basing above, I'll tell
you the only time I'd really be bullish.
All right, I'd be willing to play a
counter trend up into sort of here and
here and I'd be risk off into those. The
only time I'd really be thinking about
bullish is if they based above this for
that move there. But this is likely to
be a failed breakout for buyers. I see
this as a big range being developed.
Want to be careful about fail breakout
rotation. Want to be careful about fail
breakout rotation. But if they based
above here, that is possible. Won't I
won't rule it out. It's highly unlikely,
but it's possible. So, we're going to
talk about it. All right. ES
and we'll go uh through everything else.
All right. So, ES currently at the
previous week low. Remember ENQ well
below that. If we just have a little
zoom out on the dailies, you'll see the
relative strength. All right, ES is
still technically in its range. It's
starting to leave its range right around
here, the 97s. Okay, but technically
speaking, right, ES if even if we wanted
to do just these pivots, all right, it's
still holding. Remember, we're down
here. We've we've cooked these on the
Q's already, right? We we're thinking
about attacking down here now. So,
relative strength because of the
rotation, we went over it yesterday. So,
want to be careful. ES can still hold
and pivot. It might steal some liquidity
and go. So, we want to be aware of that.
If we have a look at the spiders, you're
going to see the same thing,
right? Still holding a pivot, but
actually undercutting some of it. This
is a key key level now on the spiders.
Uh 76ers and I would say there's
probably gamma knowing what they do at
75. So, I'd be watching that into 75 if
they get continued weakness. Uh if we
zoom this in for a moment
underneath previous day low right now.
So if we reject previous day low,
if we reject previous day low, there's a
drift lower.
All right, if we reclaim that, that's
where you can potentially get a squeeze
up into this pivot, this pre-market
pivot, uh 683s and then gap fill if they
really want to get going. Q's is going
to be sort of similar, uh, but with
relative weakness, right? Sort of
similar. So into this key level on the
cues, I can zoom this out, show you that
key level. We've been looking at this
green box, right? Big big level here
under here. Then we come into this huge
node where we found this bid in early
November. So in the immediate future, if
you're trading options or the cues, I'd
be watching this previous day low right
here. Might as well call it 650 over 650
up to 60265. If they really want to
squeeze, that is a big big pivot from
after hours and pre-market right here.
Right. Bull traps can live here. So I'd
be very aware of that. But if they
really want to squeeze, they have a gap
fill up here. If they want to do it, we
will see. We will see. Remember, we have
jolts at 10:00 today, folks, as well.
Okay, Dixie, uh, still trying to find
this bid off the lows, you can see, but
it's coming back into range. It's
probably coming back to the midpoint
since here right now. So, I wouldn't be
surprised. There you go, 61. If it finds
a sell soon, it might struggle a little
bit in the immediate future. Uh, let's
have a look at the VIX.
Still pumping. You can see breaking out
of this. We talked about these higher
lows being built. And then there's the
breakout. So really any hold over sort
of 20 21s today, you know, if they want
to get really aggressive, they're going
for that push upside. Normally speaking,
we would expect the VIX to pull back
today. We'd expect a fail breakout and
pull back, but we are not in a normal
market right now. Uh Bitcoin, I want to
talk about some of these markets we went
over yesterday. Like I said, we finished
that thousand day cycle. This might
really get nasty. You're starting to see
it. It's very possible it does an 80%
sale. That doesn't mean it goes straight
down in one go, but like like I said to
you guys, be very careful about buying
Bitcoin when we can actually consider a
move all the way down here somewhere. I
know sounds ridiculous, but it's
possible. We are coming into an area of
potential support here. So maybe there
is a buy from 73 down to sort of 50s.
Um, but it would be speculatory because
we are now starting to break down. So
you'd want to see a dip, hold, a turn uh
for that push back up. And I'd be
selling into that push back up if you're
going to do it. But we are starting to
see a riskoff environment. Right, let's
go through the mag. Relative strength,
Mr. Apple. Absolutely love it. Still
long Apple from 208, remember? So, still
comfortably up in this uh holding that
drive up yesterday. This was probably
mainly off Nancy Pelosi. All right, if
you uh had watched, she they started to
reveal her latest investments and yes,
she was long Apple. So, it's being seen
as bit more of a safe haven than the
other mags. Why? Because it doesn't have
the same exposure into AI that
everything else does. All right, Amazon
earnings tonight, remember? So, we're
still getting uh washed down on Amazon,
but it's still actually just in quite a
big chunky bit of range here. Nothing
really too scared to let go of, but we
have had a failed breakout. But in the
immediate future, yes, we are uh
starting to get a little heavy here.
Google uh earnings last night, earnings
were pretty good, but already pulling
back down to this low point. So, they're
selling everything right now. Even
everything that where they're even
offering good guidance, they're actually
selling everything right now. That is a
uh key sign of a rotation out of tech
like we've talked about. Meta continues
to get weak. So coming back down into
these uh some of these pivots
right down into here. So big gap up.
Fill that gap right down into this pivot
at 68. Remember I'm still long from down
here at the moment. So we're waiting to
see what happens. Uh if it's able to
hold gains or not, but if we're going to
go rotation off, then unlikely it will
be able to hold gains. Microsoft's
trying to find a bit of a bid. Uh did I
start a long on Microsoft yesterday? Was
that what I started a a feeler on on the
swings? Have a look at the swing
channel. I'm trying to remember. I think
it might have been. It was. So, I
started a feeler yesterday because we're
into a 61 fib from that tariff low. All
right. So, I've got a feeler on very
very very tiny position just so mainly I
can keep watching of it in the next few
days, but it is weak. Nvidia uh still
the same kind of story, but we actually
are starting to break down under here.
So failure to reclaim 77s opens up this
move lower and we can come and clear out
some of these stops like we're doing on
the Q. So we can talk about that like we
did yesterday, right? Failing to reclaim
this will lead to that weakness. Same
story we talked about yesterday. Uh
Tesla
weak. That is weak. We're moving out of
that choppy range. Yeah, there's your
choppy range, right? Failed breakout.
I'd say any failure into 420s. Anytime
we're under 420s, this is looking for a
drive down to clean out these stops and
we had gap fill potential all the way
back here. And if we measured that from
a fib and if we did a measured move
under here, it would probably be down to
that. So maybe at some point that starts
to play out. Um, weaker names right now.
Uh, they're moving out of anything uh
softwarebased. So if you have a look at
like Oracle continues to puke um if you
have a look at uh like Adobe or anything
like that they're actually they're
completely moving out of anything where
AI software wise can have an impact. And
that's pretty much it folks. Um I guess
we should have a quick look at AMD. They
got absolutely murdered yesterday. But
remember that had relative strength
versus Nvidia for a while. All we're
doing is coming back into gap fill
potential on AMD back down into 72s. All
right. So it did really well as the gap
up. It held. It has potential to come
back down into here if it wants. And
that's pretty much that.
Zoom this in. All right. So, we have
this gray block below, blue block below
that. Um, I will not be looking to get
too aggressive at the open. I would be
very, very concerned about failed
breakouts and breakouts either side of
this. And this might look small, but
this is over 100 points what they've
done here. If they want to repric this
in here, they will. If they want a
failed look and come back down, they
will. If they want a failed look and
come back in, they will. And if they
want to stay heavy, then it's going to
be hard to join. I'll be honest. If they
want to stay heavy at the lows, we're
going to need a lot of liquidity built
out. Right, I'm coming straight back. I
just got to turn my air con off cuz this
is freezing cold right now.
All right. Looks trappy. Yeah, it does
look trappy.
It does look trappy. Uh, what I would
ask if you can all smash that like
button nice and early for me, then I
don't we don't have to talk about it
anymore. Um, and we should have a good
stream here together. Again, we had a
monstrous day yesterday. Remember when
you've gone like, you know, last week
was a huge week. Yesterday was a really
good day. The day before was okay. I
missed a lot of the shorts. We don't
expect like, you know, huge moves every
day. So, just remember that. Have that
in the back of your head. Like, it's
very possible that this market needs to
slow down at some point.
Silver crashed hard. Yeah. Well, it did
the failed followrough. We went over all
those moves yesterday, right? We can go
over it again. It did the failed follow
through. That's what I was saying. What
I'd be looking at on the silver after a
big You know, you look at it's basically
the creation of a bare flag. There's the
sell, there's your first bounce, there's
the liquidity we talked about and down.
Same story on gold, right? First bounce
into the key level, they will try and
sell this back downside. Now, it's uh
it's fairly normal move. It's like about
as obvious as you ever get in the
market. Um honestly, once you see those
big sell, we expect a bounce and then we
look to sell that bounce, right? That's
probably the easiest move you can get.
Okay, here we go, folks. So, here's the
open.
Let's see what we get. Let's see what we
get.
But already playing games for me, are
you? Can't see anything. Come on. But
Matt, honestly,
this is madness. But Matt, what are you
doing? I'm going to have to close this
and reopen it.
Hilarious.
Showing me 500 points higher than price.
Are you joking? There we go. Right into
into this gray box potentially or a
failed breakout underneath this
overnight low right here, which is what
we were saying. We got to be very
careful about failed breakouts under
here right now. We have this gray box
below. I'd be very, very careful about
them trapping underneath that right now.
I think that's highly highly highly
probable and likely.
You want to be careful.
Gray box is there as uh some structural
support though.
Right here is the start of this move. So
it's done a first look below and fail.
Most of the liquidity up at 45s. Now,
let's get a New Yorker
one of these on. Bit more patience today
than we've had recently as we haven't
got the same setup.
Okay, like we said, there's the
liquidity up into 45s.
So, here comes the sell through
down into this gray box potentially.
Remember, we have got gap fill potential
that we talked about all the way down to
where is it? 700 to 550. So, we want to
think about that. 700 to 550. We're
already in that kind of area right now.
We can talk about the MAG. Tesla opening
up 2.93% down. Getting very washy here
very early. 2.93% down on Tesla. Uh
Nvidia holding up okay. Microsoft 2.61%
down. Meta 1 and a half% down. Google
7.64% down. Amazon 4.85% down. And Apple
slightly up on the day. Right. Just be
careful down here into this support
system. All right. be very very careful.
I won't be getting short down here. I
think we will probably to see a trap
being set down here, which is what we're
starting to see. So, looking potentially
for an explosion back upside now at this
point. Here we go. And let's see if we
can get through this next node and start
ripping some faces. This was the trap
that we talked about, folks. Here we go.
So, taking some profit into there.
Moment I saw them start to lift that,
that was join time. Watching New York
open. See if we get above New York open
now for the runners. And if we do and we
rebase, I will start to add above that
New York open if we can do that. Right.
So there's the trap into the gray box
back into range. We build out liquidity
now. And I'll probably move my stop up a
little bit here. Try and protect this
node at 88.
If we wash me out, that's fine on the
runner.
67 big level. Nice protection of 88.
Here we go. Right back into value area
high again. Let's see if we can get
through. Really nerd. Really good. Let's
go. Let's go. Let's go. Come on. Get
through the New York open. Let's turn
this squeeze on.
Let's go, baby. Let's go, baby. Nice
start. Not going to catch me getting
trapped down there. Tell you that much.
Come on, bookmap. Second day in a row
that you are pausing on me. Really can't
be having that.
I'm going to have to close this book
down and start again. [\h__\h] hell,
mate.
Give me a second on but guys. Sorry.
What a pain. What a pain. Still in this
guys. We're still protecting that node.
I still think we can get above this New
York open and start to push.
Here we go. So watching this now
previous day low reclaim of 83s we can
see a squeeze here. So watching this New
York open. Here we go is New York open.
So first TP here. Let's see if we can
get through these 80s now and start
exploding.
Sorry guys, but look at this on match.
It's just a joke what I'm dealing with
here today. Right, here we go. Really
nice through the 80s. All right, so we
will now look to see if we can trade up
into here to 70. There can be a trap
above 70. So I'll be trimming some
probably at 40 and 70 and then holding
to see if we come up to 964 and 989. And
this will be an absolute huge winner to
start the day if we get this. And we
said trap was set down here. TP here and
then all the way up here, folks.
Here we go.
Who got short at the lows? Some idiot
did. Some idiot did and we are playing
against him. So, this is already
comfortably into approaching the 100
point mark. Yeah, already 100 points. We
want to trim a lot up here, folks. We
don't know if we can get through that,
but if we can, that's where we're going.
So, top side of this range is the fail
breakout. This is what we talked about
pre-market. Be very careful about a look
below and a hold of here and this move
here. We trim some here and we wait and
see if we can get all the way up into
that now. But, we are locking in profits
no matter what. There's 100 pointer.
Been gone, done. Thank you very much.
Alex equals genius. Oh, thank you very
much. That's very kind of you guys.
Honestly, it's not it's it's not uh you
don't have to be a genius for this
stuff. We just know we we've done a huge
move down. Shorts have chased the low.
We expect a pullback. We join for this
pullback and uh if it doesn't make it
all the way up to previous day value
area low, that's fine because we've
locked in a ton of money already, right?
So, the job is done. We've done our uh
we've done our job. That's all we that's
all we can do, folks, is do our job.
The lowhanging fruit, right? we talk
about all the time. We take the low
hanging fruits.
Remember we have jolts as well coming
folks. 10:00.
All right. ES Doug struggling to get
over the New York open. I'm watching
that carefully. It's struggling right
now. If ES can get going, that will
help.
Um we're actually equally weighted right
now.
Watching this New York open. I'd want to
see this hold uh hold into 50s otherwise
I will cut this. I can always think
about a re-entry.
Still holding well. Yes, trying to hold
VW up. Needs to get back above the New
York open. So ES letting the side down a
little bit at the moment.
Looking good though. Here we go. Great
hold of 50s. Here we go folks. Let's see
if we can go upside here. Really nice
hold of 50s.
Yes. Trying to get back over it New York
open and it's got that previous day low.
We've got liquidity above to go and
attack.
Beautiful.
Really nice. Here we go, folks.
Come on.
Looking for a lift through this this
node here. This is where all the stops
are into 68s.
Come on.
Come on. Who does it like this? Let's
go. Let's go. Job done. Okay. So, last
TP right right now is uh we'll be
looking for GlobeEx and up here now.
Really nice. But we expect there might
be we might start to get stuck here.
Okay. If we look uh left yesterday,
right, we we might get start to get
stuck in this kind of range if we keep
lifting. Great. But we positioned
perfectly for this. That was a big uh TP
here. So, you're now 150 points up.
GlobeEx and VW up coming up, which would
be 190 points. And then all the way up
here, which would be uh 237 points into
value area low from yesterday, and 270
points into previous day close, which
would be the efficient market. Thank you
for playing.
Thank you for playing.
What a beauty. All right, building out a
node here. Do not let this collapse all
the way down on you to 800. All right,
so move your stop up to start protecting
these profits very aggressively. You do
not want if we start breaking 77, there
is a flush all the way down to 800s
here. I will uh going to move this the
other side of this so you can see price
action a bit better. All right, so we
want to watch this node here. We do not
want to get flushy under this. We will
cut it or any flush under this. Okay? We
do not want to see this be lost. So far,
we're holding well. So, I'd move my stop
right up to protect that if I was you.
And then we just see how far we can
squeeze here.
So, VW up here. So, big level here,
folks. This green line, big big level.
Hopefully, we can keep lifting. But I
would I would have paid yourself 70 80%
of your move right now at least.
Let's see what else it's got left.
Should we go back to sleep?
Breezy. I got in at 760s. I cut all the
micros already. That's all right. Well,
that's still fantastic move. 760s to
900, mate. It's 140 points. That's all
right, buddy. Don't Don't even stress
about it. 140 points in the opening 10
minutes.
Can we get through this speed up? Keep
getting stuck up here. See this shelf
being very, very important. If we lose
this shelf, do not hold on. Okay, do not
hold on if we lose this shelf. If we're
very lucky, they set a little trap. But
if we lose this shelf, do not hold them.
We're very thin. All the way back down
to 800. You will not be happy if you
give 100 points back in one go. All
right. You need them to complete this or
just cut the whole thing. Here we go.
Come on. Let's do it. Let's do it. Let's
do it. Let's do it.
Come on, baby.
Almost there. Come on.
We're over 200 points now. Come on.
Please hold it. Please hold this shelf.
Want full TP up there.
We lose this amount, folks. If I lose
this amount, move my stop right up here.
We This is now Vpo on the day for me as
well. Based on Delta Vo moved up here.
Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on.
Holding all right so far. I just don't
I'm not going to add any size. I'm in
from these lows. Low risk low risk long
down here for the trap. If it washes me
out, so so be it.
All right. Out here, folks. Done. We can
come all the way back down to here. So,
I'm not going to sit through that. They
set a little low volume, no trap. Uh
would be fun, but that's it.
Where did I enter this trade? Uh right
on the reclaim down here. So if we look
at this,
guess what happened on the undercut of
the lows?
Look what happened on the undercut. Who
entered shorts? Where did I like to
start getting long once we started
reclaiming? Right, there's the undercut
and we held. Goodbye shorts. Right, look
at the delta flip. Sell, sell, sell,
sell. Bye.
They're trying to do that little trap
down here. I'm not going to play it.
This is what I talked about that it's
possible they set a trap in a low volume
node if they want to do this move. I'm
not going to play that. It's too risky
for me. Low hanging fruit's gone. So, we
got up to VWAP. That was my best cover
was into there. And I'm out of it now.
And I'll just wait to see how we now.
Remember, we've done the damage. We can
have a failed breakout above here like
we talked about. Each side of it can
have a failed breakout. If we're lucky,
they're going to keep lifting, but I'm
out of it now anyway.
We went over silver already. I'm not
going to keep going over the metals,
guys. You need to be here early in the
morning. I'm not going to keep going
over it, especially we're in a trading
day,
right? They held they filled some
imbalance and held. They set that little
low volume low trap. ES might want it to
be up. So ES is trying to do the
catch-up trade. Look at VIX failed
breakout coming right back down into the
low 20s.
Note starting to build up here.
This is your overunder for current
sentiment.
So if we think where we might go,
previous day value area low, previous
day point control, previous day close,
sorry, previous day point of control.
Somewhere in here, I'd imagine we fail
one of these blocks. We will probably
fail at least for a back test.
Maybe it does this to one of these, but
I don't know which. But I'm out now
anyway. 200 points. That was enough.
Got my money, right? Got my money.
ES coming back up to its VWAP.
Big old squeeze out.
Very close to previous day value area
low here now. And we're back inside
potentially inside the uh well we are
inside already current developing weeks
value. All right. We've got a node I
would say up into
yeah pro pretty much where previous day
is. It's going to get tight up here.
It's going to get tight up here.
How much more can they lift it is the
question. ES almost to VW up. Looks like
it wants it to VW up right now.
VIX still coming downside.
We're still bidding above this gray box
for now. So long's still okay
technically. I mean they washed me out.
I wasn't willing to sit through in case
they washed down to here. That gray box
is going to become key for sentiment.
Absolutely key.
It's back down to VPO again. This key
level, this is where the sellers keep
getting stuck into 880. They cannot find
a sell underneath that. They keeps
getting stuck into the 880 right into
here. Lots of sellers keep stepping in
here, not getting their way. Right? So,
we might keep lifting all the way all
the time. They keep doing that.
Nice, Rob. Great work.
Asia highs. I mean, 180s. It's possible.
I wouldn't say it's probable. It's
possible. When we zoom out and think
about what we're looking at, you know,
we'd have to get through all of this
first. Previous day value. This will be
a big level, folks. Like into previous
day value low and the cash gap, right?
cash gap here, settlement here. All
right, this will be a big big level
through that. This is a huge level to
get to Asia. You're talking about all
the way up here. We're asking it to do a
decent amount of work. All right,
because we're still bearish. There's the
range. There's the breakout. We know
it's thin here. We said we might repric
thin structure, right? We're repricing
the thin structure. Doesn't guarantee
that we're going to come all the way up
here. We might very well reject this
range or just go sideways in it once we
get here.
All those things are possible.
We are strug struggling a little bit up
here to like break out which is what
they're trying to do. They want to hold
880s on this gray box and force the
breakout. They are struggling a little
bit.
They're now starting to bid at the 20s.
They just want to get up to 50s. They're
trying to get a rip a face ripper up 50s
at the moment by the looks of it.
Here they go. So they're going for that
value. Yes. going for VWAP as well.
Here comes the move for value. So
through to the 50s
value just up here at 64s. They're
starting to get stuck up there. Buyers
keep getting caught on those highs. They
haven't completed the move yet.
I'm not using Think or Swim. This is
Trading View. I execute on Ninja Trader
to not use Think or Swim.
How many screens do I have? Uh,
five. All right, back down into this
gray box. Big big level. There's no
shorts until we leave this. All right.
And you want to be very careful being
short. There's no shorts until we leave
this gray box. All the time we're above
this. This is a long trying to extend
up. They're trying to extend up to hit
their targets right now. There's no
short until you leave this gray box. Any
of you that are thinking about short,
not until you leave volume. We talk
about it all the time. You would be
front side on this move.
You don't know how high up this can go.
Maybe it stops here and leaves. Maybe
they base here and do a big big squeeze.
We don't know. So, we respect the
structure in front of us.
Buyers definitely caught the moment at
930s.
Just hanging around this bot.
Yes, stuck right now between it 24-hour
VW up and it New York view up. Just
completely stuck.
Watch your ATR. It's still pretty high.
All right, ATR is still pretty high.
We're still holding this gray box. There
is still no change here until that
changes. We start to change that and
it'll be a drive lower.
Holding the edge of gray box again. Back
upside we go. No change. The only short
here and it'd be very very tough to take
today would be something like this down
to here. Right.
Otherwise, we have low hanging fruit
above for them to aim for.
Yeah, the gray boxes. You see, we can
actually extend this gray box now. But
you can see this volume here.
If we looked inside of that,
right? You can see
at the lows we have sellers keep get
getting stuck.
At the highs, we have buyers stuck. So,
we're boxed in in here. The breakout
will get this continuation or that move
up there. You want to be very careful
about a fail breakout. That's why I'm
not adding up here because I know that
we've had a decent move. We've had a
decent run already. They're going to try
and get into this value area low and
previous day close. They want to close
this gap. Remember, this is where Oh,
don't move that. This is where we held
overnight. So, this is where all buyers
are currently stuck. Right. The reason
I'm not too interested about the next
long from here to here is because
there's not too much room. If they'd let
me hold my runners, I would have been
willing to hold all the way up. It looks
like they're going to do it. Here you
go. So, we know buyers are stuck up
here. So, we want to be very careful.
There is a shelf up here that they're
trying to repric into. Reclaim that and
we get very, very bullish. Okay. So,
here's value.
So tagged now. Previous day value area
low now tagged.
It's actually
here. Just moved that accidentally with
my mouse. Okay. So previous day value
area low tagged. The only thing left now
is PDC. The yellow line above.
Where have those gone? I just
There we go. The yellow line above.
Jesus Christ. Almost lost it. The yellow
line above is for a full gap fill. Q is
trying to get there as well. So ETF has
not made it there yet either. SPY has
now just popped above that pre-market
level and failed and driven into VWAP
and failed. So value holding so far.
We can move this up a little bit. We've
got like a double shelf here. It's
pretty ugly. I'm going to be honest.
It's not what you want to see. But
buyers are still in control for a
squeeze. But how much longer for? Well,
we're going to find out very shortly.
back down into this gray box and VWAP
again. Do they finish bidding with this
now? Are they done with this gray box?
Here's the sell into the lower end of
the gray box. Watching in case we start
to leave it. If we leave it, I will
consider the move down into here. Not
the forehands. I won't just take the
break either. It's too risky for them to
retra.
Big buyer here at 79. Now out of
position all time. We're under him at
79.
still holding. ES still holding uh New
York VWAP is stuck between 24-hour New
York VW. Still not leaving this gray
box. Watching this now. If they if they
fail 9005s in this low volume node and
do this move here, I'll think about
joining. If they fail this low volume
node and do this move here, I'll think
about joining there.
If they can't reclaim the top side of
this shelf, getting close.
I need a rejection of 80 80s
a flush. Here we go. And let's see if it
rejects the next tap back in. I'm
waiting for a tap back in. I'm not going
to take the break down here. If it goes
without me, it goes without me to wait
to see if they tap back in and retra.
Watching these 880s.
Come on, bookming
880s. Reclaimed. Not taking yet. Still
watching. Still watching. Still
watching. Watching this develop. Still
bids here. We might get this flush soon,
but I don't want to get caught in a
resqueeze. Watching ES right into its
New York VW up as well. I need it under
all of that. Really still holding.
Buyers got trapped on that last push
into the low volume node. Still not in.
Still not comfortable with this. Still
don't like what I'm seeing on the tape.
Pushing back up. Not going to touch it.
Buyers stepping in here. If you look at
the tape, 65, 70, 75, 80, and 90 all
starting to try and lift. Push it up.
Why I didn't take it. Didn't see the bid
support leave. Saw them step up. So,
ignored that move there for the trap.
and just see if they want to keep
lifting this again now. So, going to
ignore it until it's clean.
I guess that what would I see there? It
just comes with experience, I guess.
Just what how they were acting on the
tape. We just rejected point of control
there again. How long till news? 7
minutes.
Do I want to take the trade before 7
before the news? Probably not.
ES back down to that VWAP again. If ES
starts getting heavy here, we might get
that flush, but uh do they want to do
it? They just tap to the top side of it.
It's quite quite dirty what they're
doing here. Very very risky, especially
into news.
Very very very risky, especially into
news.
Yes. Held previous week again.
Bookmat failing on me again. Stalling
out again. Come on, mate.
There is a flush here if they want it.
Do they want it? Do they want to let go
of it?
Here we go. All right. Trying a little
piece now. Watching these imbalances to
43s and then 20s.
Here we go. And then can we get VW up
here? Peeling some off there. Don't like
that. Straight away bid coming in. I
want to see if them pull these bids.
Don't want to see them rebid up. Come
on, flush it down.
Stop moving to 79's now.
We've got a little imbalance at 75. So
79's I'll tap back out.
Rebidding. They're rebidding this. Be
careful. Sellers got stuck on that last
move. Need a breakdown here underneath
47s. Here we go. Let's [\h__\h] go.
Let's go. Took patience. All right.
Covering a lot into this. And the next
node I'll be looking for is down here.
And I won't be expecting price to come
below this really to be honest. So, I'll
be taking most my position off here.
Covering most into here. Oh, we're
taking most off here. So, versus this
flush, leaving this shelf back down into
here. If we get this, great.
Repricing some of these imbalances now.
Right. So, maybe I can show them to you
on here. See these imbalances where we
ripped back up. We're starting to repric
some of these. It's why we're peeling
some off into this. Let's [\h__\h] go.
I'm on a new level. I'm on a new level.
Here we go. Give me that TP. Give me
that TP. Watching 800s. It's value area
low as well. They might rebid this
moving stop tighter here on a runner.
There we go. Out here. It's fine. Almost
got that. I don't want to be a dip for a
tip, especially into news.
What's the bet now? They do this cuz I
just got out being protective.
Probably.
Probably. No, my [\h__\h] luck.
FCT made my entire month in a day. You
are fire, sir. Hey, Mike. Love it. Love
it. It's clean though, guys. Like, the
action has been clean recently. Like,
it's been so much like Oh, can you see
the difference in my [\h__\h] do it,
aren't they? Alex, you idiot.
Mom meatloaf. Um
gh can you see the difference in my
trading when we leave value when we have
trap players how much easier it is for
for me to trade. It's my favorite man
when we've got people stuck. Just the
momentum so much better. Okay. Into that
node and finding a bid. So, like I said,
I don't actually expect it to come below
here, but I was saying knowing my luck,
they're going to do this with it, but
it's very possible that for the rest of
the day, we might just chop in here,
folks. All right, so we did a fail
breakdown,
fail breakout back into the mid. All
right, we don't know what it wants to
do. Maybe they do the continuation, but
I think it's very likely we need to
build out liquidity. All right. If we
think about on like on a daily right
now, right, it's very very likely we
need to just have a slower day and build
something out here and then maybe offer
this and then this in the next week,
right? So, but you know, it doesn't
matter what I think. If they're going to
go risk off, they will just [\h__\h] dump
this stuff like they did for the last
few days.
Where was my entry? It was right here.
It was right around here. 90s. All
right. So once I saw, do you remember I
said if we leave it, if we leave this
gray box, I will be looking for the
short. We left and I said I want them
now to reject 905s. I think I said this
low volume node for the trade under.
They did this move and then the bids
started stacking and walking up. So I
was like, I'm not touching that. They're
walking it up. They had one more push.
This push here trapped all the buyers.
So once we failed back under this shelf,
that was my short and I was covering
into here and I think into here. I
didn't even get my final target. I
missed it by like two points. And if
they start letting go of New York open,
it means that all the buyers
will be out of position and we will
rotate. Oh, they're going to do the
whole [\h__\h] move. I mean, that is just
terrible for me. I'm going to be honest.
This is terrible for me. We might have
had the best trade of the day there.
That might be perfect position if
they're going to go really risk off.
Right, you've got news coming in uh
under a minute here, folks. Lots of
sellers coming in at these lows. Be
very, very careful. They're being very
aggressive down here. Be very, very
careful because if they get caught, we
will rip back up. That's a straight move
down.
Let's get a Trump uh impression
celebration.
We need the YMCA song.
So good. Beautiful trade, FCT. Beautiful
trade. We trapped him at the top. At the
top. We trapped him.
What's the gray box? It's just volume.
All right. It's just how I mark out
volume. It's just volume. All right.
Here comes the news, folks. Be very
careful. If they reclaim this guy here,
they can do a rip ripe a cup if they
want to come and retest this. Right.
Remember, we've made very good money.
So, the trades we've called on stream
again today. It's a very early day.
Uh where's the short? Let me do it.
There we go. Into this node down to
here.
Oh, Alex. Oh, this is going to [\h__\h]
hurt, man. This is gonna hurt if they if
they want to do a new leg down and I
have the best position on the day. This
is gonna hurt. This is going to hurt my
ego. This is how I get tilty. This is
how I get tilty. Even with big wins,
this is how I get tilty. If they start
puking this and I know that I've stopped
out when I shouldn't have stopped out, I
will get very upset at myself.
Oh my god.
Is anyone still in this? You should be
still in this. If it wasn't for news,
Alex. Alex. Alex. Yes, please.
You're still in. Nice. Jolts. This was
Jolts. We had 10 a.m. news. Jolts.
Jolts. I just didn't want to hold
through Jolts.
because you had this huge candle, right?
We moved from 96 to it's almost 100
point candle. I didn't want to sit in
this and get ripped all the way back up.
The market is bleeding. All right, we're
back into a key level. The 700s was the
turnaround point earlier. This same key
level. So, be careful here. Right, if
you are still in this short, I would be
covering some here. And then we can
think about if you're going to get
expansion. Remember, we talked about 700
to five. I want to make sure I'm
accurate here. 700 to 561 is potential
gap fill. Um, I'm going to just draw
this out on here so I don't lose sight
of it.
We do that as what should we do it as?
Light yellow.
Okay, we're into that gap, folks. All
right,
we've been straight down. If they get a
reaction, they can go straight up. So,
just I would just trail your stop on
stuff like this. 700 is where the big
sellers came in this morning, got stuck.
This white line is where the sellers
came in this morning, got stuck. That's
where we went under, over squeeze. So,
just be careful. I'll be watching these
nodes back up here. Now, I'm going to
remove this.
You would want them to protect that on
the way back up. All right. I think we
will develop a range here now today.
No, I don't speak Italian. Not enough of
it. Just enough to swear.
Nice work, everyone. Nice work.
Only bonds. Well, also Netflix, those of
you who started that swing position with
me, Netflix relative strength again, two
and a half% up. Love to see it. Love to
see it. That one's starting to look
good.
So, I actually want Netflix to come a
little bit lower. We started that swing
position.
I'd love it into the 70s, but that's a
nice drive today. You can see we're
starting to base out here. I would have
loved it a little bit deeper into this
gap. We might still get it. It might be
a drive which rejects and comes down,
but we are now what, like 40% down off
the highs, maybe more.
Yeah, 40% off the highs. I'd love it
that little bit weaker any any
aggressive flush down and Alex will be
scooping and he'll be scooping
aggressively
longterm
two plus year swing
you can always play leaps the lower we
go the better in my mind for Netflix.
Okay,
what do I think about Hood? Um,
I imagine they're absolutely dumping it.
Yeah,
it's been priced up so hard. It's been
stupid the amount of uh price up. You
can see where I talked about come back
to this is uh Yeah, I mean anyone buying
it up there is frankly is I mean I hope
I'm not offending you is frankly a
[\h__\h] idiot. Like this whole thought
that this is going to keep going just
ridiculous. They've got exposure to
crypto which has finished its
thousand-day rally like we talked about.
We go swing to swing,
right? You're into an interesting area
right now, but you're very very weak.
So, I think into here would be
interesting to scoop some up, right? If
you're really if you're really bullish
on it, I think there'd be a reaction
somewhere around here for at least a
back test. So, there's probably if you
can get 70s, there's probably like a 30
point a 30 uh dollar move. And if it
reclaims, great. if we're going to go
bullish on the rest of the year. If we
start losing this though, you want to be
real careful. We actually have an old
gap down there still. So, it really
depends on sentiment of the market.
Really depends on sentiment of the
market. Like, if I'm going to scoop up
individual names, they either need to
have been sold off way way way way too
much and be a very very good name. Um,
or if it's like a speculatory buy for
me, it's where I think there's like some
news coming or something like that. But
normally it's just
looking for uh mag seven kind of names
deep in discount.
Oh god, this is going to hurt guys. This
is going to really hurt me.
I'd be very careful about the fail
breakout again down here. If you're
still short, just as long as you paid
yourself some um
we can think about the extension that
you could potentially do.
Yeah, we might you might get 500 today
if you get really lucky. Remember, we're
into a gap. This sort of greeny or
orangey yellowy box is a gap. Why is
that on that color? We want you gray.
My method's complicated. Um, I don't
think so. I think it's really simple.
Um, it might seem complicated. All we're
doing is looking for players on multiple
time frames who are trapped. All right.
So, where did bulls enter today who are
not very smart? They enter on a
breakout. All right. They bought here.
We see them trapped here. We see them
trapped here. We use their pain to trade
lower. Where did shorts enter today?
Underneath this low down here. Uh, we've
already puked out lots. We don't expect
this to just keep going down. When we
zoom right out and we think about where
this move started yesterday and the day
before, you know, even higher. We can't
just keep nailing down without providing
liquidity for market makers to get
involved in. So, you know, were market
makers likely to short lower dayto-day?
No. Was retail? Yes. So, they get
trapped, we use their pain, we trade up.
They get trapped. Buying the top, we use
their pain, we trade down. Right? That's
all it is. And it's the same thing on
multiple time frames. That's where the
edge comes from. And you're using flow
zones or everything else for confluence
and key levels.
What indicator am I using? This is
anchored volume profile and this are the
flow zone pros. Uh someone just asked
where how do you get discord? You do the
20our course, the beginner to advanced
course. You get discord for free with
that. Look at bookmap. It's really
starting to annoy me, guys. Is there a
shortcut where I can get this to stay
pinned? Cuz it keeps not staying pinned.
It's starting to be frustrating.
If they trap shorts here, it's a good
long. Yeah, I mean, I'd want a lower day
break at this point. Uh ES has already
done it. You just got to remember we're
in a bearish market leaving uh and VIX
has just found a pivot. Thank you. VIX
has just found a bid and it's breaking
out. So, you know, you'd you'd need the
VIX to start going the other way. You'd
probably want us to finish filling that
gap. Right? So, look at VIX. It's just
found a bid on this old resistance
level. All right. Here's the old
resistance level. Here's the pin low.
Look at VIX. Did the same thing that we
did for the longs. All right. Undercut,
turn around, gone. All right. V-shaped
recovery into key level gone. All right.
So, if VIX blows through this and comes
back down, maybe you get that kind of
move down here, but you want to be very
careful. All right. This is a high
volume node. This gray box here is a
high volume node that we're trading into
based on a daily and a weekly. Um, but
we can come all the way down to 550.
Like I said, gap fill would be 550.
Would be 550. So, we want to be very
careful.
I wouldn't be short down here, that's
for sure. We had the best short of the
day. I am an absolute idiot. Uh, that
was another 220 points back down to low
there if I just held that.
Sorry, folks.
All right.
Zoom in and watch this a little bit.
Now, I think we're going to go in a
range today. Honestly, my gut feeling is
we shouldn't trade gut feeling, but we
just trapped shorts at the lows again.
650s, right? If we look again at the
lows, all the lows. And there you go.
650s. The undercut. Guess what happened?
Breakout shorts came in underneath the
previous or the current daily low. And
they now just got themselves caught
again. All right. So, if we don't get a
break under here, if they tap this and
stay and buy a step back in, we will
probably get a squeeze back out. I
wouldn't be playing the buys down here.
It's very, very risky right now. I'd
kind of wait for it to start pivoting
and showing me.
How do I set my levels for value high
and value low? They're based on New
York. They're not based on the whole
day.
All right, I will tell you there's
definitely some sellers getting caught
at these lows. We are starting to see
them get caught down here. Look at this.
658 to the low of day. So, if buyers
protect that, it's a big [\h__\h] ask
because you haven't turned around yet.
But if they protect this and reclaim up
here, they reclaim value. There's
probably a move, you know, I'd be more
interested if they reclaimed 720 for a
move up to 800. Otherwise, I wouldn't
really be touching it.
But they're definitely piling in at the
lows.
Like
600 and 550 still possible. If you're
still holding your shorts, you're still
possible.
But let's see if bookmap moves down with
this thing. I don't think it's going to.
Does anyone know of a shortcut? No, it's
not going to again.
Got to be something I've clicked
accidentally. What is this control panel
really annoying
VIX matters over analysis? Uh it's just
good confluence, right? It's more like
if we see divergence for VIX, it's a day
that I don't want to trade, right? And
it does occasionally happen, especially
into rollover, right? So if you see like
VIX moving higher and the market moving
higher that is a nogo for me days like
that. Right click on the price line
reenter.
What do I want to put? AutoBBO.
Nope.
I want it to follow it and it's just not
resent to last price. There we go. Thank
you. Thank you. Thank you. You guys are
the best. You guys are the best. Thank
you.
Okay, here we go. So, you might get us
gapful, folks. Oh my god. We had the
best short of the day. Alex, you are I
knew this was going to happen. I might
not be able to trade the rest of the
day. Now, this is going to put me on
full tilt. This is going to be a 330
point trade that I've missed.
Oh, that's hard to take. That's really
hard to take. I'm sorry team. Lots of
you are getting it though, which is
great. So, I'd be TP into here, the edge
of this gray, and then I'd be looking
for 550s. Now, this was what we talked
about earlier. 700 to 550 possible today
after a fail break. Oh god, this is
going to be sting. This is going to
really sting.
This is going to sting.
Oh, Alex
turn up my mic volume. Uh, can try.
It's pretty high up, man. I think it's
just that I'm speaking low. It's uh,
it's actually pretty high up.
Yeah, I know. I'm close to fully knees.
Oh
god.
God,
you I'm telling you now, this is like a
huge tilt thing for me, me personally,
when I do my diary. too many break evens
and stuff like this. Huge tilt. Huge
tilt thing.
Okay, you look good here, folks. Uh I
would manage I'd manage this position.
You're getting very close to filling
that gap. So, if they want to be
efficient, they will fill this gap and
then maybe find a bid until the end of
this if they're going to remain heavy.
All right. Gosh, we're running out of
things for me to look for here. If we're
going to remain heavy,
we are now looking at an hourly chart
based on November sort of 20th. Uh yeah,
November 20th to 21st. So we're looking
maybe 47. There's definitely uh 450 down
to 150. Oh, it's a long way. It's down
here, guys. Oh, all right. There you go.
You're about to get it. You are about to
finish that gap fill.
Oh my god, that's painful. Well,
congrats anyone that got it. You just
got 330 point gift while Alex got 80 of
it. Oh god.
Oh my god. It might keep coming.
Bing bing bing bing bing bing bing bing
bing bing bing. Did any of you get that
full move? Did any of you get the full
move? I'd love to know.
Hopefully you did. It would make me very
happy if you did. So, a little reaction
off the gap fill here. Did anyone get
the full move? You got it. Oh my god,
you guys got it. Look at that reaction
off the gap, Phil.
God, that was accurate.
Stick with me, kids. Stick with me,
kids. I'll get you paid.
They can afford to rip this now if they
want to. Uh they can afford 600 and then
all the way up to 650. Remember, this is
thin down here, right? So if they just
want to be efficient, if it's a big if,
they might come all the way back up for
660 and then 700. He go,
what do I say? All the way up to 650. If
they get through it, it's 700 720.
You're welcome.
They're 650s.
Who's this guy? Flowzone.
Oh god.
Markets like to be efficient, folks.
Honestly, that's why markets really like
to be efficient.
So, like if I was short in this, you
think everyone's I'm I'm just a
40year-old, you know, guy wearing
spectacles living in Los Angeles who
used to be a DJ. If I've worked out that
if we leave volume here, all right, and
we want to trade lower and that there's
gap fill potential into there, you know
what? Banks have worked that out. So,
guess what they're going to do? They're
at least going to cover some of their
position into there, which means what?
We're probably going to get a reaction
off that to here. And if they get
through there to here and if they get
through there, think about how thin we
were all the way back up to here. All
right. So, if I can work that out as a
complete numpty, then obviously big
players can work that out. time big
players move the market.
All right, so here you go. Here's the
50s. And if you get through that, I'd
watch, if you're long now for any
reason, I'd watch 90s and then seven
sort of 20s. Great work.
Alex, when should we leave the charts?
Well, if you've if you've hit like a
daily target, if you've had a really
good day, leave. If you've had a bad
day, leave. If you're feeling
frustrated, leave. Um, if you don't
understand what's going on and you want
to learn, stay. If you are waiting for
the next trade setup, stay. If you feel
calm and composed, stay. If you've made
really good money, but you want to just
learn more and switch to SIM, stay.
Don't overtrade though.
Can I show my anchor view uh anchor
profile settings? Yep. Right here. All
right. I use two ticks. I have this set
to tick, but if you're using rows set to
a,000, I use two ticks and I just set it
to 20% width. That's it. That's all I
do. That is all I do.
How do I mark out those value areas or
gaps? Uh the gap was literally go to the
daily, right? Can you see this on the
daily? We we were inefficient here. So
we gapped up this day from no from
Friday that there was a weekly gap up
from Friday to Monday. We gapped up. We
never filled that gap, right? This gap
was left open. We've now just been
efficient and filled it right to the
tick. We just filled it, right? So it's
just the market being efficient.
So if we think about the the gaps the
same way as any form of imbalance,
right? At some point there want to be.
Why have we got a gap there? That
doesn't exist. That's just in Trading
View being stupid. Bad data from CME
again
is the anchored volume profile
on trading view. Yeah, it's a tool guys.
So, it's not an indicator. We go about
this so many days, right? Forecasting.
Come down to volume based anchored
volume profile. Set it to your 930. All
right. It's a tool. There's some videos
for it. Uh if you go to my YouTube,
there's a ton of free videos that I
teach you how to how to use it, how to
use all these things.
You should remix a version of should I
say or should I go with trading lyrics?
What What should we change the lyrics
to? JD, we're do Let's do it in AI. What
should we change the lyrics to? Should I
long or should I short?
Okay. So, we got imbalances now that
we've left from from this upside.
All right. So, we watch this. If buyers
step back in here, we can form a higher
low. All right, if buyers step back in
here, we can form an high low and a
reclaim of that can be a squeeze. If
they trade straight through this and
we're going to get more downside,
you have a course for sale, but do you
have any monthly memberships for
Discord? No, I don't do any monthly
fees. Okay, so everything's included in
the course. So if you do the 20our
course, all right, then Discord comes
for free with it. If you do the beginner
to advanced course, it has Discord in
it. There's no monthly fees, guys. It's
just a straight up you get it as part of
it.
No, still NQ. Still NQ.
How do I trade like you on trading on
Robin Hood? Well, Robin Hood shouldn't
make a difference how you trade. Uh,
I've never traded on Robin Hood. Do they
have like a um sort of professional
platform? Do you have tools on Robin
Hood? I I don't know if you do or can
you link it to Trading View if not?
Okay, so we're coming down towards these
imbalances. Imbalances are 80, 71, and
64. Like I said, if they put in a a
higher low here and start to reclaim
there is a bigger squeeze up for a
repric. If they just flush through all
of this, it would be night night. They
are trying to put in a higher low. They
haven't actually filled in any of those
imbalances yet. They're trying to put in
a higher low here for a move back up at
the moment
and they're going to look for this. So,
I'm actually very very tempted to
consider this long, but I will actually
want to see us either dip a bit lower or
rip a bit higher in base. I don't really
want to trade around here. The
imbalances are a little bit lower, so I
just want to see if we're going to fill
any of these out first.
Maybe they come down for it. So, if we
trade down to sort of 80s and below and
hold and then pivot back above 50s or
definitely 70s, I'll consider the long
on a rotation. It's my least favorite
trade. We all know Alex hates that
trade. But if we do something like this,
I will consider this play here. Right
from here, if we hold this, they are
starting to base here. They haven't
filled the imbalances though, which is
annoying me a little bit. But they are
trying to put in the higher low. This
can be possible here. They're starting
to do it. Oh, you dirty buggers. Trying
to do it without me.
Trying to do it without me.
So, the gap that just filled is no
longer valid as a key area. I mean, it's
still a key area, right? Or we we're
still in it. We are still in it.
um you know we can trade below if they
if they lose the gap. Let me show you.
Let me get you onto an hourly chart
because it's hard for me to explain all
this otherwise. Right, you've got two
things happening here in this hourly
chart. If we zoom left,
remember all the way back to here. All
right, this was a pivot right here
Monday the 24th. The gap was down into
this low which we just tapped. If we
lose that gap, right, we're going to
come into this area which was a big
section that we bid off. Now if we think
about what happened here, why was it so
important? We went into a major sell and
big big institutional buyers down here
said no. And this was the start of a
huge drive up. So we are here. We can
maybe come into here. We probably don't
expect this in one go. Not in one
session. It's possible. Like I said,
anything is possible if they go full
risk off. But we're into a big area.
This is also like this contract sort of
started here. We're starting to go
beyond this contract, right? We're
starting to go back on the contracts.
What's the old contract? We're on an H.
Was it an M contract? My brain can't
think. Right. So, I don't think we're
going to come below here in one session.
I think we will eventually come below
here. Right. But, we have to be aware of
that. We're probably going to see some
reaction down here at some point. Think
about how heavy we've got, right? We're
probably unlikely to see this go
straight down, right? And just keep
puking. What we're more likely to see is
probably something like this and then a
pull back in and liquidity being built
out here for a session or two, right?
And maybe one more trap next week and
then that maybe. And then if we get that
move, what are we going to look for?
Like we've talked about on the dailies
the last few days, right? If we we're
going to get that catch-up trade. the
undercut and the 200 day are starting to
match up really really well. This area
will be such a big cover point uh for
anyone that got short. So all the
institutions who took this gap fill here
failed break above right this is your if
you think about woff there's your spring
failed breakout there's your sign of
strength there's the continuation this
is to the other side this would be a big
cover point now if they let go of this
oh my gosh it's going to get dangerous
right we have a node down here into 24k
they will not want to lose that too
quickly all right I would expect a bid
to start developing somewhere down here
for a back test up here, right? Think
about we're leaving this. We will expect
to bid somewhere down here for a back
test there. If they reclaim it, uber
bullish all the way back up. If they
reject this, then we can think about a
big bare market back down into some of
these tariff areas. Can't rule it out,
guys. I'm not willing to rule anything
out. I can only trade what's on the
chart. Both of those things are
possible,
right? They're trying to do this higher
low right now. talked about they keep
getting stuck in this block. You can see
this gray box that I marked out was very
very key
for entering trades. Do I use market or
limits? Where possible? I will use limit
orders. But uh you kind of need trend to
be going on your side for a limit order.
All right. So like if I'm when I was
here, I was able to use a limit order,
right? But actually here today, I didn't
use limit order. I used a market because
the trap came and I was like, well, I
need to get in now before that happens.
All right. That's right. It's not a
chase for me. It's just like I need to
get in now and if I lose a tick or two,
I don't care because I'm have that much
conviction. What I will not do is if
we're moving away, try and market in
down here. All right? So, it's limit
where possible. But if I miss it by a
tick or two and it's moving fast, I
don't mind marketing. As long as I'm
buying still in discount or I'm selling
that market in premium, it's okay. But
where possible, I always limit. And I
try and cover with my limits. That's why
I put limits out for my cover positions
or my partial positions all the time. If
I miss it by a tick, I just drag it down
and fill it. All right, now we're into
those imbalances. So 77s is one. Then
there's one at 61 and there's another
one at 53. They will need to hold this
and then pivot back up. Otherwise, we
will break down and we go for new lows.
So like I said, we haven't seen they
will need to hold this, pivot back above
all this for me to be interested in the
long. Not going to bid down here. I need
to see them do something like this for
me to be any interest at all. But we
have just started to fill some of these
imbalances
right down into here. We talked about
these imbalances all the way down here.
They will need to now pivot above all of
this and then maybe I'm interested.
Maybe it will be a counter trend trade,
but it will be I'd have to reclaim uh
value and think about a rotation. It
would need to confirm to me the only way
I'm trading this right is basically if
this is a failed breakout and we come
back inside value and I think we can
trade value for the day if I think we're
going to do a rotation in here for the
day. If we're going to stay aggressive
obviously I'm not going to bid, right?
I'm not going to bid. I'm also not going
to sell here. It's very hard for me to
sell here now when I have the best sell
position for the day. Very hard. Sulky
Alex. Sulky sulky.
Do I trade London? No, I don't. Um, I
live in I live in Los Angeles, so I am
asleep during London.
I'm asleep during London.
What volume profile is it? It is I need
to do a sheet for you guys, don't I? It
is an anchored volume profile based on
the New York session. So, anchored to
9:30. So, they just filled that
imbalance like we talked about and we
are starting to catch a bid. All right,
if I show you here, right, we just
filled this imbalance on this long wick.
We left the one tiny piece left and
they're starting to catch a bid. Now, if
they can pivot above, then maybe it's
got a shot, right? Maybe it's got a
shot. I will not be long down here. It
will need to prove to me with higher
lows, right? I'm not going to go fishing
today in a bare market. It would need to
prove to me with higher lows.
What's the cost of the course? Uh, it
should be 699. If he hasn't changed it,
I'm going to get very upset. I've been
asking him and he promised me this week,
Blow Zone Trader, but if not, it's going
to be 649 until I shout at my uh
web developer. It's still $649.
God damn it. Okay, it's $649 right now
for the 20our course and it's $399 for
the um orderflow course and if you get a
bundle, I think you get $100 off
together.
Trappy PA, we're just building out now.
We're building out now.
Probably think about spy into uh 800s.
And we can probably think about a spy.
Probably think about spy into 75s.
Uh has anyone got gamma up? I would
imagine 75 is going to be massive. Uh
just cuz it's a whole number. They love
stuff like that. Um we have an old pivot
down there right into 75. So if we look
at 16th of December and 18th of December
and if we look at the high of the 25th
of November and the 20th of November and
the 14th of November, I'm going to guess
uh 675 on SPY is a big level. I'm going
to have a guess. I would imagine it's a
big level. All right, initial balance
now set. All right, so here's the IB. So
those of you who like the IB trade, we
can think about the fail breakout of IB
or the hold of IB back to VWAP. All
right. If we're going to get a trend
day, we're going to need to reject IB.
Remember, we are down fairly
significantly on this session already
off the highs,
right? It's a 420 point move. Okay. So,
if we start to bid above here, the move
back to VWAP is very probable, isn't it?
This is filling the imbalance. They're
trying to put in the higher low. If we
start to reclaim some of these areas,
it's possible that they squeeze back up
to the VWOPS. And they're going to have
to reclaim 660s. All right. And then
maybe I'm interested. Maybe I'm
interested if they can do that.
Do I see any bids on the 200 day? Uh,
let me just remind myself where that 200
day is.
24200.
Hang on a second.
No, no one's down there yet. Too far
down.
Here's 24, right? 24200
240. Yeah, no one's down there yet.
20 24500 is 132 lot, but uh there's no
one really under that. No, no one
notable size yet. Not yet.
Okay. Right. So, I'll tell you now
sellers at 81 is where they keep getting
stuck. 81 and under. Um, and definitely
57 is basically that low of day auction.
I would like a bit more excess really
when I look at that. But I'm definitely
not going to long down here. We'll have
to pivot and hold.
It will have to pivot and hold.
I was trying to catch up with what you
guys are saying in chat. I've missed
some of this. Sorry. Uh,
to enable subtitles in your videos, you
as a creator must activate the feature
on YouTube Studio. Go to settings.
Unfortunately, I can't hear you because
I'm deaf. Go to YouTube settings. See, I
can't work out how to do it on the live
videos. I want to do it for you. Um,
I cannot figure out how to do it when
we're live. I'm going to try and have a
look now.
If anyone knows, let let me know. But I
can do it on videos that I post, but I
can't do it on the live videos at the
moment. Language and captions, English
recording date, remixing category.
Yeah, I can't see a way to do it. I wish
I could do it. I would not like nothing
more than full inclusion.
I don't think there's a way it can do it
live. Probably because it can't um work
out what I'm saying. Unless there's like
an AI tool we can do for it.
Yeah, I can't see it. I'm really sorry.
I'm really really sorry. It's If I'm
wrong there, I I will I will do some
extensive research when I got get off
stream to try and find it for you.
I use bit map and ninja, not quant
tower.
Can you please show the footprint chart
on how trapped buyers and sellers are
looking like? Uh yeah.
So at the moment we have some buyers
caught up here at 649 and above
and we don't have much excess. What I
was just saying like I'd like to see if
this was like big big red it would feel
better. If this was like a big red bar
uh here and we were pivoting up, it
would feel better. But we are starting
to hold that ID.
So I don't love the low of day, but it's
not it's not the best auction at the low
on Ninja Trader. How does it look? Does
it look a bit better? I mean, there is
on Ninja Trader, I can tell you it's a
little bit better at these lows.
All right, based on tick data, you can
see sellers keep coming here.
like I keep talking about 57s. They keep
piling in. You can see on this candle,
this five minute candle uh 1020 they
piled in. This is the imbalance which
has now been filled like we talked
about. They've just piled again in again
and got caught. So like I said 57s would
be a big level and then uh 71s and then
we need to pivot above all of that. We
need to leave sellers trapped down here
and then if we can put in higher lows
and pivot up, I'll be interested. Not
before then. I'm not going to play and
fish in here in what is a very bearish
market overall. It's too risky. If
you're bidding here, right, and then and
these sellers win and you get wicked
down to here and your stops here, you're
going to get filled down here. So, I'm
not going to be willing to do that. I
want to see strength, all right, for me
to really come and bid in.
They're doing a decent job so far,
though.
is on the right hand side of the screen.
Maybe you can't enable it while live.
Yeah, I can't see how to enable it while
live. That's it.
Yeah. See, I can do all the automatic
captions
uh once it's like um
finished. But when it's live, it's not
giving me a way of doing it. I'm really
sorry. I will extensively look into it
and maybe there's a way we can run some
AI that listens to my voice and prints
it down below. I will have a look for
you. I will I will make an effort to do
that. What are we trading? We're trading
ENQ.
Trading ENQ. Alex at 10:15. Why does
your one minute chart have a gap but
mine doesn't? I don't know because
Trading View for whatever reason has had
some fault there. But there's no gap
there. It's just whatever data from CME
to Trading View has just been terrible
there. But there is no gap there. It
doesn't exist.
You can do it before the stream. Really?
Okay, I'll have another look, Abdullah.
I will I will try um tomorrow. We we
I'll try, but I couldn't see it. I did
look yesterday as well.
You're the best. Thanks for your time.
You're welcome. Right, they're still
trying to bid down here. There's some
bids at 550s. Like I said, there is a
bigger lot uh underneath at 500. Yeah,
there's a bigger lot still at 500. So,
I'm still waiting here. I'm not going to
go fishing for the longs. We're not
fishing for longs today. We'll wait to
see uh if they trap sufficient and start
to hold, but we are seeing some sort
compression down here. So, maybe a
flush, you know, trap even more under
here, leave a nice excess and then do
it. I mean, that would be really good if
we then did it
for that move back up and we would we're
going to have to respect this guy here
and each little node here. So, if we do
think about this, we'll be uh trying to
get into these and if we get through
this relief into that.
Do I use an indicator to plot the gaps?
I do not. I do it everything manually.
Is there a solution for bracket trading
with Apex on Trader 8? I have no idea.
Um, I use Ninja Trader for that reason.
Does my course also work on options?
Yeah, it works on everything. Uh, even
if you don't trade futures, it's all
markets work the same way. Doesn't
matter what you trade. Right. Starting
to see some aggressive buyers trying to
step in here. Starting to perk my
interest a little bit. Oh, you mother
clockers. Right, back to this Vpo.
Uh 30s is the level here. 30s and then
70s. So, they've got to start basing
above some of this to per my interest.
We got this is fair value. Remember, on
the day, this is where we've had the
most buyers and sellers operate on the
day. We don't I don't love the excess
down here. I really don't love the
excess down there. It's the only thing
that's making me not love it. But it's
possible they're going to go for one of
these IB to VWAP. What we call the Tyson
trade. It's possible.
Here they go. They're moving VPO up.
There we go.
Dirty, dirty. They're going to make this
very, very, very hard to get involved.
But we held above those 60s or 57s at
the lows.
Oh my god, look at this. is there's 100
points already off that line.
Well, these sellers are about to get
wrecked. All right, so if we start
basing here, they were going to get that
VWOP trade. We're going to have to watch
these nodes here into the top side of
the gap.
In it early nice, Tyson,
you're going to get it. You're going to
get it. I would just be be careful into
this sort of top of this gray box that
we're at now. You want pull back to hold
VPo. Now, if you hold uh point control
and they base, you got a shot.
You got a shot at it.
This is your target. Target one, target
two, I'd say.
And we said I think we get a rotational
date. So you need this to hold here. You
do not want it under this now. It must
hold there or above and then coming to
this and this. So here we go back
towards VPOT coming now. They've got a
hold above this now. Failing to do that
will mean uh nothing. No interest. It's
a good hold into the low volume node.
Watching 20s here.
There's Vpo 20s here to see if they trap
into 20s. I'm not long yet folks. I'm
waiting to see if they trap into these
20s
cuz I've got a node there that I'm
looking at.
Very good so far. Rebid that.
Coming back for it again. Someone's
flashing at 600 though. It's a rebid.
That's a higher low there on uh on but
can they squeeze now?
Yep.
I want to see this guy at 35 move up.
Nice.
Come on. Bid at 35. Move up. Don't just
sit there. What was that? He bid 35,
pulled it, and then sold it. What a
dirty [\h__\h] I'm out of this. I don't
like that. I just put a starter on on
that last move down reaction 20s. I
don't like what he just did. So, I don't
know if anyone wants to rewind that, but
he bid 35, pulled pulled it, and then
sold 40s instantly. Very dirty.
They do that now after I left it because
of him be upset with myself.
Right, they're offering 75 now.
Hopefully they lift this for you
straight to 75s.
You want this? There's someone playing
around at 1335 is being a bit of a bit
of a silly boy.
Want him to like stop being a silly boy
and just start stepping up here. 50s. If
you break this, you should go 6575
pretty quickly. Come on. There you go.
Boom. There you go. All right. Now
they're going to lift. There you go.
There you go. Oh,
beautiful. Tyson, you're going to get
it. All right. So, there was the hold of
20s and Vpo. We talked about the higher
low. All right. I didn't want to go
fishing today. There's the higher low.
So, I had a go and then I got shaken out
not liking what I saw on the tape, but
uh he came back in and there's the
ripper and this is your target now. So,
you can take some off into this node. Be
very careful. And then you're looking
for VWAP and then you're looking for
sort of 96s. Hopefully, this would be
down here by that point. So, basically
800s. You've got another 100 points in
this if they start lifting it folks
because this will be the rotation,
right? This will be the rotation we
talked about.
This is huge. if they get through that
squeezy squeezy. But I would imagine the
rotation will be to about 800.
So definitely some to sort of where we
are now. 7s 715s squeeze through 75s
will lift to 800. Sellers getting
trapped to that low like we talked
about. Wasn't huge excess but we talked
about it right here. All right. Remember
this right here? These sellers down here
got trapped twice at the low and then
they pivoted and look at the delta
change. The exchange we went straight
positive delta and we are lifting now.
We are attacking this shelf at sevens
through sevens. We can potentially lift
at eights, but I'd be paying yourself
into sevens.
Hopefully that made sense.
Oh, that's frustrating for me. That's
frustrating for me.
was in it. Was in it. And then I didn't
like his uh his spoofy behavior.
Can you make a cheat sheet for Anchor
volume profile? There's a vid there's a
free video for it, Marlon, on my on my
YouTube. You can watch some stuff there.
Nice. Lots of you taking the IB to VWOP
trade. You're about to get it. Don't be
a dick here though. Make sure there's a
big big node here. All right. Understand
that you should get it right. But you
must, you know, pay yourself a little
bit into this volume node. Huge node
here. But through that, you should get
New York VW up. And if you get through
720s,
there is a chance to fill all the way
back up here in towards this sort of
790s. All right? So, I would be paying
myself a lot into here, a bit into here,
and then the last lot into this, right
into this guy here.
But you've got to respect this guy here.
Please respect this guy here.
Um, anchor to 9:30. Yeah, anchored to
9:30.
TPS VWAP and value area low. Value area
low. Uh,
do you mean value area high or do you
mean previous day value area low all the
way up here? W is asking a lot. I'd say
TP's a little bit now where we've just
been this node a little bit. 7:15.
Well, a lot now. A bit 715, a bit 800. I
would not expect it necessarily to get
above 800 based on value. We do that,
you'll see expansion. But like this node
here, you see how key this node here is?
He's being key. He's important.
Rest of today going to rotate around
Fair Valley. I think so. Uh who is that?
Samir. Yeah, my I think we're going to
need to build out some volume. I really
think we're going to need to do it.
We've had like I talked about on the
hourlys. All right,
here's your failed break. Look above and
fail. There's your first rejection.
There's your lower high. The same on
silver, guys. Think about the alltime
high on silver. Pull back. Fail to
recover. Okay, we start the sell. There
we go. Start the sell. Start the sell.
Right. We're going to need to build
volume here, right? To get down into
here. So either we're going to base here
or we're going to return inside, build
some volume, little trap, and then come
back for it next week. Very possible,
right? We can't. Unless they're going to
just if they're just like, we need to be
out of everything. This market is
[\h__\h] And they can do that. Then we
will just keep going straight down. All
right. The market has done that before.
It can do it again. That requires them
to just completely want out of all
inventory. All right. So when have we
done that before? Well, tariffs.
All right. when they
we think about this move here in the
tariffs on the daily failed to make a
new high volume trapped here went inside
had one more go and then they went [\h__\h]
all right this breakdown here [\h__\h] get
me out of all the inventory and then it
was too discounted and they bit it back
up. If we look back to every crash,
every actual crash, it looks the same,
right? Where we get overly aggressive
24s. So this was the carry trade. This
was the carry trade August 24. Right.
[\h__\h] Big inventory dump.
Overaggressive. Lower bowls. Pick it
back up.
Co will be the same. It will be an
aggressive move.
Where are you? Co. Was that it? There.
Did I just miss it? There. That's the co
one.
All right. Straight down. Failed to get
back inside. Dump.
We'd have to go back to like 08. Here's
one here. 15 2015.
08 took a while to develop. It actually
took to 09 and it was walked.
Right. So, we did this
failed to get a new high. Aggressive
failed to make a new high. And then this
one here was the big panic.
Right, that's the panic. Look at the
5day 20-day but lower bowl. Right,
history repeats itself. Same thing. So,
we're in the same kind of setup here,
but we're going to need some liquidity,
I think,
unless they go full panic. And remember,
we've got earnings tonight as well. Mag
earnings still
gap filled. The only thing left now is
this 200 day, this guy right here. Is
there anything left to to really target
as a low hanging fruit?
Wait, I'll be right back.
Okay.
H catching up with what he said. Right.
Big W. Lots of you got that then. Um
excited for the Apex account giveaway.
Yep. I'll do it out and do it um once we
get those likes up. How many likes we
at?
There's 1,257
of you watching. We have 465 likes,
guys. I don't think that's very fair. I
think that's not fair. Well, the first
trade today was for 200 points if you
took the full move up. The second trade
today, if you took it with me, you only
got 80 points. If you continued to hold
for the gap fill, you got 330 points.
Uh, this stream is completely free. It
costs you nothing. I teach you as I go.
I'd really appreciate it if you could at
least hit the like button. Come on,
people. Be kind.
Be kind, right? It doesn't cost you
anything.
Alex bought the 20our course. Nice.
Looking forward to working with you.
Alex, you're goated. I just passed five
evals. Thank you, brother. Love it. Nice
work, folks. Nice work.
So, still the same level down here,
right? Where we trapped those sellers.
It's still the same level holding,
right? Can This is why I love footprint.
All right. down here. We are still not
letting these sellers out. All right,
we're trading around point of control.
Now, I don't love trading around point
control, but these sellers are still
stuck versus 60. If you're a bottom
fisher, basically, you can be long
versus 60s. Uh, you would not want it.
You'd want to be as long as close to 60
as possible, and you could risk it. But
for me, I'm not a bottom fisher. I don't
pick bottoms. It's not what I'm trying
to do. I'm want to wait to see if we
rotate. It's very possible, though. Look
how we're building this out. This is
like a B-shaped profile. All right. We
can just build out lots and lots in
here. Maybe they snap it this way. Maybe
they get lift this way. But this is
definitely the rotation that they're
starting to build.
I would actually like to see this lift.
Okay, I want to see this lift. Not
necessarily just cuz I want to get long.
It's just going to offer better
opportunities for the market for
tomorrow and this afternoon if we can
just start to lift this up a little bit.
Charlie, that's very kind of you. Newbie
here from Hong Kong. Thank you very
much, Charlie. I'm going go and get a
nice coffee after this stream. Thank
you. Thank you. Thank you.
Lots of lot sounds like lots of you have
had a good day. That's great to hear.
Today is my last
Today is my last day to pass my evals.
Please help. I mean, I think you've had
opportunities. All right? Like, we can
only trade what the market's giving us.
There there was an opportunity here.
Like I said, I'm waiting for the higher
low. There was an opportunity here. If
you wanted to go fishing, you had to
respect this node like I talked about.
That's why I said I would be selling a
big chunk into there. All right. The
main trend, remember, is still downside,
but we are outside the daily Ballinger
bands. Alex can't draw a B very well
today. Right. We're outside the daily
Ballinger bands. So your risk assessment
for more downside is not very good right
and we talk about riskreward maybe we
can get down into this but your
positioning remember when we trade we
are always thinking about what is the
location and what is the momentum
momentum's been great for bearish moves
right really really good for bearish
moves and bearish moves where the
location today wasn't very good which is
why we looked for that the location here
for a short is not good right we are
trading you'll remember this is the
lowest point we have traded since the
24th of November. All right, we're in
February, folks. We don't really want to
start a new short position, right? If
we're at the lowest point since
November, do we? No, no, no, no, no. We
don't want to do that. It means we're
trying to sell deep in discount to get
lower. Very, very risky to do that.
We want to be careful.
Alex, I'm an XDJ. bought my Technics uh
1210s back in 1992. I love the streams
and appreciate what you do. Thank you.
Hey, awesome, man. Awesome. Awesome.
What type What type of uh stuff did you
used to play?
Why is everyone long? Not everyone's
long. It's not that everyone's long. The
short was from here to here. It might
very well be that you rotate under it.
It might, but the there's not for me. I
don't think there's a good short
position down here. It's more likely to
see relief at the moment. All right.
It's more likely to see relief unless we
build out lots here for another hour or
so and then let go and then even then
you got to be very careful about a
failed breakout. But if you do get a
sustained breakout, there is a move down
to here. I just won't be short down
here. It's way way way too risky in my
mind. That's just how I play. I was
short earlier today up here. Like I
said,
people tuning in here from all over the
world. Fantastic. We've got Hong Kong,
we've got Sweden in the house, England
in the house. Just found my your stream
on Monday. I caught a trading with you
and helped me pass my first eval. Now
fighting to keep it. Just take your
time. Nice and slow. Nice and slow.
Don't need to go pushing too hard.
Another Flowzone member. Thank you for
joining. Um,
Panto Crater, I think that's how you say
it. Thank you for joining.
Bought your course last week. I watch
your streams every day. My trading has
improved a lot in this short time. Thank
you so much. Hey, nice. Tim,
how long does it usually take for Apex
to tell you you passed your eval? If you
passed it today, you'll get an email
after the close tonight before the open
tomorrow. Purchased your course last
night. Looking forward to opening my
eyes on how the market works. Hey, lots
of you joining. I can't wait to work
with all of you.
First time here from UK. Welcome.
Welcome. How do you join? Uh, how do you
join? What the Discord are you talking
about? It you do the 20our course. All
right. On my website, links down below
or you can see the pinned link above
that has everything in there. Can I go
over the volume settings? I've got I've
got I've got to get that on a Nightbot.
I'm going to get Nightbot to tell you
this. All right. Anchored volume profile
width 20. All right. Ticks per row is
what I have it set to as two. That's it.
And I anchor it to the 930 open. Right.
That's it.
watching from the UAE. Nice, nice, nice,
nice. I love Dubai.
Watching from Essex. Look at this. Look
at where everyone's joining in from.
It's awesome. Canada, Thailand,
Brighton, UK. Big up Brighton. I got
lots of friends there. Uh, Sleepy Sam.
Uh, is where's this? DSAS, New York,
Italy, Germany, Essex, Argentina,
Singapore, Sweden, Paris, New Zealand,
Colombia, Oklahoma, India, Sydney,
Thailand, uh, more from Dubai, Hungary,
Amsterdam, Uruguay,
Austin. I'm honestly considering a move
there very soon. Belgium, more from
Brighton. I love it. I got so many
friends in Brighton. I grew up just
outside of Brighton, West Sussex where I
grew up, but all my friends uh most of
them went to Brighton College in Lancing
actually. Uh San Diego, Texas,
Philippines,
Jordan. Welcome, welcome. Morocco,
Morocco, living in Essex. I love it.
More from Singapore, Denver, Brazil.
Lots of you from Texas. Well, maybe
we'll do like a get together in Texas if
I if I end up moving there. Florida, New
York, Perth, Australia. Love it.
Caribbean, France. Wow.
South Africa, Nigeria,
Atlanta. Wow. Wow. Guys, this is
amazing. So many from Austin. I love it,
guys. I'm going to do go and do a wrecky
there soon to see if I want to live
there. Um I was looking I've been doing
a lot of research. So, the two areas
I've been looking in are uh just outside
of Georgetown and then one like 15
minutes from Austin. Uh like east
southeast Austin. I don't know. Maybe
you guys can tell me where's where's the
best place to live. But I want to be not
too far from I want to be able to walk
or a short drive to get like, you know,
a decent beer and watch some bands and
stuff like that. And then I don't mind
being a little bit further out from
Austin if I have to be. But
are you from Brighton? Did you ever go
to drum and bass nights at Vogs? Uh, no.
I used to go to, so growing up I used to
go to Zap and Honey Club and then I used
to DJ in Honey Club. Um, and uh, what
was some of the after hours places
called down there? Uh, under the arches.
I used to play there a lot, man. Back in
the day. A lot.
British expat in Cyprus. Good move
there. Very tax efficient. I was also
looking there.
Romania, Florida, Vancouver. So many.
What other key levels do you look at in
the morning? New York open VP previous
day high and lows. Yeah, that's it. So,
uh, previous day um, value area, high
and lows. Previous week value area and
obviously point controls as well and the
current developing. So, previous day,
previous week, current developing, and
then also obviously the high and any key
high and low pivots and any big nodes. I
know guys, like some of you might think,
why aren't we talking about trading
here? Uh the market's going sideways,
right? We're in like a 100 point
rotation range down here. You can see
value starting to get tighter and
tighter and tighter, right? My
expectation is that we're just going to
do this for a while and I don't want to
trade range. Anyone who trades with me
knows that I do not like trading range.
Do we have trap traders at the bottom?
Yeah, I will be willing to or I would
have been more willing to do that, but
now New York VW's there. It's becoming
less and less interesting for me for the
day. So, we just have to let this
develop. See what we can get. See if
there's another trade in the next hour
for us.
Shush in the arches in Brighton. Was
that what it was called or is that what
it's called now?
Trading day is dead today. I mean, it
had some we we caught these, right? Had
some really good good nice moves. But
remember, trap traders, trap shorts, big
drive up. Trap longs, big drive down.
Build liquidity. We will get a move once
it's finished building liquidity. All
right. Right. We are in a liquidity
building stage now. The market has to
build some liquidity for us to get the
next move. It will come. It will come.
Alex, why not make a detailed video
explaining all the indicators you use
and how you actually apply them? That
way, whenever someone asks the same
question, you can simply point them out
on the video. Yeah, I mean, it's it's a
good idea. I should probably do that. I
mean, there are quite a few videos on my
YouTube for it. Most what most people
ask is just they want the settings for
this. Everyone seems to ask the seconds
for this. So, I'll probably get Nightbot
to just post it in chat.
Have I been to Switzerland? Yes, I have.
Uh, DJed in Switzerland. Uh,
don't remember the club. I remember I
remember coming out of the club the next
morning at the early hours and it was
the first time I'd ever seen a Tesla
ever, ever, ever. So, that would have
been like 2014,
2015.
B Cave and Lakeway is awesome. So,
Lakeway is northwest, isn't it? I was I
was I was looking there. That did look
really nice. The houses there look
lovely. I haven't heard of Bave, so I'll
check that out.
Horizon now was whoosh. Okay, that makes
sense.
If you say that, we are fine. We'll be
buying till lunchtime. Alex got to let
us know. Do we bid or do we hold? Idea
for a new song lyrics. Oh, do we bid or
do we hold? I get what you're saying.
That's funny. It's a good one. How do
you know the buyers and sellers were
trapped? Uh because they were
aggressively, right? They were
aggressively selling down here. So, this
delta here can be seen on
this footprint
down here. But even better, it can be
seen on Ninja Trader at the lows.
Right. So if I bring NT up,
right, right here,
these aggressive participants down here
and down here, right? These are market
order selling. They're trying to get the
breakdown. We can see big delta here, a
value area low. Did we break below it?
No. What then happened? We squeezed up.
Right? So bids came back in, sellers
came back in, tried to get back down to
that level. They haven't been let out.
Right? So they got out like break even
or as close to and now we're in this
range rotation. All right? So I know
sellers are trapped down there because I
can I can quite literally see them
trapped down there. Right? I can quite
literally see them trapped down there.
It's not a guesswork. It's not like, oh,
the candle says, no, I can literally see
where they came in and got themselves
stuck. And until they are let out, all
right, they will remain stuck. And what
I would also be very concerned about
today if I was a short seller is if too
many of them pile in down here and you
get this that is where a bigger squeeze
will happen. They will be looking for
this down here. But like we talked about
positionally. All right. When we talk
about location and momentum where are we
right now? Are we in a good location to
be short? All right. Are we in a good
location to be short? This is not a good
location to be short, folks.
Down here. This is is an awful location
to be short. Where were the good
locations? Well, the failed breakout,
this location here was a great location.
This rejection of here yesterday was a
great location. This drive up this
morning was not a bad location. It
wasn't prime. Prime was up here. This
location down here, it is terrible. That
is a terrible location to be short. All
right? Because your risk is for this up
here, isn't it? Right? So, you don't
want to be short down there as a new
money short for that when your target is
just there. That's a one to one at best
on a swing position. So I don't want to
be short down there. I want to manage my
expectation. Where we got short this
morning was a good location to be short.
Why? Let's just think more about trapped
volume. Why did we get this flush here
this morning? Think about this box. Same
same condition, right? This box
overnight. There's your box overnight.
Think about all the volume in here who
are buyers. When they get stopped out,
what happens? They become sellers. Boom.
Then sellers try and sell the low.
Idiots. We buy that back to where the
trap buyers are. What happens? No
acceptance back in. So what happens? All
these trap buyers, they start selling
break even. Break even. Boom. Back down.
Do we want to sell this low? No, we
don't. More likely that we're probably
going to return up here some point and
then maybe there's a sell. But even that
is not prime location, right? Really,
the best sell is going to be way up here
at some point. Right? It's just
structure, guys. It is just structure.
We don't like selling lows. It's asking
for it the same way as we don't like
buying highs.
Do I use fibs? Yeah, I do. I use returns
back inside for fibs uh for golden
pockets. I use it for extensions as
well. Random question, but have you ever
been to a Man United game is on my back
bucket list? Well, I'm an Arsenal
supporter. So the only game I've been to
which Man United game is United Arsenal.
Actually the m the last game I went to
see United Arsenal was at uh the Sofi
last year
in LA. Do flow zones only work on time
based candle candlesticks? No, they will
work on tick charts or anything.
Have I noticed value areas differ
depending on time frame? Yes, especially
for Trading View. The lower time frame
that you can draw a value area on or
volume on, the more accurate it is.
Absolutely. Absolutely. It's just how
Trading View uh processes the data.
Still waiting for this to build out,
guys. I I know like we're talking less
and less about trading at the moment.
We're just waiting for this to build out
at the moment. All right.
Uh,
what are you guys saying? Sorry. Why
would you not short sellers not hit
their stop loss already? Do you hold on
for dear life? Why would you Why would
the short sellers not have hit their
stop loss in this move up here?
I mean, they might well have done above
this for sure. And then if those sellers
became buyers, all right, then it let
the market makers sell back into them
for sure. Like that's that's what
happened up there. But I would not
guarantee they all hit it. Uh you'd be
surprised how long uh people hold on
for. But I get what you're saying. I'm
I'm with you. But uh you would be very
surprised.
What is that volume profile on the right
on the daily chart? Uh,
let me get over to it. Oh, okay. So,
this is
pivoted off the all-time high. All
right. So, this is off the alltime high.
So, it's showing all the volume created
from here. So, all of this and this one
here is for the last 12 months. All
right. So, I know that this level here
is a big node. You see this node? We've
left it. All right. We might travel back
into here and if we get really lucky
down to here. All right. But it's very
possible we're going to need some form
of retest of this first, isn't it? Over
the next day or week, retest this. And
if they resell that or this node here or
this node here, then we can look for
this move here. And then Alex is
probably going to be thinking about
being a buyer somewhere down here.
Unless we're going to get very heavy and
let the whole thing go. But I might
start being a speculatory buyer down
here
cuz that will be then
think from the highs
high down to 200 day be 10% and if we
can get into this node yeah 10.33% if we
come all the way back down to this pivot
it'll be a 12% pullback which would
still be healthy. So somewhere in here
is probably a very healthy pullback.
It's probably a very very healthy
pullback.
Alex, Austin, Trafford is worse than LA.
Way behind on infrastructure. Still
better in better in Texas and
California. Yeah, I I know, man. I know.
But the taxes are better.
The taxes are better. And I might fancy
a change. I'll see.
Think
we swipe the lows and then ping up on ES
S2 and ENQ below the S2 pivot big value
area uh on ES. Well, ES. Yeah, you're
you're about to sweep the lows now.
Well, we all are about on everything
right now. Vick still holding price up.
Like I said, I think I'd be watching the
75s on SPY. You still got another dollar
to go there on the spy. I'd be watching
those 75s. I imagine there's a big area
there.
Arsenal doing good at the moment. We're
doing great, man. We're doing great.
We'll see how we go the next couple
months. Going to the World Cup. Yeah,
I'll definitely be going to the World
Cup. I I applied for lottery tickets
here. Didn't get any. Did not get any,
but I applied, so I'll probably just
have to buy some. All right, still
holding there. So, you got divergence.
These sellers are still stuck right now
under here. You have divergence. ES just
swiped below. ENQ didn't. Still too
early. Like I said, I will not be
fishing down here. I'm not going to be
fishing today. It was going to have to
pivot and hold.
What time frame is this? One minute time
frame, guys. Purple cloud deep flow zone
uh EMA 7289.
Do I think we chop around for the rest
of the day? Yeah, I do. I do. uh is the
only thing right is if they are adamant
on just keeping selling then they can
use this volume to go lower but I think
we will do some [\h__\h] for the rest of
the day just because of where we are on
the daily I think it's going to struggle
to keep moving too much lower I'll give
you a readout on the MAG right Tesla
3.60% down Nvidia 1% down Microsoft
3.37% down Meta pretty much flat Google
3.80% 80% down. Amazon 4.39% down. Apple
1% down. Uh overall we're 1.61% down. If
we look at the daily, if we think about
the size of the move this week, it's now
go from the high of this week.
Where's
just measure this out?
Wednesday, Monday. So, we go from the
high of this week to the low.
All right, we are almost 1,500 points
down on the week. If we measure out a
sigma from like Ballinger
and we do a third standard deviation of
the Ballinger right now,
where is that? It would actually take us
to the to the 20-day. So, we're we're
about two and a half standard deviations
from the 20-day right now. So remember
the get you on the chart. So remember
the 20-day is our mean, right?
Ballingers are are two standard
deviations. We're about a two and a half
because we're at the midpoint of this. A
three standard deviation will take us
right down into this. It's very very
very very unlikely. It's possible, but
it's very unusual that we do standard
deviation moves outside of two. We're at
two and a half. To get to three is
asking a lot. You are going to need mass
panic in the market to do that. It's not
to say it can't happen, but it it's
unlikely. Okay, it's unlikely. If you
even if you just want to like look at
the pivot on like NQ1,
right? We are trading right into the
August highs. So, if we just go
I'm going to put you on NQ1, okay?
Rather than the H contract just for a
second. We are coming right into these
pivots. All right, we're right into this
high of August. Right? We're asking a
lot for it to just do this, right, in
one go. What's more reasonable is like a
back test of this and then down here.
All right. And into this basket where we
went sideways for a while and then we
broke out from, retested, broke out,
undercut, retested, held, failed,
breakout, back down, probably retest
here somewhere in here. It's probably
coming at some point. All right. All
right. So, they're asking a lot to keep
just driving lower and lower and lower
and lower without a back test.
Manage your expectations, right? It's
why I wouldn't be short down here for
me.
We left Cali for Oklahoma a few years
ago. Love it out here. Have you seen gas
is 188 a gallon? Well, there you go,
Jason. Exactly. Exactly that.
if there is a negative to using bookmap
on Think or Swim compared to the actual
application. I've never used it on Think
or Swim, so I can't comment. I cannot
comment
property tax there sucks. Yeah, it does.
But it would still be far less than I
pay in total tax here for sure.
But yeah, I mean I'll consider anywhere.
I'm considering Miami as well. I will
consider anywhere.
Alex, the order flow course is more for
mean reversion. I use volume profile for
mean reversion. It's for everything.
It's for everything because anything's
possible once you understand the order
flow. But yeah, a lot of people use
orderflow for mean reversion. It's it
can be very it can lure you into bottom
picking. So you want to be careful with
that.
Have I seen a 20-day moving average plus
ballinger bands one standard deviation
up? Have you you have a No, it a 20-day
with normal standard deviation with
normal Ballinger bands are two standard
deviations.
Nice. Rick
moved from LA to Dallas in 2021 outside
the ocean. Thought about Los Angeles.
Yeah, that's the one thing. It is the
ocean. That's the one thing that I have
to let go of which is really hard
because I live very close to it. Can
literally see it from where I live. I
can cycle there in 5 minutes.
Okay, so they're coming down for the
swipe. Remember, they keep getting stuck
down here. There's a swipe and a return
back inside instantly. More sellers just
got caught down there again, folks. More
sellers got caught down there again. I'd
still think SPY might want to come to 75
and ES maybe to that whole number of
800. You're close though. Look at that
return straight back inside.
Straight back inside for the lift. Back
to point of control. I would watch this
long now. If they swipe and reclaim
point of control, which they are trying
to All right,
watching this. Looking for this long
now. Said I wouldn't do it, but this is
too good to miss. They just caught
everyone off guard down there. Here we
go. Let's watch this imbalance into 23s.
I'm long. See if we can get through 23s
and start to really squeeze. There's the
23 tap. I'm already long. We'll add into
this if we start to firm up here. Here
we go. So, those sellers at the low of
day are absolute wies.
Here we go, folks. All right. Next
imbalance can take us all the way up to
60 uh 650 and 63s. So, I want all
pullbacks to hold here and just see this
expansion up towards the top side of
this to 92s. Right. I'm trying to attack
from here now. The reclaim through this
selling some here. And if we can get
through 92 is great. And then we'll look
for that same move. So they got caught
low day again. Again,
look at the delta lower day. Look at the
delta lower day. These these silly
people keep trying to sell the lows.
That's who we're going to use their pain
to go higher, right? Silly silly people.
Lovely. Right. I'm just holding a little
piece now. So if the pullback holds 600,
I'll sit in this. If we pull back and
hold 600, I will sit in this. Pull back
and hold 600, I will sit in this.
Already selling some into here and try
and get up into this. And if we get over
that, the squeeze is on.
So, imbalances here right now into 53.
Up to 52. Here we go. 53s up to 62s.
Filling the first 53s. Here we go,
folks. Here we go. All right. Let's see
if we can get up into 93s. If we get
through 93s, the squeeze is on. Like
I've talked about these silly people at
the lower days, they just don't learn,
do they? They just don't learn.
Come on. We want to just lift up in the
92s. I've only got a little bit left.
Only got a little bit left. I want to
lift into 92s.
Remember, we're thin up. That was a
squeeze up. So, they can flush back
down. We don't want that flush back down
to the PC. We want a base now above this
node here. We want a base above 34s. We
want a base above this for a
continuation squeeze. Base above this
guy here, ideally to here, and then up
into here if we get lucky.
All because they got stuck.
All because Alex knew they would get
stuck down there because they are just
silly people. What did I say? Don't
short the low days.
100 points later. 110 points later.
So, I'm long from this turn around.
I'm already partiing out.
Let's see if we can get VWAP. We were
looking for this here. 92s and if we can
get VWAP 707s and then really I'd love
to get 800s. This is what we're longing
at the moment, folks.
Come on, baby.
Come on, baby. Let's do it.
I want this to hold now. 57s. They can
afford a drift to 36s, but I'd love 57s
to hold. I feel more comfortable. Here
we go.
Don't [\h__\h] with me.
Been in this game too long.
you. All right. Lots of you lots of you
in this with me. Li one of you up 4K
today. Love to see it. Hex the 20our
course. Is it on demand or live? It's on
demand so you can watch it as many times
as you want. It comes with a set of the
indicators, right? A version of this for
free and the Discord for free. All
right. All included. It's on demand. 20
hours. Watch as many times as you want
and Discord. And then I do private.
Well, we do group lessons in Discord
every two weeks.
Yeah, look at you guys. Look at all you
guys longing this. Love it. How long
have I been trading? Um, I started
yesterday. It's my first ever day
yesterday. It's It's guess work this.
Here we go.
Yay.
All right. Runners now. Runners now. If
we get lucky, we're going to get the
800s. But I'm 80% out of this now. And
it's runners now only. All right. So 80%
out of this into here. 20% in case we
want to do something nasty up into this.
Okay. And I will move my stop up to
protect these 60s. Now I do want to do
not want it under these.
Like I said, don't follow me, guys. I am
just a stupid 40-year-old man with a
dodgy patchy beard and glasses on
YouTube. Don't listen to me.
Hi, Alex. What ATM strategies do you
use? They are they ATR based or do you
enter with uh SL and stop loss? No,
they're just automatic based on me. So,
I do like wide stops. So, it's like 40
point stop and like a 50 to 100 point um
uh profit and then I move them instantly
to where I want. Right? So, that all
they really do is make sure that I'm
positioning my limits where I want them.
That's all they do.
Yeah, we all got it. We all got it. We
were We had to wait for it. We've hit
our TP, so we're just a little bit
Banger of the day. It is another banger
of the day. You know why it's a banger
of the day? Because the market is
leaving volume and trapping volume and
that's what we like. Like you see how
when we were down here, guys, you see
how we started talking about me moving
to Texas and like we did a few lessons
and I said we will do something once
we've trapped enough and I would not
short the low of day cuz they keep
getting trapped down here. I said it a
million times. They did it again. The
turnaround. Here we go. So 800's on deck
now. If we can get going above this
green box, right, 800 is on deck. We
might get a runner to 800 here. It would
be lovely if we can get up into this
node. I'm going to call it 800. It's
actually more. We're going to have to
watch New York open. We're going to have
to watch 70. Is that New York open? I
just want to make sure it is. All right.
We're watching here for 70s up to 800s.
Okay. 70s up to 800s is our target here.
And I don't want to hear anyone say I
didn't know what we were looking for. I
literally spelled it out the whole time
we were down here. Would
I recommend getting out of trading view
into Ninja to get most additional value
of the indicators? Um, it's personal
preference for me. Yeah, I love Ninja
Trader. Like, but it is personal
preference. And a top knot. Yeah, and a
top knot. Thanks, Adam. And a top knot.
And stupid glasses
and massive guns.
Best ICT trader out there. Thank you.
Yeah, exactly.
Baby face. Oh, I'll take that.
Uh, I'm English, not Aussie. English,
not Aussie.
Here we go. Can we lift? All right.
You'd want it to defend 90s. Now I might
move my stop up to 90s here. Just under
VWAP. I'd want it to defend sort of this
area here now. 90s. I don't want it to
flush under that. We're almost there,
but I'm not going to give this whole
squeeze back. All right. So, I'm going
to probably risk 90s here. What's this
level right under here? 88. Let's risk
88s.
So, stop moved up to here. Remember,
I've taken most of it off. About to get
washed out here. Out of here on the
runner is what it is. But that was still
really good. All right. We almost got
all the way. Maybe some of you want to
hold longer, but I'm not going to hold
through that. Uh I think a best fill I
got here was 720s.
I just don't want to risk this coming
back down here and setting a higher low
down here before it has another go
because now this can be a fail breakout
of that again and it can come back into
the range again. So I don't want to
position myself here for that. It's too
risky. Same as that's like position
yourself short for that. All right, so
we got the rotation. Maybe some of you
are willing to hold a runner longer. You
might still get it. I I do think it
wants to try and lift up into here, but
I got my target right. So ES also hit
New York B.
Where was my original stop loss? Right
into the lows basically. Um I can tell
you cuz I did it on NT
it was into 60s. All right. And this is
why. Oh, you're going to get it right.
See this
big seller here came in. They market
sold underneath. We reclaimed once we
ripped through that. I did not want it
to come back under 60s. Hopefully that
makes sense. Uh hopefully you can see
that this is where the seller's pain
point was. So that was I literally moved
straight to 60s. I'm like no reason to
come back. Oh, this is going to [\h__\h]
go after doing a dirty on me. You see
you next Tuesday.
You
What did I do? 88s.
Oh, you bastard.
You bastard. You couldn't hold that
shelf for me, could you? [\h__\h] me. Going
to miss another hundred here. Right,
Alex is going to use the bathroom here.
And we all know what happens when Alex
uses the bathroom. All right, I'll be
I'll be right back. Uh when I'm back, we
will do some giveaways. Don't go
anywhere. And um yeah, hold your runners
if you can get up into here. You can all
laugh at me for cutting it. All right,
folks. Be right back.
Oh, of course it is. Of course it is. We
all know where it's going.
Alex, you numpty.
Oh my god. All right, get ready here for
blue line and green line and V up. All
right, get ready here. If they do
something very nasty here, guys. All
right, so your TPS are into this block
here. I can't believe they knocked me
out to do that. Your TPS are into here.
If they rip through this, it is worth
holding a little piece in case they come
right back for this. Right. So, I would
be like 80 90% out here. It is worth
holding a little piece in case they come
back for this. It is possible, right?
You're going to get this for sure. It is
possible they do this. It is possible
they do this if they get a close and a
hold over 800. So you can hold a little
piece for that. I'm coming right back.
I'm gonna get some milk for this. I'm
sulking now. I am sulking.
Oh my god.
Oh my god. All right, guys. Make sure
you're paying yourself. I'd say like at
least 80%. All right, you probably took
some here, some here. There's no
guarantee we go higher, but you can hold
like if you were trading micros, say you
had like 10 10 micros on or 20 micros
on, you could hold one or two just in
case you do this full move. But the the
low the high probability move was to
here to this node. You can see previous
lows, New York open, VWAP, all here.
And uh yeah, if you got that um you
know, we live, it's funny, isn't it?
We're in a market where I can get
120 points and I feel gutted because the
market's giving us two and 300 point
trades. So, we I've had I've had a what
was this one today?
We had a
200 point ripper to start the day. I got
only 80 points out of the 330.1 then and
I've only got 100 out of this 200 one
and this might offer you 300 up to here.
You might very well get a 300 point
trade here again, guys.
Hopefully some of you got this target
here. Didn't stop out where I stopped
out at 88. So you
It's funny, isn't it? When 100 points
isn't good enough anymore.
It's all right. You can watch YouTube
other YouTubers who trade for eight
ticks. Good luck with that. How you ever
going to make money doing that? All
right.
Nice. Lots of you passing accounts or
taking big big money out of this, right?
Am I short 800? No. Absolutely not. No
reason to be short. Zero reason to be
short now.
What's the difference between Trading
View and Ninja Trader Indicators? It's
just a different package. They're on
different sides. There you go. Nice
work. Nice work. The Tyson trade paying.
All right. Anyone knows why do we call
it the Tyson trade? I banned Tyson from
taking any other trade than this to here
and here for a while. All right. When we
talk about knowing our trade setups,
adding one tool at a time. All right.
Tyson's been a student of mine probably
for about a year now. Is it Tyson?
Something like that. And this is his
bread and butter. IB to VWAP. This is
his trade. And all you need is that
trade each day or the IB expansion.
We're in expansion mode. And you ignore
everything else. You just wait for that
trade to set up and it will pay you. All
right. And that's what we call, you
know, using your toolbox, having a tool,
a toolbox, right? So, you got to know I
have many, many different tools in my
toolbox now, but I've been around the
block for a little while. when you
start, find something that works for
you. Maybe it's the opening range trade,
maybe it's the IB trade, maybe it's a
pro trend, maybe it's counter trend,
whatever it is. All right? And we talk
about the book that I think you should
read for that. And like I always say,
golf is not a game of perfect, right?
You can go and read that book. Very
short little book, but basically about
when you start being a beginner playing
golf, you want to get around the golf
course with an eight iron. You don't
want to be getting out, you know, your
big big birther driver and hooking it
left, right, and all over the place cuz
you want to show off. But in natural
fact, all you do is you get frustrated,
you snap your golf club over your knee,
and then you need to go and buy another
one. But if you got your eight iron out,
all right, you might come in 10 over par
or whatever for the whole 18 holes, but
you probably keep your balls, you don't
be frustrated, and you play some decent
shots.
I know, Fresh Trader. I know it is.
I know it is. I might have to rethink
stuff. I'm trying to play off nodes and
sometimes they're just swiping me. I
might have to give stuff a little bit
more room. Look, we're starting to base
over this New York open. Now, ES is
still not at it 24-hour VWAP or New York
Open. This has got a shot here. Um, this
has got a shot here. Do not be a new
money long, but if you're long in this,
this has got a shot of this, right? If
we collapse this, this is your rotation
back down. We have some nodes here that
might come and protect. So, you'd want
this to base, but if it can base here,
you've got a shot. You have absolutely
got a shot at it.
What's that about micros and contracts?
Oh, well, if you're trading minis,
right? So, depending on size account,
it's very unlikely you're trading like
10 plus minis down here, isn't it? Or
five minis, right? unless you've got a
massive account or unless you're way way
over leveraged in risk. So, it's more
likely that you're probably trading
micros or maybe one or two minis. So, if
you're trading one or two minis, then
you'd be taking one off there and maybe
you're one off here or maybe you're just
moving your stop real tight trading that
one. If you're trading micros,
right, for the difference of one to two
minis, you could be trading 10 to 20
micros, for example. You could maybe
just be trading five micros. So, we come
up here. Let's say you're 10 micros
long, right? So, we sell three. we sell
maybe three more and we hold, you know,
the last four to get up here. Or maybe
you sell four and four and you're
holding two in case you get up here, for
example. It just gives you a little bit
more flexibility to capture the full
move. And it's also very good for, you
know, being used to sitting in the
moves, right? If you're trading minis,
especially if you're new, you're
probably seeing it up here and you're
like, "Oh, I'm up 300 bucks. I'm I'm
done. I'm done. I'm done." Then you're
going to watch it do this whole move
without you because you haven't built up
the tolerance and resilience to
understand that this can do this.
Just passed my first ever eval watching
you. Nice. Congratulations.
Uh the only thing with micros is it will
cost you more for the round trip. Right?
10 micros versus one mini will cost you
a little bit more from the round trip.
But like if you wanted to move from one
mini to two minis, I would say you'd be
better off moving from one mini to 15
micros than than jumping right up to two
minis. It's going to cost you more. But
you know, the jump from you literally
doubling your risk. You go from one mini
to two minis, you're doubling your risk,
right? You've gone from 200 points, $200
per one per 10 points to $400 per 10
points. All right? And if you've got 20,
30 point risk, you're going to get
wrecked real quick.
Lots of you killing this. Order flows 3K
across two TPT Pro accounts.
Congratulations. I love it. I love
trading with take profit traders. One of
my favorites to trade with regular
payouts from there. I really like it. Um
if if any of you are interested, should
probably promote these guys as they all
help us. Uh code flowzone uh for take
profit trader will get you 40% off with
no activation fee. Use code FCT for
everything else.
The Tyson trade strikes again. Yeah, it
does indeed. Does indeed.
Hey Alex, I just win on the funded
account, but on Ninja I have a total P&L
1,146 and a gross of 1,246. Can you
explain the deal of the gross not
realized? So that's your cost. So you've
spent like $200. Your cost, right? So
your in and out, your your contract
cost, however many trades you've taken
today is why
your net is all that matters.
Alex, please explain the IB to VWAP or
the IB high or low to New York VWAP on
the daily VWAP. Please can you explain
is the IB to VWAP? Oh, it's both. It's
both. It just depends what they're
looking to do on that day, which is why
I always respect both. I would always be
a partial partial. I wouldn't be looking
to trade one. And we stop at both. Same.
Let's see. Look, we stop started here.
We're stop starting here. ES will be the
same,
right? IB, New York VW, stop start
extension 24-hour VW up, New York open
here, stop start here. Might pull back
to here at some point now.
Right. So, I that's why I say like take
partials into both. It really depends.
Sometimes they're lined up and they're
very close together. Other days they're
really far apart. It all depends what
happened overnight really.
Do I trade uh across Apex, TPT, Lucid
all at once if it's not too personal?
I'm actually not doing that at the
moment. I was doing it and what I was
finding is too many accounts and they'd
be lagging and then some wouldn't fill
in stuff. So, I'm trading in blocks at
the moment is how I'm trading them. Like
five to 10 at a time blocks
for some reason. I don't think the um
the uh trade copier liked all the
different accounts. I'd get like errors
mainly on my TPT ones. I kept getting
errors when they were uh trading with
the other firms for some reason.
One runner left. Yeah, nice. It's still
Look, it's still holding this node.
There is a chance to come up into this
node. Like we've talked about, there is
a chance to come up into this node.
What's the ticker? This is NQ. You're
looking at NQ. For anyone just joining,
what are your confluences taking the
trade? uh trapped trapped participants,
right? Trapped parti understanding what
type of day we're in, understanding the
loc location and then looking for
trapped participants. You would have
heard me today. I wanted to get long
here for this. We got long there for
that once shorts were trapped. I wanted
to get short here once we left this for
a move back down to here and then Alex
sold or covered before the news and we
ped the whole way down for the gap fill.
Once we filled the gap, the market is
now efficient, right? There's no reason
for this market to go lower in one go.
We know that shorts kept getting stuck
down here. We know that we're at 2.5
standard deviations on a daily. That is
unsustainable on a daily. So, we are not
going to sell the low of day, low of
week, low of month, low of quarter, low
of contract. It's [\h__\h] psychopath
move to do that when you understand what
it is. So, what are we going to look
for? these trap sellers who don't
understand that to compiling in and
we're going to position their pain point
against them for the mean reversion back
up. Thank you. That's it. There's the
confluence. We're in a range rotation.
We've built out traders. We have trap
shorts at the lows. We trade the other
way to them. There you go. That's the
confluence.
How do I see that? Order flow.
That's how I see it.
Sorry guys. I I'm sure some of you are
typing a lot here. Trying to catch up
with the chat. I'm trying to catch up
with the chat. Give me a second. I'm
trying to catch up with the chat.
Look at spy as well. It hit the 75s.
Didn't come flat in 75s, but hit 75s.
Q's hit the 93s on that little nasty
flash as well. Really good.
Um,
okay. I would cut this down if I was
you. You don't want to have this drift
all the way down. But you know, you
manage as as you want. But there can be
a retest of the 713s. If they don't hold
New York open, they can retest right
down into here. You do not. But we're
straight up. You do not want to give all
this back, right? You do not want to
give all this back on the long. Still
think there's a chance for it to come up
here, but I would not be willing to see
that move happen if I was you. I'm
already out. Like we said, I'd be 80
plus% out where we are because this was
the target. This this node here was the
target, right? The runner, if you got
very lucky, would be up here.
And how we operate down here now becomes
key because this is the base out.
Failed break up. How we operate here now
becomes key. If they base out here, they
will have another go to get higher. They
base out down here, right? Because
that's where all the sellers are now
stuck. So this would be a breakout
retest. If they hold this retest
something like this, you can potentially
get a long back up. If we come back into
here, I would just leave this zone alone
for the rest of the day. I would not
touch anything from 700 to 550 for the
rest of the day. Completely ignore that
zone.
In my mind, that's how I would trade it.
Do I see a short opportunity? Not right
now. Not unless we do something nasty.
Um maybe up into all of this maybe but
all right not not right now. Not right
now. I think the shorts have the shorts
are gone for me for a while. We need to
build out liquidity for a while now
before we think about any more short
trades. Okay. Just based on where we are
higher time frames.
Based on where we are high in time
frames. Um
what does IB stand for? Initial balance.
Does your trading course include the
order flow as well, or do I need to get
the volume order flow course separately?
You can get it as a bundle. You'll save
like a $100 or $150 if you get them both
at once. It might well get up here. You
might well get your targets here, folks.
We will see. Um, is it smart to move
stop loss to break even as soon as
available? No. It caused me to lose some
trades, but also save me from losers. If
you're positioning well, you shouldn't
really be moving to break even until
that that the run has proved itself,
right? Depends on what you're doing.
Like in something like this, I will move
to break even. The moment we accelerate
away and we break out. Okay, I'm break
even. It's got no reason to come back
down below this. All right, and then
I'll hold. But like it it depends on
your positioning. Like if you got break
even too early here, you're going to get
knocked out three or four times, right,
before it does that move, which does
happen to me sometimes. But you don't
want to move break even too quick. You
want to move break even when the when
the trade's proven itself to you.
Can it hit today's high? Um, what do you
mean by today's high? Uh, GlobeEx high
or New York high. It can hit New York
high potentially. It's got to get
through all of this first, right? So,
it's got to get over this to this. Then
we probably do this for a bit. And if it
does this, we could fill this gap, which
we haven't filled. We could come up into
this value area, and we could hit that
potentially
uh to get into high of day up here,
which is GlobeEx. We're asking quite a
lot of it. We're asking quite a lot of
it, but can't rule it out.
I would say it's more likely that we
just rotate.
Why not back to VPO? I mean, it could
come all the way back down to here, but
we've just broken out of here. So,
we would think that it might want to
hold this first, then assuming it comes
all the way back down. It's possible,
but it would need to get under this
first. So I think there's probably this
builds out first unless they complete
this in one go. So I would be very very
careful about thinking about being
shorts here because it could do this
this this
and now you've got VWAP above this key
level and trap players down here and VPO
down here. Now this this looks like
potential to be nasty for the rest of
the day in the rotation.
You're on a 50k looking to pass combine
today. Um, okay. I don't see a question
there though, Mopar.
Can you work out trap traders without
books? I guess you could be like, well,
there's a wick there and we reclaimed
and it could get long, but you don't
know what's actually inside there. We
identified them from here this morning,
right? We knew their exact position
where they were trapped from early on
this morning. All right, so here you go.
Coming back for this now. It's going to
come and back test this.
So if buyers step in here, they will
have another go and then if they use
this liquidity, they'll go higher. If
they step in and they fail this, the
rotation will happen. Like I said, I I
would be done with personally, I'd be
done with this for the day at this point
or you got 15 minutes to lunch. We're
going to do giveaways. We're going to do
some giveaways.
Relatively new trader coming from ICT,
what's the best way to begin learning
this style of trading without dropping
money on a course just yet? Uh tons on
my YouTube for free, my friend. Right.
So, I would do if I was going to start,
if you're already experienced, you
understand structure and all that stuff,
if you've been watching ICT, then go and
look at um there's a section on my
YouTube for free all about volume,
right? Go and understand volume.
And that is a good place for you to
start. And if you've learned ICT and you
understand fair value gaps and stuff,
the volume stuff is going to start to
make sense to you very, very quickly.
you understand all the blocks and all
that stuff, then you you're going to
see, but you're going to see it being in
my mind more accurate to exact precise
levels.
So, it's all for free on my YouTube. You
can start there.
What volume indicator am I using?
Anchored volume profile. Alex has got to
write this down.
Can you describe how you came up with
this gap? This gap here, this gap here,
it was a daily gap. We went over it
right here.
Untested right here. You see this gap?
This is a Friday to a Monday. So from
the 21st of November into the 24th of
November. All right. We closed the 21st
here. We gapped up. We never filled it.
All right. We had a little dig in, but
we never filled it. We have now filled
it in a New York session. All right. In
a New York session, we have filled this
gap. That is an efficient market. That
is what the market likes to do. That's
how we came up with a gap.
It's why you got to look really far back
for like untested gaps.
Um, what do you make of this? 820
looking left. Been a big resistance
since overnight. 820.
I mean, yeah, I mean, it's a key level.
That's why we've got the gray box there.
The nodes here or here about over over
820 though. very thin in New York up to
here. So, a break over this. What I'd be
very careful about, like I talked about,
is something like this happening for the
rest of the day. So, I'd be very
careful. The shorts, I guess,
technically, if we're going to do a
rotation day, all right, it could be a
short back down to here, but I do not
like that. Not now that we've left this.
All right, all the sellers are trapped
down here. My expectation would be if
buyers want to step in, they want to
step in down here. Remember, we are deep
discount down here on every single even
on a even on the current year, we would
be deep discount down here. All right?
So, it's very possible it wants to come
a bit higher before they resell. That's
not to say you can't scalp it, but
remember, I'm looking to position on
highly probable multi-time frame moves.
Any reason you use Ninja Trade, Ninja
Trader instead of Trader 8 integrated
into Trading View? Yeah, way faster in
executions, way better in terms of data,
way better in terms of hotkeys and ATM.
Just for me, way way way way better.
Even like the order flow that I use,
right? Maybe you've just joined. Like I
can't have anything like this on Trading
View. Like this is so good for me. Like
it's so key. Look how clearly we
identified. Here's the trap seller at
60. There's Vpo. There's the squeeze.
Thanks very much. Where are we going to
the other side of value? All right. And
we're still holding above these pivots.
Look in here. This where that seller got
trapped. 40. All right. 40. We're still
holding 40. I wouldn't know any of this
on Trading View. So, that's why it's uh
Look at the What did we just talk about,
folks? What did we just talk about?
Holding
around here,
but something like this can be possible.
I literally just told you it. That's not
me being arrogant and that's why I'm
saying like you got to understand who's
trapped now. These shorts are trapped
down here. They are not being let out.
There's the pullback. If they build this
liquidity now, the squeeze will happen
back to here. Okay?
I'm not like a genius guys. Like I'm
telling you this because this is this is
just how the market moves. These are the
rules of engagement to the market.
the trade copier. Yeah, I can post it,
Jay. Um,
give me a second. Just finding it for
you.
There you go, Jay. Just posted it for
I'm new to trading, start watching your
stream. Are you providing any training
courses? Yeah, they're all on my
website. All the links are down below.
Flowzone Trader.com. All the links are
down below. Like I always say, if you're
brand new, if you've turned up here for
the first day, go and do everything for
free on my YouTube first. Don't go and
spend a load of money. Here you go,
folks.
Don't say I didn't tell you. Don't say I
didn't tell you.
ES into New York open here. All right.
Big level ES here. If ES gets through
the New York open, then it can afford a
squeeze up to 63. So this big level here
of ES at 53 is 10 points higher if it
wants to do it. We've just swiped here.
So you want to see a base out now and
hold. You do not want to see them stuff
this. Let me see who got caught in this.
You do not want to see them stuff this
with buyers caught. We're going to get
any data. There we go. So, some buyers
got caught above 26s. So, they need to
get back above the 26s here on the cues
and then we're going to get a move up
into these 80s
and you're going to get full TP if you
held through that. Or if you bought that
dip into flow zones before, like I said,
I wouldn't be short here. I think
they'll probably reclaim. I would cut
the long and then they'll probably
reclaim. And here we go.
Like I said, don't know what I'm talking
about.
How long have I been trading for? Uh,
full-time, like six or seven years. But
I mean, I started when I was 21, so half
my life ago.
Yeah, whoever went short at the bottom
haven't done Alex's course quite right.
Nice, Morgan. Looking forward to working
with you. Pass neo. I made good money on
my funded account. Thanks, Alex. Been a
great day. Hey, I love it. Love it,
guys. Would it be smart to start looking
for a short down to lows of day? Not
right now. Right, we just went over
this. Maybe you said that before.
Remember, shorts are caught in here
right now. Here's the rotation and lots
of them caught at the lows. We have
broken out. All right, this is a very
small woff type thing. All right, this
little wick here, there's a fail
breakout. There's your spring. There's
your sign of strength. There's the
pullback to hold. There's the volume.
All right. This is a key level. Now, if
we hold this, the rotation is on and
they have reasons to go higher. We can
come and test previous day value area
low. We can come and test the IB. We can
come and close the New York gap. We can
come up to current uh profile from the
developing week. We can come and test
this naked point of control. We can come
all the way up here. If they want to
really [\h__\h] send it, they can. So why
be short against this right now? Look at
the structure we've left. This is
bullish structure, right? This is
bearish structure. This is flattening.
This is breakout, pullback, hold. We're
in the next leg higher. Do not be trying
to short this. You will be guessing for
the rotation which is not given you.
Same way down here. We don't just long
for no reason. We wait. It's got good
reason to come up into this node. And
it's possible if we get through this
gray box. I would not rule out this.
I would not rule out that. That is a 500
[\h__\h] point trade. But uh it's
possible. It' be it would take a long
time to get there. But probable is to
here right now is to like 90s. Possible
is a 500 point trade up there.
Sorry guys, trying to catch up with chat
chat here.
What does the flow zone course cover?
It's it's everything's on the website,
guys. So, I tell you um all these
questions you're asking is on the
website. So, in the 20our course, we do
like fundamentals, technical, advanced
market structure, smart money concept,
Malaysian SNR, supply and demand,
pattern recognition, market maker model,
psychology, risk reward, play my
playbook, and a ton more. And then you
also get the flow zone indicator, a
version of this, right? You can upgrade
for the probe, but a version of this
plots all the key levels for you and the
discord all included in uh the volume
and order flow course. We go over
auction theory, volume profile, profile
types, developing profiles, delta,
bookmap, footprints, and my playbook and
repeatable setups, right? But there's no
uh no inclusion into Discord and no
indicator in that. So, it all depend.
It's all up to you guys. If you get them
together for a bundle, you'll save some
money. Here you go, guys. You're about
to hit the next TP, right? gray box. All
right, if you're really [\h__\h] lucky
here, you might get a 500 point banger,
pardon my French. Yeah, all the links
are pinned above, guys.
Alex, just heard your stop-loss TP
starting point. Any recommendations for
utilizing these great calls while Apex
funded until the buffer? What do you
mean, Mike? Uh
oh. You mean for my ATM until you're
past the buffer, you want to trail very
aggressively and you want to take
profits like aggressively. So like if
you're trading Apex, like you want to
trim some here. You want to trim some
here. You want to trim some here. You
want to move your stop up with it. If
this doesn't hold this gray box now, be
careful of a flush back down. What's the
time here? Coming into the new hour. So
they almost got there. They were just
shy by the tiniest tiniest bit here.
They might well hold this gray box
still. This is still your key level. You
do not want them to lose this. All
right, this is where they're trying to
complete. We missed it by or like 20
points. If they hold this, they're going
to have one more shot at it. So, this
gray box, see this gray box, this volume
node, is still bidding off this trying
to get up into here. All right, you
don't need to cut the trade until you
come under that gray box. Under that
gray box, you cut this trade.
Uh, is it okay if I use 2,000 ticks on
MS? I you'd have to back test it for
your strategy, but it's okay to use it.
Yeah, any anything works, right?
Anything works.
Uh, yeah, the Trading View is, what do
they call it? Pro or whatever it is.
You'll need one of those accounts. Your
best to get it off in the sale, Nick.
They they do sales two or three times a
year where you'll save like 70 or 80%.
That's when you want to buy it.
I watch you on TV, so had to go online.
You are the man. You are the man from
Oklahoma. Thanks, Max Payne. New here to
your channel. How would you recommend?
How How would you recommend before
buying? I'm not sure what you mean.
Sorry. Let me know what you mean. Alex,
do I have a personal account with Ninja?
Uh, not with Ninja. I did. I moved it.
and they closed it because I had it set
as a uh UK
um
citizen and I couldn't move it over to
when I got my green card so I closed it.
I have personal accounts elsewhere
though.
Click quick explanation of an order
block, man. Like order blocks are just
support resistance just made more
complicated.
It's all it is, right? This here,
resistance becomes support. This here,
resistance becomes support. We want to
call that an order block. You call it
whatever you [\h__\h] want, right? This
here support becomes resistance. Support
becomes resistance. That's all it is.
Can say it's some magic [\h__\h] thing,
but it isn't, right? It's SNR. It's just
SNR just regurgitated. I don't care what
anyone says. It is SNR regurgitated.
Uh,
Alex, how long did it take you to get an
understanding and grasp of futures and
when did you finally get that aha
moment? It took like I'll be honest, it
took me a while to adapt to futures. Uh,
moving from small caps was hard. small
caps you have to trade like in a very
very different manner to the rest of the
market especially when they're really
aggressive when they're like gapping 100
200 300 points moving from small caps to
mids and large like took a little bit of
developing moving from that to futures I
it took me a while to understand sizing
to understand the leverage uh to really
utilize the best features that we have
for futures futures are a centralized
exchange very different to trading
stocks. When I was trading stocks, you
know, I'd be using scanners and I'd be
using the level two, but obviously on
the level two, you're looking at like
five, three to five different exchanges
trading that one stock and it's very
easy for them to hide uh contracts doing
that. The best thing about futures is
it's centralized on CME. So, we have
centralized data. They can't, you know,
they can't hide in the same way. And
that's why it's for me where the edge
is, right? For the me where the edges is
understanding we have all the data in
front of us. It's quite literally
showing you who's trapped, where they're
trapped, where the levels are. It's just
do you have the discipline and
understanding? That took me a little bit
of time. From then it became much
easier.
Does the indicator in the course include
the gray boxes? No. No. No indicator
includes these. I draw these on. I draw
these on. You can draw these on. Look,
all you have to do is get the profile
and draw them on based on the profile.
All right. If we start losing this, I
would cut this trade. This is a failed
opportunity to break higher. They might
be really dirty and dip down to 45, but
I would cut this trade now that you're
losing this. I personally, I would not
be holding on to this, right?
Personally, they might be really dirty
and do this. But personally, I would not
be keeping holding on to this. They if
they lose this gray box, I would just
let it go. Just be happy with what
you've got. But, you know, maybe some of
you are still positioned from here and
you can afford to to hold a better
position. But those of you who are long
from here, I wouldn't give the whole
thing back.
Uh,
what's the biggest loss I've ever had?
Um,
of real money, I think it was, uh, about
$28,000
on uh, what was the stock name? M O XC M
O
something like that. Some rigged Chinese
ticker absolutely [\h__\h] me. I had a few
big big losses
back in the day.
Uh few more questions here and then
we'll do these giveaways. Folks,
do I view the world through bookmap or
like Neo in the matrix? Yeah, exactly
that.
This is a healthy uptrend. Uh yeah.
Well, we're we're we're in a downtrend.
I can draw like if we think about
think about what's happened, right? So
the daily did this for a while, right?
And then this is what the daily is
doing, right? Currently, we're in this
part of the daily, right? We're in this
part of the daily. So on a lower time
frame today, if we just saw this on a
daily, it would look like this,
right? That's what we're seeing on a
lower time frame on like an hourly. So
we're trying to join this leg here or
range rotation in here. Now, we don't
know how far this comes up. Does it come
all the way up to here? Is it possible
that they do this? Yep. Is it possible
on a daily that they do this and reject?
Yeah. So, we're just playing this leg
here on a daily. Right. This is where we
talk about multi-time frame. The easiest
trades, right, the layup trades are the
protrend
are the protrend. But we are too
extended now. We've had multi-legg down.
We expect a pullback.
So, we're trying to play the long for
the relief on the pullback. Hopefully
that makes sense.
That's where we are in this market at
the moment. So the main trend has been
down, but we are overextended. So to
draw that out for you really quickly as
a lesson, right? I'm going to draw this
out on a line chart.
Right, this is what happened. The daily
went sideways for ages and ages and
ages. I'm going to like just simplify
it. This is what we did on the daily.
Then we did a fail breakout and then
this has started. All right, we're here.
We're here. We expect the market
probably to do this. All right. Once
it's done this move, it would make a
decision. Is it going to come here or is
it going to do this and come higher and
then come down for a retest and then
make a decision of what it's going to
do. All right. But we are in this little
part here, right? We don't expect the
market like we talked about to just keep
go straight down in one one direction.
The only time that happens is when
they're dumping inventory. All right? If
there is like a big black swan event and
it's like, "Hey, the market's on fire.
We're going to war. Everything's wrong."
Blah blah blah blah blah blah blah.
Okay. Yeah, maybe COVID, right? COVID
type thing. Other than that, it's
probably more likely to look something
like this. Even if we come for the low
or maybe we do this, this and come back
inside here and then reject. Right? So
just understanding the positioning of
how the market moves will help you.
This does Discord come with any of your
courses and indicators? Yeah, the 20our
course, man. The beginner to advanced
course has indicators and Discord in it.
Where do you see ES Spy will go if it
stays bullish?
Well, SPY's just come back into a pivot.
So that 81s to 8177 is that old low. So
it's just rejected that. So you're going
to need spy to reclaim 81s and 82s. You
got IB higher 8372s. Once we get through
that it's going to be tough though. But
if it could get through if it can get
through 8177 which was previous day low.
There is a potential lift to 8372s.
Through 8372s I'd be watching that pivot
low yesterday. 8466s.
if it can get through that gap fill and
the 50-day at 8620. But you're asking an
awful lot. It's more likely that we just
range.
Are these indicators that I created?
Yes, they are. They are. Best place to
learn about prop firms. Free videos on
my YouTube. There's there's a whole
channel on prop firms. You can learn
which ones to trade, how to trade them,
which ones are good, what their
positives are, which ones work for you.
Do I uh live stream on YouTube daily?
Yeah, Monday to Friday, 9:15 New York
time.
Uh no, there's no code, guys, right now.
No sale for indicators right now or or
anything like that. Sorry.
Do I swing futures? No. ETFs? Yes. ETFs
and stocks? Yes. So, I'm currently I can
tell you uh positions I'm in currently.
Um
I am long Apple, AMD, Meta, Amazon,
Open, just holding one share. Uh
Microsoft, US uh Rare Earth, and uh Yuyu
Yuyu and Netflix. All right. So, uh
Apple I'm long since 208. Uh AMD, I'm
only got a little piece left, but I'm
long since
162s. Sold most into the alltime high.
Meta, I am long from 590s. Small size in
there, not really scaled in. Amazon
pretty much flat on that. I'm long from
216s.
Um open I was long from 198. I sold most
into that huge squeeze. I'm just holding
one share just for shits and giggles.
Microsoft I put a feeler on yesterday.
So I'm very very tiny size on Microsoft
just to put a feeler on. Uh USA Rare
Earth I have a small position on I start
a position and uh uh Yu Yuyu both versus
20s kind of levels. Waiting to see if we
base out. We talked about that on
stream. And then Netflix I've got a a
tiny piece on that as a starter that I
put on I think either beginning of this
week or last week. looking to see if we
flush Netflix into 70s for a for a
rescoop with some size. Right. So, but I
go over all of those in Discord.
Okay, we're into lunch. Jeez, that came
around quick. Right, I'm going to read
his last few questions, then we're going
to do the giveaways.
No, I left Oracle. I was watching
Oracle. Um, but they are they are
absolutely uh dumping. we talked about
at the beginning of the stream, right?
I've been watching it. I check in on it
every day. But the rotation out of
software has been massive.
All right. Is it undervalued? Probably.
But there's a huge rotation. It's coming
into a really interesting area for me in
here. Like I really like this area, but
I don't feel the need to be first in it.
What are we down off alltime highs? Like
60%. It's tempting, man. It's tempting
to put a starter on there. I will be
honest with you. Um
but we are dumping out of this is what
they're rotating out of because the AI
exposure to this they're too worried
about software. So if we think about
what's Adobe Adobe Same thing dumping
off it, right? There's your daily on
Adobe. It's the same kind of sector,
right? They're dumping anything where
they think they've got negative exposure
to AI, right? So I'd be watching Adobe.
We've now undercut this. If we undercut
this,
[\h__\h] hell, man. That's bleak. That is
bleak. If they do a measured move.
Oh my [\h__\h] lord. Yeah, I'm not
touching that. No way. Not right now.
Interesting levels. But yeah, we'll see.
They're they're on watch for me every
day. I'm watching all of these every
day. Um but you know, if the market's
going to bleed more, like if if we're
going to bleed more in tech, then we're
going to expect these to have weakness.
Um so we can scoop them up. When
everyone's saying, look, look, it's very
simple. When everyone's like, "The
market's dead. It's [\h__\h] done. Oh my
god." Then we're gonna buy it. Same as
like, you know, your mom and your gran
were talking about buying silver and
gold last week. Well, guess what?
That will be the high, right?
How old am I? I'm 40. I'm 40. 85, baby.
Yeah, I'm here every day. Monday to
Friday. Monday to Friday. Wife, yes. No
children. That's probably why I look
like look young.
No live in the afternoons, guys. Just in
Discord.
Uh 9:30. So Kate, I do the this this
profile that you're looking at is to
9:30, but we mark out previous days
here, right? They're all above us,
right? So I mark these out every single
day. And we also have the developing
week. We have the developing week as
well.
We went over traps already. I've been
over them a few times.
Rotating into what? Uh well, we are
rotating into the broader sector. All
right. So, I'll go over this one more
time. Really want to do these giveaways
here before you all got so you all have
a chance. All right. So if we get this
up.
Oh, Finn Viz playing games again. Sorry
guys. So buggy that website. Does anyone
else find that? Just let this refresh
and I can bring it over to you.
There we go.
Okay. So
this is the whole market right we are
rotating out of defense out of tech into
defensive into some financials. Yes,
today's having a pullback day, but yes,
they look pretty good. The lagging
sectors have been finance, healthcare,
and defensive. Lots going back into
these. You're also going to see it like
back into metals, right? Which is what
we're seeing. So, out of these, which
have been up, you know, we tal we went
over this yesterday. Worth going back to
yesterday's stream and having a watch.
Like some of these are up hundreds and
thousands of percent. These are all
lagging behind. These are very, very
easy sectors to hold in. like we are
always going to Costco's always going to
be there. All these Coca-Cola, they're
always going to be there. So, we're
going back into lagging sectors because
we're going risk off. All right. So,
we're rotating out. All right. Out of
right, we're rotating out of parabolic
markets.
out of parabolic markets which are up
2,000%
since the low in 22. All right, into
sectors which are lagging behind. All
right, into sectors which are lagging
behind. Right, because we don't want to
it's the same story, right? They don't
want to buy up here. here. All right.
So, if they can rotate out of this, if
they lock in some of their profits and
they rotate into sectors which are
lagging behind here and they bid this
back up, right? Then these sectors start
going, this comes back down, then they
rotate back into this, they get this in
discount, they bid this back up, they
sell this one that they bought. Does
that make sense? So, if I drew that out,
right, if this is NQ, uh, or let's just
call this whole of tech and then we have
defensive stocks, which would maybe look
something like this.
Okay, so they're going to sell this,
take profits in this, which means this
will sell and they're going to buy this
because it's only the equivalent of
here. And this will drive up and then
once they get new highs, they will sell
some of this and they will rotate back
into the cues and this will go up,
right? And this is what we see all the
time. All the time. So we think about
COVID. We came out of all of this,
right? And originally, what did we go
into down here, right? Ma
Uh trying to think of all these stocks.
Uh PayPal,
Zoom,
right? They rotated into all these
[\h__\h] names, all the healthc care
stuff, right? And that went rippy rippy
rippy. And once they rotated out of
that, they went, "All right, right. Tech
time, right?" And that's how we move.
That's how we move assets because we
can't just pump one thing over and over
and over and over and over again. They
they have like a shelf life and then we
have to reset for a moment.
Uh any prop firms that support Trader 8
will work with Trading View. Yeah,
sorry. That's you guys answering each
other. Pelatin. Yeah, a Pelaton a great
example. Uh that got absolutely dunked
on today again on earnings I'm pretty
sure. So we can have a look at Peton.
It's got absolutely [\h__\h] on. There we
go. Right. So this is what you call like
over ambition and rotation. We go back
to COVID.
You can see these levels that I was
trading. I was trading Pelatin at back
in the day. All right. These these are
all still on my chart from when I was
trading this back in the day. All right.
So, everyone's going to stay at home. No
one can use a gym. Boom. All right.
Failed to make a new high. All right.
Co's over. Everyone's going back to the
gym. [\h__\h] Oh my god. We can't keep
track of any of our bikes. We're sending
too many to too many people. This
doesn't work. Boom. We're missing
earnings. Boom. Oh, we're undervalued.
Okay, rotate back in. And then today
they went, actually, we missed on
earnings. Boom. All right, there's a
very typical rotation. Make our money,
get out of the high, [\h__\h] sell it
off. But the difference is this is a
turd of a stock. All right, it's an
absolute turd.
Uh, you're going to see small cap start
to like be pumped into at the moment as
well. lot. That's why you're seeing like
RTY has done very very well, right?
Because you're seeing that small cap
rotation, right? Think about where RTY
is. All right, it's look at this. If you
compared this to NQ,
all right, we are still holding very,
very well up here because this is a
different rotation. All right.
All right. I'm going to set up this uh
giveaway now for you guys. Hopefully,
you've learned something here today,
whether it was a trade with me or
whether it was a uh
understanding of how the markets
operate. Give me a second.
Okay. So, best code for all your prop
firms, FZT. That's the code to use. That
money goes back into this stream. You
can type that once in chat now. Please
don't spam and we will pick a winner at
random to win a free Apex account, any
size that you want. If you want to trade
with take profit trader, then you need
to use code FlozzO, not FCT. But for
everyone else, FCT.
Give you guys a minute to do that.
been on stream a lot longer recently.
Losing track of time
All
right.
Right. Pulling this winner.
Five, four, three, two, and one.
Aaron
Hanei. Sorry if I've said that wrong.
Aaron Haneiki, I think it is. 1299. Are
you here, Aaron?
Let me know you're here.
Let me know you're here. Still in chat.
Yeah. Congratulations, Aaron. Okay. All
I need you to do, buddy, uh, send me an
email info@flowzonerader.com.
Just send me a screenshot, please, of
you logged in uh to your YouTube and uh
I will give you a code for a free Apex
account, any size account that you want.
That has you sorted out.
You're welcome, mate. No worries. You're
absolutely welcome.
Okay. And the last thing we're going to
do, as we always do, we're going to give
away a free course. It is not the full
course. It is not the orderflow course
or the 20our course. It's just an
introduction to the markets. Great for
someone who's never traded before who
has no idea. All right? So, if you don't
want to do it, you can always give it to
a family member or a friend. Just type
course in chat once and we'll pick a
winner. I'll give you guys a minute to
do that as well.
Guys, please don't spam.
Guys, if you spam, you don't get entered
anyway, and you're just going to get
pulled out. All right, pull in the
winner. Five, four, three, two, and one.
Uh, Julie Julie Scaledo. Julie Scaledo.
Hopefully I've said that right. Are you
here? Julie Scaledo.
Julie Scaledo. 9757. Let me know you're
here.
Yes, that's you. Indeed, that's you. All
right. Congratulations. you've won a
free course, introduction to trading.
Please can you email me
info@flonetrader.com?
Just send me a screenshot of you logged
in to your YouTube just so I know it's
you and uh I will hook you up with a
free course.
All right, everyone.
That's me done. Um,
I can just tell you what I'd be looking
at for the rest of the day. You're in
rotation now. So, we lost this shelf,
right? They failed. Unfortunately, they
failed to get all the way up here.
You've now got trapped volume above
this. Here's your new view up. Here's
the top of that old gap. All right,
where the sellers got trapped originally
on the day. They're trying to pivot
above this. So, maybe this is like a 50%
pullback. Um, I would be less and less
interested in this as the day develops.
Now, I think they're just going to have
to build out liquidity. um you've got
opportunities both sides. This would be
like buying the midpoint of of this
range to try and get up here and if they
lose this they can also do this. So the
your probability is not so good. Main
trend is down but I think we finished
that. I think we might need to do this
rotation up here but it's have they got
the juice to do it today? I don't know.
I will remind you you have mag earnings
at the bell. I still think this is
possible up here. All right. And if they
get going over these 800s, 820s, you're
looking for 890s, 900s, and then maybe
even all the way up here. Right, they
just held that New York view up. You can
see cash still coming in and playing. I
think there could be relief here this
afternoon, but I uh I will not be
playing anymore. I don't think those in
Discord, I will pop in this afternoon.
Uh my email info@flowzonerader.com.
info@flowzontrader.com.
Can't access the website. really sounds
like your anti that's your antivirus.
Just turn your antivirus off. I don't
know why it's doing that.
Um
website's definitely safe, my end. I can
check with Google again, but it should
be all fine.
Gray boxes on the chart, you draw them
on just like I do. All right, peace and
love everyone. If if you're long and
strong, hopefully you can get up there
for you guys. I'll see you tomorrow
morning. Let's close out this week
strong. All right, let's have a great
end of week. We've had a monstrous week.
It has been a massive week, two weeks in
a row of some absolutely huge trades.
So, let's see if we can close out this
week strong. Peace and love, everyone.
See you tomorrow morning. Use hard
stops, all that good stuff. Be kind. See
you in the morning.