morning team.
Good morning everyone. How are we doing?
Hopefully you had a great afternoon
session. Hopefully some of you held that
short through the afternoon and maybe
even some of you recognized those trap
traders at the lows and took that
squeeze back up for the end of day cover
rally. Where did that squeeze happen?
Well, surprise surprise. Here it is. The
lower Ballinger band. How many times did
we go over that? All right. No
acceptance above, none below. Still
boxed in. Nothing's changed. There is
the possibility today of a continuation.
All right. because we've had a failed
breakout, right? Failed to break out,
failed to hold games, pulled all the way
down, pumped back up, have left these
traders trapped after that gap fill.
It's possible we see a continuation.
What's the big problem? Well, we
probably need to build out some
liquidity down here so that we've got
some shorts to uh get into and we've got
some buyers to use for the stop run and
we need this Ballinger band to start
opening up. But maybe we have a day
where we come a little bit outside. So,
we're watching these uh yesterday's lows
and the ones from the week before one or
two 225s and and into sort of 200s,
right? We're watching that. If we start
to see an acceptance below that, it is
not the ideal location for the short. As
we know, the ideal location for the
short was up here or even on a pop up
here today to fade back down. So, we
want to be very very careful shorting
the lows of a rotation, don't we? So,
we're going to have to need to see
buyers stuck. The easiest way would be a
push that fails or a dunk underneath
that fails to reclaim. That's a riskier
trade given what we've got with the
Ballinger bands. But we will have to be
aware of it in case it plays out. If we
are going to just dip and hold again,
which would be just like here and here
and here and here. All right, it would
be a range rotation back to the 20-day.
So, those are the possibilities. This
morning, we're either going to see that
continuation or the rotation back up. I
guess the other possibility which we
should talk about is just an inside bar.
All right, which just builds liquidity
down here and we don't do much. It's
also possible we have news 945 10:00 and
we have uh mag earnings tonight. So
things to be aware of folks. All right,
let's have a look at the uh hourly
chart. Find some clues from here. I'm
going to move this up so it's a bit
bigger for you guys to see. This is the
developing week profile. Anyone that's
new to stream, this right here is
developing week. This is the previous
week. So the easiest location to be
short would actually be a drive up into
here. All right, sort of just in front
of 600's. A little stop hunt above there
and a failure. That would be a great
location to short. That would be a two
leg that we could short into looking to
retest these lows. It doesn't look like
we're going to get it. It looks at the
moment like they've done it overnight.
There's your first leg into the close.
There's the second leg. There's the
failure to make a new high. And maybe
versus sort of 420s they're going to
rotate this down. I don't know. So
ideally we get a morning drive which we
can sell into. I'm not convinced we're
going to get it but that would be the
most ideal circumstance. Right? If we
don't do that what are the other levels
I'm looking at? Why is someone's been on
my keyboard? There is chocolate on my
keyboard. Right. If we if we don't do
that then what I'll be looking for is
this developing point of control
previous day value area low. So
somewhere into here 377s up to sort of
420ish. This area here is currently
blue. Can we turn this Well, I'm going
to put it gray for now, but could we
turn it into a red block and then sell
down from that? So, sort of 3 380s
into 420s. All right, that kind of level
here. Could we push up, fail, and sell
that back down? We will be covering some
into previous low swing points. All
right, we're going to, you know, we're
going to respect those low swing points,
aren't we? Let's put this back to gray.
Right. If we miss that opportunity, all
right, we're going to have to be careful
about this. If we miss this opportunity,
if this doesn't set up and this doesn't
set up, we want to be very careful
getting short down here. All right, lots
of guys that have ripped us up from here
before. So, if you're going to be short
down here, you're really going to need
it to fail under everything and back
test and stay heavy. You do not want to
just join in um trying to chase that
momentum because momentum might be good,
but the location here will be terrible.
Remember, the lower Ballinger band on
the daily is down here. Let's talk about
the other way, right? If if we're going
to come down here, maybe we sweep, maybe
we don't, and we hold and we go back
into rotation, then we'd be looking like
this yesterday for those dips with
sellers caught at the lows or that move
back up again. We would have to sell
some into these key levels. So, the same
level we're looking to fade, we'd have
to take a partial on and then hopefully
we could get into 500s and maybe even
600s. I will tell you now, where will
this get squeezy? A base above this. All
right, 600 to 650. If they base in here
and they start breaking 650, you can see
how thin we are all the way back up to
800. So, a base of 600 to 650, a break
of 650, and then I would expect a move
to 800. That would be the squeeze move.
All right. So, whether that happens or
not, we don't know because we know we
were very thin down, very thin up, very
thin down. All right. So maybe they want
to repric this back up and then reade
it. We don't know folks. Who knows what
these lot are doing. We're in a massive
rotation. We got to be careful. Um edge
or is slightly more to the downside
given the momentum yesterday. But we
just got to be aware that every single
time we come into here, right, we can't
find acceptance lower. All right, look
at all this. These are remember these
are weekly profiles. every single time
we come down here, we can't find
acceptance. But like I've talked about,
if we start to find acceptance, if they
are going to deem that all of this
volume is way too high in price and they
want to go risk off, then we're going to
have months and months and months worth
of volume trapped above and that would
be a nice trade if that happens. All
right, move this down. We can have a
quick look at what happened overnight.
Make sure you can see enough. Not too
much really. Globex basically went
sideways. All right, so Asia definitely
went sideways. There's the pump after
the trap, right into the low. There's
the pump after the trap. Asia popped up
into Mr. 200. Failed the 200 on London.
Back for a retest. Failed it again.
We're just watching this previous day
low down here. I'd be watching this move
into 180s because we didn't Oh, it's
it's uh sorry, it's from Monday. It's
the Monday Sunday open. We didn't clear
that out yesterday. So, so far it's
protected. So, we're watching that.
Okay, let's have a go up here and we
will get into ES and some of the ETFs.
You're going to be looking at very, very
similar stuff right now across the
broader market.
All right, big fail here. We got very,
very close to taking out the highs like
we talked about. All right, they came
right up into these highs and they
stuffed it and you can see right now
we're right at that point of control.
Right, so not much doing here. Uh,
relative strength I would say on ES
right now.
Right. And if we think about this sort
of range here, we're right in the
middle, aren't we? All right. We did see
rotation yesterday. If you had a look at
the sectors, you saw rotation yesterday
back into healthcare, back into
defensive kind of names, back into
finance names. All right, out of tech
into those. So that's why the ES is
holding up better. All right, a broader
market. Remember 500 stocks in here that
we're looking at, only 100 in ENQ and
very tech heavy in NQ. So, so far
holding up okay on ES. All right,
relative strength there. But again, we
can see we keep getting stuck. We cannot
get above that 7,000 and base. All
right, that's the big problem right now.
So, very similar thing. Are we going to
flush down and clean all of this out?
Right, this is our first big sell.
That's your bounce. We expect a retest
down here. So, that's probably what
we're going to be looking for this
morning. We can have a look at the ETFs
to make it a little bit simpler. There
you go. SPY ETF. If we go from that high
to low, it's probably done a 50%
retracement already there, almost to 61.
So, looking good here. It's uh into its
gap. So, if we start losing the gap,
then we're going to look for this attack
down here. And you must be paying
yourself into this because if they set a
higher low there and want to come up for
a second leg, they can before they
resell it. Okay? So, we're protective if
we get that move there. If we get this
morning drive, then as long as these
buyers up here stay stuck, we will be
selling into it. Same thing on the cues,
right? Exactly the same. You can see the
relative weakness. Nowhere near a 50%
push. All right, if we think about this
from high to low, nowhere near up here
like the ES, right? So that's the
broadening market into the ES where
we're seeing weakness in tech. So Q's
looking for this. If we get very lucky,
they'll pop up somewhere into here and
we can fade that back down. But the
moment looks very heavy. Dixie continues
to try and find a bid. All right, it's
starting to try and find a bid. If we do
this here, you can see this old beauty
that we look for. All right, a bit of a
quasi there. All right, can it get back
into here is the question on the Dixie?
I don't know. Uh, we can talk about
gold. We're doing that move. We're doing
that move. All right, there's the high.
There's the flush. Do we get failure to
follow through? This is the key question
now on gold and silver. Do the metals
fail to follow through and get a resell
or do they reclaim base and go for new
highs? These are all the opportunities.
Same on silver. We talked about this for
the last few days. All right, there's
the drive down. Buyers are stuck above
here. We can do this to this. We're
looking for something into here. Even if
you wanted to measure out some volume
for all of this, where are you? You
could use the same kind of thing. It's
very rough, but to give you an idea. All
right, we're looking you're into this
thin level. So, anywhere short from 91
up to 99 is possible on silver for a
swing position. If it starts reclaiming,
night, don't touch it. VIX. All right,
we can see still sort of in this messy
channel that's still producing higher
lows, higher lows, higher lows, and it's
trying to base to get out of this. So,
we're watching VIX today. I can give you
some slightly more accurate levels here
if we zoom in. Right, watching VIX here.
If it starts breaking 1826s, right, then
we're going to look for a retest towards
these 19s. Obviously, a breakout over
that is problematic. You can see this
channel. I know it's rough, but every
time we come outside of this channel,
we're not then reholding. All right,
we're not reholding. So, if we break
this on VIX, maybe we get going
and uh we will see. If we start dropping
under here on VIX and rotating,
then the market probably finds a bid
today for that rotation up. I would be
very aware today about a big divergence
kind of day. If we see that, I wonder if
they sell tech regardless. Um, let's
have a quick look at the mag. We are
running out of time. I'm going to have
to be very, very quick here. All right,
Apple had some positive data come out
this morning. still looks good, holding
its gains after earnings driving out
really, really well. Amazon weaker here.
MAG coming this week. Remember, earnings
on the way right here. Uh, still in a
range. Still no full breakdown. Google
uh earnings as well. Is this tonight?
Yes, after the bell tonight for Google.
So, we're watching that. So, this might
get wonky. Here's your current range
while they decide what they do with it.
Options expire is going to be key on
that. Meta continues to slide. All
right, back down into this area. So,
repricing that whole earnings. Remember,
this is a breakout retest. Do they reby
that back up? That's the big question
right now. I'm still long in that small
position. Microsoft, that looks
terrible. That looks terrible. Uh that's
going to start perking my interest soon
as we come into this kind of area here.
All right, they're going risk off on
tech. If we start coming sliding under
here, I will start bidding back up. I
will consider some here, but if we slide
under longterm, I will start bidding
some back up because that is a
overexaggerated move at this point. I
know everyone's saying it's doomsday.
It's the end of AI. It's the end of
tech. But that's 26% down already
without a pullback. So, we will see. If
we slide too much more, I'll start
getting interested. Nvidia still in this
range at the highs, right? Just going
sideways. We've got a peak high,
possible blowoff top on that peak
formation high. Um, but we are sideways
ever since. It is gapping down today. Is
that right? Let me see. No, we're flat.
Flat on Nvidia. Tesla. I mean, that
looks like one of the worst traders I've
seen. Unless you're a range trader. I
mean, it continues to just do this,
right? Until it loses some of this.
Those 420s have been key for well, must
be the best part of a year now. So,
that's it folks. That is it for this
morning. We have about four minutes
left. We can have a look at some broad
names. Um in um Netflix started to
undercut yesterday. Remember this is
perking my interest. I've got a small
piece on this uh long by the way. Just a
feeler to keep me interested. I'm
watching really for it to come down into
here somewhere into here. Ideally this
high here and even if it really wants to
drift and be ridiculous then I'll scoop
some up. This is uh we're talking about
a 3 to five year swing here. Right guys?
I'm not talking about a trade. I'm
talking about a big swing position. So
if we come down into this or even this
it will perk my interest
and I did start long in these as we
talked about yesterday. Uu looking for
that breakout and hold over 20s which it
did and USA is also same kind of thing.
Hold over 20s looking for that
continuation breakout. So I've got small
starters on there. If we start to build
build and build this uh sort of right
shoulder in here now. Hello. All right.
I will start to build a position. If we
start to hold this right shoulder. Um
and this is a macro type news based on
Trump's positioning into rare earth.
Okay.
Into rare earth. Okay. Let's get us back
on track here.
Uh oh. Is Ninja Trader down again?
Please tell me not. Is that what you
guys are all saying? Let me have a look.
We're trading at 82. Mine's okay. Mine's
okay.
Mine is okay. Thank goodness. You guys
scared me then. Right, let's end this
poll. See what the results were of the
poll.
Most of you thinking range rotation.
Some of you thinking continuation short.
None of you are thinking pump.
Lots of you saying trade of eight is
down. Okay, we want to be see we want to
be careful here then. We want to be
careful here. Sounds like there's some
issues with trade of eight and ninja.
Let's be careful then, folks. Let's be
careful.
Yeah, mine's all right. Do me a favor.
Smash that like button nice and early
for me. Then I don't have to say it any
longer on stream.
And um let's have a good day here. Let's
have a good day. Let's see if we can uh
we're going to retest this sort of 420s
and if they fade that. If they don't
fade that, then we're expecting that
move back up towards 500s. And we can
have a look at that in there.
We want to be very careful getting short
at the lows in a range. Remember, very,
very, very, very careful. So, I want to
see if there is a pop that fails this
morning, which would be the most ideal
kind of situation.
Okay, come on guys. Almost a thousand of
you in here this morning. Let's smash
that like button. Let's get it moving. I
want to do some giveaways on stream.
We will do another funded next giveaway
this month now as well. So, I've got to
uh maybe we'll come up with that
question together on stream.
What are we doing here? There's the
open, folks. All right. So, it's selling
off on that morning drive.
Where's this 500 lot I just seen flash?
Even bookmap feels a bit slow here. It's
seeing me having some troubles here. Is
it? Here's the 500 lot at 300. They've
just gone straight into him at 300
and bouncing off that for now.
Is there going to be continuation under
it? Not yet. Not yet.
Drive underneath that 300 now.
And book even bookmaps very laggy for me
here folks
in the short for the snap underneath.
See if we can come down to previous day
low. Lovely. Nice start to the day.
Fantastic. This is what we want to see.
So gray box rejecting. I was watching
the 300 in short once we let go of 300.
Looking for this down here. Protecting
my money now. No matter what value area
is down here. Uh watching some of these
nodes here into 85. This is what we
want. 219. So nice early trade to start
the day. Rejecting the gray box.
Rejecting value. Here we go. How much
lower can we go? Protecting some of this
already. Now can start to see some bids
trying to show up here. So, I'm going to
watch that same area where I got in for
that 300 break on a retest. I do not
want that to be reclaimed. Already
paying myself nicely. That is a great
start to the day. Beautiful 50 point
plus.
Can we get down to previous days low?
Once that big buyer got washed, it
became easier. They are bidding down
towards 22 225s to 200. So, we should
get it here, folks. Here we go. Here we
go. We're going to go have a 100 pointer
to start the day. Come on, baby. Come
on, baby. Come on, baby. Come to papa.
Come to papa to start the day. We're
going to be one and done here. Let's go.
Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go.
Move this stop. They're going to front
run this a little bit. Watching ES into
Globeex. Same level. Come on.
You got to love it when they're kind to
us in the market.
Let's go.
still looking for previous day low and
under that uh we have more liquidity as
well. So we just previous day low and
then this green line down here. These
are the two final cover points but I'm
going to make sure and paid myself no
matter what. They are adding liquidity
down here. I do think we have another
attempt down. They might just want to
drift up towards 300 first before they
come back down there. So 280 to 300 will
be a key level they come. So, just a
small size left on this to see if we can
get down. Watching this 300 test now. If
they rip back through this, I'll be out.
They can force a squeeze right back to
350. But this is the 300 level.
Watching this very careful whether I
take this off or not on the runner.
Still holding pretty firm here so far.
Very thin above this. Remember, that's a
nice rejection. Can we get a
continuation now? Can we get down? There
we go. Come on, baby.
Come on, baby. Beautiful 300 rejection.
Here we go. Come on, baby.
Come to papa.
Can I sing to it? What do I have to do
to make this come down? Come to papa.
Here we come to papa.
Really nice 300 rejection there. You can
see the exact level I gave you. Just
want to see if this will wash.
Trader bait's down. You guys are saying
well I'm not having problems guys. Uh
don't want to I don't know what to tell
you. Um I'm trading on Ninja Trader via
trader bait and it's working for me.
Back to 300 then. Oh, if they reclaim
this I will cut the runners which will
be a shame. I tell you what, there must
be a little lag because I am on a copy
trader and these are not all together.
These are all PAs and you can see
there's a little bit of lag between
them. Back to 300. 300 is is the level.
Above 300, they can squeeze to probably
325 and even 350, but as long as we hold
here, we look good. Remember, we are at
the lower Ballinger band. So, we want to
be careful. We've talked about this on
the daily. This is a question right now
as if we can expand. Can we do almost
like a black swan type event here?
Right, when we have a look at this right
here, you can see we are defending right
now value on the current developing
week. We are looking to sweep this low
and get into this low and cover into
this. If we get under this, the lower
Ballinger band is like right here where
we keep bouncing off under this. We have
a shot all the way down to here. 25,000
basically
25,000. No matter what, we are locking
in money.
You guys seem to be having some some
issues here.
Web also down. If you're logged in when
it went down, it still works. If you
weren't, you can't log in. I'm really
sorry to hear that, guys. That's uh
that's got to be frustrating. All right.
Out here on the runners watching this
now as we come back into 25s, right?
They can reject 25s to 50s. Otherwise,
they can rip this back up. If this is
going to be another failed, make sure
I've got you on the right channel. Uh,
if we fail to sweep these lows,
remember, we can rip this straight back
up to this box, which is where I was
first interested in short, but I took
the 300 break right around here. So,
reclaim here. We'll watch these same
levels. I'll give you a little readout
on the mag. Tesla 0.03% down. So,
basically flat. Nvidia 0.75% down.
Microsoft 0.70%
up. Meta 1.32% down. Google 0.77% up.
Amazon quarter% down. Apple 2% up. They
cannot make up their mind here. All
right. Back to previous day value area
low. So they've ripped this back up
through the 300 on the squeeze. Back to
previous day value area low. Back to the
current New York open. Back to the
24hour VWAP. Right. Big big big levels.
You can see the rotation here. It's very
very very aggressive today. Very very
violent the way we're moving. Uh VIX
just rejected that pivot at 1830s that
we talked about pre-market come back
down to its PDC. So rotation definitely
taking place right now. I am still what
is going on bookmap? Can you start
following price instead of being a dick?
Thank you.
So still rejecting that New York open.
Um I would say over New York open there
is potential for a squeeze up to 513s if
we're going to play both sides. I'm
still short biased technically, but you
know, up here would be a very nice short
location. If they want to come and run
all these stops and come up here, this
is where I'd love to get short.
So, flat now and just waiting. I'm not
going to play this long on a return
unless I really see it start to base and
hold far too early. But, uh, ES holding
up pretty well here this morning.
Relative strength in the ES. If you look
at the broader market, ES 0.08% up. Uh,
ENQ half a percent down. So, we have
weakness in tech. Like I said, wouldn't
surprise me if we have a very big
divergent day today
30 ATR. Yeah, I mean it was actually
higher than that. It was actually at an
87 on an M1 ATR.
huge amounts of orders at 620. Let me
have a look what you guys are saying.
Zoom right out.
Wouldn't say huge, but there are some
orders up there. Yeah, it's where we got
thick, isn't it? Before I wouldn't say
huge. We still can't get through that
New York open right now. We can't get
through the New York open right now.
They will have to trigger through that
to get any form of squeeze upside into
this. And at the moment they keep
getting stuck up there. Absolutely
getting stuck up there at the moment.
ES is through it. VIX just found a bid
on PDC.
So my bias is technically still short.
Until we get over all of this, uh I
still think there's a chance to come and
clean up the lows. If we get over all of
it, there might be a squeeze up and
there might be a short further further
up later on in the day. But we'll just
see. Like like I said, I've made my
money. You've seen it on the screen.
Waiting now to see what the next setup
brings. I still think we can clean up
all of this. It's a lot of stops down
here now been left.
Lots of you sound like you're having
lots of issues. It sounds like CME
issues. Honestly, if you guys are having
trade issues and rhythmic issues and
bookmat was slow and I'm getting a few
sort of spready orders. Sounds like CME
are having issues to me.
Okay, can these guys make up their mind?
Let's get some volume on here.
Traded for a few minutes.
See, at the moment, we can't get over
this New York open and get up into this
this GlobeEx session and we have not
cleaned up all these stops. So, we're
just in the rotation. We have protected
yet again so far. If I take you over to
the daily yet again, we have protected
this right here, haven't we? All right.
So, three lots of uh dips down here
holding the edge of this value area from
this high. All right. And the Ballinger
band, we keep protecting that. I'd say
underneath 178, it gets very very thin
very very quickly. All right. So, it's a
big level for them to keep trying to
protect.
We might need to build up liquidity for
a session or two. It might very possible
we have to do that. Are we in a trend
day? Uh no, we not yet. I I think we
could develop one. It could be a kind of
black swan event kind of day, but we
will see. We will see. And they might
well build liquidity for a session or
two, wait for the earnings and then dunk
it. I am watching this again around this
300 level. That's where uh point of
control now is for me based on delta and
they are starting to sell into this
level again. If they don't rebid this,
this market is likely to get heavy. So
I'm watching this 300 again. We have
some buildup of liquidity down at 72s,
272s.
So watching this, they're still bidding
in and around here. It's where that big
seller came in this morning. So it's a
huge huge level. If they start losing
this, it's possible we go back towards
that low of day there. I will respect
80s and 72s though and we have a node
here at sort of 37s to 40s. So 300 to
40s current rotation over that potential
squeeze through the New York open and uh
VWAP. So here they go back to the 40s.
Can they get through the 50s to New York
open? Yes. So they held 300 back to the
40s back towards trying to get to this
gray box in the New York open. This is a
very thick level. I want to remind you
this is not just like a random gray box.
All right. the developing profile with
the point of control. We can see this is
our contested level. Okay, shorts under
here all the time they're holding this,
they're looking for this. If buyers get
above this, they're looking for that
rotation. And above here, I would
imagine shorts will try and come back
in. If buyers hold this, there's a
gigantic squeeze. All right? So, we have
to be willing to play both sides. We
have to be willing to play both sides
based on what has been built out in
front of us. It's not cuz I don't know
what I'm doing. It's because this is
what the market's setting up. Be willing
to play both sides. Yeah. News at 9:45
and at 10, folks. 9:45 and at 10. We
have uh D
PMI 9:45 and ISM 10:00. Right. PMI 945,
ISM 10:00.
Okay, let's see here. They're coming up
for these 80s. Big lot up here at 80s.
New York open over that potential
squeeze. Uh gapill would be to 453 if it
wants to be an efficient market. I will
not be playing the longs for this first
drive up. I can tell you that now. No
way. No way am I doing that today. And
already locked in some great money this
morning.
Another global trade issue, guys. I'm so
sorry. I mean, it's got to be so
frustrating, hasn't it? It's got to be
so frustrating. But, you know, maybe
trade your cash accounts. If you've got
a cash account, even if it's a ETF based
account, you could trade Q's. If you
didn't have a futures based account, you
could trade Q's or SQ or TQ if you
wanted to be triple leveraged in it.
Or use another provider. You could
always get a rhythmic account setup or
Motive Wave or something else.
I don't think it's too often. I think I
I can remember twice in the last two or
three years that we've had this. It's
just that they've been close together.
If they start happening too regularly,
though, it'll be a problem. All right,
we just failed that New York open again.
Right, this thing is struggling to get
through that. Struggling to get through
that.
And it's back into this shelf at these
40s again. So 40s to uh
to 80s is the rotation. If they lose
40s, we're coming back for 300. If we
lose 300, we're probably going back for
the lows and a big snap. So watching
this, this level here is big. This is
300. You can see it. This is kind of
sentiment right now. So you can see this
here and this node here being developed
to sort of 40s up to this higher 80s.
They lose 40s, they're going to come
300. they lose that we probably break
down into this if they lose that. Big
ifs, but uh if they did, that's what we
would expect.
Can't even connect your regular account
to Ninja. That seems odd.
That seems odd. Mine are working so I
haven't got that problem. Let me just
Sorry, guys. We're blowing up my phone.
They never learn. It's like this is the
time I work.
Yeah. They want to ring and call me and
text me at this time. Right. Here we go.
Back to these 40s again.
Back down. If we lose this back down to
the 300. So, watching this now. If they
start losing this and I see follow
through, then I think there's a
potential low day move here. So, we're
watching point of control into 300 here.
Here we go.
Back towards this 300. And can we get
follow through underneath this now? 40s
to 300. Here's 300. We got a small piece
on in case we fail underneath this. Here
we go. Under the 300. Want to see this
stay heavy on a rejection and then we
can go low of day.
Not staying heavy yet. So just 40 to 300
so far.
Bookmap, please. Please bookming
today.
So, want to see if we retest 30s and
stay heavy and then snap uh 300s and go
low of day.
So, can we retest 30s and stay heavy and
then snap 300 and go low of day. If we
reclaim 40s then uh there's no trade
downside here. News coming here as well.
Another lot of news coming in uh how
long? 15 minutes now.
Okay. It's still basing around this 300
this gray box. So the opportunities here
will either be the uh a straight fade
underneath or this this this this is an
opportunity or I guess this to here and
then reade that back down. Those are the
opportunities.
Here's the move back towards the 30s. We
only got to 24s.
Still think this got liquidity lower to
clean up. The ES holding up pretty well.
Still absorbing on its view up. Its flow
zones are flat. It's on the New York
open. still have relative weakness in
the cues. Give you another readout on
the mag. Tesla basically flat. Nvidia
almost 1% down. Microsoft basically
flat. Meta almost 2% down. Google third
of a percent up. Amazon 0.63%
down. Apple having a strong day. 2.84%
up. That thing's absolutely ripping back
up towards highs, which is great for me
because I'm still swing long. Um that
might be because of uh what came out
last night with Nancy Pelosy's recent
investment. she is back long into Apple.
So, out of all the tech, obviously it
doesn't have big AI
um what would you call it? Exposure,
let's call it.
If if you're stuck in a guy, guys, what
I would say is relax. All right? If
you're stuck in a trade on trade of
eight, uh don't stress. They they will
get it fixed like for you afterwards. If
it's a global outage, it will not make a
difference. If you're trading prop, you
will be okay. All right, back down to
these 300s. We still can't get through
this 40 that we just talked about. This
is still possible here. It's very, very
whippy between 40 and 300. They cannot
make their mind up here. So, here to
here is the liquidity through here.
Here, stop hunt through this gap. Fill
possible. I'm not going to trade the
long. Like I said, if we lose this, I'll
be interested.
So big squeeze all the way back up
based on absolutely nothing other than
ES catching a bid and then rotating the
300 to 40s back to the high of day. If
they can't pop these stops, it's going
to be pretty pathetic at this point.
Oh, slam my desk.
Yes, almost at GlobeEx.
Seriously, you got to go and run the
stops out one side. You can't do
nothing, market. You're going to do
nothing for another day.
You're not going to give us one more
trade. Just that opening trade and
that's it. Come on.
Apple on an absolute tear here. 3% up
now, which great for me. How much am I
now up on my swing position?
Approaching 30% up on that swing. I've
been long since uh what is it? Get my
core position up. Open Apple, please.
Average position is 208 on Apple. We're
currently trading
277s, which is great. All right, failed
the height again. This thing is awful.
cannot make its mind up what it's doing
here. Range much tighter today. It might
be that we do an inside day and just
wash around a little bit.
Yeah, AMD down on earnings. It beat it
actually beat on earnings, but they're
selling it off.
This thing is stuck now. Stuck in this
value. Tight value now. 70 to 95. Pretty
tight here. Pretty tight here. Let's see
what they do.
feel like they're going to wash it. They
cannot break the highs, but you just it
would be much better if they clean one
side out. Back to the 300 again. So, we
are not breaking this New York open and
VWAP and getting above here. We're still
in a ro small rotation here. Under 300,
low of day is possible. I've said it so
many times. Under 300, low of days. Back
to the point of control. Here we go.
Back to these 300. So, if they don't
save this now, I would imagine low of
day.
Very, very possible.
Here we go, folks.
If they stay heavy, 300 to 317 is kind
of the level where the sellers came in
at. They stay heavy there, I would
imagine, low of day. If they don't stay
heavy, obviously we go straight back to
the 40s again. You can see we're very
tight in this rotation. If we lose this
gray box, I will assume that we're going
to try and come down towards this. 317s
was a level where a big seller came in.
So, they will need it under that. Uh a
lift through that would be back to the
40s again. They cannot make up their
mind. But I tell you what, ES tap
GlobeEx, it's still just hanging around
on its VWAP and New York open. Just
everything's stuck right now.
VIX looks like it's got that look, that
sort of inverted head and shoulders look
and VIX will really get going on a break
over 1845 probably. All right, looks
like they're going to try and do this
wash towards lower day. Watching this
now. Here we come. Is the 80s value area
low on the day? Do they find acceptance
down here in in towards the 70s and then
the lows? Watching this now in this
short
peeling some off in case we keep
protecting these 80s and 70s. I want to
see this just flush the lows now at this
point. Come on. It's just getting You're
just getting stupid here, market. Come
on. Here we come towards the 70s. Don't
want them to protect this little node.
Want to just wash through this.
Please come and clean something out.
Out rotation. Come on, Mark. Get out the
rotation. Maybe they're waiting for
10:00. Lots of buyers down at 25. So, I
think we should get down into there.
They can just stop [\h__\h] around with
it. Here come the 70s. So, TP1 here. I'm
peeling some off into this in case they
hold. But I am expecting a new low of
day. I'm watching previous day low and
then this here 185s.
Here we go.
Like we talked rejection a gray box. So,
we can move lower. Still protecting 70s.
We just want this to snap now. ES
starting to really let go. Come on. We
should accelerate at this point. Come
on. Stop [\h__\h] around. You're done
with it. Let's have it. Let's [\h__\h] go
down. Down. Down. Down. Down. Let's go.
Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go.
Accelerate. Accelerate. Accelerate.
Accelerate. Accelerate. Pay the daddy.
Here we come. Here we come. Two
attempts. Same trade. Here we come. So,
a little bit left here. I'm watching for
all the way down into these two green
ones for Get Out my way. I'm looking for
cover points into this and this and
this.
Let's go.
They are stacking 37s down to 20s right
now. I think we will get it. There's a
buyer keep stepping in here. There's a
shelf being built at 50. I think we will
get lower here. Come on.
Stop saving it. You [\h__\h] idiots.
Get out my way and give me the fill. ES
down to low of day. In fact, ES just
wicked low of day. Come on, ENQ. Don't
do me like that. Massive divergence. ES
just wicked low of day. I'm glad I got a
partial. [\h__\h] me. Making my life hard.
Right. Watching this for rejection of
300. Got to stay heavy versus 300 here.
Worst case scenario, 320. But really, we
want to stay heavy versus gray box.
These are still recover points. Still
holding this. Got one left on. Let this
work now.
Let this work now. Back to the 300. Oh,
ES has done me dirty there. It's a
divergence there with ES. I still think
we're going to get the move, but ES has
done me dirty there. Big fail. Washed
the low of day and found a bid. That is
dirty. That ENQ will not do it with it
when we've got relative weakness. You
bunch of clowns. Absolute bunch of
clowns.
Get out my [\h__\h] way and drop this,
please.
O.
So, back to the 300s. 320 is where that
big seller came in. 3 320 there will
probably squeeze to 40s, but all the
time we're holding that. It's not too
bad.
Come on, you idiots. Absolute idiots.
VIX can't get that breakout through the
45s that we talked about. It just came
right up to 40. Very, very volatile.
We're still protecting 300 320. I'm
still in this all the time. We're
protecting 300 and 320s. I'm happy to
sit in it. This is a pullback. We're
going to reject New York VW up and gray
box. Hopefully, we can get some follow
through now. Hopefully, this is enough
liquidity to get us down into here. Now,
I will not hold above this though. 320s
is the level I can show you if we get
this up.
All right, this is the guy that I'm
playing against. This seller here. I'm
using him. He's the big whale dragging
us. Come on. Come on. This is the
opportunity now. Want to see this
breakdown now. We got lots of stops down
here. We should This time we should
absolutely snap it. These buyers can't
keep trying to save it. Little shelf
here at 50 or 48. Through that we should
go. Looking good. Looking good. Looking
good. Looking good. Come on, baby. Come
on, baby. Come on, baby. Come on, baby.
Please. Pretty please.
Pretty please.
Just snap it for God's sake.
It's getting stuck on bookmat. Come on.
They're all here. They're all stacked
down to 225s and 200s. We should get it
here. They're coming for it now. Come
on. Come on. Come on. Just someone just
sell through. Stop [\h__\h] around. I'm
trying to hold for the breakdown here.
Here we go. Here we go. It's coming.
It's coming.
It's coming. Give me that green line.
Don't you dare. Don't you [\h__\h] dare
protect it.
Come on.
Give it. Give it to me. I'm not going to
be a dick for a ticket. Come on.
I had to pay myself a little bit. Almost
there, folks. It's going to come. So,
we're watching this green line for a
cover and this green line for a cover
and then runners underneath.
And this will be 100 point. Another over
100 pointer. All right. So, 340
rejected. 320 stayed heavy. Rejection of
here. Here's your trade. TP1, TP2, TP3.
There you starting to get a few sellers
getting a little bit caught down here
underneath 27s. Want to be careful. Want
to be careful on the runners here. I
don't want to give it all the way back
again. It's been a really good move.
Don't want to give 70 points back. Big
seller coming in on the tape here. 300
lot just above us. I want to see him
walk down. I don't want him to sit there
at 45. I actually want to
get out of my way. Get out of my way.
Get out of my way. Thank you very much.
Nothing but nets on Flowzone Trader. All
right, let's see how far can we go. How
far can we go? Let's see, folks. This
guy on YouTube doesn't know what he's
doing, does he? He's an absolute
plonker. All right, here here we go. One
into here. One into here. Next TP. We're
almost there, folks. You are almost
almost there. We're looking for this 84s
and then after that down here. Absolute
beauty. You're over 100 points again.
Can you dig it?
Let's go.
On a [\h__\h] heater here, baby. On a
heater here, baby. Here's your green
line. TP into this. Don't be a dick for
a tick. It is literally a tick. And then
this is your next TP. And then this gray
box. All right, we're starting to get
follow through now. But we are going to
be careful into here, right? We're going
to be careful. This is the protected
low. If we snap that, I will tell you if
we snap that, we are then looking for a
trade into 131s and 2520s. And we can
have a look on the daily here. Um cuz I
will show you. We've gone over this
numerous times. Look at the shelf. We
are taking these wicks out. We get very
thin under here. All right. They will
want to protect this. if they cannot
protect this. Look at this. This is
since the all-time high. All right, this
profile here is based since the all-time
high. We're starting to see followth
through outside of the Ballinger. I will
respect this is the LA for the current
year. So, we've got a gap here. 188 down
to 25100ish
95s and then under that we're going to
start getting [\h__\h] weak, baby. Let's
go. Get out my way.
Come on. Come on.
Come on. I'd love to see who gave you
this outside of here.
Gray box coming up. And then after that,
it's just if we get lucky. It's really
like if we get lucky, we get all the way
down into this. But this is our main
trade for the day. Low hanging fruit's
gone. Job done, guys. Nothing but net.
Yeah. Job done, guys.
What a beauty. What an absolute beauty.
So protective. Now we don't want this to
reclaim here. You can move your stop
down if you want to try and hold this
all day. Uh you can move your stop down
and try and protect sort of 250s. But uh
this is your lowhanging fruit trade.
It's happened. We never reclaimed. Okay.
So here was the thesis today. If we
reject this gray box, we're looking
short. We rejected them open. First
trade on the open. I didn't take that
first rejection. I took the 300 break
once I saw that buyer get caught. So,
the first trade today was the 300 break
right here. So, I was just using
orderflow for that. Um, where is my
short position? Right. Was right here.
You're not going to do it for me really.
There we go. First one was right here
into We were trying to get to the low of
day, right? We're trying to get to that.
We only got to like here.
That was trade one. Trade two into gray
box. So, final targets hit. Now, you're
just a runner, folks. And, uh, you can
try and hold this. Now, the next level
of liquidity I'll be watching at is
basically 25,09. So, you're looking for
25,000. Now, uh Dere
on your runner. All right. If you've got
anything left, that is what you're
looking for.
And I want to see some likes. How many
likes have we got in chat today? 400
likes. 1,200 of you watching. I've just
gifted you. So far, you're in uh
166 points short. and you might well get
a 300 plus point short today. So, if you
can just do me at least the courtesy of
hitting the like button. Like I told
you, I was not going to be looking for
longs today. I knew we're at the lower
ballinger band, but I said I think we
might get that black swan type of event.
We're going to get divergence to the ES
because we had a broadening of the
market yesterday and that's what we've
had. ES only 0.44% down. ENQ 1.30% down.
Why? Because tech is weak. Yesterday I
told you we rotated back into defensive
names which is why ES is holding up. But
if we look at the sectors in the market,
you got to understand the difference
between them two. It's not some [\h__\h]
madeup algo stuff. It's about actual
rotation. All right. So this is why. All
right. Look at what is staying heavy.
Palanteer, Oracle, MU, AMD, AVGO, NVDA,
Amazon, Meta, all of these, all the
tech. And look what's looking okay.
finances, healthcare, energy. All right,
industrials, that's more RTY to be
honest. So, the rotation has been in
full effect and that's why we're seeing
the weakness. Look at the little bid on
the gray box. All right, be done with
this now. You are done. Be done with it,
my friends. Be done with it. Be happy
with this.
They might well lift this back up for a
retest up here for where we've got
volume. All right, but the damage has
been done. We've made our money. If you
were going to do a re-short today, all
right, then you would need this pop up
here versus this, this, and certainly
this one of these to fail. But remember,
your low hanging fruits have gone.
We love those low hanging fruits.
Yeah, dubs in chat for me. Dubs in chat
for me. Thank you, Taylor. That's very
kind of you. I'll get myself a nice
Starbucks after this with that. Thank
you very much.
What do I mean by the broadening of the
market? Okay. So, if we think about
if we think about let's get you to uh
I take you over to a daily. Right.
Right. If we think about
this run. All right. If we think about
this run
and this run, all right, in the Q's,
right? What caused this run in the Q's
in the ES? Right, the MAG, right? The
MAG 7. If you look in this run here,
right, the amount of stocks over their
50-day moving average was very small for
a very long period of time. Why? All
right. In the Q's, 60% of the Q's is
made up by the Mag Seven. All right. So,
if we have a really, really, really,
really, really strong Mag 7, which is
what we've had. All right. If we think
about what we've had, let's look at like
during this time, if we look at Nvidia,
the growth of Nvidia,
right? From like from December, we just
said from 22s 20 like we've moved from
the equivalent of 11 bucks to 200 bucks.
So, I know it's done a split, but
percentage games is the same. We're up
2,000%.
Right? 2,000%.
All right. So, in that time, are we
having other sectors move up 2,000%.
Remember, this is the number one stock
in the world, right? No. If we look at
some of the other things like AVGO, same
kind of thing. Look at this run from
2023, right? 2023 we have moved from the
equivalent of what 59 bucks all the way
up to 400 bucks. All right. Again 579%.
If we look at Meta
from 2023
we've moved from 88 bucks
all the way up to 800 bucks. Right? 800%
gains. Right? So if we think about that
the MAG doing these huge gains they are
dragging the markets up but the other
sectors all right the other names the
finances if we look like the best
performing financial stock is JP Morgan
all right and in that equivalent time is
it up anywhere near as much and this is
the best performing stock no it's not up
we're not talking about thousand% are we
not talking about th000% all right
140% all right and that's a good
performing stock That's a good good
performing stock. It's the best stock in
the financial sector. So, what we're
seeing is profits being taken out of
tech and rotated into the other sectors,
some of the defensive names. Look at the
metals, right? Look at the metals. Look
at all these things like that starting
to gain a bid. Right? Look at what I've
uh started looking at this week. Uh like
uranium,
energy. All right. Where have we gone?
Right? We're starting to find bid.
You're starting to see flow come out of
NQ or the MAG and into some of these
broadening broadening names, which is
why we're starting to get some of this.
I need to move this down for you guys,
don't I? There we go. Which is why we're
starting to get some of this. Right? So,
it's the broadening of the market. It's
it's financial
uh institutions moving into some other
name. Same as we've seen, right? Why is
the Russell caught a bid? Right? It's
the catchup trade, right? This the
Russell is not the tech sector. It's all
the other sectors. Look at what we've
been doing right since 2021. Bugger all
really, right? But we found a bid as
we've started to rotate in. Compare this
exact chart here from 2021 right till
today. If we compare that exact chart to
the ENQ
to the ENQ
this up a bit
2021 to today. I remember the Russell
looked boxed in. Uh the ENQ, this is
what ENQ's done during that time.
Huge, right? We've moved from 10,000
to 26,000,
right? Very, very different market. So
that broadening has started to become
evident and you can really see it in the
ES. It's the easiest place to see it.
Right? So we're finding bid off that
gray box like we talked about. big node
there on that gray box and we've drifted
right the way up to the previous day
low. We have a low volume node here. Now
shorts will need to protect this. All
right, if shorts fail to protect this,
this will be a sweep of these levels
here which is why it was low hanging
fruit and this is possible. Uh and this
will be back into a range for the day
and Alex will not be trading in here.
All right, Alex will not be trading in
here. So there needs to be a
continuation short here. You would have
to cover into this node here now and
then look for a break underneath. If
they reclaim this, unless you like
playing rotation, which I don't, you
could trade in there, but I won't be
trading that today. Right? So, I'd be
looking for a short somewhere in where
we are now. Somewhere around here,
right? You would want to see buyers get
trapped and then resell that back down
and covering some here. If we go
rotation for me, it will mean no more
trades, but that's fine.
What time frame do I use for the
Ballinger bands? I only use it on a
daily. I only use it on a daily, right?
Let me zoom up here. Lots of you
catching that trade with me. Nice work
everyone. Cooper, Hangry Unicorn, some
great names here. Antler Foster, Scott,
Steve, Big Up, Selector, Dean, Infoisk,
JJ, Nathan, Jeff, um,
massive red fan,
uh, Jacob, sniping candles, SS joking
88. Is that maybe I've got that wrong.
Sorry. Uh, Candlestick Cricket, great
name. Alan P. Bradley, Tartan Trader,
Tina,
uh, Joanvoc, uh, Niels, JD, Bart, Niels,
Niels, Niels obviously absolutely killed
that. Nice work, Delina, Emerald,
Frankie, Troy on the cash account since
trade of eight's down. There you go.
Great reason to have a cash account even
if it's small. Uh, Yogi Bear
Krypton says, "Trader of eight trolling
me." I'm sorry to hear that, guys. I
didn't have a problem. Very lucky me.
Um,
Christy got it. Nice work, Christie.
Mini W once trade came back online.
There you go. Ma got it. What are you
guys saying? Am I completely closed out?
Yeah, completely closed out once we hit
this was my target, wasn't it? Once we
hit that, we probably had excess on that
low. I didn't even look cuz I was
already out, but I would imagine there's
selling excess on the low. Yeah. So even
on an hourly time frame if we go down to
like a five minute there will be selling
on their low there you go. So some
excess right now at this low of day
delta at the low of day. So sellers
right now are stuck under 25s right that
is the end of the auction so far we are
coming back up to these key levels we
just talked about you want to see a
rejection there and I would be covering
some into these levels assuming those
sellers stay stuck. If they don't stay
stuck you get lucky and you get the
continuation. So this, like we talked
about, this shelf here, look at that.
46s we just talked about. Somewhere in
there, you'd want sellers to come back
in, right? That's what you're seeing
right now. So somewhere in here, you'd
want sellers to come back in. And you
would need to respect these levels. All
right? So if you're short somewhere like
here, you would need to cover most of it
here. And it's starting to reclaim
already and squeeze. So they're already
rebidding over this. There is possibly a
short from here to here. We do not know
if it wants to break down underneath.
You must respect that. Sellers are
definitely that is a good auction at the
lows. That wick here when we look inside
the profile right we can see that is a
good auction 24 and under is all sell
side that means there is a passive buyer
right down here who was covering and he
has now joined this tape to try and get
a continuation so I'd be watching here
I'd be respecting even sellers getting a
little bit caught here if they break
under here I'd be respecting this level
and this level I wouldn't be expecting
it to go lower than that be nice if it
would but I wouldn't expect it. Like I
said, low hanging fruit's gone, right?
The low hanging fruit trade is gone.
We've just got exactly what we wanted.
If we go back inside this rotation, I
would, for me personally, I would leave
it alone.
So many of you getting this. It's great.
What was my first trigger for the first
short? I can show you on bookmap. It was
a buyer who got himself caught. Um,
let's get the on map. All right, I got
have to go to the start of there. You
might get this now. So guys, if you are
short in this now versus the sort of
250s, like I said, I would be covering a
little bit into this shelf towards sort
of 180s, 170s. Um, we had remind myself
where those sellers are stuck. Uh,
sellers are stuck
underneath 26s, right? So, you're going
to need continuation underneath 26s. If
you don't get that, if they start
bidding between 60s and 26s, you must
pay yourself a little bit. You must pay
yourself. So, this shelf, if you are
short in this shelf, right on these
wicks, I would be taking some TP here
and hoping you can get lower, but not
guaranteeing it because if they want to
do a second leg, they will do a second
leg. Uh,
right. So, sorry, I've got to get you
back on, but sorry, I forgot you're on
here. My trigger for that short was this
player who got caught. I've got to come
right back to what time was that? Like
right at the start of the day.
There he is.
This guy. See this guy here? All right.
There was a big bid here. See this guy?
These lots. We sold through it with a
719 lot and I waited to see if there was
a reaction to go upside and there was no
reaction. Right? There was literally
nothing. So I was like right well I'm
joining short risking that and if we
can't get back above it then I know I'm
going to be comfortably placed because
I've got a 719 lot seller who I'm going
to assume is going to reload there. So
there's the drift down. We didn't quite
quite miss uh get to our first target.
You can see we came back up to this same
level and they tried to sell it twice
against that 300 level which is what we
talked about. Once they lifted through I
covered uh my runner where I was hoping
to get lower. So we got down we got from
300 to 37. So we got we got six 50 60
points here. Once they went through that
a squeeze happened. So 300 became that
same level. So you can see they dipped
down they held 300. So now I know 300's
the key level. They tried again. They
held 300 and then they lifted back up.
So we know 300 is the big overunder.
They came back in again here trying to
sell the 300s. You can see the
importance of uh order flow for me
again. 300s 300s 300s and then they let
it go and then we washed back down to
the 50s which was the same level as
before and then this time we broke.
Right? So it was the same thesis on both
trades and 300 was the key level.
It was very very obvious. In fact it was
so obvious that uh he was on there even
before the open. That guy was just
hanging out there.
Okay.
Do I know Kyle Cox? I do not. Who's Kyle
Cox? Carl Cox, maybe you mean? I don't
know who Kyle Cox is. Carl Cox. I don't
know him personally.
Kyle Cox. It's like a uh a parody name
of it.
Does map show micro or or macro? Do you
mean minis or micros? I only use it for
minis. I'm only interested in uh in what
the big guys are using. Yeah. lot size
is the amount of units correct sorry
Ninja Trader and TV are way off again
into price running well for me it's all
okay so far
did we swipe previous day low yeah we we
swipe previous day low and we swipe
previous week low we took both out these
green lines on the charts were those
levels right green lines on the charts
were the levels so this was previous day
low uh this was an old weekly low and
the only thing really left. If we're
going to go outside of the bowls, it's
25,042
like we just talked about on the
dailies, those big levels.
How do I trade Aussie USD? Um, I don't.
I don't.
There you go. You're using Weeble. There
you go. Great. Perfect.
When you go short like that, requiring
very ex quick execution, do you use a
stop order to get in? And are there some
parts of your execution that's
semi-automated? Uh, I marketed orders in
that one because I was scared I was not
going to get filled, but I have an ATM,
right? So, I know on those market
orders, even if I hot use a hotkey, I
have a max loss automatically goes in
and a cover point automatically goes in.
So, if I mark it ordered here, right, my
max loss is probably up here and my
cover points here. And then I just drag
it to where I want to be. And if I don't
hit it, I just mark it out. I'll close
all. That's one of the advantages of
using Ninja Trader. You still look good.
This short looks good, guys. This short
still looks good. You can see, let's
have a look on here. Have we trapped
buyers? Yes. So, buyers are currently
caught over 240s. All right. You need to
see follow through under this. This is
where these buyers joined in. All right.
So, I'd be covering a little piece into
this. If you break that, we're looking
for 25s and if you break that new low of
day, but the rotation is taking place
here between these buyers and these
buyers here. So far, it looks all right.
The question is, does it need a second
leg higher? But if if you were short in
this little shelf, it's looking okay.
I'd be watching trying to see if you can
get down underneath here. Here you go.
Starting to accelerate now. Remember,
sellers are caught under 25s. All right?
So, you must be reactive into sort of
this node here. Here I'd be covering a
little piece into sort of where you are
now and then looking to see if you can
get to 25s.
If they hold this, they will look for
that second leg. All right? If they hold
this, there's your 50%. Right? So buyers
are trapped here. If they hold this,
they will look for a second leg relief.
So you are short here and you're
covering some here hoping you break 25
for a snap. But there is no guarantee
that it's going to do it. So you must
pay yourself because you are not the
first opportunity for lowhanging fruit.
You are trying to now join a
continuation at a very risky area on a
higher time frame. But you do have this
to protect you.
Map's been really stupid today. It's
very annoying not keeping up with price.
I know mate CC, I'm absolute buzzing. I
was going to almost wear my shirt today,
but I'm sure lots of you are Spurs fans
and it would upset you. or even worse,
Chelsea fans from last night.
Where did I get the indicator I'm
looking at? Which one? This one. This is
my indicator. It's a Flowzone Pro
system. You can get it on my website.
Version of it comes for free when you do
the course. Everything's all the links
down below, guys. All the links are in
down below.
Is Topstep a good start trading on first
timer? Uh, it's not bad. It would
wouldn't be my preference. I would think
you you
my top five don't include them. I would
say Lucid Funded Next, uh, Apex probably
cheapest, but
a little tricky to to manage, but it
will keep you teach you good discipline.
Um, Lucid Funded Next, um, probably the
kindest in terms of, uh, being able to
pass them and hold positions.
PA looks untradable. I mean, I'd say
that was pretty tradable. PA, the price
action was pretty good. Look at map.
Can't keep up. What are we doing? It's
like the auto I clicked something that
auto follows off.
Right.
They're still rejecting the same level.
It's where those buyers were trapped.
Remember, buyers are trapped up here.
You can see they've just got caught
again. This is where those buyers are
trapped into 40. 40 to 62 is where those
buyers are trapped. Right? 40-62.
These guys here.
This is all buy side delta. So, there
has been a passive seller here. Looking
for this move to the 50% pullback. You
should have taken a partial here in case
they want to do a second leg. Second leg
would probably look like this into that
same level.
If we did a measured move, it would
probably be exactly that. Go from the
high to the
high to the low.
There you go. Measured move would have
been 314s.
the map again. Getting stuck.
Uh, sorry guys, I'm trying to catch up
with you.
On your PAS, can you talk about what lot
position size you use? It all depends
which what I'm trading with. If I'm
trading trading something with a
trailing draw down and I'm not past the
buffer, I use um micros two, three,
four, and I start to scale up. If I'm
past the draw down or if I'm trading
something where I'm a set and forget, I
don't mind using minis as long as I'm
being accurate.
If I'm not trading well, I always go
down to micros as well.
Why don't I like Topep? I I hate TopSep
X. I hate their morals. I hate their
their ethics. I hate lots of things
about them. Can you make money from
them? Yeah. Is Top Set X a good
platform? No. It's [\h__\h] awful. It's a
joke.
Right. Still rejecting. Look, the 40s up
here are still rejecting. The buyers are
still cooked up here. You can see again
they just got cooked again up there.
They're still rejecting. So, you're
still good to hold this short right now.
So, you should have taken one TP. You
are just waiting to see now if you can
get into this area down here. So, 75s
underneath 75s. You have a little
imbalance down here into into the 50s,
but the sellers uh are stuck at 25. So,
as long as you've paid yourself
somewhere into here, then you can sit
and hold to see if it's willing to go.
They just are bouncing between these
two. Maybe they let these buyers out.
Now, this aggressive bid from 95. Jesus
Christ. Someone's just been Someone's
getting very upset that he's obviously
out of position and he needs to push it.
There you go. He's just cleared everyone
out. Gross.
That is gross. ES finding a bid there as
well. Back to its New York open on ES.
So, relative strength there again. So ES
positive on the day by the way ENQ is
flat flat 75% down. So that could be a
clear out of the high for the second
leg. Remember the measured move would be
into 14 somewhere up here. That' be the
measured move. But you are now inside
this means you're starting to see a
failed breakdown. I really wouldn't be
surprised to see them [\h__\h] around with
this all day and build liquidity all day
now. Now that we've had the low hanging
fruit, I will not be touching the long
here. There's just no way
why Topep is dist distrusted. Um well
okay here's why they used to use uh data
from or like platforms other platforms
used to be able to use other platforms.
Then what happened is Michael Pek got
very greedy and decided he was going to
create his own platform. Okay. and he
made that platform cheaper for you to
trade on than the other platforms. So,
everyone migrated over to this new
platform. Is that new platform good? No.
Can you use third party apps? No. Is
VWAP accurate? No. Are EMAs accurate?
No. Is any of it ever good? No. Have
they ever fixed any of it? No. Okay. So,
then what happened? Then they got rid of
all the other platforms. So, you could
only trade on his platform which he
would make money from no matter what.
Okay. And then what happened then? That
platform? Well, it kept [\h__\h] up and
going down. So then all these traders
who had migrated over, been forced to
move to that platform. I was not one of
them because I refused to play [\h__\h]
games. Then would get stuck in trades.
Then they would lose their money. They
would lose accounts. They would be up
big and not given that money. So what
did they do? Oh, you can have a free
account. That is not okay. That is not
good justification. Did this happen
once? No. Twice? No. This happened
numerous times. In fact, it happened one
week where it pretty much happened every
single day in a row. What's their
ambition now? Their ambition now is to
open up a brokerage house where you will
trade on their platform on a brokerage
house and they will try and get a
monopoly. Do you want to see that
happen? Do you? [\h__\h] That is the most
greedy [\h__\h] I've ever heard from. And on
top of that, the coaching and trading
education full of arrogance from people
on their page is a joke. It is woeful.
It is absolutely terrible. Their ethics
are awful. They want to talk [\h__\h] about
other people when they are an absolute
joke. And on top of that as well, not
that I was one of them, but I know lots
of people who were affiliates for them
who really helped grow their business
from early on and then they just
completely cut them loose with like no
phone call, no explanation, just
completely [\h__\h] them over. So, in
terms of morals and ethics, there's the
drive up towards the 14s that we talked
about. same gray box in terms of morals
and ethics. Well, I'm a big moral and
ethics guy. And do they have any? They
do not. All right. So, there's the
measured move, folks. So, that's the
second leg. All right. So, they held
this 50%. There's the measured move.
This is your now edge here. All right.
And we might very well rotate in here
for a long time in this session. Very
very well. Can can do that.
uh funded next over lucid. They're both
very very good. I like both of those a
lot.
How delta offset works.
Uh yes. Well, del delta is difference
between the buyers and sellers. When we
have big delta,
when we're measuring delta, we're
measuring aggressive participants. That
means that they're market orders, right?
They're aggressive. They're market
orders. So, if we have lots of market
orders who are sellers, see all this red
down here, this big delta down here at
the bottom. If these are all market
orders and price is not moving lower and
we're moving higher, what does that
mean? That means in here there's a
passive order. A passive order would be
a limit buyer, which means someone is
absorbing these market orders and
everyone's selling into them. And this
limit buyer is going, "Yes, I'm going to
have all of that like a sponge, right?"
Okay. And as price fails to move lower
and it starts to move higher, what do
they do? They start to stop out. All
right. And so we get this drive up.
Right. Same as here. We got caught here
for a while with these market buyers.
Got caught at the highs. We've now
cleared them out. More market buyers
have been caught at the highs. So we
will probably trade between these points
for a little bit, right? While they make
their mind up of what they're doing,
right? And you can see that even on a
lower time frame, you'd be able to see
exactly the same things. Come right down
a lower time frame. You can see this
bottom candle is all sellers. All right,
this is all sell side, isn't it? Down
here, right? Those are all aggressive
sellers being absorbed. That means
there's someone huge absorbing 481 lots,
right? To move back up, right? Some some
limit buyer just sat there like a sponge
absorbing it. And then you get the
shift. We go back to buy side. Why?
Because these guys start stopping out.
All right, that's why. Remember, auction
can't take place unless there's buyers
and sellers. And you need both
aggressive buyers and aggressive sellers
for an auction to take place. Like I
talked about yesterday, if you just had
limit orders, if you just have passive
sellers, they will never meet each
other, will they? Because if you're
willing, I always give that same
example. If you own a Rolex Daytona and
you currently want to sell it for
$60,000
and I want to buy a Rolex Daytona for
$30,000, then we have a $30,000 spread.
And until we agree price, no auction is
uh is done. No handshake is made.
I purchased, sorry, I can't even talk. I
purchased your course and I can honestly
say it's the most comprehensive course
I've paid for. Unfortunately, I paid for
some that are not worth it. Yours is
fantastic. That's great to hear. Thank
you very much for the kind words. I
dislike Topep more than Apex. I actually
do. Yeah, everyone's got a issue with a
What makes me laugh. Everyone has this
issue with Apex, right? But it's pretty
clear. Stick to the rules. There,
there's the rules. Stick to the rules.
You get 20 accounts, it's cheap. You
stick to the rules, you get paid. All
this [\h__\h] about you don't get paid
and blah blah. No, you get paid. Stick
to the rules, you get paid. Right? Don't
stick to the rules, you don't get paid.
But all that happens is you roll over
for the next eight days.
Everyone's like, "Oh, I can't deal with
the trailing draw down." It's really not
that hard. It is not that hard to deal
with. Like if you're oversizing, you
won't deal with it. If you're not
disciplined and you don't stop out, you
won't deal with it. If you're not taking
the correct setups, you won't deal with
it. Means you shouldn't be trading
anyway. It should teach you some
discipline to get past it. It's the same
if you get TPT pass the account and then
you never get paid. It's because you
don't know how to manage your positions.
You're probably oversizing.
Gold doing the move. Is it Is it doing
what we talked about this morning and
the last few days? probably it's
probably had that push to sell into.
There you go. We talked about this,
didn't we? If it has failed failure to
follow through.
Beautiful.
Beautiful failure to follow through. If
we uh
do this even from here. Yeah, look at
that node we talked about. Look how thin
we are about. This is everything we
talked about premarket. So, there's
probably a good a good continuation
short here, right? So, if you were short
into this block here, I'd be targeting
here for a TP1, TP2, and if they wanted
to let go, we can think about coming
underneath. Really nice. Very simple.
Don't over complicate it, folks. When
everyone stops talking about gold, like
I will start positioning short side soon
because everyone's going to like stop
talking about it. And this this to me
looks like a small cap. And when
everyone stops talking about it and we
start doing like this and everyone's
talking about tech again and blah blah
blah blah blah and we get something
maybe something like this,
right? And that would take years and we
can just sit in that trade. All right,
if we hold this and do this then higher
macro wise at the moment it points to
higher prices but we'll see if dollar
starts going then that all goes off the
table and we get a fantastic sell.
Okay, back down into the same block.
Right, so clear out of the 340s up
towards the 300, the measured move back
into the same area of liquidity. And
again, we have trapped sellers down here
still. All right, but we're into the
edge of this range, 190. You start
letting go of that, there'll be a
rotation further lower.
Rain says, "I've had an issue weekly. A
lockout after winds for the day and it
just disappears. Happened yesterday with
tops." Yeah, does not surprise me. I've
lost five XFAS during the ex December
outage. Was out of their window time by
2 minutes. It was cringe not going for
top step again. There you go.
Yeah, totally. I'm sorry. I'm just
catching up with everything.
Yes, it is. Project X is owned by
Michael Pekka. top step.
Like I said, you can still get payouts
from them. Like if you like their
platform and you all that matters is
that you guys get payouts, right? If you
like their platform, you can still get
payouts from them. Um don't don't like
don't listen to me, but just
spread your bets, right? Have some firms
not with them is what I would say.
Not much difference between top and
lucid. No, I agree. I think Lucid is a
better package now um than Top Step. But
look, it's each to their own
Padilla. Um they're good for swings.
Here you go. So coming back down to this
level. All right. So this is everything
we just drew out into here. This little
imbalance, right? So here's the
rotation. So TP1 and then you have to
respect this 26s, right? So we've got an
imbalance down in towards these 55s and
then we have to respect sort of 26 and
below. If you get that fade underneath
so all they did was clear out the stops,
do the second leg, right? One, two, do
the second leg, break down under here.
If they break down under this now, we
will see a bigger puke. But we must
respect 50s and 26s.
So anyone who took that short, it was
good. Just a clear out. And then they
reshorted the same level. So they ran
the stops, right? Made market buyers,
stopped everyone out, paired it off, and
then failed that same level. And we're
coming down to the 50s. The imbalance of
the 50s. And remember, the sellers are
stuck at 26s and under 26s. We have
room. We have room.
Is there an indicator for I think you're
saying for think or swim platform that
will highlight zones where buyers and
sellers are stuck. Not unless it has
footprint or something like that.
How much is the course? Depends on which
course, but I think it should be $699.
Now, they better have updated it. He
promised me he was going to update it.
yesterday. If not, you're going to get
lucky and you'll get $50 off. Have a
look. Should be $699.
It's still not updated. Oh my god. Air,
if you're watching, you're going to get
a bollocking.
Been waiting since January.
All right, here you come. So 50 is now
tagged. So now you'd be watching the
25s. Remember 25s is where the seller
got stuck right here. Sort of 26 and
below. This is the imbalance. Imbalance
now been filled. these green lines.
There you go. So, next level is 25s and
if you get under 25s, new low day. Here
it comes. So, anyone in this really nice
if you took it took it would have taken
two attempts. You would have had one
attempt uh
from here to here and then the
breakdown. Same level and you might get
continuation now. So, back in towards
these 25s and then break down under
there. We can look for 25,000. You can
look for 25,000 folks. Really good. Here
we go.
Really nice.
There's a bid here at 130, 110, and 100.
Any tricks on Apex draw down? You can be
in the money but still negative draw
down. Trail out stops ATR. Yeah, you
should like trail and size down. Got to
size down. If you size down, the draw
down won't matter too much.
There you go. Let's see if they can get
it under these underneath these trap
participants for you.
Number 25s and under is where they're
stuck.
My ninja's just gone funny. I've just
got a
candle out of nowhere.
So, I'm Let me restart this. That
doesn't exist.
Let's try that again.
Right into these 25s. Remember, this is
where the sell is stuck. Continuation
under here. You'll get a new low of day
and you'll be looking for 25,000.
Uh let me just check. You'll be looking
for 25,000 20 and then 25,000.
So, right into where they where they're
stuck, right? 25 25 and under. There's
the push. So, you can see they're still
stuck there. This is what we talked
about these trapped traders. See that?
That's where they're trapped. So, no
acceptance underneath, which is why it's
saying you have to take some money off
into that. They remain stuck. So, they
covered the first opportunity that they
had to get out break even. They just
took, right? Hopefully that makes sense
to you all. Look at that. It seems like
that candle that was printed happened
afterwards.
Mental
Trump news. Really? What? right at that
time when they when they got down there.
That'd be hilarious. It's probably him
stuck, him and his cronies.
I've just completed an excellent
telephone call with President Xi of
China. It was long and and thorough call
where many important subjects were
discussed including trade military the
April trip and I'll be making
uh ch I will be trip that will be making
to China which I very much look forward
to Taiwan the war between Russia Ukraine
the situation between Iran the purchase
of oil and gas and China and the United
States the consideration of China of the
purchase of add additional agricultural
pro products including lifting the
source soybean count to 20 million tons
of the current season. They have
committed 25 million tons for the next
season. Airplane engines, deliveries,
and numerous other subjects. All very
positive. The relationship with China,
my personal relationship with Xi is an
extremely good one, and we'll both
realize how important it is to keep it
that way. I believe that there will be
many positive results achieved over the
next three years of my presidency having
to do with President Xi and the People's
Republic of China. Sounds like a load of
[\h__\h] waffle to me. But uh Okay,
we react to that, do we? An orange man
saying, "I've got I've had a good
telephone call."
No, that's just trap traders down there.
I had a great conversation with
President Xi and you know now it's
really good but next week I'm going to
tell you I'm the best. He [\h__\h] up.
We're going to war. I mean he literally
what a load of bollocks. Who [\h__\h]
cares what he tweets honestly.
Who's this guy knower at the at the
Oscars? What a joke.
Almost as bad as Jimmy Kimmel. I mean, I
can't believe the [\h__\h] that this guy
comes out with. It's amazing.
You Golden Globes in the Oscars. What a
joke. I should win. They should give me
an Oscar.
Jesus Christ. What a world we live in,
guys. What a world we live in.
It's crazy, man. Not just that. Just all
of it. The Epstein stuff. Not even with
him. Like watching all these UK
politicians have to resign.
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] from the Labour Party.
They're all They're all a joke.
Cali Liberals. Not even, man. Like
I think um
Newsome's an absolute prick.
It's It's not even one side or the
other. We're just The world's full of
cretins. It doesn't matter whether you
wear wear red or blue. It's just most of
them are [\h__\h] [\h__\h] They're just
complete [\h__\h]
Well, that's my whole thing, Z. That's
what I was just saying about Peter
Mandelson. That's the whole thing. Like,
suck it.
Oh, look at that pump. All right, so
we've now got more stops down here. Let
me just have a look on that last move.
See who came in there.
The big aggressive bid. All right, so
this is how I'm seeing this. These
sellers are stuck.
We came into this level where they got
stuck. A little bit more excess here.
Buyers came back in here. So buyers are
trying to protect this low. Now, that's
very obvious, right? We can see it right
here. Buyers are trying to protect that
low. We come back to the highs. Where
are the buyers stuck? Well, where we
just traded all the way up to? Buyers
got caught up here
on the excess of that clear out push.
And they also got put caught
at 40s, wasn't it? Was it 40s earlier
today? Confusing. I have to go lower
time frame there. Give me a second.
Yes, buyers just got caught here. And
this is now the rotation. This is the
same level where we failed at from
before. So, we're now going to rotate
and build out liquidity between here. If
they take control of this, there's a
potential squeeze. If we start snapping
under here, there might be continuation.
Like, as you can see, you've probably
noticed I'm done. Uh because I think the
trade setups now require a lot more
liquidity to be built out. You can see
we've just gone sideways basically since
those nice moves. There was a good short
like I would say this was a decent short
to here and then knock out the runner
break even and then that exact same
short after they cleared out into that
same level.
Nice short down to here into where those
trapped players are. Probably knocked
out break even on that. And now it's
just waiting. It is just a waiting game.
This will need to be built out one way
or another. Even if they're going to use
it for either direction, they'll need to
be built out. I will not be playing the
edges in this. It's not what I'm looking
to do personally. Personally, but you
guys do what you want. And you know,
there's how many of you hit? 1,200. Uh
that means 600 of you have not hit the
like button. We will do some giveaways.
I'm happy to talk about anything. Um I'm
not going to hammer a load of politics,
guys. I I I don't care who you vote for.
You It is your right. And it's also your
right not to vote. You can do whatever
you want. It really doesn't bother me.
It makes no difference. I'm not having a
go at one person or another. All I'm
saying is, you know,
how many times have we heard a
conversation like that from Trump? I got
a great a great relationship, you know,
and at the weekend when the markets are
closed, you be like, "That's it. 500%
tariff
on China. China, you know, so, you know,
I don't believe a word any of these lots
say. It's not because of red or blue.
It's cuz I It's cuz I trade and I just
don't [\h__\h] believe any of them,
right? So that's all it is. You can vote
for whoever you want. Uh you can be
whatever religion you want. I will not
judge you. That is your rights. It's
absolutely your your right. Okay. Back
down towards these trap players. Bias
technically is still lower. It's just
whether they can break underneath these.
All right. So this same level,
this same level that we've talked about
where we have these guys trapped. So we
need continuation. We'll need to like
make these guys be back in the money. We
will not want to protect this. So if you
are in this short again I wouldn't blame
you. You need to see this expansion. Be
very careful of this kind of move of
taking it out and reclaiming just like
we did the top side right because we are
in range but point control is moving
down. We are starting to reject it. The
uh lows basically or 21s is the end of
the current weekly profile on the
auction. So we look at this the current
weekly developing
right we are starting to reject our
current day point of control. We have
not been able to get back up to the
previous or the weekly point of control.
Big old B shape here, I would say, with
some distribution left at the top. If we
move under this expansion down to here,
but we want to be careful. Look how thin
we are here. We want to be very careful
trading at these lows. Very, very
careful. Wouldn't be adding a short
position near the lows. I'd be like
short up here, covering the lows, hoping
we break lower. Not hope likeium, just
positioned for it. Right. Positioned for
it. A little bit different.
Any thoughts on BTC? Um, yeah. I mean,
I've gone over this the last few days,
but I will go over it again.
Right. Looking for the undercut and see
if we do continuation. Right. There's
the undercut. I would not be positioned
in much right now. Like I talked about,
I think if this is a big big if, but if
we're going to go risk off, right, you
got to understand how BTC works.
We go from this low,
this would be over a thousand days to
the high, right?
Over 1,000 days to the high. So 1,066
days and we did a move of 706%.
All right, I will show you why I'm
showing you this.
You could argue that this was the low
here, but we'll see.
over a thousand days. 1,100 and that was
a 2,000% rise. All right, this will be
the same every single time. I can keep
showing you it's going to be over the
bull markets are over a,000 days just
based on the cycles and the pivot low to
here, right? 170 days. So, 170 days,
1,100 days, 1,066
days. All right, all of them with very,
very big gains. Right, let's look at
what the downside looks like once we put
that in. Right, so here if we're going
to do the draw down from this
84%
right and it lasts 300 days. If we do
this draw down from here,
78% and it lasts 300 days. All right, so
guess what I would consider here as
possible.
Right. We're going to look at 70 to 80%
and up to 300 days.
So
somewhere like this is possible. Is that
enough days? Somewhere like
this is possible. Now that's not to say
it has to happen but based on the cycles
right if I just zoom this out right
based on the cycles that is what we get
right from the from the beginning of
time of BTC we get a th00and day bull
market run with huge gains and we get a
70 to 80% pullback we get a th00and day
bull run 70 to 80% pullback we get a
th00andday bull run so 70 to 80%
pullback where would that leave you into
I know it's going to be break some
hearts here and this doesn't have to
happen, but it would lead you into
around the 25 to 30,000 mark. All right,
which is into this gate here. All right,
so
could it be that this just undercuts and
reclaims? Yes. Could it just come down
to here and find a bid here because we
know it's a big section? Absolutely, it
could. All right, I'm not saying it
can't. Maybe this year is different and
they do this and you know, that's that's
what we look at. But I would just be
aware right now all that we're seeing is
a snap of liquidity. All right, we're
breaking lows. There's a nice quasi and
even if we looked for a measured move
from this, let's see how far this would
get us from like leg one. And if we look
to leg two, right, then we're going to
at least look for 60,000. So I want to
be very careful. I'm considering it. If
we w if we wick it and we reclaim, I'd
consider it. But I actually think, you
know, based on the cycles, we want to be
thinking about a move much, much lower,
right? So, I just want to be careful of
that. And this probably needs repairing.
Look how thin this is on a squeeze. I
don't think it's ever been repaired,
right? Very thin this move up here. So,
maybe somewhere into here. So, that
would be my thoughts on BTC, right? But
obviously, if I'm going to trade BTC, um
I'm looking for huge swing uh positions,
as in not necessarily hu huge positions,
but long-term swing positions.
XRP, it'll be the same thing. You just
need to I mean XRP is like getting
absolutely clobbered. It's currently
trading at what 1.5.
It's given back like 50% of its gains.
It's going to be the same. It's going to
be the same kind of story, guys. You're
you're going to need until uh until we
catch a bid.
Uh
until we catch a bid on the uh whole
market.
All right. Look how thin we are. Think
about what we talk about all the time.
Look how thin we are from this breakout,
right? We're probably going to repric a
decent chunk of that.
It's interesting.
I don't think there'll be enough data
here to do this, but I will give it a
go.
No, not enough data. Right. What about
Can you let me draw one on
Yeah, that is what would worry me.
Very thin. Very, very, very, very thin.
If you're very lucky, you're going to
find a bid here.
Um, but you can see we've lost this
shelf. All right. So, buyers, all buyers
are now caught
over 180 and certainly over twos.
All right. So, we've got buyers stuck.
And until we reclaim that, look how thin
we are. Where's the next level where it
gets thick? I hate to [\h__\h] say it. I
hope it doesn't come down there for you
lot, but you know, maybe maybe it finds
a bid here at like a 50% retracement of
this gap, but this is very very thin.
Very very thin.
All markets move the same way. So, we'll
just have to see. Hopefully, they do
some horrible trap for you. Hopefully,
you see something like this. But, you
know, if BTC does a 70 80% pullback,
then you best believe that's probably
going to get filled in.
Okay. How we doing for likes? I would
like to do some giveaways.
Let's get these likes up.
Gold and silver sh have gone over gold
and silver a few times, buddy. I've g
gone over them a few times. Just just
rewind the show.
Um, gold and silver are doing the fa
failure to follow through kind of move.
All right, so golden from a swing
position. I'll just do it very quickly
from a swing point of view,
right? You'd be looking for the short
for the failure to follow through, which
is what you're starting to see today.
It's no different to a small cap. You go
from the high to the low, we come into
that golden kind of pocket. All right.
We talked about the volume.
All right. Tapped back into this.
Right. So, this is where buyers last
came in with size. as we tap back in.
They just got out break even. You're now
likely to see a rotation back down. I
mean, if it can't hold a bid over 930,
then we're probably going to come back
into 95 uh 930. Is that right? 930, then
we're going to come back into 650s. All
right. So, if it can't, this is your
failure to follow through. A revisit
down here is likely. There's probably a
short down into here, unless they go for
a second leg and then do the same thing.
All right. And then you have to see if
they collapse it and sweep all of this
out. If they reclaim this, all right, if
this, this, this, and this happens, then
new highs are possible, right? But right
now, that is a clear failure to follow
through. And I will be looking for a
long-term position. Uh, after after I
get off stream and start figuring out
what the market's trying to do,
get some limit orders out in some areas
of interest for me.
Um,
sorry guys, I'm trying to read all the
chat. Does the market work the same way
for ENQ a thousand days and pullback?
No, it's just it's just for BTC. That's
the BTC market. Uh, it would be it would
be it would all be to do with the
halfing cycles, I would imagine. I'm not
a big crypto guy, but I would imagine
that's why.
What is the blue and gray volume
indicator you're using? This is anchored
volume profile.
How do I qu How do you qualify for the
giveaways? I announce it on stream and
then we type a word in and it pulls it
at random. Any thoughts on day trade on
trade day? Yeah, trade day are pretty
good. If you want same day payouts, they
take a bit long to pass, but they're
pretty good.
Nvidia. Um,
have a quick look. So, if you're still
in the short, you look good. You just
need acceptance. Remember, underneath
the sort of 25s, and this is looking
more and more like that sort of
basketball sort of short failure.
Cleared out the stops. Failure. Little
pump off a stupid tweet. Failure. And
under here, here is your TP. So, I'd pay
yourself some into here if you haven't
already. And then you're looking for
25,000.
You're looking for 25,000.
Where do I draw my profile from from the
930 open, my friend? 9:30 open.
How can you learn from me? Well, you
turn up each day. You can do all the
free videos on my YouTube and you can do
the courses if you want to do the 20our
course or the volume profile course.
Links are down below or just head over
to flzone trader.com.
Come on. But Matt, what is up with you
today? Starting to really piss me off.
Not recentering properly. All right, big
sellers coming in here looking for that
wash. Remember 25 is where they kept
getting stuck before.
still not getting that wash underneath
my five minute chart. There we go.
Still protecting some of these nodes
down here. Gray box
AI is telling me 25,040. We'll see.
Testing it. Um I mean we just did. We've
seen it already. Have I heard of deep
charts? I have. I've not used them so I
can't comment but they look pretty good.
My YouTube channel deserves a thousandk
subs in here. So much value each day
from market open. Alex is insane. Oh,
thank you. Newbie spy. Is there another
market cycle strategy for ENQ? Um, I've
never really measured out on NQ, but I
would say, you know, we can just follow
the diff. Okay, let me tell you
something. The big difference between NQ
or or indexes and the rest of the
market, right? The indexes are built to
go higher. Okay, the indexes are built
to go higher. Why? Right? If any of you
follow football in or especially in
Europe, all right, we have what we would
have relegations, right? Relegations and
um promotions. Okay, so we have all
these different divisions of soccer
teams. Hate that I'm calling it soccer,
but just for you your Americans, all
these different divisions of soccer
teams. And if you are a top uh team from
let's say division two, all right, you
get promoted into division one. And if
you are a lower team for if you're a bad
performing team in division one, you get
taken out and put into division two.
Right? So why am I telling you that?
Because the indexes work the same way.
We call it rebalancing. Okay? We call it
rebalancing, which means if there is a
badly performing stock in the QQQ, which
is the NQ, guess what they do? They boot
those stocks the [\h__\h] out of there. And
what do they do? They replace it with
wellperforming stocks with stocks which
are doing really really well which means
if we think about the QQQ it's a 100
stocks we boot five weak ones out we put
five strong ones in what's it going to
do it can only grow all right they are
fixing it so there is good growth for it
when you are looking at individual names
you don't have that you do not have the
luxury of it being a bundle which is
positioned to go higher long term term.
Okay. So, understanding the difference
of that is really, really key. Right
back towards these 25s. Remember, under
here, there is a chance that they might
come in sweep mode still. But that keeps
getting stuck. I'm very tempted to re
reopen this.
So, here you go. 25s again. 25s again.
25s again. And you might get follow
through if they can get under here for a
new low of day. But this is key now. And
potentially you're looking for 25,000.
So, if you're in this short from up
here, you better be paying yourself a
little bit and then look to see if you
can break low of day and get down. I
mean, I do have a block here 25,090 down
to 25,030 and then 25,000.
Yes, holding up very well like we talked
about broadening market. I think you
might get a lower day sweep here at the
very minimum, but we will see. Very,
very close there or you may miss it by a
couple ticks. We go over to here in
these same levels. These guys, remember
these are the guys that are stuck. So
they keep covering. The moment they stop
covering, you will get this lower day
break. Here it comes, folks. There's
your lower day break. Congratulations.
Pay yourself now and then look to see if
you can get into 25,090.
Oh, just happened there. Let's get that
back, please, for the team. All right,
so you're looking for 90 and then all
the way down into 25,000. Here we go,
team. Big snap. So we've just built out
all the liquidity and now we're going to
use it to drive lower. Right, we're
going to use this to drive lower now.
So, into 90. I would say this is a bit
of a cover point just based on some key
levels. Let me just check this level on
the daily. Uh, next liquidity 25,30.
Going to mark this out for you. 25,030
is what you're looking for.
This right here. All right. If you can
get into that, that's your next TP
point. Do not let it reclaim. Now, if
you were short from any of these up
here, do not let it reclaim 135s. Okay,
here we go. It's getting very, very
weak.
And as long as you stay heavy versus
this gray box now, then we should have a
continuation lower. As long as they
don't let them out.
Come on, bookmap. You're making my life
really hard.
uh fixed volume. It's anchored volume
right here. It's anchored volume. Two
ticks per row and I have a width of 20.
Okay. So, they're still selling into
this. We're building out a bit of a
volume node down here into in towards
these 90s, these 86s. There is an
imbalance here to 91, then another to
13, and then another to 19. Remember,
very thin down. So, we would expect some
kind of retracement up and then see if
they resell it. If they don't resell it,
it will be a failed auction, but I think
they will want to resell this. I don't
think they're done with it yet. ES
coming down to its IB low as well. So,
you can watch that. If ES starts getting
weak, the broader market will get weak
with tech. That will help you, but we're
building out a little node down here. We
might very well want to come up to these
180s, but you can stay short as long as
you were short obviously above all of
this versus this sort of 130. You won't
want to reclaim. Ideally, they reject uh
somewhere in here and come down into
this is what you'd be looking for. Here
we go.
Can we get under this?
Just want to check I'm not missing
anything on an hourly basis. An old
hourly wick. Yeah, we're coming into
these. Looks good. Trading into that uh
Jan 21st. That's where we're trading
into right now. Looks really good. So,
can they get under all of this and get
into those 30s for you guys? Looks good.
Looks good.
Right, while you guys wait on that, I'm
going to get a little coffee here if
that's all right. I'll be right back.
How we doing for time? I want to do a
giveaway as soon as we get get back.
Right. So, just be uh
be mindful of that. Smash the like
button. Uh look at the VIX. Look at the
VIX. Right back up into these 19s. So,
VIX will be looking for a 1962 break. If
we get that break on the VIX, we're
going to go back to previous day high.
This looks really good. So, make sure
you're getting ready to cover some into
this green line. If we get to that green
line, you very well might get a really
nasty stop hunt. So, you can put some
wish orders out down here because if we
break that, you might get a stop hunt.
So, you cover some into this, but you
might want some wish orders down here
for this. All right, I'll be right back.
This is the kind of black swan day we've
talked about.
All right. Sorry folks. I had to make a
fresh brew.
Okay. You're still building out down
here. Nice rejection of the IB low.
There you go. That was what you should
have been looking for. So anywhere from
IB low up to value. Remember rejection
of that and you're looking for this. And
hopefully this breaks now this shelf for
you and you can get that move. Really
good. Fantastic. Hopefully some of you
took that if you weren't already in.
Right, there's your IBL. Really good.
And this is your TP now down into this.
And move your stop down. Make sure
you're protecting some profits here.
Fantastic.
Fantastic. Here you go, folks. You're
going to get it. So 30s and then uh
after 30s, what can we think about? I'm
going to have to keep going back a long
way. After 30s, we can try and look for
24,900.
Right. So, we're going to respect
25,000. We're now going back to the 17th
of December. Right. Here we go. Starting
to see acceleration here. So, happy for
you guys. Really good.
Yeah. Have your wish orders. Have your
wish orders out. Oh, wish orders. What
are they? Wish orders are like hoping
price gets somewhere. So, like if we
snap this, you might see a stop run of a
really nasty candle. So, you can cover
some towards this, but you can have some
limit orders down here, hoping that it
fills them all in one quick go. Right?
Or that's that's what I do. That's what
what I have. So, I have my main TP, but
when we're about to break a big pivotal
level, I might have some limits set
further down just in case we do a big
swipe and then a reclaim.
Oh, Nvidia. Yeah, no worries, mate. So,
let's just manage this. Get down into
here if possible and then I'll have a
look at it. Remind me again if I don't
if I don't do it. Where can you reach
out to me on email?
info@flowzonetrader.com.
Nice work, everyone.
Sometimes I use the Dixie, but um at the
moment, you know, not not needing to use
it too much. I think this
they're going to push the Dixie a little
bit, which might help market rotate, but
it's more about the Dixie and gold
relationship right now, I'd say.
Right. When we let's get to these
targets, guys. I'll tell you what, let's
make a deal. Let's get to these targets.
Once we get off these targets, I will
happily look at Invidia, Palanteer, and
what some someone said something else.
Was it PayPal? We can look at all of
those together.
Happy to look at them together.
So, a little bit of front running here.
Just know ES just bounced off its IBL.
All right. So, watching them as a pair.
ES has just found a bid on its IBL right
now, right in front of it. Right? So,
you need ES to stay weak and wash down
into some of these levels. Remember,
we're all the way under this. All right?
So, we are already on ENQ. We're way
down under this. Remember, these were
the low hanging fruits for us. So, we
shorted the weaker asset. We took this
out. We've just rejected. We're down
here now. Very, very different charts.
Why? Because the broadening market is
still holding up some broadening market.
some of the other sectors.
You do not want a reclaim of this up
here. You do not want to see that
reclaim.
Making this very tricky by saving that
by that much. Very silly of them. Very
silly of them. Bit like this morning
they did the same bollocks.
Why is your initial balance low much
higher than mine? I I don't know. Well,
it shouldn't be. low of day was IBL was
putting at 10:00 a.m. and the high was
the open and we had didn't trade under
or over that before 10:30.
So the initial balance is your first
hour of trading. So it's a reclaim here.
So I'd be out of this now and then you'd
have to watch if they're going to reject
150 here. They want to you've got to see
this reject this kind of level it's in
now. If you don't see that the way
they're washing this around is is pretty
gross. Look at this 100 point ripper
almost straight back upside.
Pretty disgusting.
That's ES off the IBL doing that move.
Is Trump still speaking? Um,
I don't think so. It was just a tweet
that he did. It's just a tweet.
There you go. Back into the red box.
Still still okay here. If they reclaim
IB and hold though, I'd be completely
done with it for the day. You wouldn't
want to see that. All right, let's go
over these charts quickly that you
wanted and then we're going to do the
giveaway. So, Nvidia, some of you
interested Nvidia selling off that AMD
news, I'd imagine.
Starting to look a little bit dangerous
here, folks. I'm not going to lie to
you. This is a quasi
failing to make a new high. That's not
good. Uh lots of liquidity and stops
will be under here.
Yeah, you can see where it gets thin. If
you start losing these 170s, all right,
if you start seeing this move here,
uh we are coming straight down to this,
right? The only other option is that
they come under trap, reclaim and go
again. This looks not good. This is not
bullish. All right, this quasi point of
control failing to hold above point of
control, starting to lose it very thin
under here. The moment you start to lose
that, it is good night sweetheart. All
right. And that will be the start of the
move with everything else. So, it's not
looking too good for Nvidia right now.
Um, someone asked about Palunteer.
Same kind of story, folks. We're seeing
we're going to see this story across the
indexes. All right. Way too frothy. Way
way way too frothy. That is ridiculous.
All right. That is absolutely
ridiculous. So I know like macro point
of view did all the government news uh
giving it new contracts but uh even for
a mean reversion and we're likely to see
something.
I mean I can't even measure it out. I'm
going to have to do it another way.
Same kind of story.
I'll be watching into this pivot right
here. 23s.
23s. If we lose 23s, you know where
we're going.
Maybe a little undercut there would be
good.
You could set price alerts. Really
depends what the tone of the market is
for the next for the rest of the year.
But something like this, right?
Potential buy then. But look, failed to
make a new high. Broke down underneath.
Breaking down under this swing. Starting
to go bearish into some key levels.
If we let go of that deeper pullback,
very possible.
What was the other one? PayPal. I wonder
if someone wanted PayPal. I was tried to
be long PayPal earlier this year and cut
it. I was up a few times. Oh, that's
getting crushed.
Bad earnings. Was it missed? Missed on
earnings. Uh, that is not a good look.
That is a big miss.
Yeah, they're getting wrecked. Let's go
to a weekly. Oh my gosh. Probably into
an interesting area though if I'm
honest.
Uh, I would imagine you're going to see
some accumulation happen start to happen
down here now.
Not a bad area.
Not a bad area to start buying in. Uh
doesn't mean it can't break lower. Like
if they really want to start breaking
these 30s, you know, don't think we
can't come under all that. But I would
imagine that's a pretty good area to
start uh looking at for the next few
days or the next few weeks. Uh at the
very least, you're going to see a retest
of this, right? even if they resell that
down. Um, under here is obviously a
nogo. But this is a interesting area for
accumulation. That was the CO pump and
then the postco collapse
and then they failed to reclaim this
level. So you've got lots of trap buyers
in here. But I would imagine there is
some relief from here to here at some
point. At some point we will see a
relief bounce or a back test. Remember
how the market moves. If we just
consider this a wave, right?
Right. We will come and at least back
test this. So there is a trade from here
to here at the very least going to
happen.
Yeah, that's uh that PayPal's
interesting for uh to scoop up to be
honest. Right. How are we doing in the
market? Where are we?
Okay, back down towards the low. Nice
rejection of red box. Nice rejection of
value. [\h__\h] had to like squeeze
that a little bit more than they should
have. Still looking for You're still
looking for 30s. If you added back on
there, you're still looking for 30s. And
under that new lows.
Have a look at the profile here. How we
developing? Bit of a shelf here at sort
of 70s. We should break We should break
lower. We should break lower. It's just
whether they want to play more games. If
ES breaks IB, that will uh really really
really help.
really help. Okay, let's uh
here you go. I think you're going to get
it folks. They are very very close to
giving this move for you guys. Liquidity
here at 5 uh where is he? 70 550 is 150
lot at 550. Once we trade through him,
we should get that 30 move. Here we go.
Here's the 50s. Come on. Get out of
[\h__\h] way. Just let it snap. You're
not going to hold this up, you absolute
[\h__\h] Get out of [\h__\h] way.
Lots of sellers down here. Let's see if
we can get 30s.
You don't want this back above 50s. Here
we go. 40s. You're going to get the 30s
here, folks. It's almost there. And get
your wish orders out. Do not let this
reclaim. Get your wish orders out. You
want a snap of 30s. So, you should be
taking some profit in front of this.
like we talked about. Take some profit
in front of this and have your wish
orders out here because if they run this
stop and you get a really nice wash, it
would be amazing. And you would want to
protect this gray box. Now, I'm going to
draw it in for you. You'd want to
protect this now. You should get it,
folks. You should get it.
The short was
40s.
We would have had to have a couple goes
at this.
And then the
IB short. Not too bad either.
This is your last target. Or here. And
then here.
Okay, big seller came in there at 50. He
got absorbed. The other big seller above
was at 77. So 52. There is a little
imbalance to 80 is is the level if they
want to save.
Let me
get this ready. How we doing for time?
How are we doing for likes? How are we
doing for people on the stream?
Pretty good. Not too bad, guys. Not too
bad. I think lots of people made their
money early again today.
Okay, I should say it's also last um day
of the Apex sale. So 90% off today is
the last day for that sale. You're
rejecting gray box here. That's your
overunder for continuation. Um
hopefully
you can get the final targets down here.
So far you're rejecting gray box, which
is what we just said. You want to see it
reject that. This is your TP right into
here. And then wish orders down into
here, please.
And as soon as this is done, we will uh
do the giveaway. You're almost there.
You're so close. It's coming. It's
coming. It's coming. It's coming. Back
to the 50s. Under these 50s again, they
resell it. You should get that move.
Come on. Stop holding up 50s.
Anchor volume profile settings. Yep.
Gone over them a few times already. It's
uh two ticks.
Two ticks. All right. And style 20% set
to right. That's all I change.
Come on. Give the team the money. All
right. Give the team the money. TP into
here. Don't be a dick for a tick. If
this doesn't want to give it to you, at
least pay yourself some in case they're
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] Hopefully they're not.
Pardon my French. And and hopefully we
get down into here.
How do I decide where to place my stop
loss? The other side of volume. Right.
So, if you just got short on this re
attempt here, you want it to protect the
other side of volume. So, I'd be short
in here with my stop here. All right.
This would be a bit of a pain. You could
have, I guess, shorted this node with
your stop into this one, or you could
have reshorted this with your stop into
that, for example. Uh, the IB trade was
very good and then they washed you out
and it would have needed a re-entry. But
I used volume or where or where the
trade is no longer valid, right? So, if
you were going to be short down here,
you would have to have your stop here or
you would have to do it on the change of
character up here, which means you would
have to use very small size because it's
over 100 points away.
I can't sorry 80% I can't do what you
want. I'm really sorry. Like I I'm also
having to trade and having to manage
stuff. I can't say all the numbers all
the times. I I get what you're saying
but I'm drawing it on. I will try my
best, but very hard for me to do that
cuz if I'm saying here and I put it the
other side of this node, I'm not going
to give you the price of the node. I'm
really sorry. I get that. It makes it
harder for you.
Can I hold your hand here? Take it. Take
it.
Okay. Type FCT in chat. Just type it
once. Please don't spam. and we will
pick a winner for the Apex giveaway with
that.
So, just type it once code FCT for your
cheapest prop firms. It's the best code
to use. Give you guys a minute to do
that.
going to squeeze back up to the red. I
can't believe they protected that low
again. ES again holding the IB. So that
holding the market up pretty well there
on the ES.
Pretty well there on the ES. Just give
you guys another minute.
Right. If we start to reclaim here,
if we start to reclaim here and do a W
and base above here, you will expect
range rotation from sort of above 140
150 for relief up to the 210s. I would
not be trading that long. Those of you
who like range rotation, that is a
viable setup if they start to trade
through some of this. It's very, very
risky. In my mind, you want to stay
short on a day like today. But we will
see if they're starting to reclaim. We
have to be willing to at least think
about that moment. They've just washed
everyone out. Come up to the red box.
Gray box becomes key now. So if they
trade between gray and red, build the
liquidity, build the liquidity, build
liquidity. Relief will come outside of
this or that or outside of this or a
wash into these. They are dirty. We
missed our final TP there by eight
points. 12 points. Horrible. Horrible
buzzers.
Can I show my indicators? It's the Flow
Zone Pros. They're here.
Right. A version of it comes with a
20our course. Otherwise, you can you can
you can buy it on my website, but uh
probably best to do the course you
understand how to use it.
Okay. Pulling this winner. Five. Four.
Three.
two and one.
Oh, look at that. I know this guy,
Foster Scott. That's two That's two big
wins
for Foster Scott. He He won in the
community recently as well. Nice, dude.
I will um hook you up on uh Discord.
Make it easier. That's nice and easy.
Nice and easy. Me send you a code now.
Uh, where are you? There you are,
Scotley. There you go, buddy. I just
sent it to you on Discord. Always nice
when a member wins.
It's sad. I missed the short on NQ and
on gold and silver. I felt so much fo to
chase, but I ended up not taking the
trade. Well, don't worry about it.
Tomorrow is a new day. This after this
afternoon's a new session.
Don't worry about it. It's just a trade.
It's just a trade. There's going to be
lots of trades set up this year. Trust
me. The amount of volatility we're
having, amount of shakeouts in the
market, there will be lots of trades
happening.
That is
not a good rule.
JC
15sec imbalances. Really get out of here
with that.
Get out of there with that.
Might as well mark out a two second
imbalance.
Get out of here. 15 second imbalances.
Get out of here, mate. No such [\h__\h]
thing.
One tick imbalances. Yeah, exactly.
Alex, what's your thought on anchored
VWOUP? Per example, gold rejected
exactly the alltime high anchored VW up
before reversing. Oh, I love anchored
VWs. There's free lesson on my YouTube
about them. I absolutely love anchored
VWAPs.
The New York one is anchored to the
open. We could probably anchor one to
the low and the high of of day.
You could probably do one to the
overnight high.
You go. It's rejection all day long.
Right. There you go.
Yeah. I I love them. I love anchor VW. I
think they're very very useful. I like
them on like news events or big pivot
events. Something like you said like
gold an alltime high anchor V. Very very
good. A low swing pivot very very good.
Yeah.
Okay. Um, going to give away an
introduction course, guys. So, this is
just for someone who's very new to
trading. If you've traded for a while,
this will not probably be that helpful
for you, but um, you do get a discount
into the main course if you do it, but
feel free to give it to a friend. Uh,
type course in chat once and we'll do
that giveaway.
Give you guys a moment to do that.
Someone said, "What do I think of ICT
teachings?"
They are what they are. Some of it's
good, some of it's a joke. Most of it's
regurgitated.
I think he's an arrogant [\h__\h] Tell you
that much.
I AM THE MARKET. IT'S ME. IT'S not
volume profile. It's me. Yeah, it's you.
Of course it is, mate.
I'd like I'd like you to sit down with
Jamie Diamond and say that to his face.
You [\h__\h]
Are some of his teachings good? Yeah,
I'm not going to lie. Some of the
teachings are good. They are useful.
But he is not the algorithm. He is not
the market. Get the [\h__\h] out of there.
It's me.
I was kidnapped in a van and told the
secrets of the market by God himself.
Yeah, mate. And my name's Dirk Diggler.
Yeah, there you go. psychos. I I I agree
with that. He's annoying, but he does
drop some decent knowledge. Yeah, that's
it.
All right, let's let's pull this winner
for the course. Five, four, three,
two, and one.
Uh,
how do I say that?
UT UTFKO3,
are you here?
UTFK3.
Yeah, nice. Okay, if you can just email
me, please info@flowzonerader.com
and I'll sort you out with a uh course.
just uh send me a screenshot of you
logged into your YouTube.
I will I will sort you out.
Congratulations.
He's Woff before Woff. I mean,
yeah. I mean, he must be 400 years old
if he's W before Woff.
Crazy. It's a crazy world.
I mean the whole I created the algo
thing is just he's copying Woff's theory
of of seeing the market as an individual
person. Even I I I say that I call them
them them being market makers and stuff.
It's easier to think of the market that
way but there is no one outgo that's if
you believe that then um I don't know
what to tell you. You're going to have a
very unhappy life. You're incredibly
gullible person if you believe that.
info@flowzonerader.com.
That's it. That's it. The composite I
think is it operator or the composite
man, isn't it? Composite man. There's a
free video on my YouTube on that. The
composite man. Okay. They're still
looking to reject up here this same
node, but the gray box to this node is
be starting to become important. All
right. From here to here is becoming
important. And we still have lowhanging
fruit down here as the last chance for
it to get lower. Uh but ES is holding
the market up pretty well right now. But
this is starting to look very
aggressive. Sellers last got stuck here
at 70s. By the way, there were sellers
at lower of days at 50s.
It's looking like it's trying to
accelerate. It is attempting to
accelerate lower here to clean up the
low of day, but I'd be watching these
50s. Okay, 50s. We had a big seller at
that low. So 70s there was some selling
before 70s to 77 50s is where that uh
big seller at low of day got caught. If
you get under there under 50s we should
get that 30s which is what we're looking
for. We would like to see 30s. So we're
letting go of 50s here
and we let go to 50s here. Still
hovering around me 70s.
Reason I'm talking about this right
here. Right down into here. 50 is where
these sellers got stuck. And underneath
that, we should break and get the
target. If we can, if we can let these
sellers out, we should break and get the
target. Leaving this shelf. If we can
leave this shelf, we should break. We're
just going to have to respect 50s on the
nose. I can show you it right here. Can
I move this up? No. Come on. Move up,
please. M this guy right here.
Right. This big lot here. 50s 89 lot
down there. We're going to respect him.
So, you take a partial into him and then
see if we can break down. And ideally,
ES joins the game. Remember, ES has
still not taken out his IB low yet or
anything,
but that continues to be annoying today.
Show my trades. I mean, I'm not in a
trade. Uh, we had them this morning.
These were my trades this morning. Here
and here. This is what I've called for
you since.
VIX is climbing. No, VIX is still stuck
in between those ranges. Right. So, VIX
keeps finding bids down at 1850. It's
still not broken out of its like 1925
pivot. The big pivot is 1960s. All
right, through 1960s we're going to go
previous day high on Vicks.
Start cursing to push it down. It's
coming, folks. It's coming. Look, we're
still just in the gray box. If we reject
gray box, we should get the swipe. We
just need ES to stop [\h__\h] around.
What do I think about longing after we
hit TP? I wouldn't I wouldn't be doing
that unless we trap a significant amount
of liquidity. You've got to remember we
are starting to break down daily,
weekly, monthly levels, right? Be zoomed
out. Understand what we're trading to
and why. I wouldn't be trying to guess
the bottom on a day like today. They
tried to do that yesterday and saved it.
All right. Watch these 50s now as a
cover point. You can cover some in front
of 50s. And if we snap 50s, you're
looking for 30s. So right into these 50s
again. ES still not breaking down under
IB.
So you've got a TP here into 50s. If
they cannot break 50s, be very careful.
If you break 50s, you're going to get a
new lower day. So 50s back up to 70s
potential rotation, 20 point rotation
here. Sellers came in at 76s and 70s. 50
is still the level where those sellers
at the lower of day got stuck, which I
showed you earlier. Under 50s, we should
get that break. Here's the 50 tag. So
50, your TP now hit TP1. And let's see
if you can get the 30s.
Let's see if you can get the 30s here.
They are adding liquidity lower. I would
like to see you just trade under
underneath all of this now. Here you go.
Get under 50s. We don't want them stuck
down there. If you want to hit final TP,
we want these sellers. They got to be
aggressive and they're aggressive now.
And get rid of all this absorption. Just
snap it. They've got to snap it all.
They're trying. They're adding down at
50 25,20. You should get it. One big
swipe will do it here. Come on sellers.
Wakey wakey
wakey wakey. They're piling in down here
without follow through. Be very careful.
They keep piling in down here without
follow through.
That 50 is still being absorbed. The
same level that we've talked about, this
same level. Sellers keep getting stuck
right into here again. You see it again.
They just tried very aggressively to get
through here. So, we come back to this
imbalance and they might have one more
attempt. If they fail that attempt, I'd
be done with it. If they fail this next
attempt, I'd be done with it. Here they
go. Back to the 50s again.
Come on, give it to the team for God's
sake. Under the 50s, give them some
follow through to 30s. Come on, for
goodness sake. Here we go, folks. 40s,
low of day break. You want 50s to be
protected now and then you're going to
get green line and then wish orders
underneath green line, please. Here you
go. 40s. Come on. Give it to the team.
Come on. Come on. Come on. Remember,
your next TP is here and your wish
orders are down to here. Down to 25k and
under.
Gray box still holding up really well.
Get under this 50 for goodness sake.
It's coming, folks. It's coming. Come
on.
Someone is absorbing down here. Someone
is definitely absorbing down here. I
think you're going to get the break,
though. I cannot imagine that they keep
saving this, but
long as you paid yourself some.
50s to 70 still a rotation. They want to
pop it same as they did last time.
You would not want it above that. I tell
you that much. There is liquidity down
at 20. So, I think we should swipe this
guy our level here at 30. We should
swipe him. If ES can stop [\h__\h] about,
it will really help.
Here you go. 40s again.
40s again. Get your wish orders out,
folks. Get your wish orders out. We're
very close. Get your wish orders out.
Here we go. Here we go. 35s, 33s. You
can see they're front running that a
bit. There's a sellside imbalance here
into 39, which they're just tapping back
into. Hopefully, we reject it and wash.
Otherwise, we're going to go back to 50
for one last check. Look at that. The
front run by a tick, maybe a point. Come
on. Give it to the team and then wash
it. Here it comes. Here it comes. Woo.
Okay, wish orders out. Hopefully they
snap this down now. There you go. Some
of your wish orders should be getting
hit here. And what a beauty. What an
absolute beauty. All right, so we can
think about 25,000
now. And here we go. Here's the wish
order. This is what I'm talking about.
We are snapping big big levels. You can
start washing aggressively here. So you
can just start trailing now. And we can
get very very nasty here. We can get
very nasty here. potentially down into
24,880.
Here we go, folks.
What a be. Oh, why did he say wish
orders down to this blue box? I
wondered. Why did we say wish orders
down to this blue box?
It's cuz I am the algo.
It's nothing to do with volume. I'm the
algo.
Let's go, baby. What a be. What a be.
What a be.
Look at you guys making so much money.
You're maxing it out all your accounts.
I love it. I love it. Nice work. Nice
work.
Are these blue light glasses? Uh, they
are blue light glasses, but they are
more just normal glasses as well, cuz I
am blind. That's why you always see me
wear glasses. I have got a new pair
coming. No, no reversals, guys. You guys
keep calling for reversals. Look,
please, guys, please, please, please,
please, you got to understand what we're
doing today,
right? You got to understand what we're
doing today. We're we're we're
potentially leaving
three months worth of trap participants.
Okay, remember, we filled the gap up
here last week. We failed to hold the
breakout. We traded back underneath. We
have a shelf here. If we leave this
shelf, we will come back down towards
the 200 day. This can be the black swan,
start of the black swan kind of event
where we start to sell tech underneath
the lower Ballinger band where we have
divergence to ES. Go back to the
beginning of the video today. 9:15 to
9:30. I talked about this move today.
Reject gray come down. Stops here, stops
here, stops here to hunt. We are
starting to really get aggressive.
Here's 25,000 now.
Big level.
No offense, but you're making the same
trade using only moving averages. Cool
story, bro. Uh, I've got moving averages
on here. Doesn't mean [\h__\h] though, if
you can't manage your position. Cool
story. What's your moving average down
here that you're trading into? Because
the only thing left to attack now is the
200. Don't think I don't use moving
averages. I use them.
Why are we in a cell?
What? What rolled over? Oh. Oh, there it
is.
I have to be a genius.
Here we go. All right. So, let's see if
we can dig down any further. Uh, I'm
watching the next daily pivot. We have
an old an old open here at 76 and then
we're watching 24,890.
24,890.
So, here we go into the top of the blue
box. We can trim some here. And then
we're looking for all the way down to
890. Here would be the next level. I'm
going to put a horizontal line here.
Right, this is our next level. So,
trimming some into here and then down
into there for your next spot. We're
getting extended here, folks. So, move
your stop down. You do not want to let
this rip all the way back, you know, 70
80 points on you, do you? All right. So,
a break above this shelf here where we
get thin above 13, we can see a squeeze
back up. So, do not let it do that on
you when you're managing your position,
please.
There's no news, guys. It's not It's not
This is
No, guys. Okay. News doesn't trigger
stuff, right? volume trigger stuff. News
news is just fluff. We're rotating out
of tech. There's your news. You know, we
sold AMD when it had good earnings.
There's your news. Do you know what I
mean? We're selling Palanteer after the
push up. There's your news. It's all
bollocks. All that matters is the
volume. We are leaving track volume.
All right. Into the top of the blue box
here. We know this is starting to be
quite a key level here. All right. This
this goes back to a node that we created
from the week starting the 15th of
December and we can trade down to this
green line. But this is an area we found
bids on the 15th of December. So you
know how far back I'm currently looking
Uh there's lots of ways to skin a market
trader on tilt. Uh it's not about the
teachings. It's about saying that you
own it all and that you are the algo.
You you want to talk about ways to skin
a market. I'll tell you there's a
million ways to trade.
I'm not the one that thinks it's only my
way. That would be the gay-head man that
you currently look up to. Clearly,
how old are you? 18, probably. You're
probably one or two years into it. I
mean, your name's Trader on Tilt.
Okay, top of the blue box. Starting to
find a bit of a bid here. Like we said,
dates back to the 15th of December.
Might find a bid here. And the trigger
back for a squeeze would be above 14s.
Do not take the long squeeze, but back
above 14s. There is a squeeze out to
50s.
Oh my god,
dude. You're insufferable.
Goodbye.
Okay.
Any ideas to get back in? No.
No, we're extended now. We're leaving
shelves now.
So, you should be out most of your TP.
The only thing left to do is come down
here. We're starting to see big, big
extensions. You're starting to see
panic. You're starting to see ES, right?
ES now trading down towards that
previous day, previous week low.
All right. So, we're watching ES into
and 6878,
but we're into the key level, right? If
we go back on the daily here, you
understand where we are. I can move this
down a little bit. One
here and one
here. Right? This is where we're trading
back into this block.
And then the bottom of this blue right
here.
And you got to understand like we talked
about, we are potentially going to leave
all this volume trapped. And if we start
to find acceptance here, we will start
to rotate into some of this.
It's what we've been going over for
weeks, right? We've built out so much
liquidity dating back to 5th of Jan. So
much liquidity dating back to the 5th of
Jan.
You managed to make double your target
in five minutes. Nice work.
Yeah, like we said, guys, guys, why does
everyone bang on about ICT so much? It's
insane. Yes, some of his concepts are
great. Yes, like I said, some of his
teachings are really good. They're not
always that accurate, but they're really
good. But he did not create the
algorithm. He does not own the stock
market. You should not be [\h__\h] on
volume profile and all this other stuff.
Like I said, if you think you created
the stock market, go and sit down with
Jamie Diamond and I'd like to see him
have a chat with him. All right?
Otherwise, shut the [\h__\h] up talking
about a gray old man. Who [\h__\h] cares?
Your job is to make money. The end. The
end. I don't care how you make money,
right? The end. The end. That's the end
of it.
Right. They're not his concepts. [\h__\h]
hell. I don't know how many times I can
say this on stream. Why do people want
to protect this person that they don't
know? It's insane.
Made 146 points. I'm out. I got scared.
I don't blame you. It's It's such a good
trade. So, what? You're to here.
Did you take it from up there? I'm not
sure. Maybe you took a re-entry here.
But we're into the blue box. It's a good
place to start covering now, isn't it?
You don't want to like Look how steep we
are since the snap. Remember we said
since this snaps since here you should
have wish orders down to the blue box
because this can happen and they might
well put in a pivot at some point. All
right, we'd expect some kind of retrace.
We don't just trade straight down, do
we? But some since snapping this, right,
we said there probably be wish orders
down into the blue box.
Why did I mark out the blue box? It's
dating back to where we found a bid from
the 17th of December. So if you look at
the lows of both November the 25th, all
right, and the 17th of December, those
have been protected lows. All right,
that's why
right here, right?
If we think about the swing points,
right, since we found a bid in November,
right, this level here, we drifted away,
we came back to it, right? We retested
it, we held, we are coming back to that
same level, right? This means that every
participant other than these guys here,
right? Every participant in this market
Since what? What did I say? 5th of
November. Is probably somewhere around
here. Since here, let's move this out
the way. Since the 5th of November.
There you go. Since the 5th of November.
Pretty much all that volume will be
trapped. We have a shelf here. We have
some buyers who stepped in here. On what
day? The 20th of November to the 24th.
But if we find acceptance under here, it
means that all of this volume three
months worth of volume, which for you
guys who want to keep talking about ICT,
who he says does not exist, volume
doesn't matter. Well, it [\h__\h] does
because if we leave that, we will get
very, very, very heavy. Remember, most
of the range has been created in here.
This has been the rotation. Look below,
fail, rotate, look above, fail. Rotate,
look below, fail. Rotate, look above,
fail. Rotate, look below, look above.
And now we're right back down into this.
That's why.
No, it's not that I'm triggered by. It's
that everyone in chat wants to talk
about. Do you know how many [\h__\h]
insanely amazing traders there are on
out there? There are some incredible
traders out there that are not these
guys. Like, go and read Market Wizards,
right? Go and read Market Wizards.
There's a good start for you guys who
who want to talk about real traders
who've done some like big big trades and
made real money.
Go and read some of the memoirs by guys
who are running like legit hedge funds
who are working in like the emerging
banks who go and read like oh my gosh
I'm not even going to it's not even
worth it.
Even go and listen to like guys like
Mike Catz,
all those guys like who were trading
like the small cats
pre pre209.
I mean, like we're talking about
incredible, incredible traders here
trading incredible size,
right? You want to talk about real
trailers, not like me and you or anyone.
Are we talking about monsters? We're
talking about monsters in the game.
even retail guys who have done well like
uh oh my god I'm gonna have to get them
up
I used to bug and follow like go and go
and look at like ducks Steven ducks go
and look at like Nate um
who's the guy I used to get long in the
small caps
remind myself
stopped following a lot of these guys
Jack Kellogg Like go and look at all
these guys. You want to see like guys
trading real size doing real stuff.
All right. So relief from the blue
blocks like we expect. We'd imagine
we're pretty thin here above 80. They
might come and test test this 25,000 and
then all the way up here. I would kind
of be done with it for the day. You got
5 minutes left until lunch.
You like Steven D? Beast. Beast. Like
absolute beast. Like you just can't even
fathom the size that he's trading. Like
million. Making millions of dollars a
day when there's an A+ opportunity on
some scammy small cap. Like nerves of
steel, man. And records his trades. You
can find some of his old trades on on
YouTube. All right. So, starting to see
relief like we've talked about through
here. Probably come up and test this
next node and through here. So, this is
the next area for them to defend. And if
they don't defend it, we will get
relief. Remember, we've hit main target.
All the way up here now is possible for
the relief. So, into this node, through
here all the way possible. Remember, we
went straight down. We can go straight
back up, which is why I saying be done
with the trade as you come into this
blue box. And we would imagine all right
they will have to make a decision in
here whether they want to resell this
down and find a bid. This may very well
be the range for the afternoon while
they make that decision. Now
um for you guys who trade IB
right Scottly Mr. Foster Scott did we
hit your target? We might well have
done. We did. We did. We hit your
target. One and a half extension of IB.
So, lots of reasons to be done with
this. Low hanging fruit gone,
overextended. Probably saw some sellers
trapped at that low now. Yep, there we
go. So, excess at the low was pretty
good. So, I'd say from 47s is the level.
Yeah, Fabio's awesome, man.
What is the blue box? this blue box. We
just went over it. It's It's an area
where I think we will probably find some
bids. Um, if you just Yeah, I'm just
going to show you one more time. Right.
Look how many times If I just keep
pulling this area along, if it will let
me
You going to let me do the horizontal?
There we go. If we just keep pulling
this area along. You can see since the
new contract how sticky this area has
been. Look,
we break under, we reclaim, we squeeze.
We break under, we try again, we
reclaim, we squeeze. We come to it, we
squeeze. We come to it, we squeeze. We
break under, we squeeze. We dip under,
we reclaim, we hold it, we squeeze. We
trade back to it, we squeeze. This is
our first time visiting it since. Right.
So, it's the first time visiting this
area since 17th of December. before that
since the 25th of November. Before that,
you know, we started putting this pivot
in from the start of this new contract
dating way back to September. Okay, so
it's a big area, guys. It's a really,
really big area. We don't expect markets
to just completely tank in one
direction, right? The key for this week
was there was the failed breakout last
week. We left volume trapped up there.
All right, so now we've got two sets of
volume trapped. We had the all-time high
volume trapped here. We left volume
trapped up here. We rotated in this
range, which was gross. All I wanted to
do is leave this range. Today was the
first attempt to leave the range
properly. We're starting to do it. We
might well find a bid there for a day or
two, session or two, maybe even a week
or two before we look for this kind of
move down here and below. If we want to
think about what that's going to look
like on a daily, uh those of you who
have been here for a number of weeks
will know that we've been thinking about
this move on the daily for a while,
right? We have a big volume shelf right
here which we're trading right into.
We're already starting to leave this
one. This is anchored from the high.
This is your whole year. All right. So,
this is 12 months. This is anchored from
the all-time high. We are starting to
leave this. If we start to leave this,
we will start to attack this stop here
and the 200 day SMA. Yes, I use SMAs in
EMAs also do. They're very important.
This is our yearly average. If we start
to lose that, you know, if we start to
open up these Ballingers and trend down
and get stuck underneath that, then
maybe we go risk off into some of this.
We will see. We will see. But right now,
the main thing is probably thinking
about a pullback based on the tariff
pivot.
We can afford to come very very deep
here. Like even here is only a 30%
pullback, folks. This can still be a
very bullish pullback longterm unless
we're going to come to 50 and below. So,
lots of opportunities here in the market
this year for swing positions. Lots of
opportunities for swing positions.
The deeper we go, the better. All right.
So, through here now, probably up to the
next gray box, right? Squeeze. So, be
done with it. I would be done with it.
Uh, what are you guys saying? Sorry, I'm
having to play catch up here.
What time does the afternoon session
start? Um, I don't trade uh in the
afternoon, but you would trade like an
hour after lunch. Or you could just
trade the new 4hour bar if you wanted.
That would be the other opportunity. You
could trade like the uh 2:00.
But yeah, we're we're done now for the
next hour, hour and a half.
Brother, you help me truly. You helped
me break my losing streak. 150 point
ride. Hey, nice work. Nice work.
Yeah, wealth chart's good. I don't use
Wealth Chart, but I use something very,
very similar on Ninja Trader. Alex, I've
been watching you for some time. Uh, I
trade options for about a year on and
off with a lot still to learn. Would you
recommend to start trading futures?
Horses for courses, my friend. Like, if
you like options, um, I don't like
options for day trading. Um, personally,
uh, I'm not that comfortable with the
Greeks. Uh, I hate decay. I will take
leaps for swing trades. Um, especially
if it's for like a very expensive stock
and I want, uh, a bit more leverage. Um,
normally I try and trade commons where
possible, but it's totally up to you.
The nice thing about futures is is it is
a centralized exchange, so you can see
all the data, but it it is up to you.
They they trade the same way.
Yeah, ask away Adam.
Can I talk more about the IB trade? Uh,
it's an extension, right? So, so there
is a thought process that once we do the
initial balance, this purple line to
this purple line if we're going to go
into an expansion, right? A common place
to look is for an expansion to the 50.
You can hit see today we hit the 161
expansion, right? That's a common trade.
If we go for an IB expansion model,
that's a very common trade. That's all I
was referring to. It's not something I
regularly look at, but I know Mr. Foster
Scott in chat does trade it.
You like Ross Cameron? Yeah, I mean I I
used to trade with Ross. I just used to
take the other side of the positions.
What am I teaching in my orderflow
course? bookmap footprint delta delta
divergence um spotting traps volume
profile it's all on my website you can
see what I teach on my website go
through it
nice ding enjoy
nice work Jerome good work good work
is there another trade setup uh I'd say
we probably need a rebalance at some
point so if they're going to stay heavy
right they're going to need to protect
this here right they're going to stay
heavy they're going to to protect this
here. Just know that you are start you
are losing location. Now remember the
best short opportunities were up here,
maybe even here, but now we're
underneath initial balance. We are
underneath
want to show you just as a reminder to
you folks. Right, we are underneath the
daily Ballinger band. All right, it
doesn't mean we can't trade lower, but
if you are entering new short positions
underneath this, you are asking for
problems. Do I think we could have a
black swan kind of event? I do. I
already think we're starting to see such
big divergence between all of these, but
be careful. Remember, we've got is it
Google at close? I've got to remind
myself. Alex has almost forgotten
already. Is it Google at close or do we
have a close here today?
Wednesday at close. Yes, Google, ARM,
Qualcomm, those are the big ones really
at the close. And then Amazon after
close tomorrow. So, we will get wonky um
as we get into close for sure. Worth
noting that. Worth noting that.
Uh I have global plus, but I only think
you really need global if I'm in if I'm
honest, Thomas or but Matt.
So, I think we go to 25,080 now. 25,080.
I mean, we have an old gap fill.
Oh, you mean to go upside 25,080?
Yeah, this box. Yeah, it I mean it's
trying to it's trying to retest this,
right? So, we went from here to here.
They now bid above this. They should
build liquidity here. If they go above
this, we go to the next node. If they
reject this, we trade back down to this.
If they find acceptance lower, we trade
back down to this. It's always block to
block, guys. See? block down into here.
Over here. Up to this. Down to this.
Down to this. Up to this. Down to this.
Up to this. Let go of this. Wash. Back
to here. Up to here. Maybe down to here
again. Maybe acceptance up. Maybe a
little swipe. Maybe dunk back down.
Right.
We don't trade in like one straight
line. It's not how we trade.
Oh, I had you on the wrong bloody thing,
didn't I? You missed all of that. Sorry.
When I'm hitting first TP and closing my
follower trades fully, I can't figure
out what it's doing. I have mode set to
the same ATM strategy.
Uh, hit me in Discord, mate. Hit Let's
talk about that in Discord.
So I can understand fully.
Would I be looking for a short here now?
For me, no. For me now, we're too far
into discount. All right. There is a
last target left, but remember we've
we've washed out so much, guys. We've
we've taken out so many key levels. Um
we can afford for a little repric. Um
if if they build in my mind if they
build sufficient liquidity out here and
then you know come and swipe these and
come back under maybe there's a short
back down but you have to ask yourself
like is it worth it? If we were short
here, short here and short here, do we
need one more or have we made enough
money for the day and we come back
tomorrow and trade again?
That's what I would ask myself.
I certainly wouldn't be getting long
personally.
I think there's panic in the market a
little bit.
How high up might it reclaim or chop?
Only 1.64% red day two. Might just be
another October November pullback event.
Uh
it might be, but I think you're likely
to see like I talked about on the hourly
and daily, we're starting to be very
dangerous. I mean, if you The difference
was the pullback in December,
uh we didn't have all the liquidity
built out, right? We've now got all the
liquidity from 19th,
19th of December. We've got like two
months worth of liquidity built out that
we can wreck, maybe even more.
What's the indicator? Blue white profile
at the right hand side. This anchored
volume profile. It's not an indicator.
It's a drawing tool. It's just a drawing
tool. It's free.
Is it too late to buy calls? Uh, I don't
know. I haven't I haven't looked at the
options data, but
I I wouldn't be buying calls today
personally. But also, when you're saying
something like that, you have to
understand I don't understand what
you're looking at. Are you looking at
for a swing position? Are you looking
for a scalp position?
How do you do your stops? That's my
biggest problem. 90% right, but always
get stopped out. Use use volume or
structure to protect you. So if you were
getting short in here, you don't want it
to reclaim this. So your stop would have
to be the other side. If you were short
versus this, your stop would need to be
I mean that's actually quite ugly. You
would probably got stopped out. But
let's say you're short versus this, I'd
put your stop the other side. If you
were short versus here, you'd put your
stop at that swing high, which it
protected. All right. Your stop should
be where the trade is no longer valid.
All right. So if if for some reason
you've bought this, all right, your stop
would have to be at that low, wouldn't
it?
If you don't put your stock where it's
no longer valid, if you're just doing it
based on a number that you like or or a
profit amount, you will get stopped out
all the time. The market doesn't care
about how much money you're going to
make or lose. It cares about what's in
front of you.
You still have week low signals. I mean,
yeah, it might be like ES did just miss
the low. Look, it still hasn't taken it.
It still has not taken these loads.
Remember, we've taken all these out. It
found a bid in front. It's come back to
IB.
All right, we know this is a big level.
It's come back to IB. All right, if they
can snap this, market will get weak. But
you want to be careful. Think about
where we built all this liquidity. This
is the liquidity build, right? We
finally broke down. We're revisiting
that. You want that to reject and come
back down. And if they reclaim this,
they can come and hunt stops. Like I
said, I wouldn't be long biased today
personally.
Doesn't make sense to me.
About to get out of here, folks. Last
few questions.
Orderflow question. If you're looking
for a long and buyers get trapped near
highs and then get out as the market
trades through the upside, is that a
viable entry?
You're looking for a long, buyers get
trapped at the highs and then get out.
Oh, you mean Okay, so you're talking
about this move here.
You're saying the market's done this,
buyers are trapped here, we pull back.
Is it viable to get long as they break
as as this? That would be a breakout
trade. Better trade would be to position
here,
right? And then look for that.
Yes, it's viable, but that would be the
better trade.
I think it will wash all the way back to
value area low. You mean drive up to
value area low? I mean, it's got to get
through a lot of nodes to do that. So
far, we're still staying heavy, but we
just rejected. We just make this. It's
actually this tiny little node here has
just been developed. It's gross. Should
have come up to here really. Still looks
like it wants to trade lower. It's still
got this target. Still no change in
structure if you think about how we're
moving.
Right. There's no pivot. It's still a
sell. I'd probably be done with it, but
you know, there's argument to keep
trading lower, but for me, too far a
discount for a new position.
What an em this one. 7289. The purple
one. You mean 7289?
Hey Rick, how's it going? When I see
bookmap going down, but it's green
bubbles all the way down and CBD up,
that means there's a major divergence,
strong bull absorption. Well, if you see
price going down, but it's green bubbles
up. That means there's passive selling.
Price can't go down with green. You mean
afterwards? You mean like this here?
Trying to I'm trying to understand the
uh way you framed it. Right. If we see
this here, these blue bubbles, these
green bubbles here and here, right?
These are aggressive market
participants. These are market orders,
right? These are aggressive buyers. Was
price able to move higher after those
aggressive buyers came in? No. So, what
does that mean? It means there's
absorption sell side. So, there's
sellers here willing to sell and force
this market lower, which we're starting
to see. Now, we're going to retest this
same level here where we just broke down
from. All right. So, buyers are coming
flying in here. If they don't get their
way and we use this pivot to sell, which
we're now using just structurally, we're
going to come down to where these buyers
just came in. If we lose these bids
under here where these buyers just came
flying in. So, we're using now I
basically saying this is the pivot
somewhere in here, right? And if we lose
that, then we will try and trade
underneath this pivot. And if we lose
that, right, we can trade into this
cluster here, which is where the low of
day auction is right now. And you can
see there's a buyer here trying to
support that low of day auction. and
he's trying to provide liquidity down
there. So that when we see this buyers
at high and price not moving higher that
is a seller absorbing the tape moving it
lower. When we see selling at lows and
not able to move lower that is a buyer
in the tape this right here and we move
price higher. So we had 150 lot sellside
above that 30 lot 50 lot and then we see
this buying come in and we absorb it. So
you see selling at loes being absorbed
as we move higher.
Do I trade gold? No, not really. Not
unless it's a swing position. What was
my job before trading? I was a music
producer and DJ.
How to get volume on the right hand
side. Anchored volume profile, guys.
It's a drawing tool. Anchored volume
profile. GX looking like a sell
possibility all the way down to 600. Let
me have a look. Uh you were talking
about the QQQ. Okay. What? So, we've got
a put wall down at 600 is what you're
saying. That makes sense because I have
got a big level there drawn out which
dates back a long long way. Zoom this
out a bit.
All the way back to 17th of December.
So, it makes sense. So, it's kind of the
same block. We're actually kind of
trading in that block now on the ENQ.
Uh, so QQQ needs to catch up the ETF.
It's the same block. 17th of December.
This is this block. So on the NQ, that
block here is 600 on the QQQ. If you
look at where 600 is on the QQQ, it's
the 17th of December. If you look at
this block here that we've just traded
into, it's the same level. So we've got
a little bit of divergence.
I know I don't trade hyenashi
early in the session. anchor volume
profile not showing
showing much. Yeah, because there's no
volume to test off. How are you choosing
where to place your stops? Uh probably
using Bookmap more or the previous
sessions.
Yeah, I'm absolutely done for today.
Yeah, 100%. I'm done for today.
I want to ask this from you. Can you
repeat every time you remember before
you go the market will be there? I'll
repeat myself, but since you have more
experience and hearing
the market will be there. Oh, you mean
the market will be there again tomorrow?
I see what you're saying. Yeah. I mean,
you got to just tell yourself that all
the time. This is just one session. Just
one session.
Okay.
Anchor volume profile in here.
Forecasting and measuring tools. Come
down here. Right here, anchored volume
profile. Click on 930
and then I have it set to two ticks.
It's up to you. You can have it set to
two ticks or you could just do this as
rows and do a thousand rows. I have it
set to a width of 20. That's all you
need to do, folks. That's all you need
to do. Right. Last few questions before
I go.
How far are your stop losses? It depends
on structure, guys. You cannot I cannot
repeat this hard enough. Right? Let's
say you've entered late here on a short
here, right? Your stop loss would need
to be up here. Okay, that's what the
market is dictating your stop loss to
be. If your stop loss is 10 points
because you only want to trade 10
points, then you know why would the
market care about you? It doesn't. It
cares about the swing. So asking how big
your stop loss is really depends where
your entry is and where the trade is no
longer valid. And then this size, right,
the size of that stop should dictate the
amount of contracts that you take.
Is being a profitable trader boring as
you have to wait for setups? Yeah, that
like most of the day is spent stalking
stuff. Yes,
it is. It should be boring. At the
moment, we got a very very very volatile
market. So, there are opportunities
quite regularly, but normally it's very
boring.
Yeah, I might get a bot to do that.
JD, your jokes.
Do I use RSI? No, I don't.
Anchor volume profile, not an ATS. Then
then you're going to need to find some
kind of volume profile that you can use
where you can just do it to the 930. I'm
sure it will have uh something. Same on
uh Ninja Trader. I don't use an anchor,
but I am able to set it to a 930 print.
How much would I risk on a 50K? Uh are
you talking about a 50k prop firm? So
really what you're talking about is a
$25,000 account. One or two micros. One
or two micros. Start small. You're
talking about ranges with You're talking
about this. This was a 181 point trade
earlier. Almost 200 point trade. All
right. Two micros.
Uh
two 46 like 800 $700 odd in there. It's
enough, man. It's enough. It's enough.
Is bitmap a must? I don't think it's a
must. I find it very useful. You can see
still on bookmap. We're bouncing between
these levels. We just went over these
levels. Look, the horizontal lines. So
buyers are stuck up here. We traded down
to the horizontal line. We reclaimed
this line. We went back to the same area
the buyers stuck. We came down onto the
horizontal lines. We're now trapped
between these two. We snap this. You can
see this bids just left the tape. If we
snap this, we'll probably wash down into
here. If we reclaim this yellow line,
we'll trade back onto here again. It's
just level to level. It's just how the
market trades, guys.
There you go. Sh saying one to two
micros is literally paying them 3 to 500
a trade. There you go. Do I have a video
how to set up your chart? Gray, blue,
box, arrow, session.
Uh in probably in the course I do, but
these are just drawing out key levels.
What makes the market choppy? Uh, when
we need to build liquidity.
Yeah. So, the market the last thing I'm
going to do today, but I'm going to have
to go. I do have an appointment. Right.
When we're when we're in this phase of a
higher time frame, right? When we're in
this phase,
then lower time frames doing this,
right? when we're in this phase of the
market, a pullback in a higher time
frame, then lower time frames doing
this.
And more recently, if we think about
more recently what the markets looked
like, if this was like the leg up uh
into like October or wherever it was
from, we we've been doing this on the
higher time frame.
All right, building out liquidity. All
right. So, if that's your higher time
frame, that means lower time frame,
right? Looks like this. Looks
disgusting. I didn't mean to do that bit
in here. Right. Today,
we are here. All right. We had we
actually had a failed breakout last
week, trapped buyers, and we came back
into range and today we are breaking out
the other side. So, if you were white,
that could have been the spring, right?
So this today and yesterday was a sign
of strength. It might be that we get a
trend down which means this on lower
time frames will start to look like this
more which is what we've seen the last
few days. Right? So this is building
liquidity that means building volume.
This is using the volume right intraday.
Now because we've done such a big move
if we're going to move lower we need to
build volume out don't we? So how how do
we move lower?
If buyers come in here and they bid the
market up and more buyers come in here
and bid the market up and more buyers
come in here and bid the market up and
then this buyer gets stuck and we come
down and this buyer gets stuck and we
come down then these buyers are the
buildout stage. All right. And their
stops when we run their stops become
sellside and we use them to go lower.
That's how we build the liquidity.
Right? Same as here. This will be a big
pivot here. Right? I would imagine if we
come above this, lots of buyers will
chase in and it's very possible we use
their liquidity then to come back down.
All right, so we go choppy when we need
to build liquidity. We cannot move in a
straight line.
Am I on every day? Yes. 9:15 Eastern
into lunch.
What prop gives you 90% off Apex right
now?
You ever think about doing a backcountry
heli ride on the mountains in Alaska?
Don't worry about blocked roads. I don't
know. Why would I think about doing
that?
We often do a Vshape on rebounds. Uh I
would change that statement quite
drastically. often?
No. Vshapes are not often. Do they
happen? Yes. Are they often? No. When do
they happen? They happen when we have
something like this, right? So, if the
higher time frame,
let's say, uh,
we've moved down. Jesus Christ. Let's
say it's like this, right? Higher time
frame. Big extension. Big extension. Big
extension. and we move down here for the
first time and we left lots of limit
buyers waiting here. This is where
you'll get a Vshape. All right,
especially if it's a drastic move and a
drastic move and especially if this is
news and it's very very thin, right?
Then we'll be thin back up, right?
Whenever the market's thin one side, it
would go thin the other way. Uh if you
want an example of that,
All
right. Thin up. Straight up. This shot
here. Straight up and straight down. All
right. Because there's no structure.
Right. If we'd built structure out in
here,
right, then this on the way down would
have respected each level, but it didn't
have any structure. So, we're not going
to have structure on the way down
either.
Right? So Vshapes happen when we come
into areas where we have a huge buyer
waiting
to get involved.
How much discount do I get on your code
with funded next? I'm not sure at the
moment to be honest. I'm genuinely not
sure. Um but it's always the maximum
possible discount using FCT.
Oh, I see what you're saying. Super. I
got you now. I got you now. Yeah, my
snowboards are still outside my back
door right now. I still haven't been
able to use it. Um,
running out of time. I wouldn't mind
doing a Euro trip.
Would be nice.
Uh, the fun next giveaway will be on
YouTube. Uh, we will I always do at
least one a month. So, one a month in
YouTube, one a month on Discord, and I'm
going to start doing one a month on
Twitter as well. So, I'll probably do
that question on YouTube later today.
Probably do it later today.
Do I believe trading personal cash is
better than prop firm? I do. Yeah, of
course I do. But as long as you're, you
know,
confident in doing it, you don't want to
go blowing. If you're brand new, you
don't want to be doing that. You want
the cheapest lesson lessons possible
because you will have to learn hard
lessons.
You're welcome, Bradley.
Yes, Morgan. Yeah, that's pretty much
it, Morgan. If we leave a high volume
area, we try and trade down to the next
high volume area. That's that's pretty
much it.
Footprint won't show the limit orders.
No, no. You can buy some footprint
programs which will show you depth of
market like but Matt would will but
footprint um is showing you what's
happen happening inside each candle
right inside each I have this set to
delta. Not everyone has this. Some some
people will have this set up
differently. I only like to look at
delta but some people where is it will
have it like like a ladder like this.
All right. So they have it split or
maybe they have buy and sell
right like this. I like to see the
delta. So all I want is a really quick
look of where someone's stuck. That's
all I care about. You will hear me talk
about it all the time. Where are they
stuck? Where are they stuck? All I care
about is where someone is stuck. But you
will not see the limit orders on Delta.
You will see them on bookmap. You will
see them on the dom and level two.
What country do I live in? I live in
America.
Do I have friends working in banks?
What's their uh day trading strategy?
Yeah, I have a few friends. Uh most of
them use EMAs and to be honest, they are
taking massive positions. Um one of them
is a very big uh trader of copper.
Actually,
I went long 25300 on NASDAQ. Super down.
Can we recover the stop loss? Here we
go. Here we go, folks. We're going to
get that next hit. Here it comes.
Literally tagging into it. There you go.
Just taken. So, your final one finally
came out there. There you go. See the
reaction around here. And the only thing
left now. The only thing left now is the
bottom of this blue box. And under that
I will have to put some new lines in. We
are getting very very weak. This is like
what we're talking about potential black
swan type events where we go outside of
uh two standard deviations. The reason I
thought that was probable is because
this like we talked about four standard
deviations recently has only been nine
points. Normally it's about 3 to 4,000
points. So, green line now taken. That
is a
323 point trade if you took it. And I
would look for this next.
You got it. Oh, you all got it. Oh, I
love it. I love it. Nice work, folks.
Look at you guys. You must be mega rich.
Beautiful move. green line tags. So, we
can remove that green line now. We've
hit it. The only thing left now is the
bottom of the blue box. But, uh, like I
said, be done with it. I wouldn't, like
I said, I would not be long today. This
is a big sell day.
Is it possible to turn on subs? How do I
do that? Is there a way for me to do
that? I didn't know it wasn't done. Um,
customization.
If you tell me where I can do it, I will
do it. I didn't know it wasn't done. Let
me have a look.
Language set to English, United States.
If you tell me where to do it, I I'll do
it, guys. I can't see it for the live
stream. Here you go, guys. Almost bottom
of blue box.
Almost bottom of blue blocks. You do not
have to buy this. So, do not just buy
this for the sake of buying it. Why?
We're breaking away from all the trapped
buyers from three months worth of
volume. Like, even if it works for you,
it's just not a trade. It's not a valid
trade.
Yeah, on the daily now. Oh, it's making
me stay here way too long. Remember on
the daily now
we're starting to break away. Uh it's
very possible now we can trade 24800s.
Remember we talked about that 24800s is
possible now today. Uh based on these
nodes, look how we're leaving all this
volume. I've talked about this so many
times on stream, especially up here. We
left this volume. We're about to leave.
This is yearly. This is based on the
last 12 months. Understand that if we
leave all these participants stuck from
the last 12 months, we're going to keep
trading down this level. Then we get
thin this level. Guess what's there? A
big stop and the 200 day. That is my
target. That is my big old target that
I'd like to see hit.
Almost there. What is this blue box? Uh,
it is the pivot right down to the 25th
of November. Is the 25th, isn't it?
Yeah, 25th of November.
What order flow software do I think is
best? Um,
I use Quant Tower, but I feel there's
something missing. I I don't know what
you could get for Quant to Tower. I'm
sure there's something really good for
Quant Tower. Um, I use uh City by
um,
Twin Peaks is what I use. Okay. So, bit
of a bid in front of the bottom of this
blue box here. Probably look to resell
it around 46es. I would not be selling
these lows. Okay. I would not be selling
these lows, but there's a bit of a edge
now being developed down here. There's
the drive back in towards 46es. If they
want to resell it and finish this and
clean this up, they will.
Nice. Nice work everyone. Lots of you
got that. That's awesome.
What account size best? Small accounts,
25 or 50K account? 50k count's great.
They're still rejecting this new shelf
now where we just broke down from.
Remember, we're thin up. Don't want it
reclaiming all of this. Otherwise, it's
going to come right up into here. But if
they keep rejecting this, they can
potentially come down to the lows. Let's
just check to the low of day of auction.
So, they're coming for this imbalance
here where we just sold from. It's not
bad excess at the low. So, this is key.
Now, this is the imbalance where we just
sold from. Why does it do that? Right.
So, we're trading back into where we
just sold from. If they resell it,
they'll come back to these lows. Now,
do not I, like I said, I would not be
longing this. You're asking for it. Here
we go.
And a break now will take you to the
850s.
ES, by the way, is finally taking out
its key levels. So, ES did that move.
Remember, we talked about the green
lines on ES. It needs to take out those
green lines. And look at there. There
you go. So ES now completed the move
that we did at the start of the day and
if ES stays weak under this you will see
continuation on NQ.
Why can't orderflow get students get
into the discord? Because it the discord
is like it teaches how I trade in
general like how I position myself what
I'm looking for the patterns all this
stuff. If you trade order flow and
you're constantly looking for reversals,
you're going to really hurt students who
are like continuation traders if you
like. So the order flow teaches you how
to trade order flow, but it doesn't
teach you on like the setups necessarily
that we're looking for. Um, so it would
just it would be problematic to the
students in Discord. I think it would
cause too many I thought about it a few
times, but I don't want students trading
like different directions. I want them
to support each other. It creates like
the best possible uh environment for
them to trade together, especially when
I'm not there. That's the only reason
why.
Well, and that there you go. And if and
if people pay less and get in, then
everyone else be upset. Yeah, fair
enough. Hadn't even thought of that,
Adam.
an influence. Look at VIX. VIX now doing
that breakout. All right, Vick's
absolutely screaming. So, your next
target is here, folks. This will now be
a
367 point winner. And it's coming. It's
coming. And I would say you will have
wish orders down here. This this is
getting very very very heavy. Now, there
is a gap fill right from 24700
down to 24560
as well. Right. There's a gap, an
untested gap from the 24th of November
as well. I've never used Jigsaw. I can't
comment. Can't comment.
The zones, I just draw them based on
like pivots and volume, guys. Pivots and
volume. There's lots of stuff for free
on my YouTube, but you you can go
through all of that. I'm not going to do
it now. Uh, and otherwise you can uh, of
course, do the course.
All right, I'm going to wait for this to
hit and then I'm going to get off
stream. I just want this to hit for you
guys.
You can hold runners beyond this. Uh, it
is possible. Like I said, it might well
come down into here.
Might well come down here. I'll do this
as gray because this is a gap.
Almost there.
Almost there. Some bids down here to be
filled. I think you're going to get it.
Here we go.
Come on. Get under it. I want to make
sure this is accurate.
Oh, it's accurate. All right. Get under
it. Here it goes, folks. Here it goes.
Get your wish orders underneath in case
they really snap. It could be really
nasty. Pretty much tagged there. Missed
it by a tick or two.
Come on. Just snap that last bit. Just
snap that last bit. Mainly so I can get
off stream.
So close. So so close.
Yeah, exactly. Monthly lows. Exactly it.
We're right back to November.
We're We're so far back now. If we trade
under this, we can we can We're looking
at November 21st after this. If we trade
under this. Here we go. Tagged. Tagged.
Tagged. There you go. Tagged. Boom.
Right. Wish orders. Now, if you get if
you get really nasty, it's good night
sweetheart time down into all of this.
Uh, notable relative strength today in
Netflix. Those that were thinking about
the swing position with me. Notable
relative strength. I'll give you a
readout and you'll see what I mean.
Tesla 4.90% down. Nvidia 4.24% down.
Microsoft third of a percent up. Meta
3.25% down. Google 2.70% down. Amazon
2.40% down. Apple 1.8 85% up and still
long Apple up over $70 a share right now
and Netflix 0.75% up. So a nice sort of
hold on Netflix. Interesting interesting
relative strength, right?
Uh I am Yeah, exactly Mike. Exactly, my
friend. Like I said, I'm still long. I
think 208 is my average price on Apple.
Uh, so the next the next stop is down
here, right? I think if we if we're
going to continue to get weak, this is
where you're looking to trade into this
gray box. All right, if we're going to
continue to be weak, we can extend down
into here if they're going to be really
violent with it. Um, I would not be a
new money short. Now, think about where
we were shorting this morning. Our first
short this morning was at 25 315s, then
25300, then 2500s. We're now trading
24800s.
All right, we're way way down. We are
way down. We're 630 points down on the
session.
All right, so this is possible. Yeah,
we're getting heavy. The reason is
because we're leaving the volume, isn't
it? The reason is because we're leaving
trap volume. These are the days you want
to be aggressive.
Um, all right folks, I am done and I'm
going to get out of here. Great session.
Um, I've got an appointment
in 20 minutes and then I'll be in
Discord afterwards. Uh, just sit in the
shorts and let them work or just leave
it alone. Definitely don't be looking to
try and play in the counter trend long.
All right, we are in a continuation day.
I'm going to Last time I'm going to say
this. All right,
we had a failed breakout
of the highs last week.
We came back to mean. We failed to
recover those highs. Yesterday was a
massive sell day. Today is the
continuation. It is very viable. You can
see we're already coming to this. It is
viable. We come into this over the next
week or so. All right. Do not be stupid
trying to bid it back up. Okay? Don't
try and be a hero. You are going to end
up a very upset person who has to go to
bed crying at night. Do not be the hero.
Please. Please don't do it. Um,
is there codes for the course or is it
900? It's not 900. It's $645.
It should be $699, but 645 if you bundle
it together, it's a bit cheaper if you
get uh the volume order flow and the
main course. Um,
all right.
All right. Big love everyone. Um, good
luck in your afternoon session. Those in
Discord, I'll be back this afternoon. If
you want to support uh the stream um
then you can use my codes that helps me
out. All right, everything underneath.
All my codes are underneath uh for all
your favorite prop firms. FCT is the
main one to use. Other than take profit
trader, you can use code flow zone. And
uh yeah, I'll see you back tomorrow
morning. We'll see what we get. We'll
see how uh how nutsy this market gets
today and see where we close. And
everyone, Discord, I'll see you soon.
Peace and love, everyone. See you
tomorrow morning.