Morning everyone.
Good morning everyone. Hope you're doing
well. Hope you had a good afternoon's
trading. Maybe some of you have traded
some of GlobeEx overnight. And before we
get into the charts, I do talk about
this a lot, but make sure you're doing
it. Go through your morning prep even
before you get to these charts, right?
Have you had your tea or your coffee or
your water? Have you done your
visualization or your morning meditation
or gone to the gym or even gone for a
walk? Whatever is part of your morning
routine. I cannot tell you the
importance of sticking to that morning
routine or maybe for you it's an
afternoon or evening routine, but you
have to be sticking to that routine. All
right, as always, we're going to start
off on the daily. We are starting off
with an outside bar, which is good news.
All right, so yesterday set the tone. So
far, we've drifted outside. Um, this
right here, this volume profile we're
looking at right here is pinned to this
all-time high. All right? And I want you
to just take note of the amount of
liquidity we have built in here. All
right? We have another level down here.
We're basically split into two halves
here. All right? And we are struggling
to find acceptance over 26,000. We are
struggling to find acceptance underneath
25,200.
And we are starting to build a huge
amount of liquidity between 26,000 and
25,600.
All right. So sort of 400 point range in
here. And the rest of the time we're in
range here. No acceptance outside either
side of it. All right. So we're coming
back to test this same level. Now we do
we do have Ballinger bands which are
starting to trade upside. All right. And
a 5day which will need to turn around.
It would take a couple days after what
happened last week. And if we do that,
we can go back looking for this again.
All right. So, what are the
opportunities today? We want to be very
careful, don't we? As we come towards
this edge where we keep failing and we
had a look above and fail. All right. We
want to be very careful. If we measure
from that look above and fail to the
low, right, we can see we're right in
the golden pocket. We're right in the
edge of the value area high based on
that pin from October 30th. All right.
So we want to be careful thinking about
longs up here. All right, the location
is not ideal for longs. We are in a
range. However, if we start to break out
and hold above and base, there is an
argument for this now to be a long. Same
as we had here. This time it failed. All
right, but we fail the lows. We're back
up. All right, so there's an argument
for this move here. Right, there is an
argument for it. You want to be very
careful for this move here back down
again. So, we're going to need to look
for location and momentum. We're going
to have to respect the range that we're
in there. Best way to do that is move
down into the hourly chart. Uh let's
move this up a little bit just so we can
get a bit more depth on here. Okay, so
this is the current week developing
profile. You can see
when we say we're not on an inside,
we're not on an inside daily bar, but we
are most certainly inside the previous
week. All right, here's the previous
week value area high. Here's previous
week value area low. Here's previous
week point of control. These are our key
levels. It is as simple as that. We are
going to respect them. So, we expect
right 26 down 261
26,100.
There we go. You got it out eventually.
All right. To be resistance, we expect
that to potentially reject. Now, if we
break above and reclaim that, we have
some liquidity here. You can see it's
much much thinner. So, I'd say over 150s
and the squeeze is on. All right. So, a
hold of 100 or a hold of yeah 100, a
break of 150 and the squeeze is on.
Right. A look above 100 into 150 even
and a fail. And we would expect that to
be a failed break above the previous
week and a rotation probably back down
into sort of these 800s. Okay. So, we're
watching that. Traps, right? traps can
live. We can see we've had three drives
here. We want to be very, very careful.
One, two, three. Right? Bullish traps
can live underneath this swing. I want
you to be aware of that. We're very thin
under here. Okay? So, there's two
arguments that can happen down here.
One, we flush, we fail to reclaim, and
we rotate right the way back down,
repairing this thin structure. Very,
very possible that we can do that. So,
we're going to pay close attention to
these sort of 900s down to, I don't
know, 800s, 850. The other option is
that they come for a little stop hunt.
Maybe they don't even make it all the
way and they do something dirty like
this. They come in here, breakout shorts
come flying in looking for this move
here, and they go, "Nope, f you
everyone. We just wanted your stops, and
we're going back to the upside." Right?
These are the areas I'm looking at, and
I'm willing to play both ways. And if
you're new here and you're like, "Well,
what's the bias? What's the bias?" Well,
the bias is we're inside the previous
week. That's the bias, right? So, we're
not going to say that we're going
straight upside or straight downside.
We're going to respect this massive node
from previous week, which is also from
many, many weeks before. All right?
We're trading in 1 2 3 4 five. You could
even argue this one. Six, seven. Seven
weeks of volume we're trading in right
now. So, we're going to respect that
volume. We're not going to be arrogant
enough to say the market has to do this
or has to do that, right? We're going to
be willing to play both sides. So the
opportunities today are this, are this,
are this, and are this. All right, these
are the opportunities. I guess the other
opportunity is it goes f you to all of
us and just does that. It is possible.
It is possible it could do that if it
wants. All right, so that's what we're
looking at this morning. These these pa
things here. So we're going to take big
note as we come drift down into some of
these. All right, need to get a bit of a
move on here. Let's have a look at what
happened in GlobeEx overnight. Let move
this down.
All right. So, if we think about what we
did yesterday, we reclaimed that all
important 20-day. Remember, this was
lower Ballinger band tag. This is mean
reversion. This is 20-day to 5day. We
talked about that rotation a lot. Get
above 5day. Holding above 5day now. And
we will wait and see. So, what we had
overnight was just a slow drift high.
That's all it is. So a little pullback
which held this key volume node. Asia
came in, bought the bids. London sold
the highs against this in front of this
old level front running it back down to
the 5day. Caught a bid inside London
back down to the 5day again. We're
watching this level here. This level
here is the big overunder. All right,
that's what we're watching. All right,
let's move into the lower time frame.
Look at some of the ETFs, etc., etc.
Get rid of this guy.
Uh, starting off with ES, it's going to
be the same story. We're very close to
alltime highs here, folks. All right,
very, very close to alltime highs. You
can see this big shelf being developed
here. It needs to get above 17s.
Basically, you're looking for a base
above 17s on ES. Make it really, really
clear, right? Every time it's come up
here, it's failed. All right. And the
low of that is 31. So, that's your
rotation. All right.
If it gets above here and it can base,
all right, then you're looking for that
upside shot. Simple as that. If we want
to have a look at that on the spiders on
the cash market,
same kind of story. They're probably
looking for the 700s. All right, it will
look exactly the same on the cash
market. It looks exactly the same. So,
it's just a question of can they get
going for that breakout over all-time
highs or that breakout above the base.
So, we can we just put a little alert in
here. Thanks very much. So that we can
remember that is the high, isn't it? It
is indeed. Make sure going left. Yes.
Okay. So we put price alert in there in
case we do break out. QQQ. Same story.
You can see this the level we're trying
to come and back test. Right. This is
where buyers are stuck. We must remember
this on QQQ on the cash market. We have
buyers stuck here until we get
acceptance back inside I'd say of 32s.
All right. Until we find acceptance back
inside of 32s.
Let's draw that out.
Let's just quickly put one of these on
here. Just want to make sure. Yeah, 32s
is a good level. So, let's put a price
alert on there. Um, I would imagine
there's some gamma in here. So, let's
add an alert in there.
QQQ 32 reclaim just so we've got that
ready.
All right. So, until QQQ's get inside of
that, we know that the buyers are stuck
up here. All right. This is the
rotation. We can build this out here.
This can be the head, left shoulder,
right shoulder. It might need to do a
little dunk and then what happens in
here becomes key. If it does this, we're
going to expect bullish moves. If we
come up, poke, reject, do this, then
we're coming straight back downside. All
right, Dixie still trying to find a bit
of a bid here. Let's just zoom out of
this. Right, you can see same kind of
story into a key pivot. All right, so if
you were long Dixie, you should be
selling a good chunk of your position
now because again, this is same thing.
That's where trap buyers are. If we find
acceptance in this, then you get a
continuation squeeze. But at the moment,
you want to be selling some of your
Dixie into that move. We can have a
quick look at metals. All right, we are
looking for a trade upside here. Um, and
then to resell into for failed
followrough. So, we're getting close.
So, I'm interested in this kind of move
here to see if buyers get stuck and we
get a retest of somewhere down towards
these lows is what my expectation would
be on the metals. Same here. Same kind
of move for any of you trading metals.
All right, this is your standard first
bounce. Right, there's your trap.
There's your big flush moment. We expect
to drive somewhere into here ideally and
then a resell down and you're taking
some profits there. And if you get the
continuation, fantastic.
Okay, VIX,
really got to get a move on here. Still
in the channel or just outside of the
channel. Still finding a bid in the low
teens. So, pretty positive there for
VIX. Looks pretty good. All right, Apple
started to find a bid yesterday. Let's
have a look here. Slight gap down on
Apple. We'd be watching this pivot into
here to hold. 65s to hold on Apple. 65
holds, then we look good for
continuation. Amazon, same kind of
story. Bit of a gap up. This is the same
pivot, all right, that we're looking for
at Apple. The one that held yesterday,
you're looking for that same hold today.
It's it can might undercut it and do
that. That's fine. What you don't want
is for Amazon to lose that and snap all
the way down. Goo, let's have a look at
the GooG. Remember, some of these got
earnings this week. G big drive up
anticipation for earnings which are
coming this week. Maybe we can pull back
and hold 45s and continue higher. It
looks like they're pricing in earnings
nice and early. Very very similar to
last week. We priced in earnings early
and then sold it off Meta um being
priced in early. There you go. There's
the big move on on Meta. We can think
about that. You can think about this
whole move right. Are we pulling back?
Yeah. Still very very bullish right on
Meta. I'm still long Meta. Looking to
see if we can get up into the 760s right
now. Microsoft that looks terrible. Very
well might undercut here. So Microsoft's
got two opportunities here. One little
trap down here or two what it looks more
like. One two starting to fail and
continuation lower. If we're going to
look lower can have a little look we
might even come down all the way down
into this little zone here into the low
400s. I will be looking to scoop some on
M on Microsoft if we move too much lower
cuz that is a big move off the highs
now.
Yeah, 24% if we can get down into here.
What date was that? Feb. Yeah, I'm
interested in that. If it comes too much
lower, I will it will per my interest.
Nvidia.
We still in the dance in Nvidia. Looks
by the looks of it. Yeah, still in a
sideways dance coming to the lower side
of the range. It's got a pivot down
here. That looks messy. Not something
I'll be touching right now as a day
trade. Tesla
still in its range. Uh starting to
potentially build out more of a base
here now. So, it might have just walked
this up. Uh didn't lose this shelf. So,
if they can hold 22s, you're looking for
a drive up to 40s. If they lose 22s,
probably a flush down to take out those
lows at 14s. We can have a quick look at
some of the rest of the market. Uh
Netflix still waiting to see if we can
come down into these 70s would be ideal.
And AMD
big drive yesterday, earnings on the
way. Let's see if it takes out these
pivot highs. Very, very possible in
these markets. Uh Palanteer obviously
got going this morning off earnings as
well, folks. All right, so that should
have you pretty much covered.
this in.
There we go. All right, guys. So, this
is the level that I'm interested in.
This gray box down here, all these boxes
up here. All right. I don't really want
to trade between this. So, if we come
down here and we wash and reclaim, I
want to get long. If we come down here
and lose this gray box, uh, then there's
an argument for a drift down to 700s and
600s. All right, that's what we are
looking at here this morning.
Um,
please do me a favor. Smash that like
button nice and early so I don't have to
talk about it anymore.
Let's get this up. We got a couple
minutes left. We have news coming at
10:00. We should say that before I
forget as well. News coming at 10:00 and
the job openings. All right, job
openings delayed due to shutdown. Okay,
we maybe we're not getting them then. We
will see.
This government, what a joke. What a
joke.
Yeah, that's why that's why the news
disappeared from the calendar.
What can you do? Eh,
I don't remember time when we went into
two potential shutdowns. Hopefully they
they won't um do it as long as last
time. It was ridiculous last time. Went
on far too long, didn't it?
Far far too long.
Yeah, you're right. They're not They're
saying they're not going to release
Jolts. You're absolutely right.
Okay, so watching this this morning, I'm
going to watch these 870s and 825s
are the levels I'm watching. And if we
start losing 825s and failing to reclaim
it, we can get down into 700 and 600.
I'm just drawing this out on my screen.
Make sure I've got a node marked out for
sevens in case we want to take this
trade down lower side.
Okay team, good luck. Here comes the
open.
10 seconds.
There's gray box key. Remember, keep an
eye on that big big level.
Here comes the drift. Morning drift
down.
Globeex into GloEx into these 900s.
See if we can trade any lower than this
would be nice.
That film previous day high would be all
the way down here at 860s.
Um, previous day point of control 72s.
Previous week point control 60s.
Previous day close 50s.
Previous day value area low 825. So
looking for a little snap into here and
then see if we can trap sellers. Ideally
they come a bit lower than what they are
at the moment. But here we go. Maybe
not.
Mixed bag on the mag. Nvidia's just gone
red to green. They're starting to find a
bid already here.
Watching this
very very carefully now into previous
day value area high. If they get
acceptance over this then technically
speaking we can drift up here. It's not
the ideal setup. We want to be buying
from down here ideally.
Right that New York open right at New
York you up.
Yes, nice drive off Globeet right to its
uh VWOP to start the day there.
Not getting through VWAP or previous day
high yet.
Ideally, we want to be thinking about
moves down here. Trying to be patient.
Let it come down to those levels.
Here we go. This is looking better,
right? Perfect. Let's see how we act
when we get down here now. So, coming
towards previous day point of control,
previous week point of control. Can we
trap some sellers? Lots of selling
happening. Go down here. I'd like a bit
of a shove lower first.
And we swipe a bit lower first.
There's previous day point control
coming up. Almost there.
Come on. You got to come lower first.
Liquidity
lower. Is there liquidity low? Lots of
liquidity lower. We should come lower
here. Please, please come lower. Don't
just shove it straight back up yet.
Back to these 900s. They're reselling
900s. Hopefully, we break lower now. Not
in the short, guys. I'm waiting to see
how we act once we get into these key
levels that I'm looking at. Some of you
might have taken that short down here,
which is fine. That's just not what I'm
looking for.
finding a reaction off there so far.
Come on. Further down, please. Fill all
these guys down here.
Here
they come. They're coming for them now.
All right. So, watching ES as well for
gap fill potential.
Getting close.
Starting to per my interest now.
Nice. Here we go into these areas and
we'll see if we trap down here or even
under the area. If not, if we stay heavy
and reject it, I'm happy to play that
short further down.
Not quite a gap though. QQQ almost
there. Spy not there. VIX has filled it
gap as well. So the uh ES and the SPY
relative strength here on this flush
down right gap now filled PDC now
tagged. So only thing left previous day
value area low and we have this shelf at
the bottom of this gray box. Now do we
trap under this shelf or are we going to
fail under and give it back? So there's
a couple options here. Either we're
going to do we talked about this
premarket. We're either going to do one
of these and a straight flush down or
we're going to do some nasty little trap
and do this run back up. I'm happy to
play either. I'm just going to let it
tell me what it wants to do. But this is
the area where I'm interested in trading
in and around here.
Coming right into higher time frame
algo, previous day value area low.
Waiting to see if sellers start to get
stuck down here, which is starting to
happen. Already starting to see an
acceleration back up. I'm long now.
Trimming some straight away because
there's sellers here at 75. See if we
can get acceptance through 75 and 80s.
Big imbalance into 80s. So trimming a
little bit more. See if there's a
squeeze through it. Is the imbalance
into 80s.
Stop moving up to previous week point of
control
out there on the runner. See if they
recap lower now.
All right. You dirty bger. How many days
in a row they're going to tap me out and
do it? You dirty dirty bugger.
Oh my gosh, it is funny. It is funny.
All right, they're still adding
liquidity down here at 25s watching
this.
That is funny.
All right, some big sellers have come
down here
trying to force us to break lower. ES is
trying to reclaim New York open.
We're just dancing between previous week
point of control and previous day point
of control around here somewhere right
now. This is slightly off. I think this
is uh what this here 72s
somewhere like that
and value area low down here. Traps can
be under here. It can also be a big
flush down to here if they stay heavy.
So, I'm willing to play both sides.
Nvidia selling like crazy. Not really.
It's 0.82% down. That is definitely not
selling like crazy.
It's lost 1.54.
It's uh No, that's not a crazy sale.
Vida can move 10 plus dollars very
easily.
Okay, still waiting to see if they trap
or flush low. They're still adding
liquidity lower at the moment, but maybe
one more flush down before they do
something else with it. Back to this gap
or maybe they come and trade into these
26s. We do have lots of resting uh
orders down there.
And they're looking for these resting
orders into 25s now.
Here they come. They're looking for this
move into previous day value area low.
This is where the traps will live under
here. Otherwise, if we stay heavy,
retest, stay heavy, I will be playing
short side down to 700600. But if we
trap down here, I will be willing to
look for longs.
Let's see folks. Gap now filled on the
ES. Not quite filled on the spiders, but
it's close. Gap filled on the ES. Not
quite filled on the spiders, but it is
close.
right into value area low from
yesterday. Okay, so we're watching this
shelf now. Remember, zoom out. If we
lose this shelf, they can trap. If they
uh if they want to trap down here, they
will. If they want to do, let me draw it
for the team. Remember, we talked about
this pre-market. Please let me draw it
for the team. I'm running out of time.
All right, the trap will be something
like this. The continuation will be a
fade back down to this. All right, these
are the opportunities right now. If they
just do a straight flush 100 points
down, there's other rule we can do with
it.
So, see if they trap down here or not.
Selling still coming in for now. And
they're adding liquidity lower to 800.
So, they might want a deeper wash here
by the looks of it.
What is the YouTube OBS? Can you guys
still hear me? OBS give me an alert
there. You can still hear me. All right.
Reclaim a value area low here. No follow
through underneath.
Buyers are trying to step in here. Can
they force a squeeze back up is the
question.
They're trying. They're trying to
reclaim. Very very uh tentative here.
Watching this.
Buyers need to break 850s really
otherwise they can be still downside.
They are trying to come in here though.
The buyers don't think they're doing a
very good job right now. We're going to
need to get it above 850 and then we can
think about what's what.
SPY filled its gap now. So, we have
efficient markets now.
What are we going to do? Are we trapping
to go back higher or we going to see
that continuation?
Still adding liquidity at 800s. Think
they still want to come into these 800s.
There you go. They're trying to force to
fill these players down at 800s. There
are some old imbalances down there.
There are actually some imbalances down
at 68 and 55 if they really want to go a
bit deeper down into here. So, how we
now in this gray box will be key. If we
trap enough shorts down here and the
buyers come and reclaim, passive buyers
step in and reclaim, then you'd expect
an upside move. If we push and fail,
then we're going to expect 700s. So,
waiting to see if we start to clear 50s
or not. So far, pops are starting to
fail here this morning. Can they get
back above 40s and 50s for a potential
squeeze back up?
Vo on the session currently 65. So
reclaim that would be some serious
strength.
Am I still long? No, of course not still
long.
I told you level was long. I told you
the partial and I told you where my stop
was. I'm still waiting now. Waiting to
see if we break 45s and start to go
squeezy.
Looks like they still want these 800s.
There we go. All right, tapping into
45s. No acceptance through it yet.
Buyers got caught on that last shove up.
Sellers still want to cover into 800s at
the moment. And someone is just starting
to add way more size down at 85. So,
they're trying to drag this market lower
now. still waiting. No way I'm going to
frontr run this. If they can't reclaim
and we can go and fill all these
imbalances, which we are now starting to
do
800 break will lead to 770, 750 and
700s. Big seller at 25s now.
They're being a bit more aggressive on
the tape here this morning with the
cells. They're starting to really step
in and try and hammer it.
Maybe sevens is possible. That retest is
not enough for me to take short. No way.
This feels too trappy down here for me
to even consider that
big buyer came in at 8:05 there.
We do have excess on this low for the
first time today. Big seller stepping in
here at 810. I'm interested at the
moment. This is a battle starting to
develop down here. All right, 10's got
filled.
adding liquidity 780 77
yeah 775s
buyer currently is trapped at 804 804
and 809 are the first key levels for
buyers to reclaim otherwise we're going
to keep washing because they keep coming
in and unsuccessfully driving highs have
a look at the mag still in a wash comes
to 75 so the next lot of imbalances down
there.
Got a feeling we're going to trap here.
It's just when
back to value area low. It's the 15s
again. We're back above that buyer who
got caught at fives.
Value area low currently 20s. I'd say a
reclaim of 30s now can start to trigger
more upside.
Not just a tap into it, an actual
reclaim. Still trading between these
levels. 75. Still looking to get filled
here. These sellers looking to cover
into 75. Let's see if they're legit or
if they just spoof and drop it. No.
Straight through them all. They got
smacked. Absolutely smacked. Okay, so
700s. It is
right back down to 700s. That is not a
retest that I can short. That is a
horrible move. Cannot short that. That
is a shame. That's fast moving. Oh,
great. And now bookmap can't even keep
up the data. Thanks, CME.
Well, that's useful.
That must have been too quick for the
market because even CME can give me
data. But man, there we go. It's coming
back now. All right. 725s
into this gray box like we talked about.
That is not a retest for me to short.
That is a horrible, horrible move.
Nothing I can do with that.
This would have been nice if they
actually built out some structure. If
they build out something like this for
us to fade down into here, but that is
uh there's nothing I can do with that,
folks. No, nothing missed there. That's
not a trade setup.
They're still selling this. Still
buyers. There's a 200 lot here at 25.
They're still not done with this yet.
Where did that big seller came in? And
what was his size? 430 lot came in at
75. So that's going to be the level.
That's going to be the level. This is
the pullback. We can measure this
pullback from the low as well. We can
remember this can still be the inverse
right shoulder. We're into well 50%
pullback will be all the way down into
600 still.
Just make sure you're zoomed out. Think
about what we're doing here. We talked
about this this morning. This right
here, okay, we can build out liquidity.
We can wash these guys. If they reclaim
this, we will go higher. It is possible
we come right down into this. But this
node here is important. We marked it out
for a reason. This gray node, this gray
node, this gray node, this is where
we're finding a bid right now. We have
not really back tested any key level yet
for me. We've not back tested anything
yet.
Yeah, it was there was a data issue
there. Uh, for sure. For sure. On that
big lot. But when that 400 lot came in,
he was 165 lot. He actually chased. He
went 65, 165, 326,
and 206. All right. We're coming back to
where he was. All right. So 73s is the
level. Watching this. If they start to
reclaim, there's a squeeze and a back
test towards the 800s here, which is
what we're starting to do.
Starting to see this lift a little bit.
Um, so big sellers started to come in
here like we talked about the 73s. So if
they resell, we go lower. If they are
done with it, then you'll see a bid back
up now towards the 800s.
So 73s, this is where the sellers came
in 73s. Where is that? 73s. This is
where they were owned before. We can see
it on map. They started at 73. Well,
they started at 809's all the way to 73.
So watching this now for the counter
trend back up. Here we go. moving up
with this now as we start to drift in
towards the 800s
and if we start to reclaim buyers got
trapped to 803s. So if we get through
803s there'll be a back test of the gray
box above. So we might well come back up
into here right 803s is a big level
803's right here. If we get through that
there's a back test of that that we can
build liquidity out between this or they
can be extra dirty and have done a 100
point swipe and reclaim.
So, longing this at the moment. Small
size. I'm going to use the guy at 54 as
my stop because he got trapped at 54s.
Here we go. Watching this. It's the
first time I've been long today. Peeling
some off into these 800s in front of
800s. Here we go. Lovely. All right.
Through the buyers now. This is strong.
So, we're watching for previous day
value air low to see if we find
acceptance back through this now. So,
long from down here. Trimming some into
flow zones through the 83s. We are now
watching to find if we back test and
find acceptance through or not. You can
see where the buyers came in. Right, we
want to be careful. This is where the
buyers came in. Right, we're going to
sell most of our profits into here. If
we reclaim all this, we've got room to
go.
So, stuck where those buyers came in.
Peeling most of my profits off there.
Okay, let's see how much we can lift
now.
So, I would say sellers are stuck under
54s. So, as long as buyers protect 54s
and if they reclaim the 800s, there is
upside shot here. Here's 800s. So, we're
watching for reclaim of previous day
value area low now
into this gray box. This is the first
retest of this gray box. So, they can
resell up into here. Remember they can
absolutely resell up into here and our
buyers stepping on. This is a big deep
trap this morning so far and it will
confirm as a trap if we get over all of
this. We can watch VWAP and previous day
value area low.
Come on. Lift it. Lift it. Lift it. Lift
it. Watching these flow zones. They
might very well resell this area. This
is where the big buyers came earlier
where we are now. Uh the next node we
got to get through is 8:30. Through 830s
we can trade 865s.
So watching 830s they might very well
reject this. This is where buyers got
caught. I will stay long as as long as
we are able to protect 755ish
under that. I will cut.
There is liquidity lower still. So we
haven't pulled back and held yet. So if
they hold anywhere from 76s down to 55s,
I'll feel good that we might go for a
resqueeze here. If they can't hold,
nothing you can do. So there's the tap
into 76s there or thereabouts.
Good hold so far. Back to point of
control. We're building out volume down
here. We need to find acceptance through
this to drift up into here.
big area here where the buyers got
stuck. Can we trade through it? Can we
start to reclaim
back to 76? Remember 76s to sort of 54s
is where buyers will need to hold.
Failing to hold that, we will move
lower.
ES back inside its PDC. ES doing a good
job here. Q's uh slower Microsoft weak
today.
To see if we can get back into that gray
box or not.
Back into these sort of 76s under here.
Probably go 54s for a check. So we have
to see if they can hold here or not.
76s. So, we've built 76s. Only next
level it can protect now is 54s. Under
that, there will be a new low of day.
So, coming back down to test those 54s
now by the looks of it. Here you go.
I'm about to be stopped out
out
and potentially new low of day here.
Cannot rule out a new low of day here,
folks. cannot rule it out.
If they break under this, then all the
way down here is possible. They break
under this gray box, all the way down
here. So, I had a go at it. Give it a
time to uh settle down for a minute now.
Staying heavy here, though. QQQ into its
20day as well. Man, we're right back to
the mean. This is awful.
This is awful. All right. All right.
Well, if they don't hold this node, then
uh we should drift all the way back down
to 600. If they've just wicked me out
again, I'm going to be very upset.
Well, you know why you've got that
wrong? You hate these weird trend days
with no structure, right? Your your
first part of you getting that wrong is
the first bit. Trend day. It's We're not
in a trend, guys. I don't know how many
times I have to say this on stream. Zoom
out. Where's the trend? We're in a
range. We're in a giant range. We've
been in a giant range since the 5th of
November, right? We're in a giant range.
They are protecting these lows. They
washed me out. Um, from 54s, they traded
10 points deeper. Buyers are now caught
at 85 up to 809. So, I'll wait to see if
we get back above that. No, I'm not
sure, Alli. No, I left the short today.
I was waiting to see if we'd offer a
trap long here or here. I took this long
here. I'm out now. I'll wait to see if
we want to come back into here and
reclaim. If we start offer this squeeze
here, I'll look for the longs. If we do
this, there'll be a short back down into
here. I'm watch stalking this now for
longs. And I think we might very well
trap today, but we will see. They're
going to have to get back through 85s
and 810s for me to be interested.
I was willing to play short outside of
that gray box if we did a nice retest
and we didn't. We just didn't. Right. If
we' done this, I would have been short
down into here. This was We talked about
this pre-market, but this I can't short
that. I mean, that you can't do anything
with that. It's like 70 point candle
without a retest of anything. There's
just nothing you can do with it. It's
just one of those. That's why I hate
ranges cuz they
unless you get the very top or very
bottom of the range, this is what
happens.
We're building out a ton of liquidity
down here. Now,
still building out. This thing is still
building out.
And it's still got to fill the guy at
700 164 lot sat down there.
Delta's in line. There's nothing wrong
with the delta. I'm looking at delta on
a five minute. It's uh
pretty normal.
Okay, more big sellers coming in.
They're trying to get down to 700 by the
look of it.
Trying to get down into here. If they
lose this, then we have this all the way
down here. That would be a full rotation
for the second day in a row. Sir,
be nice if market makers could make
their mind up and move us out of these
channels on the daily because I don't
like trading these edges. So, I'm not
going to have much to do this year if
this is all we're going to do. All
right, back into this gray box. They're
looking for 700. Like I said, there's
165 lot down here.
Here they come into this guy at 700. If
they lose this, we have previous week
close down at 669.
Previous week close 669. Previous day
value area low all the way down at 605.
So we would have and then previous week
value area low 72. So we would have
rotated almost a full week, one full
week yesterday and a full week today as
well. If we get down into these sub600s,
it's mental. I mean, at least you got
volatility here. All right, 700
stacking. 230 lot. They will fill this
guy. He's just stacking up here. They
probably wash through him. Here they go.
So, he's just been filled. He's got 100
left. They're going to fill in. There's
no way they leave all that. Surely you
don't leave all that. He's rebidding
here at 700. I cannot imagine they leave
all of this. Big big selling coming in
down here, folks. and probably going to
get to previous week close if they trade
under it which was 67 670s
this gray line.
So we know massive sellers came in at
700. Huge huge huge sellers came in at
700. Here come the six towards the 670s.
Here's 670s incoming
700. the big level if they reclaim that
now
and SPY into its 5day
almost into that 670s it's 85s they
probably should come for 670s now at
this point I'm kicking myself absolutely
attack
I mean, the daily just looks
so bad.
So bad on the daily. It's insane. All
right, previous week closed, that gray
line now tagged there or thereabouts.
There's still liquidity lower. They're
still adding liquidity lower right now.
This is pretty mad how they're uh
operating here.
They might come right down into here.
Edge of current week value. It's mental.
Oh, should I have faded that pullback?
Maybe. I would have rather faded in
here. We're missing levels. ES is being
very, very well behaved by comparison.
Very, very well behaved.
Don't want to get long in this unless
there's a reaction down here. Not going
to trade in no man's land. The reason
I'm being patient this morning now just
had that one attack. You have to
understand what we are doing here. We
went straight up. We built liquidity. I
was waiting to see if they'd trap here
for the fade. No. I was willing to do a
retest for the fade. No, we've just gone
straight down. There's not a lot I can
do with that, folks. And we're coming
back into this node down here now. This
edge. If we lose that, then we're just
going to give back everything that we
did yesterday and more. And if you want
to talk about the daily or we talked
about this, those of you saying trend
day, no, there's no trend, guys. I I
don't know what to say. I don't know how
many days I start by telling you we're
in sharp, right? And failed breakout,
failed breakdown. This is not a trend.
Any of you are looking for a trend in
here, I don't know what you look at when
you look at the screens to identify a
trend, but we're certainly not in a
trend. All right. Coming down to
previous week value area low now. Oh,
could I have faded the eights? Probably.
Probably a could have, would a, should
VIX done to really get going. 17's break
on VIX will be dangerous. More buyers
coming in down here. They might get
themselves caught because I don't think
we're done with it yet. But we're thin
now all the way back up to here up to
740s.
So I'll be watching these 600s. There's
so many imbalances underneath as well
from where we ripped yesterday. There's
so many imbalances down here still.
Jesus Christ.
No bounce to fade. And now we're already
at target.
Yeah, exactly, Taylor. That's literally
exactly it. We've been ranging since
November 5th. Basically,
everything since there has just been a
range build out.
Okay, so into current week value area
low developing. Previous week value area
low down here.
Just make sure that's right. Yeah, that
is.
So, into the blue box. This would be a
cover point if you took that short from
there. Fair play. That's a That's a big
trade. That's a big big trade. All
right. We know buyers keep getting stuck
down here into 650s. They're not done
with this, folks. They're coming right
down for that previous week low. There
is a ton of imbalances in here like I
talked about. So, previous week open
here into 86s. They are not done with
this. They're just not done with it.
20-day coming up on the ES
VIX absolutely going mental right now.
Turbo time on the VIX. And I've probably
lost all opportunity to do something
now. Definitely short side. No retest of
this gray box. No retest of this. Just a
straight once they're done with it. At
the moment they are selling at like 200
plus points without any form of
retracement to get involved in. So we're
about to hit the last target here.
Previous week value low. The only thing
you could look at now is 365. So I guess
there's room for that. But we would now
be shorting in discount. It's just
they're taking away my trades right now.
This is a frustrated man.
Very frustrated man right now.
previous week open just tapped then
still imbalances all the way down to
530s right now.
Can't do anything. I cannot do anything
with this. It's so unfortunate. This is
why I flipping hate ranges when they
don't retest properly. ES has been very
good. I will tell you if you traded ES
today, this is what you want to see,
right? This is what you want to see.
Proper structure. Proper structure built
out. A proper retest of a level and a
fade. Like that is good. Like what we're
getting on ENQ is shite. That is shite
by comparison.
It is what it is. Just one of those
days.
All right. Into previous week value area
alone. No. No news today because the
government shutdown. Fantastic. No news.
Previous week open now tagged. We now
have a liquidity shelf being built out
down here. Why does this look so bad
today?
Don't know. But there is a liquidity
shelf down here into 59s. I would say
buyers got trapped 616s and 651s. So
sellers in control time we're below
those areas.
Oh my god.
We're just going to keep selling, guys.
I'm not going to be able to trade. I can
already tell the trades are gone. The
locations have gone. This is going to be
one of those days I'm going to get
nothing. Absolutely nothing.
Oh my days.
One scalp and that was it. Right into
these imbalances. Previous day opens the
next spot into 30s.
Vix is flying. There is absolutely
nothing I can do with this.
Oh my days. My days. my days.
See if they protect 600 here.
Back to 600. If they squeeze through
this as a lift to 50s potentially.
Certainly 20s is a level.
Watching 20s here through 20s. If they
go through 20s, we're going 50s.
This is a relief. Up we go through the
20s. Piece of this. Can we get to 50s?
Here we go. It's where the buyers
trapped up here at 50s. So, little scalp
there. It's all I could do, folks.
That's all I've got from blue box for a
little scalp up to here.
Terrible. Terrible.
It's all I'm being offered right now.
Can only trade what's in front of me.
I'd much rather have got a retest on a
short somewhere. All right. It might be
if we get through 50s, they can lift it
up through here would be the next spot.
I know. I know guys. I know there's
always tomorrow. It's just frust It's
frust The reason it's frustrating is
because we were prepared, right? What
did I talk about pre-market? Either
they're going to trap under here and do
one of these, right? Or we want to see
liquidity built out to come down to this
and this, right? And they just didn't
they just didn't offer it to me. They
just didn't offer it. I was ready for
it. They just didn't offer it.
So, it's just frustrating. That's all it
is. It's not a big deal. It's just
frustrating.
It's a very dramatic straight down move
as well. Might not look like enough, but
that's like 200 plus points even from
here to here without any real buildout.
250 points right into the top of this
level then 650. If they lift through
this, you got value area low into 70s.
The big level that sellers sold uh is
700s.
There's big big selling into 700s.
Better than nothing. Yeah, I guess it's
better than nothing. It's still It's
What you going to do? What you going to
do? Not a lot.
Take it on the chin. That's all you can
do. Just take it on the chin.
Okay. So, they can't get through the
50s. They're reselling this back to that
shelf we just had at 600.
And if they sell through 600, we still
have imbalances, right? At 62s, at 550s,
at 540s, at 530s, there's still
imbalances and they can still come all
the way down here.
But like I said, I'm not going to short
right now because we are right in
discount, right? We're in discount of
the current week. We're in discount of
the previous week. I don't want to be
short here. I wanted to be short in
premium if it offered me the trade. It
just didn't offer me the trade. Maybe
mugggin here missed it.
Still going lower this. They still want
lower. They are not done.
I'd say 600 is a big overunder right
now.
There they go. They're going for lower.
They're coming for these imbalances.
There is some excess down here. I think
they're going to increase this excess
previous day open maybe into 530s.
Here they come. So, first lot of
imbalances filled. Here they come. 550
is the next imbalance. Then we talked
about 540s and then 534 and previous day
open 530s
and then maybe all the way down in here.
You can't rule it out. We're in a big
big sell day. big big big big big sell
day.
Imbalances is just where the market has
moved too quick. So if we looked left
here, see this big flyer from 9:30
yesterday, we're coming back and filling
that in. So all those orders who were
left there, all the gaps that were left
there, we're filling that in. It's where
price has skipped.
Price has skipped through.
Right. Some buyers trying to step up
here. I still think we probably move
lower at this point. Don't think they're
done with it.
down here. Maybe
big buyer came in here at 60s, right?
61s. There's a big bar at 61s. So, all
the time he's out of uh placement, let's
call it. He's in trouble.
So, if we get back through 61s, then
maybe they can visit 70s, but so far
that buyer 61s has been caught. Here's
the test of that buyer. Still caught so
far.
Still caught so far. Still caught so
far. They're trying to get through him
and lift it. Here goes the lift for that
imbalance back to the value area low. We
might be in here, folks. Let's have a
look. Can they find acceptance now? Next
level would be to squeeze back up to
600s or 96s. Here we go. Just a small
counter trend play here through that 60s
and they get up to the 600s,
96s.
back under 61s will mean will mean a new
low day
and they're still adding liquidity at
500s. Okay, they held that well. Can
they lift now to 600s? Very, very
dangerous play here, but I don't want to
be short at these lows. Here we go.
600's coming. Peel some off in front of
that.
There we go.
There we go. There we go. Lovely. Peel a
bit more. Right. So, if we can lift now,
we're looking for 36s.
They might very well sell this again. We
got sellside imbalances here at 601 and
611. So, peeling some off
and see if we can get through this this
huge move up here on a squeeze if they
really want to get going. Big if, buts,
and may. Here's the 600. So this is was
the first target
point of control. Now moved down here as
well, folks.
Building around the 600. Want to see one
more flush be absorbed then I feel
pretty good.
No, no flush. Just to resqueeze. They
keep coming in for these uh imbalances
at 611. So, next lift would be for 50s,
but I want to see a flush absorbed in
front of uh 560s right now.
Point of control now is uh just under
600. So, big battle zone down here. And
we can potentially squeeze up to 50s
here and then through 50s we can get to
700s. It's still bearish. Remember, the
order flow is very bearish. Just trying
to play the lift because I don't want to
play short down here at these lows.
Oh, nice, mate. You got 937. Let me have
a look. 937.
I don't even have Look at the gaps I
have in these charts. Wow.
So, right at that New York open
basically. Really good, mate. But you
you only got 50 points of it. That's
That's dirty. Sorry about that.
All right, starting to build out a ton
of liquidity down here in this level.
This is your overunder. We can still
break lower. I want you to understand we
can still break all the way down into
this. Absolutely can do it. Market's
very heavy. Give you a readout. Tesla
0.20% down. Nvidia 2 and a half% down.
Microsoft 2% down. Meta 0.58% down.
Google 0.14% down. Amazon 1.70% down.
And Apple 0.29%
down. This might break lower here for my
stop.
Watching these 62s.
They've got protect protect 6062s.
If they do, don't mind holding a little
piece because I've already paid myself.
If they break under that, I will be out
because we will get a new low of day and
they're going to break through it. So,
done. Done with it.
You [\h__\h] If you do that to me for
the fifth time in two days, I'll be very
upset. Actually want you to break lower
at this point. I'm out with this. out of
this now, folks.
Not a bid on the tape here, so we should
break.
Should break. I don't reckon these
passive orders hold up very well.
The break's coming. Here it comes.
They're coming for the lows
down into here. possible if we break
this. Now,
there's no lift high enough for me to
feel good about shorting at the moment.
Maybe just me. Just not high enough for
me to feel good. I need a big shove up.
Good couple hundred points for me to
think about shorting back into. All
right, next lot of imbalances filled
again down here.
All right, so we just tap some of those
imbalances straight back to the 60s
again. Do they resell the 60s? I'm not
going to resell the 60s. There's just no
way I'm selling down here. Far too
dangerous. I I think there's a good
chance we break lower. I'm just not I
don't feel comfortable selling these
60s.
Not when we've moved from 900 to 500
already. We've done a 400 point move
already without any notable pullback.
These are not notable pullbacks, folks.
These are not notable pullbacks. These
are nothing nothing burgers. All right,
sellers coming in here at 50s. Buyers
trapped at 60s. So 50s and 60s big big
level now. And they are adding liquidity
lower and lower and lower and lower
trying to tug this market down.
Previous day open is uh 530. By the way,
ES has already tapped it. Already done
the move.
There we go. coming up
previous day open now. So it should now
try and run down into here if they can't
hold previous day open.
Remember 60s is the level where buyers
came in. They're currently underwater at
60. Uh 50s is the level where the most
recent seller came in. So back towards
these 60s. If we lift through 60s, then
we can go back to 600s again. I don't
know if I'm going to have another go at
this, folks. This feels very heavy on
the tape. And we've got someone playing
games adding liquidity lower and lower
and lower and lower and lower each time.
So, I don't really want to get caught
the wrong side of it.
Any levels to go short? Yeah, I mean,
they're all the way up here for me. This
is what I'm saying. I need a lift up. I
want to play a play up here to then
reshort down. I don't want to short down
at previous week value area low.
Remember, this is deep in discount. It
seems to be that we're just going to
keep going lower and lower and lower and
lower, but uh I'm definitely not going
to be the guy shorting the previous week
value low.
So, back to these 60s like we talked
about. The buyer keeps getting stuck at
these 60s and they cannot get through it
and they've just added more liquidity
again into 25,500.
So, it feels like they want to come for
500 right now.
See if Vicks pulls back in bases
into 17s here.
60 is still the level still. They can't
get through 60s. Buyers are still stuck
at these 60s. I've said it a million
times.
Big big bid down at 500s. There's the 60
lift. Okay, let's watch here. Previous
week value low. If we squeeze through
this, I'll think about joining. All
right, small piece joining then. Bucket
into previous week open here. Uh let's
see if we can go back to VPOX 600.
Can we get into 600 or not?
We are trying. There's a chance of a
break here if they start to really start
motoring.
Here's Vpo.
So this is the move into 600 we just
talked about. They've got to get above
all of this, remember, for any of this
to be meaningful. So it's just a scalp
until then. The buyer at 500 has stepped
up a little bit into 525. He's added a
400 lot there now.
Anything long here is counter trend uh
on the day.
Sellers are stuck under 550 right now.
Buyers came in at 560. So you'd want 560
550 to hold if you're going to hold any
long position here. I'd be very
skeptical about holding. Very skeptical.
There's there's someone bidding and
pulling and bidding and pulling. That's
what's worrying me. He goes straight
back down.
There is someone absolutely playing
games here. I'm not joking when I say
that.
Right. Good hold of 60.
And they've added a 400 lot at 20
though.
They have added a 400 lot at 20. Look at
these guys flashing and pulling. What
are you doing?
[\h__\h] weirdos, mate.
60 still holding here. 60s and 50s big
level. Still holding.
Catching a bid on SPY. Um it's early to
say, but it's trying. It's trying to
find a bid around its 20-day right now.
60s and 50s is the level, right? 60s is
where buyers came in. We got to get back
above the 600s, though. So 60s and 50s
is the level. I'm not in this at the
moment. I'm now waiting again. Don't
like these guys flashing on the tape. I
don't want to see another, you know, 80
point shove straight back down cuz these
guys are flashing and pulling. Look at
this on the tape. I don't know if
anyone's watching the book map. This is
ridiculous what's going on here.
Remember, we are in a uh cell right now
and we are starting to lose this blue
box. We want to be careful because this
will turn red if we don't can't like
reclaim it.
There is a 400 lot at 520. So I'm very
very aware of that. Okay, back to
previous week value area low again. VPO
on the day is up at 600. We really don't
get too much strength for a counter
trend move until we get above 600. And
this big seller coming back in here. 123
lot. He's adding 155 lot. He's adding
another 50 lot. He's trying to force us
down under the 60s to get to the 50s
that he wants. Um, we all know there's a
400 lot at 520 and I would not be
surprised if they pull it given what
I've seen so far this morning.
Could I say what what I'm seeing on
bookmap? Yeah, the horizontal lines of
these big orders being literally flashed
on and pulled and flashed on and pulled
and flashed on and pulled. It's people
spoofing the tape with big size. It's
not a joke. There you go. It flashed at
80, pulled, and they've all come back on
the books all of a sudden. At 70, 75,
80, and 90, they're now trying to lift
through to get to the 600, and you're
starting to see it try and pull
underneath. So, they're flashing 65, 60,
55. They're trying to step on the tape.
And now they just pulled a lot. And then
they came back on, and then they pulled
a lot. Now they're back on again. And
now we're going 80s. Now they're going
to try and lift to get to 600s. So, they
are playing games in this area.
strength will come above 600. All right,
strength will come above 600.
But like if we look uh here
all these imbalances upside you can see
they keep trying to hold this right they
keep trying to bid around here. If we
can get back above the 600 there is an
imbalance up here to fill and then tons
higher. So watching this now for
triggers. Here we go. Here's Vpo on the
day. Rejected VPO straight away on that
first drive. A break over 600 and we can
get going. 612s is an important level.
We have an imbalance there. If we get
through that, we can really start
motoring up to sort of 650s through
that. We are thin up to 750. So, I'm
watching because we might there is a
chance there is a chance we've repriced
to 750s because we haven't had a bid up
yet.
So, they keep testing VPO here into
600s. Here we go. Can they lift this now
through 600 650 and then go 750s?
Is 600 600 600 600 600 big big level
here.
Yes, please.
You see this edge here of this blue box
is a massive level. So, what they would
need to do if they're going to lift,
they're going to need to do this. All
right? Otherwise, this can still be
built out to get down into this. This
what you have to be aware of.
Big level here, folks. Big big big level
here. Oh, can they build above these
flow zones and start to curl?
Sellers keep coming in here at 90s.
Still haven't filled this 400 lot,
remember at 520. I'm still going to wait
and see if we can break out and above.
See, this is the problem. No follow
through over 600. This is why we wait.
Sellers just come flying in here at 80
now, stacking up 100 lots, trying to
force us down. I guarantee you, I
guarantee it, but I reckon this guy at
520 pulls his order. I reckon it's all
[\h__\h] and they're going to trade
right down into this. That's what I
reckon.
Look at these guys.
What is this down here?
20's coming. There you go. Let's see if
he spoofs or not, though. Back into
where these sellers came in at 50s. So,
same story. I I would not be surprised
to see us come down here at this point.
I don't like how we're building out
liquidity, though. It's very dangerous
how we're building out liquidity, but it
would not surprise me to see us break
now.
520s is what they're looking for. Big
player there at 520s.
Let's see. I'm just waiting to see if
he's real.
Is there anyone underneath him? Yep,
there is. 520s and 500s.
Very bearish, guys. Here's the 20s.
Look. Pulled. Gone.
[\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] Knew it. Just [\h__\h] knew it.
Knew it. Might go 25,000. Uh I don't
think so, mate. I don't think so. It
Well, I mean, you're talking about a
move beyond way beyond two sigma to do
that to do it in one day. I mean, it's
possible. You can't rule it out with how
the tape looks, I guess. Um, but I think
more let's just talk about one level at
a time before we talk about 25,000. This
is the next block, right? So, this is
where it wants to trade into at the
moment. 25,000. You're going to if
you're looking for 25,000, you're asking
for it to do a huge move.
All right? And you're not going to
respect.
Right?
This is the rotation to get to 25,000.
You're asking it to come underneath the
Ballinger bands and sweep everything
out. It's possible, but it's asking an
awful lot of it to do that in one day.
All right, here's the break. So, again,
we didn't build nice structure really
here, but
would have liked a squeeze up to be sold
into for me to get a uh better location
to get short rather than trying to short
lows to go lower, but it is what it is.
We are in panic mode right now by the
looks of it.
It's about previous day low. Yeah, right
here. It's what I keep saying right
here. It's that mark on your screen.
It's there for you.
It is emotional price action. I I would
agree with you. It feels emotional.
But it's just a r. It's a really giant
rank. Like guys, all you've got to look
at. I keep saying it to you guys. Just
look at the daily. Are we inside the
Ballinger bands? Yes. Are they going
sideways? Yes. Can we get a break and
hold over 26,100?
No. Can we get a breaking hold
underneath 25,000? I don't know, 250
300. No. So, what are we in? Giant
[\h__\h] range rotation. Huge range
rotation.
Okay. Okay, so coming to retest this. If
they stay heavy here, they will reject
and come down for this. If they reclaim
it, these are your options. Now, if
you're adamant on playing the short, you
can look for that. If they reclaim this,
there is a bigger squeeze up.
It's pretty dirty what's going on here.
Back to the 20-day on ES. So, this is
your key level. Now, we can see this
volume shelf being built out, right?
This is your overunder. Same kind of
level. Big squeeze up here, right back
into it. We have excess now underneath
as well. So same levels we just talked
about right back to the 60s right back
to this level do they reshort this level
to come down here or do they get
squeezed out now is what we are asking
and if they squeeze out after getting
this close and not taking it it's kind
of nuts but there you go you had a 400
lot seller at 520 remember
it's a big lot Nice.
So, so far rejecting this box here. This
needs to be red now. Sorry. Needs to be
like that. If we trade through it, it
will become blue again.
We have imbalances here up to previous
week value area low again. These are
exactly the same levels we traded in
before. Okay, so this is just like
retesting this same level. If you're
adamant on the short here, you can look
for a short to trade all the way back
down here. Just remember you are you do
not have location on your side. You do
not. We have drifted from we've drifted
over 500 points down this morning. I'm
going to watch for the counter trend
long today. It's the only thing I'm
going to be interested in given how much
damage we've done to the downside.
Right, watching previous week value area
low here to see if they can reclaim
ES back to 20day again.
I'm going to watch Vpo here as well.
So balances now back down to 520s.
That's where the seller came in. So
I guess there is an argument if they bid
if they look for counter trend if they
bid above 520s there's an argument we
can uh squeeze higher but like I said
counter trend player high hardest trade
in the book the easier trade will be if
we get above 600 relief up to here and
then a resell up here somewhere would be
really nice.
We're back into this same congested
zone. This sort of 60s and 70s gets
really messy here on the tape. Starting
to see some sellers get a little bit
caught here at 50s right now.
Buyers will need it above 75 really and
really above 600.
Let's see. Let's see. It would be nice
if we can get one trade. If we can get
one squeeze up and then be able to fade
it. It would be nice. One squeeze up and
then a fading opportunity up here
somewhere would be nice. If we can get
the counter trend, run all these stops
out would be nice. If we can get
something like this and then we can fade
that back down as well. So we can get
this move and maybe that move would be
good. Would make the day not completely
worthless at that point
back down to these imbalances. Previous
days open. Remember 20s was the level
where the huge huge seller came in. That
is a big overunder right now. I would
say in the very immediate future not for
the trend on the day and how we de
develop but for the very immediate
future that 20's level is going to be
massive.
If we trade under that I would expect a
new low
legend. Thank you.
They're trying to protect it so far.
This is a wonky tape, man. It feels like
we're going to lift here. They're
trying. They've got to still get through
the 75s.
So, I guess 20 to 75 is the liquidity
build. We are still rejecting this. So,
those of you who want the short from
here technically. All right.
Technically, if they fail this, you'd be
a cover point. I'd cover into some into
20s and then hold if you break 20s to
see if you can get all the way down into
here. There. Technically, like we talked
about, there is a short here down to
20s. If you get under 20s, you can look
for down here, but do not uh position
yourself if I would take some off at
20s. If it starts to hold 20s just
because of where the buyer is, right?
I'm looking at like this here. We see
this huge seller here. See this massive
delta here into 20s. Big big level 400
lot seller came in there. So, he is
currently out of position, isn't he?
Yeah, initial balance now set. Thanks,
Bradley. Almost forgot to say that.
Please, can we just squeeze up? Please.
It's not even that I necessarily want
the long, but I just cannot short down
here. If we just go short, short short
all day long, I don't think I know what
I could have done with this. Maybe could
have sold these flow zones, but I really
don't want to be selling. Even though
there's a shelf here, I really don't
want to be selling previous wheat value,
but just feel like it's too risky for my
appetite without coming and cleaning
some guys out.
This is where the sellers kept coming
in. Remember VPO 55s now still
underneath VPO. Still buyers have no
control, but uh sellers 520s is the big
level here. And they're coming back down
to those 520s again.
Same level 520s.
Do buyers hold this up here or is it
night night time? And are we about to
break low? We're about to find out. 520
is now tagged.
And there's a 636
lot just came on the book here at 500.
The games being played are by big boys
right now.
So they want to break lower at the
moment by offering that.
You want me to go to the bathroom? I can
do that.
You think you get relief if I go
bathroom?
That's funny.
Okay, remember the sellers came in at
50s.
75s is a better break. We had just held
20s. See the 20 level. We just held
those 20s. I've talked about it. We just
held those 20s. Watching this long
trigger now. If we can get back through
this, especially through 75. We just
held the 20s. Look at this. I just told
you the 20s
for a reason. There is a reason I gave
you that level as 20s. It's not just
like making it up as I go along. I'm
actually playing what's on the book. So
20s so far holding. You might see a
squeeze out here. If they can reclaim
62s now and 75s, there's a squeeze up to
90 and then 600. And through 600, you
have a lift point.
Here you go, folks. Here you go. Here
you go. Here you go. They've got They've
got a shot at this. They genuinely have
a shot at this at this point. It's the
first time today if they can hold that
level that they've got shot. I tell you
what, I'm going to go to the toilet.
Hopefully you guys get the move once I
go bathroom.
All
right. 620th break. It wouldn't be
touching this long now. Not unless it
reclaims that 620th break. Did they just
fill that guy down there? What size was
that? 78. No. So, where's the big guy
gone?
Hang on. Where's this spoofer gone?
Where's he gone?
Oh, he's disappeared. He's completely
left the tape. Okay.
Where? Here. Here he is. He's moved down
to 470. All right. We now have an 800
lot at 470. There he is. He's just come
back on the tape. 470. So, we got an 800
lot down here now.
Yeah, pulled it. Definitely pulled it.
He's moved down. You can see him on the
book. Um, here
guys up. See, he's moved down here now.
So, he pulled his order. He was, this is
why I like bookm
up at 500. He's pulled it and he's added
on more size at 470. So, we got an 800
lot now at 470. Do we have anyone below
that?
Not really. Well, we have some at 400.
So, that's a big order. That is not a
joke. So, let's see if he's legit when
we trade down into him or not.
Oh, man. It's like sell low to go lower
right now. This is probably the target.
This block down here. There isn't much
else I can do. Look at these candles,
man. Look at these candles.
Oh, it's just like yesterday. Yesterday,
we went straight up. Didn't get the pull
back I wanted to get in today. We've
gone straight down. Didn't get the pull
back I wanted to get in. What are you
going to do?
How do I know it's the same guy? Uh
well, if he's pulling an order and
putting the same size back on, then it
will be the same guy.
Okay, we're coming back to this 20s.
Remember 20s is your big level where the
sellers came in. All right, it's a
massive, massive, massive level. That's
a big level. So, if they protect that,
they're still in control and they can
look for lower.
What do I think about the IBO squeeze
back up to VWAP? Um, I mean, it's
possible, mate. Like, this is not what
you want to see, right, for shorts. So,
it's possible something like this can
happen and they reshort that.
Absolutely. Back to the 520s again here,
guys.
It's just how they're going to make this
impossible to trade. You can already
tell they're probably going to do like a
a rip out of nowhere when they do it.
So, they've now added more size at 485.
So, you got 300 lot at 485, you got 800
lot at 470. We're back through the 420s.
We're coming towards these imbalances
where we just sold down from though.
It's very hard to want to be involved
down here cuz we're not basing and
holding. We're This won't I don't think
this will I put this on. I don't think
this will hold all day. I think we will
clean these out and then resell down.
The question is when do we come and
clear all do we come and take previous
day low first? Do we come and do this
and then this and then this and then
that? Maybe. Maybe we do that first.
Trap more balls and use the liquidity to
go lower. Okay, back through the through
the 20s. Then we're going to come back
for these 50s and 60s for a test again.
So 50s is now Vpo
right here, right? Get over this and
this and this squeeze is available and
then I'd imagine they will resell that.
I would say we're very thin
up into this, but this is a higher time
frame block here. So this is possible,
right? this is possible and then
probably resell it. I don't think
they'll do this move here. I mean, they
can be very dirty and do it.
Should we put that back on for you guys?
Okay, VPO up here 55s.
We're back above those 20s again,
though. We have a buyer side imbalance
here at 20s now. So let's see if they
can hold this now and lift through point
of control. Get map back up. Man's
running slow. There must been a lot of
orders gone through this morning.
Skip data on us. And
watching this now
back to these 50s. We get pretty thick
here. You can see it on the SVP. We get
pretty thick up here. Any outliers above
sell side 50 53 buy side
47 sellside side I want to get through
47 then at least let's go let's see what
we can do
next dip's got to hold 20s again
good hold in front 20s long now let's
see then long now that was the dip for
me here we go so 3 to 50s. Let's see if
we can get up.
Got to get back above VPO. Don't want to
keep failing here. Want to lift through
55s to get to 75. And then I want to
lift through 75 to get to 600.
55. Here we go. Here we go. Here we go.
Come on. Step on the gas. Don't make me
trim here, you [\h__\h]
At least get me 75s. I really don't want
to take a TP here. At least get me 75s.
Come on.
or 70. 69 is the imbalance. Come on.
You're going to make me trim some,
aren't you? You're really going to make
me trim some. Don't want to get caught
in another flush down to 20. He's
trimming some before they do it. Can
always read if it firms up.
They're making my life hard.
Needs to hold same level, guys. Same
level. Needs to hold the same level.
Good hold there. Nice. Got to get back
through 65 and 75, though.
See this developing here. So, I'm long
some. You guys can still play short. If
you want to play the short, like I said,
you would want to trim some at 20s and
you need to get the break at the moment.
All right. Shorts didn't get the break
under here. So, shorts are trapped under
20s. So, I'm trying to use their pain
right now just to do this relief to
resell. I'll be happy to resell up here.
Even any stop hunt over this.
If we come through 20s, I will not hold
this. gone through 20s. I went old
30s.
Do that on you. You're going to knock me
out. Why do I just feel like I'm going
to get knocked out again?
They're
bidding 25s. Please hold 20s and push
this. Please.
Please.
Come on. Get back above 55s.
I want to sell this. So, I just want you
to go higher so I can sell you. Cannot
sell you down here. Come on. Back above
55s. Here we go. Nice hold. Come on.
[\h__\h] me. Making this so hard.
Big seller coming in here.
They are absorbing him. They are
absorbing him.
Want this guy at 35s to move up. Stop
flashing down there, you prick. [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
Right, this is how I'm seeing it.
There's a seller on the tape flashing
lower than price constantly. Every time
price comes down to that liquidity, he's
pulling hoping he can get that move
down. They have just taken those orders
off the book. Have they moved lower
again?
So, they've left the 800 lot on and
they've moved the 300 lot. I'm just
going to check to see if 300 lot's gone
lower.
No. All right. So, they've completely
removed that 300 lot. So, 300 lot that
was uh what was it at like 80s has gone
mega games, man.
Mega mega mega games.
I will not hold this under 20, guys. I
want to make that clear. I'm looking for
relief up. I will not hold under 20.
Come on. I need you over 55s and 75s.
It's a battle. It's a battle. I don't
want to get flushed on like 100 points
plus here. So, here comes the 20 test.
going to knock me out on you.
And they're adding 15. Oh, they're
trying to drag it.
This might be my last go, folks. I've
had a couple goes at this. This might be
my last go. If they swipe 20s, then
we've probably got enough built out here
on the rejection of this point control
to move lower. Probably should have just
played protrend lower, but uh I just
refused to sell previous week value area
low after a 500 point sell. But here we
go. I'm out of this. And there's a good
chance we continue to fade now. A really
good chance they could just continue to
come down here now.
[\h__\h] me. No relief. No relief for me to
get a squeeze, to get a good profits. No
relief for me to sell. Just a constant
drift lower. What you going to do?
Dumping inventory.
Bull flag on VIX. What on the five
minute? I mean
I mean it's something. It's holding a
bid. I'm not sure I'd call that
necessarily a bull flag, but I mean it's
got a chance if it breaks that current
high of day, which was the old close 7.
You got to understand 1750 was the close
from Friday, right? So, if it gets above
1750, then you've got relief for a gap
filled to 1835.
But, uh, it's not got above it yet.
Back to these 20s again. Seriously.
Seriously, make your mind up.
Yeah. Yeah, I mean the market will like
Finiz will be red other than RTY. So
we've come back out of tech. We've the
rotation's ridiculous. We rotated out of
tech no uh November December into the
Russell, right? Then we rotated this
month out of the Russell back into tech.
And then today we're rotating back out
of tech into the Russell. And surprise
surprise, the metals are getting a bid
back up today. So it's just a rotational
market. We can see that from where the
money's going back into RTY, back into
the metals. We can also see it in how
we've gone back into a range and failed
to break out. We've reclaimed those 20s
again. I don't know if I can be bothered
to have one more go at this. Can I be
bothered? Maybe,
maybe,
maybe. Oh, really?
It's always the time when I'm not in it,
isn't it?
Right, back to 50s again. If we go over
50s, then I'll try and get the trade to
75s, I guess.
Here we go. Here's VPO.
See if they go 75s. Here we go. Here's
70s. If we go 75s, I'm looking for 600.
Jesus Christ.
70s. Previous week area low here. If we
get acceptance back over this, we should
lift to 600. I can't believe it. I I
can't even believe it.
They've got my number today. I'm telling
you, they've got my number.
I'm in a little piece long here. Seeing
if we can get back over previous week
value area low to get into 600. All
right. So, I'm long looking to see if we
can get back over this. I've already
sold some. All right. The question is
now, can we do this in this node here
and get to here? So, your next TP and
then here and then here would be great.
All right. So, I'm long this from here
TP1. See if we can get this up here for
relief. It's counter trend relief
because I think we've built out some
horrible liquidity here that we need to
swipe. And once we've done that, I will
look to resell it back down. Right. I
don't like this is not structure I want
to really short. Not without a trap. Not
if we done that, I can short it. Same as
up here. If we'd done this two leg up,
fade that would have been great. Right
here we go. 75s then. Let's see. Can we
get going to the 600s now?
Uh 89 is a big level. 8975
just based on what happened earlier
today. Big seller there at 8975. So
through 8975 we go 600. Through 600 we
look for an imbalance at 611. through
that uh 650s ideally
counter trend. Remember this is a
counter trend long. Hardest trade in the
book we're doing right now.
Come on. We got to get through these
75s.
Don't want it back below 50s. Now
there's a node here. Just going to get
rid of this. And we can do it like this
to make it a bit easier. Right. I want
this to hold now. This has to hold for
relief.
Almost there. Almost to the 600s. We're
looking good here.
Big seller was here earlier at 90. We
got through that seller. Here we go.
Come on. 600s. [\h__\h] hell. How many
times did this take? Had like four or
five goes at this today. 600s. So,
here's like a 60 70 pointer, I guess.
And if we can get through this, we're
going to get a runner to go through the
11s. So, trim some into here, please.
And if we get going, we can get 650s
finally. Jesus.
Blasphemy, Alex. Can we get up into
here?
Oh my gosh. Am I long? Yes. Like I said,
I was late to the long. I did say I'm
going to get in once we get over VPO.
So, long trigger was 50s for me. So, I
was a bit late to it. If it had done it
the first time, I'd be up over 100
points, but I'm up over 50 points now.
And we'll see. We can get 100 point
trade here. If we lift through this now,
there's a move to 650.
I'm still holding some. Trying to see if
we can get up to 650.
Can we get up to 650? Here we go. Nodes
here into 20.
Don't want them to rinse this all the
way back down now. I also want to see
them really hold 96s,
92s maybe to get up into this VWAP. If
we get through this VWAP, we're going to
look for this one up here and then I
will get ready to sell. But I know we're
very thin on structure today.
So, moving my stop up
ES into VWAP here as well. Just be
prepared. ES is already into its VWAP.
VIX coming down to that pivot I just
talked about. It's going to have to hold
that pivot.
If it flushes through that pivot, then
we're going to get a bigger squeeze out
here.
So, needs to hold 92s. Definitely has to
hold 75, but ideally we hold this little
node here into 92s. Ideally, they bid
this node here. But remember, ES just
came into its view up. So, ES has
already tagged this. Just be very aware
of that. You should have trimmed some if
you're a long ES
or at least paid yourself a partial
just under these 92s. This is the level.
If it doesn't hold here, it's going to
test 75s. I won't hold under 75. There's
a big imbalance all the way down to 55.
So here's 7 75. Check under here. I'm
going to leave it. Leave it. I can read.
It holds a pull back. Riad
this level here now. Key has to hold
this level now.
It's a good hold. So far, it's a good
hold.
Problem is we have imbalances all the
way down to 30 if they actually want to
go and fill them.
But the protren is short. All we've done
is swipe out these stop. Didn't get that
far. But ES rejected VW like we talked
about. ES has definitely had a big big
rejection of VWAP. We if we hold this
blue box, there is a chance for a second
leg of relief. If we lose this blue box,
then all this was like we talked about
was a swipe of this for this. So, what
we'd like is something like this. All
right. But if we see this, then that
would be a resell back down. I won't be
taking that cell. It's too far into
discount for me to sell. I will sell if
we come all the way back up here
somewhere.
So, you can read adding this long if
this starts to hold. if it starts to
hold. Uh, where are those sellers? 55s
and 20s. You don't want 20s. It's got to
hold 55s.
So, coming back down for those 55s. This
Vpo level fair value on the day. ES got
absolutely crushed off VWAP. So, ES
doing again the nicer move. If we look
at ES right into its VWAP, swept almost
everything. Almost everything.
NQ making it a little bit more tricky
today.
VPO still holding here so far.
So they got to get back 75s now for a
squeeze
with this second leg up. It's possible.
There's 75s. Can they squeeze and fill
in some of these imbalances from that
last sell back down? We've got
imbalances into 85 to 92 and 99 and then
right back at the high peak and we can
get a second leg higher here. Here we
go. Great hold of the blue box. So, I
really want to see this back through the
90s now if we're going to get a second
leg. So, sellers will try and defend
this in here. Buyers are trying to
absorb here. If we get a second leg,
we're going to get this move here. And
then I'm going to look to fade that move
up there probably. Here we go. Nice fill
of these imbalances.
So I'll be take paying yourself. If
you're long from the blue, you want to
pay yourself some. Why? Because we're
counter trend. You want to pay yourself
a little bit. Move your stop in the
money and then hopefully you get this
second leg. Hopefully versus this right.
Same same level. Really nice. Looking
good.
Do I look at VIX? Yeah, absolutely.
Absolutely. I still want to do some
giveaways here, by the way, folks. We've
got an hour and a bit left. Here we go.
Right, let's get through 600 and start
pumping now, please.
Let's get get the bump. Can we get the
bump? Here come the pump. Here we go.
Here we go.
Right. Can we get a second leg now up
into our VWOP is the question.
What am I looking at? Sorry, I just see
your question. Uh, this right here,
it doesn't show it very well here, but
uh, this was the imbalance.
Actually, in this candle on Ninja, I
have lots of stuck sellers in that
candle. I don't know why it looks so
different there, but here. See all these
sellers? Sellers, sellers, sellers,
sellers. It's a nice hold into VPO and
see if we can lift up here now. Looks
good.
Really good. Really good. We're getting
second leg here. Really good. Can we get
into previous week close, which would be
670s.
670s would be fantastic.
650s and 670s is the target.
VWAP as well. We're we'll respect VWAP
as well.
Okay. Big level at 50s. So 30s a little
shelf and then 50s where buyers got
stuck. I tell you where sellers came in
really heavy this morning. 700s.
Sellers came in very heavy at 700s this
morning.
Right up here.
105 750. Is there really? Let me have a
look at him.
Oh, I see him. Nice. Thank you, mate.
Lovely.
I still think this one's higher. Move
your stop up with this. Protect your
profits. Remember, we're counter trend.
We're looking for a break really above
sort of 740, 750.
I'm not expecting too much. If we get to
700s would be fantastic.
We're just looking for that second leg.
ES still can't get through its VWAP.
VIX starting to base out in those sort
of 1680s. It can afford to come right
down into 1664 here, VIX, and find a bid
down there. So, just be careful. We're
in an area where the VIX might want to
find a bid. If it does find a bid here,
then uh this move will finish soon. Here
we go. Here we go. God, I don't know how
many attempts I needed at this. Far too
many.
Far far far too many attempts.
630 fib level. Uh, from what swing? Not
from not from the open. Or you talking
about a 30 fib?
New York open.
I think we got a chance to get in here,
right? 50% retracement
and it's where the sellers came in this
morning. We've got a chance. It's just
whether they're willing to do it or not.
We look at this. It's these guys here. I
want to get into these guys up here. And
then I want to think about, can I resell
that back down once we get up there?
Sorry it took so many attempts this
morning, folks. I I don't like picking
bottoms. It's not something I want to
do, but I'm certainly not going to sell
underneath previous week value area low.
Not without it drifting higher first
750 high volume node. Yeah. Up here.
This remember though on the if we zoom
out don't just look at today. Remember,
zoom out.
Uh, where's the developing week? We can
look at some of these areas here.
So, this is the one you're talking
about, I think, JD, but it starts at
sort of 700 from the previous week. All
right. And then you've got another one
into 750. So,
we have to be uh respectful of what
what's happened before before both in
this week and previous weeks. Dave Davis
Davis, your analysis is worth way more
than this. Please keep this stream. It's
the best. Thank you, man. Appreciate the
tip. Very kind of you. The super chat.
Do I think you can reenter longs? Um,
potentially, but you've just got to
remember we're in a rotation. Um, as
long as we hold this, there's potential
to move upside. But what I would say is
we left a low hanging fruit down here.
All right, we haven't swept IB. We
haven't taken previous day low. It's
possible they come back for it. I would
be, you know, this is a no man's land
play right now, right? We were long from
here or you're long from here. Maybe if
they hold this, you get a continuation
up into here. But we will probably want
to be thinking about a short up here. If
we if we see buyers get stuck into here,
we probably want to be selling that back
down because I'm going to assume lots of
buyers will chase this late. And if they
chase it late, we'll use their pain. And
if we do take that short, all right, if
we do lift, right, let's say we lift up
here and we see something like this and
buyers get caught, we will be covering
some into these nodes. All right, maybe
like 30% there, maybe a bit more there,
and then hoping we go lower, but
protecting our profits because we don't
know at that point, we've built out
structure. We're going to have to need
to respect the structure we've built
out.
If we go full reclaim and we don't see
any buyers trapped and we start doing
this then obviously we're not going to
short it. Right? We start reclaiming
this shelf. We can go right back. This
is a dramatic rem move like here is very
thin. Like that is look at this. Look
how thin we are in here. Right. This is
what I talked about earlier. There was
no good retest. Like this needed to come
a little bit high. ES was much a much
better looking chart this morning for
the uh short in my mind anyway. in my
mind.
Okay, one over 1,200 of you are watching
right now. 441 likes. That is not good
enough. Come on, guys. I want to do some
giveaways. Let's get it moving.
Yeah, still rejecting view up. Can't get
a close over it.
Where's our 20-day as well? Where's
mean? 772
on NQ, 623 on the QQQ.
Thanks for the commentary. I listen
while I'm looking at my charts. Ah,
nice.
Kurt Clouden, best stream I've seen so
far. Thanks, Kurt. Thanks, Kurt.
Remember, this is a counter trend
squeeze we're in, right? Please remember
that if they start losing this blue box,
they have unfinished business. If they
build out enough liquidity here, they
have unfinished business down here that
they can come for.
We can have a look at the excess at the
low.
It's not bad. It's actually pretty good.
That's not bad. That's not too bad. But,
you know, they have reasons to move
lower if they want to. If they do this
move here, they will move lower. Right
now, you're in a counter trend squeeze
relief to potentially come up here. But
remember, ES keeps getting stuck. ES has
already got to VW up. There you go. All
right. And it's already swept this guy
out. So, if we think about the
liquidity, ES has knocked these guys
out. ES has done the perfect move that
you'd want to see. Like, it's just so
much better. Like this trade here is way
better. Down, down, down, down. Push up.
Fail. New York open.
Short. Big slam.
You leave all this alone. There's the
squeeze out. There's the target. It's
hit its target. So the question now is
for ES. If it can't hold this, it will
probably collapse down to this old PC.
Messy. It's It's messy.
Might be that we're done with this at
this point.
I'll give it some time at least.
Yeah, I'm in right now with a runner
just versus here. I sold most in this
push.
So, just a runner right now. If we start
losing this, I'll just cut it again.
We're trying to I'm trying to give it a
chance,
but it's very possible it just snaps.
So, I'm basing my stops on that in that
blue box. The other side, the bottom
side of that blue box is my stop.
Amateur DJ to trader.
How did it happen?
Good question. Uh, I wanted to do this
as a career before uh before my DJ
career took over. So, I was actually
offered a few jobs doing this back in
the day. And then, um, DJing was very
kind to me. Nightlife was kind to me.
First worked in all the London clubs
first and then
and then, um, had some breakout singles
and a big career. Here we go. Still
holding. Blue Box still look okay for
now.
Blue Box still holding.
K trade, you're another XDJ. What kind
of music?
Where were ES going? Where is ES going?
If we start losing momentum, um I would
say if you look at the pivots,
yesterday's open, you'd be looking at
sort of 50s, 50s and 42. So 950, 942. If
you lose that, there's a big block into
930s. And if you lose that, 910s and if
you lose that, 9003s. And if you lose
that, 864s. Right? So, if you want to
put that into the spiders, um you can
see this morning we held 90s or in front
of 90s. I imagine there's some gamma
exposure there. Uh under 90s you're
probably looking at uh 87s and under
that you're looking at 85s again. 85s
have been a big level for months and
months and months and months and months.
Getting ready to cut this at this point.
Getting ready to cut this. Just don't
like what I'm seeing it.
You're worthy. No. No way. I know your
stuff.
Sick.
Are you still doing it? I used to play
all your stuff.
I used to play all your stuff. That was
That was back in the days when I love
that label was like you, Justin Martin,
Gorp.
still do a bit. Do you still do it with
them or not so much? I know Barkley uh
sold it, didn't he?
That's sick, man. Really cool.
I'm trying to think of your records I
used to play. I'm going to have a look
now.
Me house. I play house.
I don't play anymore really.
Are you in North America worthy?
Still holding this blue box here. Still
looks pretty good so far.
With all the people here, we could bring
a label to life. We We probably could.
I'm having a look at your um
Beatport at the moment.
Oh yeah, I remember your word remix.
That was a wicked tune back in the day.
That's a long time ago.
Super cool, man. Super cool. Good for
you.
Outside of San Fran.
Who would have thought DJs are big
traders? You'd be surprised how many uh
DJs like a bit of exposure to the
markets.
Okay, failing here. I'm out of this now.
Don't want to hold in case there's a
flush under this. I can always re-enter.
Remember, we can always reenter. But if
they flush under this, they'd probably
be looking for these 30s. Remember, the
20s has been a big level on the tape all
day. There's lots of imbalances down
here. So, we're going to come down,
probably fill some of these guys here,
potentially down into 20s. They can
scoop this. They can trap and scoop
this, but I don't want to sit through
the pain. Here we go. So, we're filling
some of these imbalances potentially
down to these 20s now. And this is your
big over under. Look at this big sell is
still here. 400 lot from earlier, right?
So, that delta is still offside. It's
not been paired off at all. So, that's
your overunder. I'd say technically
speaking, all the time we're holding
that. Technically there are sellers
trapped under that but uh there are lowh
hanging fruits to go for under 20 like
we talked about this old low.
So a shame we had divergence there with
ES. So those of you who do call it SMT
right there's your divergence on ES that
took that pivot out and then faded on NQ
we didn't. NQ's being a pain to trade
today.
Don't like the CVD. I mean, we're boxed
in really on CVD.
Did it take that pivot out though?
No, just boxed in.
Yeah, probably done with that. That was
That was a couple nice trades there. Not
the best, but uh made some good money on
those.
They lifted pretty aggressively which
was good.
Same level 20s is going to be the level
down here. This block here, we're just
going to do this as gray. We're going to
use that as our over under. We can
actually increase this size a bit if you
want. Make it like to here because
they've made it a little bit messy. So
if they sell this now, then they're
going to attack the 20s. If they lose
the 20s, they're going to attack the IB
low.
Can I look at gold? I can look at gold
for you. Yeah, I'll have a quick look.
It's getting close to that level I'd be
interested in. All right, so gold no
different to anything else. All right,
everyone freaked out about it all.
Right. Higher time frame structure is
still good. So here's your base. All
right. That's your like ABCD kind of
pattern. There's the breakout, right?
Breakout. There's your pullback. Have
you lost anything? No. All right. So big
pullback. I know it's dramatic, but
that's a big move up. We expect a big
move down. Right. It's start to found a
bid. What you'll be looking at now, all
right, high time frame, people will be
looking for is there going to be failure
to follow through. So if we do something
like this, right, we're getting up into
those areas. If we were going to put,
you know, some profile on it from the
high. Let's just do one from the high.
See if it will measure out for us. You
going to give us one? No. You're going
to be a pain. Really? You're going to be
a pain. Okay.
Hell, man.
Right. I'll be watching some of these
nodes. So, we're starting to reclaim. In
fact, let me just do this to that's from
the high. Let's do it from the breakout.
Not you.
this guy here. Let's do it from the
breakout here.
All right. I'll be watching this. Look
at this here. I'll be watching this
level here on gold.
All right. Can we trade up into that?
What's that? F five 5,87 to sort of
5,100. This kind of level here. Even
from the 50% up to here. All right.
Traders will be looking to see. All
right. Those who are adamant that we are
done with gold will be looking to see if
there's failure to follow through here.
That will mean we come up here and that
buyers get stuck and they will trade it
back down into here. Then they'd be
covering some here and then they'll be
looking to see if that is actually the
top. They would need to see this break
down here in continuation. If you don't
see that in gold, they'd be looking to
base here and then reclaim. So it just
be a squeeze down, a failure to move
lower, base out, and then back up. and
continuation will be these will be your
targets higher time frame. So anything's
available right now. I wouldn't be want
to be long here. That's for sure. Long
off here was good. Short off here, short
of the fail, this move here, failure to
follow through, great short. Failure to
follow through, great long. But you want
to be taking profits here, right? And
then seeing if it fail fails to follow
through again, then you're looking to
reshort back down. Hopefully that makes
sense for you.
QQQ might go lower, but you don't think
we see it today. I mean, there's plenty
of time, guys. There's there's a lot of
time left for it to go lower if it wants
to. Um,
we just have to understand that we
probably need a liquidity building out
phase for a bit. It's been a big move.
All right, let's think about what we've
done. The Sunday gap uh
Sunday gap and fade down Monday morning,
right? Gap and fade undercut reclaim
straight bid up three drives. One we
talked about this two mark premarket two
three drives lost backside of that. We
wanted this down to here would have been
nice didn't offer it us. Um we're coming
into previous week's value area low. We
have a big cluster here which we expect
the market to find a bid from. All
right, we have lots of time to do that.
It might need what would be ideal is a
pullback into here which is then resold
down into this and then we can see our
buyers are there actually buyers down
here. Are there actually higher time
frame buyers down here? That is a bit
like what we just talked about on gold.
If we fail to follow through up here,
right? If we now we have these buyers
trapped, we have these buyers trapped.
All right. If we reject all of these and
fail to follow through, we will see
lower prices in this market. But there's
a big butt.
We have to be respectful
of the daily, right? So, if we're going
to see failure to follow through, right?
Good rejection here. We're going to need
to reject somewhere in here and we're
going to need to start breaking down
underneath these levels. If we start
breaking down underneath these levels,
we will get this turn down here. this
will come back down and instead of
looking for this here, we will look for
this down here into this 200 day which
is getting very close to this. So
this is an area of interest right into
here at the moment. Um and then beyond
that we can talk about this as a buying
opportunity
under that then uh good night. Good
night. Uh
yeah, these are marking up not too bad.
30% pullback would be into and around
these 200 days. So, anything's possible
right now. Uh because we're in that
choppy range, right? And see last week
failed to break out the highs. Uh Mon,
Sunday, Monday failed to break out the
lows. Most your range is in here. You
can see that by here. All right. This is
the rotation
until they prove otherwise. They get
this great. They get this great in here.
Well, Alex hates in here.
Um,
what's BTC doing? Where are we trading
at? That 77. So, we're getting
interesting on BTC as well.
We are
not at a level yet, but we're getting
close.
Have we undercut?
I want to see this get wrecked.
I want to see a mega stop hunt here.
And I want to see a measured move.
In terms of percentages, when we think
about these dumps that we have after the
thousand day cycle,
that's a 31%
Yeah, into here would be nice. And that
give us a 70 overall, which would be
ideal. No, not quite.
I think it's coming.
I think we're like here.
See, these are like the 70 70% moves.
There you go. 77% in a bare market
cycle. This is not unusual
84%.
All right. So, it's possible if they do
a measured move
down into here is possible. It might be
like never possible. It's absolutely
possible because for
I don't know if they can measure this
out, but too big. That's probably only
It's just a golden pocket. It's very
doable. So, I'd like to see BTC run
these stops and come down anywhere in
here. Just start running stops and then
see see if we can base out for a bit.
It's It's going to take time, guys.
Everyone that's looking for BTC, we have
a th00and day. That's a th00and plus
days, which is normal for BTC,
right? We have a thousand plus days
normal for BTC.
A thousand plus days
normal for BTC. And then we normally see
a 70 plus% pullback, right? Pullbacks,
pullbacks. We're only just getting
started. It started in October. The last
one started
November 21 and finished no. So, it
takes a year. So, we can go all the way
until October
26, which would be like here.
It's very possible that we do some some
stuff like this. I know everyone's like
the market's different, institutions are
different now. I don't know. We do that
kind of move then I will start buying I
bet. I'm interested now for for a trade
if we swipe and and do a fail breakout.
I'm interested in a trade, not an
investment. I'm interested in a trade.
We'll see.
What do you consider to be more
important levels? High volume nodes or
low volume nodes depend on the setup.
High volume nodes obviously is an area
of liquidity being built up. That is
important level for to use as an
overunder. So like we're starting to get
stuck here. When we leave these a high
volume node, we look to trade through a
low volume node. Low volume nodes can
act as like resistance or support. So
why? Because it's thin and then sell
that back down from there. Um, but I
like tra I like trading from high volume
to high volume, right? So, if you see
all the things that I mark out, if we
think about the higher volume nodes on
the hourly charts, gray box, gray box,
blue box, there was a gray box down
here. So, we trade from high volume to
high volume. High volume to high volume,
high volume possibly to high volume,
right? So, I use that as my key levels
to trade to. And then you can use lower
volume nodes like this right here as
like potential trap plays.
Watching my live is like a trading
course. Yeah, it is. I try and explain
box to box is previous week low down
here. Uh yeah, just under it. Yeah, 365.
Um,
is that previous like week low or is
that previous day low?
Uh,
um,
yeah, it's previous week low. You're
right. It's previous week low. Yeah,
365. Uh, lower bold today is 320 on the
daily.
Market's now gone to sleep. It's
digesting, but you can see we're
starting to roll over here. So, there's
a good chance here. So they've done this
like multi-
squeeze up, run the stops, and you're
starting to see them use this liquidity
now back to the 20s. This same level,
remember 20s. And if they lose that,
then you can make potentially lower day
in a swipe down. 20s is a big level
though.
So here we are into the 20s and if we
get acceptance lower here, then you
expect a new low of day.
There were some sellers caught at the
500s.
They're getting very aggressive with
this.
So imbalance here just above 500s. I
would expect this will come and test the
500s and under that fresh lows. So you
can see this is why we said you don't
want to hold. If it can't hold this,
this is likely you remember I drew this
out. we talked about ideally we would
have done this which is what we did on
NQ and then we've lost this and this is
your short back down and this is the
continuation lower so if you're in this
short IB low is a target and then this
block down here very very possible right
now this built liquidity to move lower
can I do this for the full day I mean I
could but I'm not going to be exhausted
Good.
What are my settings for the anchor? Uh
9:30. Starts at the 9:30. I use ticks
per row. Two ticks per row. Um I can
bring it up for you. Ticks per row. Two
ticks per row. And I have it a width of
20. That's all you need to change.
Everything else is standard other than
the color obviously.
So back down to these 500s. This is
where there were some sellers caught
here a little bit earlier, but um we've
been very very heavy unless they're
going to protect these. Uh by the way,
you have divergence. ES just took out
low of day and initial balance low. So
you do have divergence here just to make
it really hard. So ENQ couldn't take out
the high and couldn't take out the low.
Like
they're being very dirty with it.
Default VWAP is different. Default VWAP
is up here. This is New York. This is
default.
Do I trade on props? Yeah, I trade props
and I trade my own accounts as well.
Blue EMA. Uh, these are the flow zones.
They're all rolling fibs. So, this is uh
7289. These are 21 344 I think. Top of
my memory.
VIX starting to get going. So it held
that base um on the VIX. Remember we
talked about that base being held into
sort of 17 807 sorry 1680 1675. It's now
back up to high of day. If VIX starts
squeezing here it has gap fill potential
to 1831 today.
Right. While this fafs around for a
minute. Um, how are we doing for likes?
We I want to get up to some more likes
here, guys. There's still over a
thousand of you watching. Let's get up
to at least 800 and we'll do some
giveaways. Uh, as soon as I get back,
I'm going to get a refill from the
coffee. Let's get 800 likes and then
we'll do some Apex giveaways and some
course giveaways. I'm going to set out a
new funding next giveaway today as well
to run for the month. So, um, maybe
we'll do that live on stream as well.
All right, see you guys in a minute.
All right. How are we doing
barely moved? Awful. Awful.
That 20 is still the key level here,
right? Let's set up uh some giveaways.
Give me a second, folks, to get this all
set up for you.
Uh,
Alex, would you which you trading view
volume levels or Ninja Trader? Well,
they're always different. Uh probably
NT. NT a little bit more. Uh the tick
data is a bit better on NT.
Bit better on NT.
How do I read charts and trust my
indicators and intuition? Uh just time
time and and testing. Back testing
forward testing. Just do I use ATR for
something? If yes, what for? And how do
I set it up? Yeah, I I use ATR on a one
minute chart. you're going to be like,
why does he want to use it on a one
minute chart? Just in case I do
something stupid like come to the chart
and not realize that the ATR is massive
on the day. If I see ATR, which is 30,
40, 50, 60 points per M1, and it's
staying up there, then I need to
seriously size down and that's what I
use it just to like analyze my size. I
think we're going to wash here and kind
of run all these stops like we talked
about. So, pops now and starting to fail
at the retest of this level. Failed
again. They're going to come for these
lows. All right. So, they've stayed
heavy versus 20. No real close above
this level. All right. They're rejecting
this. They're rejecting this. They're
coming for these. Like we said, TP is
down here for you guys. So, TP1 down
here. I would take some off in the 20s
if you haven't already. And then look
for IB low and this down here. Now, for
your follow through while you're holding
that trade, for any of you who took that
short, um I will tell you now. Code FCT,
best code to use for all your prop firms
other than for take profit trader. Use
code flow zone. There you have another
what two days left of the Apex sale for
90% off using code FCT. But if you want
a chance to win a free account right now
live on stream, just type FZT once in
chat for me and we'll pick a winner at
random. Give you guys a couple minutes
to do that.
Guys, another minute or so.
Yes, new lower day just a moment ago. By
the way, you still got divergence
playing out down there.
Major divergence.
VIX rejecting
a key level on that last drive up. What
is that previous
week low? Yeah. So, sorry, VIX QQQ. So,
the ETFs are rejecting some key levels
and VIX still starting to really get
going. So, if we can break through these
55s and get aggressive, we should trade
up to sort of 18. What's that gap, Phil?
to 1834 possible on the VIX if they can
go if they can get going right now. All
right, give you guys 10 more seconds
here. Please don't spam it if you've
already typed it once. It's all you need
to do. You don't need to type it again.
Five, four, three, two, and one. Winner
is three for five
spot shooter. Three for five spot
shooter. Are you here? Let me know
you're here in chat and I will hook you
up.
Three for five spot shooter.
Let me know you're here in chat.
Here you go. Here's the break, guys. So,
you're almost getting that IBL.
Should get it. Lots of liquidity down
here. So, those of you who are short
from this uh 550s, you're looking good.
Don't be a dick for a tick. If you have
not taken a partial yet, you should take
a small partial here. You will want it
to stay heavy versus 504ish right now
for continuation. And then you'll be
looking for the expansion model um as we
start to really push through some of
this liquidity we've built. Uh on the
current week though, we're going to have
to be careful. I would say yeah, we're
into like an edge into these sort of
470s. If you get through 470s,
there is a really, really, really good
shot of going 400s.
Oh, there you are. Three for three for
five spot. Okay, I'm going to make a
note of your name. Congratulations. All
I want you to do is send me an email,
please. info@flzonetrader.com.
Send me a screenshot of you logged into
your YouTube so I know it is you and not
someone pretending to be you. And I will
sort you out with a uh free Apex
account.
We got about 25 minutes left. So we'll
do another giveaway. We do a course
giveaway in the next sort of 10 minutes
or so.
Just checking a couple emails here. Some
of you got in touch.
So, drifting back up. If they don't
reject this now, squeeze is back on for
a failed breakdown here. Uh, sorry. Let
me just sort this out for this guy.
We go.
Same levels as earlier, guys. Exactly
the same levels.
exactly the same levels. Uh Thomas, if
you're on uh stream, I'm just replying
to you now. Um
We've
Yeah, I don't know. Some of you are
still entering. It's It's done, guys. We
did the giveaway.
We've done the giveaway. Alex, can you
explain one of your methods when you say
big buyers or sellers are stuck? Show
example as to what you're looking in the
chart for a signal. Yeah. Uh I'm using
footprint,
right? So you could use it here,
right? And I'm looking to see stuff like
this where we get excess, right? See
this big seller came in here. They
didn't get their target down here. They
want their target. If we now do not
trade underneath this level here, right?
If we protect that level, then this
seller 754
delta will remain stuck. All right? So
buyers will want to protect into here
and try and bid back up. If they're
unable to do that and this seller gets
back in control, we will trade lower.
But right now he is in pain. And if we
protect this, it's possible you can see
this imbalance holding. If it's
imbalance that you would not see on any
other chart, it is holding. We just
filled this imbalance. If they protect
this seller here, all right, then we
will use his pain to try and lift
higher. That's the kind of thing I look
at on a lower time frame. If you're
talking about like delta, you would need
like a different as in delta formed, you
would need a different indicator like
this here. I can see big selling delta
here. I can see big selling delta here.
Or if you don't want to use that and you
want to use bookmap,
I can take you up to bookmap. How would
I use it on bookmap? I would use this
here, right? Volume profile delta. If we
have a look at the low of day or if we
have a look where was the big uh sell
lot that I kept saying to you today,
520, right? 520 was a huge level we've
talked about. If we scroll up here and
come to 520, you will see right here
there was a 415 lot offside. 520 415 lot
offside. So that means at some point
today 415 lots were sold at the market,
right? A market order sell. So if we get
back above them, then you have those
sellers and everyone below stuck.
Uh it's a third party app that I use um
for that. It is uh called Twin Peaks.
Twin Peaks, but it's basically delta
volume. It's basically the same volume
profile delta, but it's shown as like a
um a profile rather than as a number as
I have it here. So you can see also on
bookmap you can see here at 500 you can
see there's a 258 lot standing out at
500.
No worries.
I make it seem easy. I don't know if I
make it seem easy. I think um it's not
easy, guys. Like anyone tell tells you
trading's easy, it's not. We had the
chat in Discord yesterday. Some of my
members in Discord are starting to have
real breakout moments. Whether that be
some of them passing evals for the first
time, some of them taking payouts for
the first time, some of them taking
record payouts, going on record wins.
There is no substitute for time. There
just isn't. the the 10,000 hour rule.
It's real, right? Once you've got your
method, once you understand what you're
trying to learn, it's just about going
back and learning it and looking at the
same thing and the same thing and the
same thing. Can you spot the people who
are trapped? Can you spot the key levels
that we want want to trade into? Can you
use their pain to trade the other way
from them? Can you see a signal of a
whale in the market? Can you join it?
Takes time, guys. It really takes time.
Okay, so you can see right now 520 and
500 rotation,
right? No close under 500. We know
there's a seller stuck at 500
and and 520. All right, 500 and 520
rotation. This is the buildout. So
through here, we lift to here. Under
here, we jump, run these stops, and
probably come down into here. This is
the buildout. Remember the protrend
currently is down. We caught the counter
trend squeeze up. I missed all the
shorts today unfortunately. Couldn't get
a short trigger. I even this I would
have liked it a little bit higher.
Arguably I could have taken this short
here. I knew it was very high
probability but it just goes against my
rules of trading near lower of days. All
right. Much rather see this base and
squeeze out and then offer a short
somewhere up here. It would be much
better. Oh, don't move that. I'm going
to need that. Okay. So, back to the 20s
again.
You can see this rotation over and over
and over again.
I've been a member for almost a year now
and I'm still learning every day. Thanks
so much for the value, Alex. You're
welcome. You're welcome. So, um I feel
bad today, guys, because we wanted the
short. We talked, if you go back to the
stream, we wanted the short under here
if it retested. We wanted the short
under here if it retested. I feel bad
guys that, you know, after last week of
having multiple amazing days, all we
needed was this to come up here or this
to build out a bit nicer. And the same
here, this to just do this, right? I
don't like chasing these kind of moves.
Look how aggressive that is. We move
from almost 800 to 550 in one, two,
three, four, five, six minutes. I mean,
very hard, very hard when we do that to
be involved.
What are the clouds again? They're
called the flow flow zones. They're just
roll. If you just do rolling fibs,
they're just rolling fibs.
So, this this is my momentum cloud. This
is showing you current momentum. This is
deep pullback. This is based on fibs.
Deep pullback. So, you can see we came
into the deep pullback. We failed. We
came into momentum, we failed. We
flipped the clouds here this morning
after being a big pump and then
sideways. So, big pump and then
sideways. And we're repricing this whole
move from yesterday, which now means
we've left all these players trapped.
Have we revisited it? No. The revisit
would have been here and we would have
played that down. We just didn't revisit
it. It's annoying. Very, very, very
annoying when the market does this.
more of your confidence level and
understanding all the dynamics of the
market. Your skill is next level. I'm
trying to absorb as much as you can as I
can. Just keep showing up, man. I've
been doing this a long time. A long
time. I'd say my trading has signific
got significantly better the last few
years, but there's still so much room
for me to improve as a trader. It's
insane. I think long as we're never
arrogant in the market or at all in life
and just understand that, you know,
we're here for a short time on this
earth, our job is to learn as much as we
can and be better at what we do. Whether
that be your job, whether that be as a
partner to someone, as a mother or
father, as a brother or sister, as a
colleague, as a friend, as a human
being, we can always do better, right?
We can always do better. You never stop
learning. And the moment you think that
you know it all, well, you will be
humbled. Whether it's by the market or
by someone else,
still the rotation. 500 to 520. Still
the rotation.
Nothing's changed here.
Did I have a down phase in this game?
Oh, yeah. I got absolutely
cooked.
More like cucked uh during the early
days of COVID. Oh yeah. So during those
days I was playing um
two to max three standard deviation
shorts on small caps. All right. So back
in the day a small cap would normally
move two to three standard deviations
prior to COVID. That's what you'd see.
So you'd see a news release in the
morning. So news release would come out
and it'd say this company's cured
cancer. All right. and it would be up, I
don't know, 100%, 200%, and it would be
past a two standard deviation, right?
And you'd be like, "All right, well,
that's [\h__\h] This thing is covered
in warrants. They've got so many people
stuck in this. I'm going to short it."
And it worked for a very, very, very,
very, very long time. And then COVID
happened. And then retail got stimulus
checks. And then we stopped going two
and three standard deviations. And we
started going four, five, six, seven,
eight, nine, 10 standard deviations. And
Alex goting cooked in that numerous
times. And it wasn't prop firm. I lost
$20,000 more than once on some of those
moves, right? So, I got absolutely
wrecked and I had to really
get off the mark. or not market to like
really reanalyze my trading,
work out what was uh
not working, where I'd gone wrong. I had
to scrap that whole way of trading. I
had to stop picking tops, although you
have to really pick tops on um small
caps because you don't have much room to
play with. But I started playing more
failed follow-through. And then I
started developing like an EMA system to
try and help and yada yada yada yada.
All right, but don't don't think I
didn't lose. I'd lost a lot of money. A
lot of money.
Am I looking long? Not yet. Not yet.
We've had We've had the long relief,
right? We've had the long relief. We're
just in a There's nothing to do yet.
Look, we're in a rotation 20 to 500. We
just talked about it, right? We're in a
rotation here to here and sellers can
still protect this. All right. This
still has lowhanging fruit down here to
come and take. Um if we get back above
all of this, all right, then we can
think about that relief, right, to come
and run these out. But you want to be
careful right now picking picking bots
down here, right? Because the main move
is in a sell, right? There's the sell.
There's the first pullback. You could
argue that that's pathetic. That's the
first pullback. All right. And they've
sold it. I think they want to run these
stops and come down into here like we've
talked about, which is what you're
starting to see.
When did I get into futures? Uh
maybe four years ago. Three years ago,
what are we now? 2026. Three years
maybe. Three years ago, I moved from
small caps to midcaps, from midcaps to
large caps, from large caps to ETFs.
That that was my journey, right? And
then I moved to futures. I still trade
large caps and ETFs. That's still my a
big source of income for me,
but I do that as a swing position.
We like the lowhanging fruits. Yes, we
do. We do like the low hanging fruits.
What's the fib cloud? These are my
clouds. This is everything you see here
is from my system, right?
Flow zone system pro.
So, it's clouds uh its GlobeEx levels,
its opening range, its initial balance,
its uh multi-time frame trend, it's uh
daily and weekly levels. All right,
here's the lift back to 20s again. So,
still in this rotation until they decide
what they're going to do with it.
Nothing has changed.
Still, we build.
Do I talk about swing positions in the
course? I don't think I really do. Uh
maybe in the foundation course the the
principles are exactly the same. But if
you do the 20hour course, what I do have
is a swing position right here. So like
my swing investments are in here, right?
So when I'm looking at stuff, you can
see talking about them here like UU and
US
uh found a bid here this morning. So I'm
interested in this versus 20s. You can
see right I'll show you. We found a bid
on the back test. All right. I've
alerted everyone to this. We found a bid
on the back test of 20s. So, we broke
out. It's the same thing, right? We
broke out. We come back. We have 20s.
Can we get up back into here? If you
look at what I said, I got my eye on UU.
If if holds 20s, same with US AR. If
pullback holds yesterday's investment
from the government, you can see it
here. And then I think I might have
rementioned it yesterday. Here you go.
So, uh,
these are both starting to come in now.
So, going to watch how we react here.
So, looking for longs on these now to
see if we can continue this and take
this out. Right. So, this is a macro
event and it's a swing position. There
you go. There's a free There's a freebie
for you guys of what I'm looking for on
some of my swing positions. But yeah,
that's all comes as part of the Discord.
I'm kind like that. I'm kind like that
because I want people to make money.
I want people to have financial freedom.
All right. 20s to 500s is maintaining
the rotation. Nothing has changed here,
folks. Same thing. We're boxed in and
basically a 20 point range.
No, unfortunately not. There's no access
to Discord in the orderflow course. It's
only for the 20our course only because
in the order flow course, I would I
teach you how to read profile, delta,
divergence, stock traders, all this
stuff, right? footprint bookmap, but the
breadand butter setups of understanding
structure and what we're looking at,
that all comes from the 20our course. If
you do the orderflow course and you
haven't done the 20our course, there's a
chance that you might trade a different
way to the traders who have done the
20our course. And if you put all of that
in one community in a Discord, what
means is you've got people taking the
other side of trades and then it can
sort of rattle you in your position
where you think, "Oh, I'm not going to
take that now." And then it goes away
and you get frustrated. So the only
reason is I want everyone to be able to
support each other.
Is ATR the best way to consider stop
limit size or key levels? Hard 80 tick
stop biting me. Yeah. So ATR will help
you understand the potential move. So
like the spikes today we've traded like
up to 80 points ATR. I'd say your
average on the day is about 31. Your
your stops should be when the where the
trade is no longer valid, right? Where
the trade is no longer valid. So for
example,
you can use volume. So if you were short
here on the breakdown, your stop should
be the other side of this volume. So if
you took this one, you would have got
stopped out. But if you had another go,
you would have got it. And we're almost
at that low now. And if we run these
stops, you're looking to cover into
here, right? So you can use, for
example, key levels. You can use volume
for protection, right? So, if you're
short here, you can put your stop the
other side of it. Here you go. So, TP1
now hit. So, congratulations those that
took this this IB low now here. And then
you're looking for a drift now into this
blue box and potentially all the way
down into here. But you should be
covering some of your position. They are
adding liquidity lower. So, there's a
good chance we can continue to drift
lower here. SPY still has levels it can
go and hit as well. But, we are coming
into big big levels of interest across
the market here, folks.
Uh, I've got a feeler. Um, is it Jay?
Jay, I've got a feeler on US long that I
put on this morning. Um, and I'm looking
if it starts to base and hold, I'm going
to add more position size in there.
Unfortunately, it came out with news
this morning before I got the chance to
put it on. So, I think there was there
was Trump news on metals again to today.
Um, so I am I am long US, but I'm not
positioned into big size yet. So I'm
just waiting. Uu, I haven't actually
looked at uranium since this, but I'd
imagine the same thing. Yeah. So dips
holding 20. Remember the the call was
for dips to hold 20 on the swing. Boom.
There you go. Right. Literally perfect.
So we didn't buy up here once we saw the
breakout to 28. We said if but if dips
hold 20, we'll get long. So, I'd now be
looking for dips down into anywhere down
into here and I'll start to accumulate a
long position for a a hold back towards
alltime highs in these. Right.
I think you might be in Discord, Jay.
So, maybe that's helped you. All right.
So, just be careful here, guys, because
we've just hunted those stops. You're
back into this same volume shelf here as
your over under
starting to come and retest this same
level. So, if we start a pop above 20s
now, there might be relief back up to
50s, but it's up to you if you really
want to dangle dangle down here or not.
You know, 5 minutes until lunch. We'll
do a course giveaway as soon as we hit
lunch.
I like TPO because the volume gives you
a clue as to when the auction is over.
For instance, we have a volume of 163 at
the low period. So, we will drive lower
as there's so much volume.
T for me TPO is more useful for seeing
time spent than volume.
What do hunting stops do? Pair off
liquidity.
Pair off liquidity. So, you got to think
the big boys in the market. If you want
to be a big big buyer in the market,
let's talk about a market maker or a
bank. All right, so let's say someone
wants to buy a,000 lot. All right, they
can't just come in and buy a thousand
lot, right? They need if they want to
buy this one's the buyer, this guy's the
buyer. They need what? They need someone
who's willing to sell a thousand lot,
right? And they won't always have that
ability to do that. So what's the best
way of doing it? Well, if lots of buyers
have come in here and bid up and they
just got stopped out there, then in this
stopout, if their stop is here, what
happens? If you're a market buyer or if
you've been a buyer in this market here
and you stop out, you become a seller.
So then you get your thousand lot sell
and the guy can limit order in a
thousand lot buy and get filled without
it affecting the market, right? And
that's just an example, but that is why
they hunt stops because they can use the
stops to pair off to get the directional
move that they want. Remember, the
market will not move unless there's both
a buyer and a seller. It will not move
otherwise. And you need an aggressive
buyer and a passive seller or an
aggressive seller and a passive buyer.
If you've just got two passive
participants, that would mean that you
have, you know, a limit order here, a
limit order here, spread in the middle,
no one is going to pair off.
No one's going to pair off. All right,
back towards these 20s again. So, the
same thing over and over and over and
over. Nothing is changing.
649 on ES is not the low. That's my
prediction. Okay. I'm not watching ES,
but you might well be right. I mean, I
would say uh SPY to 690 and obviously
that old weekly low down at 8940 is on
SPY is possible still.
Did I take any trades today? I did. Uh
the main one was this long here. I had a
few attempts at it. I was like long here
to here, long here to here. And I
finally, where did I come in? Was it a
reclaim of 30s or 50s? I can't remember.
Here to here. And then a little piece of
that and then that was it. I wanted to
get up into here and then fade it back
down. Missed the shorts today. Wanted
the shorts. Was prepared for them.
Didn't get the retest of the level I
wanted unfortunately.
Alex, do you have a particular time of
day for trading in the afternoon session
or is it based on price, action,
location? I would say definitely on
price action, location. Uh try and avoid
lunch, but sometimes lunch is good. It
really depends on the volume and what's
moving the market.
Same for you. Yeah, it was it was
annoying today. It was annoying. All
right, back to these 20s again for the
millionth time today. So, if they lift
through 20s, they will try and lift to
50s again. All right, if they fail the
20 rotation, they will come back down to
these lows again. So, nothing's changed.
So, I'd say buyers will want to protect
sort of tens here. And if they can
protect tens, they can potentially get a
move up to 50s. And then you we'll see
if they get going. Otherwise, we can
just keep trading lower. We're just in a
20 to 500 rotation, but we did wick the
low, which is a good sign for buyers,
but again into these 20s. Big big level.
We've talked about it all day. It's a
huge level where we had like a 400 lot
seller earlier in the day. So there you
go. They just resold the 20s again. Back
down to these 500s. Rotation, rotation,
rotation, rotation. Nothing's changing.
Absolutely nothing's changing.
Yeah, exactly, Julian. Yesterday just
straight straight rip, wasn't it?
Straight up yesterday, straight down
today to repric it all. It's uh it's
tough when it does it. It's tough. It's
fine if you're already positioned.
I'd say the best sell of the day really
was like 8:00 a.m. this morning. that uh
we pulled back at 8 8 till 7 a.m. and
then we pushed up 8:00 a.m. and we
failed uh to make a new high. So, we set
that lower high here. I can get you
guys. Where is it? We set that lower I
can't find you guys now. We set that
lower high up here on an hourly after
three drives. So, I wasn't at my desk
here. So, one, two, three lower high.
Failed to make a new high. That was the
break. But since then, not much we can
do with that on an hourly, honestly.
Pretty tough. Pretty tough.
Uh for the big circles for me, I'm using
a third party, but you can do it for
free on Ninja Trader. If you are trading
with uh Ninja Trader and Trader 8 prop
or have a personal account with them,
you can get the big bubbles for free. Uh
there is, if you go to my YouTube, I'm
going to find it and post it for you. If
you go on my YouTube, I show you how to
get all this stuff for free. Let's find
it now.
Order flow. There we go.
There you go. This link here.
What do I mean by 20s here? 20s. 520.
20s. 20s. I'm not going to say 520 every
time. All right. 20s. Right. So, back
down to the lows again.
And whoever what which one of you said
spy likely or ES going to make a new
low? You look highly likely right now to
be correct. Previous week low still
hanging down there. Very very possible.
So if they reject uh 500s here, you'll
probably see follow through. If they
reclaim 500s, we'll go back to the 20s
again for the gazillionth time today.
And we're into lunch now as well, folks.
Just be aware of that.
I'm using MZ pack free big trade. There
you go. So, must have one as well. Pass
a combine. Congratulations.
Congratulations.
All right, let's uh get you guys a free
course. Uh give me a second to set it
up. Please don't do anything yet. It's
just an introduction to trading course.
This is only good for people who have
never really traded before. If you know
nothing, it's a good one to do. All
right. So, just type course once in chat
and we'll pick a winner in the next
couple minutes.
One of you saying why is NVO pooping
itself? What's NVO like
Nord disk?
Did it have earnings or something?
weight loss drug outperformed
late trials June
sales decline. So their guidance sales
decline that's why
getting wrecked off that news.
So guidance bad by the looks of it.
Have a look for you. NV MVO cut 2026
outlook guiding to adjust sales and
operating profit down by 5 to 13% well
below the expectations of 10% growth. So
you've got like a 23% offset, right? So
that's why your guidance was poor. Very
poor guidance.
Give you guys like one more minute.
I'm going to get some breakfast. You
probably hear my stomach rumbling as
always.
Okay, put in the winner. Five, four,
three, two, and one.
I'm going to say this name wrong. I
know. I know I am. So, I apologize.
Soy Jav Soy. I can't do it. Soy Jav
isier.
Soy Jav isier. Let me know you're here.
It's been announced in chat so you can
see if it's your name. It would have
ated you. Let me know you're here. If
you have, I will send you a link to the
free course.
Can you do a TPT evals in two days and
then do a little Yeah, you can. So, you
can pass in two days and then just
basically just trade a micro for the
next three days. There you go. All
right. Congratulations on making a note
of your name. You've won a free
introduction course.
Nice. All I want you to do is email me,
please. info@flowzontenttrader.com.
Send me a screenshot of you logged into
YouTube and I will sort you out with a
free introduction course.
Do you do live trading and which
session? Oh, yes. Right now, New York
session.
Uh, Scott, known. I'm naughty. I have a
bit of half and half in my coffee, mate.
Soy Javier Sierra. Soy Javier Sierra.
Alex, what functionalities does city
footprint provide to you that you really
like? Well, other than the standard
footprint and the order, uh, I really I
just like the delta on the side. I
really like the delta on the side of it.
And it's very customizable. So I have uh
cumulative delta on the bottom but I
have the delta profile on the side. Here
you go. So snapping down lower. So
rejected 20s again then rejected to
reclaim 500s here. Now lows and low
hanging fruits continues to be down
here. This can continue to move lower if
it wants during lunch. It looks like
they are still not done with it. They
are just forcing this thing lower and
lower and lower at the moment.
And this bids down here at 450s. Maybe
they come all the way down there.
How long did it take me to come
profitable? Uh swings were profitable
fairly quickly. Day trading took some
time. I was really doing well in small
caps, like I said, until uh COVID and
then that that knocked me off for a
little bit.
Scott, you make me laugh.
Alex, you think it would come down to
200, which was overnight Sunday?
Um,
it's possible.
It's possible. Uh, but you need to
respect where we are. There's a lot of
volume on the current developing week
where we are right now. A lot. Right. So
if we get under that there's a node from
uh the week dating back to Monday the
19th of Jan. We have to respect the
levels right. So there's a node dating
back to 19th of sort of 450s. Under 450s
we have like a little bit of a gap. We
get a bit thin into 400s. 400s is really
thick all the way down to 120. It's
really really thick from that week of
Monday the 19th. Have to respect it.
have to respect it. Like, is it
possible? Yeah, of course it's possible.
But all we've really done, if you think
we broke out, well, we didn't break out.
We drove higher yesterday. We've
repriced it today. Nothing's actually
changed. We're still in range to come
back for previous week low. Is it
possible this week? Yes. But what we'd
need to see is more liquidity being
built out on a higher time frame. Um,
and we'd need to do it long enough that
the Ballinger bands can offer expansion
because at the moment we are so tight,
folks. Like the top bowl is currently
trading at 26,230.
The bottom bowl is trading at 25,300.
It's a 900 point uh move of four
standard deviations. Remember 20day, two
standard up, two standard down.
Normally, you're looking at, let's have
a look, 26600.
Normally, you're looking at 2,000 points
plus. Currently, we're looking at 900
points for a four standard deviation
move from top bowl to lower bowl. Right?
So, there's there's there's not a lot
here. We will get out of this at some
point. We cannot keep rotating,
rotating, rotating, rotating, failing,
failing, failing, failing, fail.
Eventually, something's going to change.
All right. Any questions, folks, before
I get out of there.
I'd be very careful um about looking for
any more shorts now. All right. So, you
had the short opportunity here and here
down to this. That's your TP1 hit. If
you get down to here, great. Be very
careful. Look at all of these nodes. All
right. Respect these nodes. Respect
this. Respect this. If they start
reclaiming this, this can happen. It can
offer relief. Look how thin we were. All
right. It can offer relief. It doesn't
happen have to happen today. It can
happen tomorrow. If you're going to hold
your shorts, if you were in here, or
hopefully some of you are in from all
the way up here, you can look for these
targets down here. Maybe you get lucky,
but uh you know, just understand we're
1.40% down on the day. This was the only
pullback that we've had so far. You
know, you can sit in this and try and
manage it, but don't don't be entering
short down here for goodness sake. Okay?
Do not be doing that. Do not be doing
that.
Right back to towards these uh 500s
again. Same bloody level over and over.
500s. If they get through 500, we go
520. VPO has moved down here. I'm going
to sit with you for a couple more
minutes. Um,
do you think volume profile from Trading
View is good enough to use? Yes, I do.
Do I mentor one-on-one? No, I don't. I
don't. I literally don't have the time.
But we do group sessions.
The look of the candles doesn't matter
for you after all the info you can get,
right? But the shape the shape matters.
Yeah, the shape matters. Like I'm not
watching footprint all the time and like
my brain would would be exhausted. Like
structure matters, volume matters, but
price matters more than anything else.
Structure structure and price and
volume.
Question about your delta column on
bookmap. I have a quote delta but that's
it. Is there another name? You mean this
one? This is um volume profile delta.
Uh, how do I set that up? Is it a right
click on here? I can't remember how to
do it. It will be configure add-ons.
Okay, here. I'm going to try and bring
this over for you. I think it's here.
How do I change the columns on this?
Maybe I've got that wrong. Visible
columns.
Here you go. Visible columns. Volume
profile delta. That's what you want.
Volume profile delta.
I can go over bar bar in a minute. Yeah,
any sort of long trigger is still all
the way back above the gray box.
I mean you could be very skeptically
play one from here to here but the safer
bet is once we leave all of this trap
because we'll keep rejecting this and we
can pop over and reject. Um just
remember the main trend is down and they
have stuff to come forward. Very it
would be very tricky to look for
anything else.
When do I trade ES? I don't I don't
really trade ES.
How important is having a heat map to my
trading style? It's useful. I don't
necessarily need it. I like using uh the
limit orders and the delta on it. It's
useful for momentum, though.
Where is the bounce? Well, it doesn't
have to happen. There's the wash. There
you go. So, they're coming down for this
now, folks. Down here.
So, they're starting to get aggressive
here. Look at these big guys selling.
Hard selling here. This is no joke. Into
the blue box. This is not a joke.
Hard hard selling. That's why I say I
wouldn't be long until we got above all
of this. This is the level that they're
looking for. This is very very very
aggressive. Previous day low now hit or
previous week low now hit on the spy.
Not hit on the ENQ yet. VIX uh about to
close that gap. Right. So here comes the
spike. VIX about to close that gap.
You got wicked out right before it. That
sucks. I'm sorry to hear that.
I am sorry to hear that. So here the
next level. So all this liquidity being
built and they're starting to drive blue
box and then here and if you get really
lucky you'll trade under underneath all
this. What's their news? Are you guys
saying the news? US House struggling to
advance major federal funding bill.
Voting continues.
Uh
remember ES uh sorry spy hit previous
week low. It's already taken it. Just be
aware of that. It's already taken it
buying the 20our course. Is there a
discount for the V V profile course?
Yeah, you can buy it as a bundle. So if
you go to the 20our course, you will see
it's available as a bundle. All right,
there's an imbalance here at 30 that
they're trading up to. Through 30, they
can actually lift this to 60. Through
30, they could actually lift it to 60
because we got very thin. I wouldn't be
buying this, but I'm just telling you
what I'm seeing. Through 30, they could
actually lift this to 60. Here's 30.
No base above. Still got low hanging
fruit. I, like I said, I would not be
buying this. This is very, very heavy.
US shot down Iranian drone. Okay, great.
So, we're going to go into war with
Iran. Fantastic.
Honestly,
any of you shorting this from up here
still? By the way, it's really good. Now
you're up 130 140 points.
Interested if any of you got it.
Patience pays. Yes, patience absolutely
pays.
Made all your money money back, all your
losses back with this one. Nice. Nice.
Oh, nice, Matt. Yes, some of you still
in it. Fantastic. Just make sure you're
paying yourself on the way down. But
this is the target really. If you can
get down here, you'd be you'd be super
happy. But we do get thick here. Like I
said, dating back to Monday the 19th.
That week, we get very very thick down
here. The last time we came down here
before the uh Sunday open, you can see
we wicked down into 369 and found a bit.
So, just be careful.
VIX previous week high soon. Well, it's
just filled that gap, hasn't it? Uh it's
got a little way to go. It's got to get
up to almost 20s, but it's into a big
area. It's a big pivot here on the VIX.
It's a big pivot. Okay, sellers trying
to come in here. If they don't get their
way that there is a rip back up to 60
coming. If they don't get their way
soon, they keep piling in here. The
sellers,
it's very thin. See this? Very, very
thin. Sellers need to protect this right
here. You can see this profile here.
Sellers need to protect this. If they
don't, there's a rip right back up here.
Still low hanging fruit. Again, I'm not
telling you to be long. I'm just telling
you what's going on right now. I would
not be long against all of this. This is
heavy, heavy tape.
Feel like they want that previous week
low. Kind of unusual they haven't
already gone and done it straight away.
Financial juice best for the news.
So, back to these 30s. Remember this
shelf here. If they rip through this, be
careful if you're short in this. You
don't want this to just rip through 30s
to come to 60 and cents. You'd be very
upset if you give the whole thing back.
Well, not the whole thing, but like a
good chunk because it can Look how thin
we are here. It can come up here, can
repric this candle. Be very careful,
please.
And watch your ATR because the ATR on
that drift down was like 83 points. They
can repric it very quickly.
VIX getting stuck off that gap. So VIX
has done everything we wanted to see.
When will it finish is the question on
the VIX.
When are they done with it?
These 30s, be careful. Be very careful
if they rip through here. Be very, very,
very, very careful. If you were in this
short, they can rip this straight back
up to 60s and 70s. Be very careful.
You're so thin up here. If they get
going here, it would be really nasty.
Here they go. They're starting to try
and get through these 30s now. And they
can lift all the way up here. Look,
there's nothing here. They can fill this
whole imbalance.
How do I see Vicks? I have it on my
monitor here.
Here you go. His coming up to 50s and
his imbalance is starts at 58 to 65. So
that you know they're going to fill this
imbalance. Be very careful. Here you go.
Should I would be I would have been out
this short personally. Oh, I hate seeing
stuff like this because if they get too
many shorts caught down here, even
though I don't like the low of day
auction, it's very very possible. Now,
here you go. So, into that imbalance.
There's the rip that up back up that we
just talked about. Said that might
happen. There you go. Just happened.
Gross.
Absolutely gross.
And the question is now, do they resell
this area?
sellers came in where 26 is down there.
So you can use this same kind of node
here.
This kind of node here. Now
all the time we're move I don't mind
staying with staying here with you a
little bit longer all the time we're
moving.
Normally we go to sleep with the lunch.
Still low hanging fruit below. But we've
just held that gray box. So they might
try and attack reattack these 80s. If
they fail that gray box we will trade
lower. We will trade lower. If they fell
this gray box, we will trade back down
into this. Just be a repric to sell
into.
Such a heavy tape today. Insane.
Back down to the 400s. Losing the gray
box. So, I would expect them to trade
lower at this point. They've done the
hard job. Repric, sold into it.
It's the hard thing for day traders when
they're moving it this much. It makes it
really hard to hold on to positions. Uh
because you can get caught so quickly
like when they rip it 80 points if you
guys were short. You don't like you've
got to take some profits when they do
those moves. You know what I mean? They
might just dump this now like even
further having knocked you guys out by
like a 50 point rip up. Like how big is
that rip from 403? Yeah, 50 point rip up
and then maybe dump it more. It's just
they make it really hard for day
traders.
Buyers coming in here. They're probably
going to get themselves caught. They're
flying in here. These buyers, they will
probably get themselves caught here.
Yep. [\h__\h] idiots. Why would they buy
that?
So, low hanging fruit down here. Still
yet to get tagged. I tell you what, I'll
go for a pee and come back and then
maybe you tag it.
All right. What are these guys doing?
Messi.
Messi. Can't imagine those bids. Hold
up.
Still want 392. One of you saying 392.
I would want 365 if I was short. This is
starting to find a bid.
This is starting to find a bit of a bid
down here.
that gray box. It's messy for sure.
Still got an imbalance up to 64 which
they can fill. If it starts reclaiming
IB, I'd be very very worried about big
big big big squeeze
holding gray box back up towards IB
then. So 5560 to 65 is the imbalances.
Back up we go through that. Watch IB now
if they start to base over it into the
imbalances here. just got tagged into
these. All right, into these imbalances
here. This is where we came big big
selling. If we start to print over this,
all right, it means we're probably going
to leave this excess and drift higher
without taking out the low hanging
fruit, which would be really dirty.
Really, really dirty. But SPY did hit
it. It's one thing to note, SPY did hit
that previous day, uh, previous week
low. So, divergence with the ETF. spy
did come and take it out right here and
it's reclaiming it.
So, I'd probably be done with a short if
I was you guys. Doesn't mean it can't
trade lower unless you if you're
positioned way up here. Obviously, it's
different, but if you took that uh wash
down, be very very careful.
Right off the previous week low on the
spy. Yeah, not on uh not on the Q's
though.
On the spy but not on the Q's.
VIX failing that level as well after
that gap fill. So we have nailed what we
called on the VIX today. That's really
really good.
Morgan, where did you close your short?
Morgan,
they're lifting again into these
imbalances
into these imbalances towards that value
area low and IB high. So they're coming
towards this. Do they reject this level
now? Is is your question, right? If they
reclaim this, there's a big squeeze to
come and run all of this out. Just be
careful. If they reclaim this is a big
squeeze. I'd say 500s would be the level
and then up into that same block again.
So, I'd be watching
these levels now, the remainder of the
session. If this slows down, I'm going
to get off, guys. I'm just I'm willing
to sit here while it's moving, but not
not other than that.
Took it at 558,
closed at 500. Took it at 558. So here's
the IB guys
rejecting value area low so far. Not
quite to IB. So big rejection there.
Sellers stepping in there. This is where
they sold from earlier. Remember if we
get through this then I'd imagine we get
to 500.
This can be a two leg that they resell.
Remember? So buyers will want to hold
431s. They can't hold 431s new lows.
This can be a two-leg
retest
which is sold or they can reclaim this
and squeeze to here and then here.
That's the opportunity in the market
right now.
If I sat on alert looking for a long way
where would I want it?
It's quite hard to to want that right
now.
You'd want a rec.
What's made it hard is this. They've
made this so thick and messy that like
where are you going to long really? You
want to get above that and leave all
this. And I feel like they're going to
struggle to get above that today. We're
in a the move is downside. They're
selling every they're selling absolutely
everything. So I' don't think you can
set an alert. Like maybe yeah, maybe if
you come above 578, but like what's your
risk going to be at that point? That's
what's going to make it really hard.
Okay. Huh.
All right.
Yeah.
Alex, when do you mark the gray zone?
Sunday. Oh, well, these ones I've just
marked now. Um, I mark them as as I go.
Yeah. S
uh morning prep each day. Depends if
they've moved.
Sounds like a good plan to me, hot tub
Mike. That sounds like a pretty good
plan.
Back to this gray box again.
And this can be a two-leg. They rejected
IB. They can sell this back down if they
want. It all depends if they can hold
this gray box or not.
Let me have a look if there's any more
news.
No, that's it. All right, folks. I'm
going to be done. There's nothing for me
to do here.
The weakness in ENQ is palpable. It's uh
annoying that I would have preferred
some squeezes higher to clean out
liquidity.
If we could just have come up here a
little bit, it would have offered a
really nice short. Uh this is a big fat
B-shaped profile. So we gone from a big
P to a big B. I mean it's big P to a big
B. I mean that is the shittest market
you can get. Basically one side to the
other side. One side to the other side.
just schizophrenia
in in a range. There's not much left to
do. If you're if you're in a short, just
manage it all the way down and hopefully
it works for you. Uh personally, I
wouldn't long unless we reclaim big
volume shelves and we're not doing that
right now. So, I just you would be going
against the grain if you do that. We
already did giveaways. We already did
giveaways. All right. We've done them
all.
Sat here 30 minutes longer to see if the
market wants to move. It's probably
going to just keep selling down at the
moment. There's no reason to be long
right now.
Yeah, exactly. Exactly.
Dr. Jack or Mr. Hide. Yeah, that's
exactly what the market is. All right,
folks. Uh, big love to everyone. Trade
safe this afternoon. Please don't guess
the lows. Don't get yourself stuck.
Don't give away like all the hard work
we did last month. Yes, the market's
rotating 900 points. Whoopy [\h__\h] do.
Like, let it do it. Who cares, right? We
missed some trades today. Who cares? The
market's going to be here tomorrow. It
really doesn't matter. It does not
matter. All right. Peace and love,
everyone. Look after yourself. Use hard
stops. Be kind to each other. All that
good stuff. And uh I'll see you here
tomorrow morning.